<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-09-03T02:36:14.147Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man jailed after high speed chase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ff2a90b4-6986-11ef-8bcc-73b86bdf1eba</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/man-jailed-after-high-speed-chase/article_ff2a90b4-6986-11ef-8bcc-73b86bdf1eba.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T23:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — A 29-year-old Eugene man was arrested Friday after fleeing from police in a stolen vehicle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX/MIDDLE FORK FIRES UPDATE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123216</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/02/diamond-complex-middle-fork-fires-update/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-middle-fork-fires-update"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T22:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 2, 2024 3:15 p.m.  The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, remains at 11,141 with containment still at 78 percent as of midday Monday. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in Crater Lake National Park continues at 5,282 acres and 48 percent contained. Fire updates have not changed: *Pine Bench...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX STILL 60 PERCENT CONTAINED, UP TO 5,918 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123213</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/02/homestead-complex-still-60-percent-contained-up-to-5918-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-still-60-percent-contained-up-to-5918-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T22:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 2, 2024 3:00 p.m.  The Homestead Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest is still 60 percent contained, with slight growth to 5,918 acres as of midday Monday. A UNF update said fire manager are fire managers are tracking weather forecasts that may produce favorable conditions for planned tactical burnout operations on the Horse...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODF Incident Management Team 3 deployed to the Copperfield Fire (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174940</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174940"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T17:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chiloquin, Ore. – Oregon Department of Forestry’s Incident Management Team 3 was mobilized last night to the Copperfield Fire in the Klamath-Lake District. The team will in brief at 1:00p.m. today and will enter unified command with the Oregon State Fire Marshal’s Red Team at 6:00 p.m. 
The Copperfield Fire, 5 miles southeast of Chiloquin, is estimated to be 2,500 acres as of this morning. 
Resources were successful overnight in laying dozer line from the heel of the fire and up the east and west flanks. Today, they will continue to work on creating dozer line along the north side of the fire to stop forward progression. Multiple air resources are on order today to help with suppression efforts. Southwest to west winds are expected to challenge the eastern fire lines throughout today. 
“Due to unfavorable weather conditions, this is a rapidly evolving incident.” Teresa Williams, Klamath-Lake District Forester said, “We’re grateful to have the help of the incident management teams in managing and working to contain this fire and protect our communities.”
According to the National Weather Service, the area is in a Red Flag Warning until 8 p.m. tonight due to strong winds with gusts up to 40 mph and low humidity. A red flag warning is issued when there are weather conditions that promote rapid spread of fire which may become life-threatening.
Klamath County Sheriff’s office has declared Level 3 (Go Now) evacuations east of Chiloquin. To check your evacuation status and for evacuation information, please visit https://www.klamathcounty.org/300/Emergency-Management.  Road closures are still in place from mile marker 5-15 on Sprague River Highway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE WOMAN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL AFTER ATV WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123211</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/02/canyonville-woman-taken-to-hospital-after-atv-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=canyonville-woman-taken-to-hospital-after-atv-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T14:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 3, 2024 7:40 a.m. A Canyonville woman was taken to the hospital after an ATV wreck on Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 9:00 p.m. a caller said the woman had been in the accident in the 15000 block of South Myrtle Road in the Red Top area, and he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SACRAMENTO WOMAN JAILED AFTER STOLEN VEHICLE RECOVERED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123209</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/02/sacramento-woman-jailed-after-stolen-vehicle-recovered/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sacramento-woman-jailed-after-stolen-vehicle-recovered"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T14:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 2, 2024 7:20 a.m. A Sacramento, California woman was jailed after a stolen vehicle was recovered on Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 10:50 a.m. the victim had his vehicle in the parking lot of a business in the 2300 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway in Roseburg. It was running with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENT JAILED AFTER ALLEGED DISORDERLY CONDUCT AT STORE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123207</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/02/transient-jailed-after-alleged-disorderly-conduct-at-store/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transient-jailed-after-alleged-disorderly-conduct-at-store"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T13:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 2, 2024 7:00 a.m. A transient was jailed after an alleged disorderly conduct incident at a store on Friday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report at 5:10 p.m. a deputy went to a business in the 300 block of North 1st Street in Drain after an employee said a man was being disorderly and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GLENDALE WOMAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123205</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/02/glendale-woman-jailed-for-alleged-harassment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=glendale-woman-jailed-for-alleged-harassment"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T13:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 2, 2024 6:30 a.m. A Glendale woman was jailed for alleged harassment on Friday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 9:40 p.m. the 41-year-old was involved in the incident in the 300 block of North Third Street in Glendale. The woman allegedly slapped the victim, pushed her up against a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LABOR DAY CLOSURES LISTED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123202</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/02/labor-day-closures-listed-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=labor-day-closures-listed-2"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T12:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 2, 2024 5:00 a.m. Monday is Labor Day and that means there are a number of closures. Federal, state, county and city offices are closed. No regular mail will be delivered. Schools are not in session. Banks and credit unions are not open. Professional offices are closed. Many retail businesses are open though some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Correction: Firefighters respond to Copperfield Fire near Chiloquin (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174934</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174934"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T02:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Correction: The Copperfield Fire is reported at 1000 acres as of 7:30 p.m.. 
Chiloquin, Ore. – Oregon Department of Forestry’s Klamath-Lake District, alongside federal, state, local and private partners, is responding to the Copperfield Fire five miles southeast of Chiloquin, Ore. The fire is approximately 1000 acres as of 7:30 p.m. today with high fire potential. 
Firefighters responded to the fire around 3:00 p.m. today, September 1. Even with aggressive initial attack, the fire progression has not yet been stopped. Last reported at 4:30 p.m., there were six engines, five airtankers, two helicopters, two water tenders and four dozers on scene with more resources ordered and on the way. Night operations will continue to work as we move into the evening. 
Klamath County Sheriff’s office has declared Level 3 (Go Now) evacuations east of Chiloquin, Sprague River Road mile post 6-7. To check your evacuation status, please visit https://www.klamathcounty.org/300/Emergency-Management. 
For residents evacuating west, an evacuation center is being stood up at the Chiloquin Community Center. Residents headed east on Sprague River Hwy. are being asked to head to the town of Sprague River. Sprague River Hwy is currently closed between mile post 5 to Lone Pine mile post 15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX 78 PERCENT CONTAINED, UP TO 11,141 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123200</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/01/diamond-complex-78-percent-contained-up-to-11141-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-78-percent-contained-up-to-11141-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T21:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 1, 2024 2:20 p.m. The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, remains 78 percent contained and is up slightly to 11,141 acres. A UNF update said Saturday’s hot, dry weather increased fire activity, exposing interior hotspots of several fires in the complex. Some instances of active fire occurred with tree torching. Most...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX REMAINS 60 PERCENT CONTAINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123197</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/01/homestead-complex-remains-60-percent-contained/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-remains-60-percent-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T20:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 1, 2024 1:50 p.m.  The Homestead Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest remains 60 percent contained, and is still listed at 5,910 acres. A UNF update said 3 of the 7 fires on the complex are now contained. Fire updates: *Horse Heaven Creek Fire remains at 2,298 acres and is 64 percent contained....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vacant spot on South Umpqua School District board of directors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3a5b7c10-63c5-11ef-8b14-c788ba45cfe2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/vacant-spot-on-south-umpqua-school-district-board-of-directors/article_3a5b7c10-63c5-11ef-8b14-c788ba45cfe2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Umpqua School District is accepting applications for the one vacant position on the board of education for Zone 2 Position 2. The applicant will serve through June 30, 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX REMAINS 78 PERCENT CONTAINED, 1,133 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123195</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/31/diamond-complex-remains-78-percent-contained-1133-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-remains-78-percent-contained-1133-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T18:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 31, 2024 11:20 a.m. The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, remains 78 percent contained, with the acreage total revised downward slightly to 11,138 acres as of midday Saturday. 1,133 personnel are working on the complex. A UNF update said Saturday at 7:00 a.m. the Southern Area Hold Complex Incident Management Team...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HOME SUSTAINS STRUCTURAL, SMOKE AND WATER DAMAGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123188</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/31/roseburg-home-sustains-structural-smoke-and-water-damage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-home-sustains-structural-smoke-and-water-damage"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T17:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 31, 2024 10:50 a.m. A Roseburg home sustained structural, smoke and water damage from an early morning fire on Saturday. Fire Chief Tyler Christopherson of the Roseburg Fire Department said just after 5:45 a.m. crews responded to a structure fire with smoke inside the home in the 500 block of West Warren Court, next...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ready to get in the school spirit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c01bf2b8-662b-11ef-8a55-83b7224ac64e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/ready-to-get-in-the-school-spirit/article_c01bf2b8-662b-11ef-8a55-83b7224ac64e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With kids headed back to school, this is a great time to read books that mirror their experiences and introduce them to new ways of considering their classmates. We recommend these titles, all of which feature students navigating their education.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurora Ropp and Kris Wiley for The News Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Residential Structure Fire - 575 Warren Court - 8-31-24 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news174926</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news174926"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T17:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 5:47 a.m. on August 31, 2024, firefighters responded to a residential structure fire with reported smoke inside the home. Firefighters arrived on scene to find a single-family residential structure with flames and smoke showing from the back portion of the structure. Upon arrival, firefighters found a male resident and his dog were still inside the structure.  The resident and his dog were able to exit the home on their own at the direction of the firefighters.
Fire crews entered the single-family residence and made an interior attack. Crews extinguished the fire found to be in the attic space and completed overhaul of the structure.  The single-family residence sustained structural, smoke, and water damage. A fire investigator responded to the scene of the fire. The cause of the fire was determined to be electrical in nature.  Umpqua Valley Ambulance evaluated the resident for smoke inhalation. The resident refused treatment. Both the resident and his dog survived the fire.
Ten firefighters assisted with firefighting operations. Other agencies assisting with the fire included Umpqua Valley Ambulance, Central Douglas Fire & Rescue, Roseburg Police Department, Avista Utilities, and Pacific Power. 
The Roseburg Fire Department would like to remind everyone of the importance of working smoke alarms and ensuring you have the appropriate number of smoke alarms installed in the home. Remember to make sure you have working smoke alarms on every level of your home, outside each sleeping area and in every bedroom. Roseburg Fire Department recommends that homeowners consider a home fire sprinkler system for increased protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Fire Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX CREWS WORK ON FINISHING UP CONTAINMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123186</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/31/homestead-complex-crews-work-on-finishing-up-containment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-crews-work-on-finishing-up-containment"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T17:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 31, 2024 10:00 a.m. Crews with the Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, continue securing, patrolling and finishing up containment throughout the fire area. A UNF update said the fire remains 60 percent contained and 5,910 acres as of midday Saturday. A high-pressure system dominates the atmosphere, causing unseasonably high temperatures. Friday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extension Spotlight: Feeling saucy?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/717db418-64a3-11ef-bb58-338bf65735ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/extension-spotlight-feeling-saucy/article_717db418-64a3-11ef-bb58-338bf65735ea.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not much of a gardener, yet somehow, this time of year, my dining room table still looks like a farm stand. Friends deliver zucchini, colleagues pile buckets of free-to-good-home plums in the break room, and flats filled with juicy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AIMEE LOVE For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHILDREN SUBJECT OF CALIFORNIA AMBER ALERT LOCATED, TWO ARRESTED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123179</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/31/children-subject-of-california-amber-alert-located-two-arrested/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-subject-of-california-amber-alert-located-two-arrested"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T13:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 31, 2024 6:30 a.m. Two children, subject of a California Amber Alert, were located Friday and their non-custodial parents were arrested. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at 1:30 p.m. DCSO deputies received information from the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department that a kidnapping suspect’s phone was near the Love’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HAD RECORD HIGH TEMPERATURE ON FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123177</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/31/roseburg-had-record-high-temperature-on-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-had-record-high-temperature-on-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T13:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 6:00 a.m. Roseburg had a record high temperature for the date on Friday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said the mercury reached 101 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport. The record for August 30th had been 99 degrees, set in 2022. Roseburg is forecast to reach 97 degrees on Saturday. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HAS RECORD HIGH TEMPERATURE ON FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123177</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/31/roseburg-has-record-high-temperature-on-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-has-record-high-temperature-on-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T13:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 6:00 a.m. Roseburg had a record high temperature for the date on Friday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said the mercury reached 101 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport. The record for August 30th had been 99 degrees, set in 2022. Roseburg is forecast to reach 97 degrees on Saturday. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg library facilitates letter-exchange project]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/246e7016-662b-11ef-a36b-6728e88d777d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/roseburg-library-facilitates-letter-exchange-project/article_246e7016-662b-11ef-a36b-6728e88d777d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library is excited to partner on a letter-writing exchange project that connects Oregonians through the mail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley for The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Children Subject of California Amber Alert Located, Two Arrested (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174923</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174923"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T05:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY, Ore. - On Friday, August 30, 2024, at 1:30 p.m., Douglas County Deputies received information from the Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department that a kidnapping suspect's phone was near the Love's Travel Stop in the Green District.
Detectives from Los Angeles County Sheriff's Office indicated that 53-year-old David James and 39-year-old Tiffany Bryant had taken their children, ages 4 and 2, from a supervised visit and fled with them against child custody orders on August 14, 2024. The pair were believed to be in a brown Buick Enclave SUV and both had active warrants out of California for Kidnapping. A California Amber Alert had been issued for the children but had not been activated in Oregon.
Douglas County Deputies, along with multiple other agencies, began searching. Approximately 1 hour later at 2:29 p.m., a Deputy located the vehicle at the 103 Chevron in Tri-City which was unoccupied. They located David James inside of the Chevron and took him into custody.
During an interview with Detectives, James agreed to show law enforcement where Bryant and the children were and took them to a camp approximately 12 miles out Cow Creek Road. Once on scene, deputies located the children in the company of Bryant who was taken into custody. The Oregon Department of Human Services - Child Welfare Division was contacted and took custody of the children.
James and Bryant were lodged at the Douglas County Jail on the Kidnapping warrants out of California. Douglas County Detectives continue to assist the Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department with the investigation.
Assisting agencies included the Oregon State Police, Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team, Myrtle Creek Police Department and Oregon Department of Human Services – Child Welfare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stargazer: Watch Saturn disappear behind the moon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/48b49406-64f9-11ef-8647-eb54bae17c0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/stargazer-watch-saturn-disappear-behind-the-moon/article_48b49406-64f9-11ef-8647-eb54bae17c0e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T04:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venus skims the horizon just after sunset. As the sky darkens, Saturn and Neptune appear in the southeast. Tonight, Uranus and Jupiter rise in the east southeast between 11 p.m. and midnight. By month’s close, Venus will set more than…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PAUL MORGAN For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER HIGH-SPEED CHASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123174</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/sutherlin-police-jail-man-after-high-speed-chase/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-after-high-speed-chase"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T22:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 3:50 p.m. Sutherlin Police jailed a man after a high-speed chase on Friday. Captain Kurt Sorenson said at about 12:15 p.m. dispatchers received information about a possible stolen vehicle that was at West Central Avenue and Hutchins Street. Sorenson said it was reported that the stolen vehicle was a white Kia sedan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NATIONAL FOREST DECREASES PUBLIC USE RESTRICTIONS TO LEVEL 2]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123171</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/national-forest-decreases-public-use-restrictions-to-level-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=national-forest-decreases-public-use-restrictions-to-level-2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T20:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 1:40 p.m.  Effective Friday, the Umpqua National Forest decreases Public Use Restrictions to Level 2. A UNF release said the forest remains in High Fire Danger and Industrial Fire Precaution Levels are at Level 2. Under Level 2: *Campfires must be in Forest Service constructed fire rings or fireplaces in designated sites...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 8.30.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123165</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/inside-douglas-county-8-30-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-8-30-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T20:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ford’s Pond Grand Opening is next Friday September 6th at 2:00 p.m. Mayor Michelle Sumner, Community Development Director Kristi Gilbert and Beth Houseman with Friends of Ford’s Pond talk about the event and all the work that has taken place in the Phase 2 project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123163</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-6/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-6"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T18:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 11:55 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged theft incident on Thursday. An RPD report said at 6:00 p.m. officers contacted a 33-year-old near the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and Northeast Winchester Avenue. He admitted to stealing a backpack off a nearby porch and had the backpack in his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN ON MULTIPLE COUNTS OF CRIMINAL MISCHIEF]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123161</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/roseburg-police-jail-man-on-multiple-counts-of-criminal-mischief/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-on-multiple-counts-of-criminal-mischief"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T18:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 11:20 a.m. Roseburg Police Jail Man on Multiple Counts of Criminal Mischief Noon Aug 30 KB Roseburg Police jailed a man on counts of criminal mischief on Thursday. An RPD report said during the early morning hours on Tuesday, 70-year-old Paul Danford allegedly damaged a windshield belonging to a business in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PUBLIC USE RESTRICTIONS MOVING TO HIGH ON SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123158</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/public-use-restrictions-moving-to-high-on-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=public-use-restrictions-moving-to-high-on-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T18:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 11:00 a.m. The Douglas Forest Protective Association is moving Public Use Restriction levels to HIGH as of Saturday. Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said this is for all private, county, state, and Bureau of Indian Affairs lands within the Douglas District.  Pope said this imposes certain fire restrictions on the public to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA KENNEL CLUB DOG SHOW STARTS THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123156</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/umpqua-kennel-club-dog-show-starts-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-kennel-club-dog-show-starts-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T17:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 10:45 a.m.  The Umpqua Kennel Club’s next AFC dog show starts Thursday September 5th. The event continues through September 8th at the Douglas County Fairgrounds, daily from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. There is no charge for admission, but parking is $5 per vehicle per day. Full details on the show are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX UP TO 78 PERCENT CONTAINMENT, 11,152 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123151</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/diamond-complex-up-to-78-percent-containment-11152-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-up-to-78-percent-containment-11152-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T17:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 10:20 a.m. Containment on the Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, is up to 78 percent with the acreage remaining at 11,152. A UNF update said containment increased by one percent on Thursday. Hotter, drier weather is leading to a slight increase in fire activity of internal fuels. There has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX REMAINS 60 PERCENT CONTAINED, NO GROWTH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123148</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/homestead-complex-remains-60-percent-contained-no-growth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-remains-60-percent-contained-no-growth"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T17:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 10:00 a.m. The Homestead Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, remains 60 percent contained and at 5,910 acres as of midday Friday/. A UNF update said the focal point on the complex is to complete primary and secondary control lines. The objective will be accomplished by mopping up to cool any...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING USE OF FORCE INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123146</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/sutherlin-police-jail-man-following-use-of-force-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-following-use-of-force-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T16:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2024 9:30 a.m. Sutherlin Police jailed a man following a use of force incident on Thursday. An SPD report said at approximately 10:30 a.m. 50-year-old Jason Nightingale showed up at a residence in the 2200 block of Eagle Loop to send a message to two victims to get them out of town. Nightengale...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Attracting hummingbirds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a714a22e-63c9-11ef-b275-1b32ca089e3e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/ask-a-master-gardener-attracting-hummingbirds/article_a714a22e-63c9-11ef-b275-1b32ca089e3e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: How can I attract hummingbirds to my garden?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CHRIS RUSCH Master Gardener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 8.30.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123143</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/local-real-estate-today-8-30-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-8-30-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T16:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group powered by Place at Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our weekly real estate update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 8.30.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123141</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/30/morning-conversation-8-30-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-8-30-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T16:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas Forest Protective Association Public Information Officer Rachel Pope talks about fire danger concerns over Labor Day weekend and officers advice to those that are recreating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>