<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-08-13T13:15:10.991Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIR QUALITY ALERT IN EFFECT THROUGH 5:00 P.M. WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122380</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/air-quality-alert-in-effect-through-500-p-m-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=air-quality-alert-in-effect-through-500-p-m-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T11:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 4:10 a.m. The Oregon Department of Environmental Quality has an Air Pollution Advisory in effect until at least 5:00 p.m. Wednesday for parts of southern Oregon. DEQ’s advisory is for eastern Douglas, northern Jackson, Klamath and Lake counties, due to wildfires burning in the region. DEQ also expects intermittent smoke in southern...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCSO UPDATE RELATED TO DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122378</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/dcso-update-related-to-dixon-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dcso-update-related-to-dixon-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T11:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 4:00 a.m.  Evacuations remain in place for the Dixon Fire. The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office has an interactive map reflecting current evacuation levels which can be found online at: www.dcso.com/evacuations The American Red Cross Shelter has been moved from Canyonville School to the Days Creek Charter School, on Tiller Trail Highway. This...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AERIAL ASSETS ASSIST SUPPRESSION EFFORTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122374</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/aerial-assets-assist-suppression-efforts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=aerial-assets-assist-suppression-efforts"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 3:50 a.m.  The Dixon Fire, burning in the Tiller area, remains estimated at 1,833 acres with zero percent containment. An update said on Monday, firefighters took advantage of cooler morning temperatures to engage with the fire and continued to establish control lines. In the afternoon, fire activity increased substantially, and air assets...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST ISSUES CLOSURE ORDER-DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122372</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/umpqua-national-forest-issues-closure-order-dixon-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-national-forest-issues-closure-order-dixon-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 3:50 a.m. On Monday, the Umpqua National Forest issued a closure order in the Tiller Ranger District in response to the Dixon Fire. A UNF release said this closure order is in addition to other closure orders which are still in effect to protect public and wildland firefighter safety. Under the new...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NORTH ENTRANCE TO CRATER LAKE NATIONAL PARK CLOSED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122370</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/north-entrance-to-crater-lake-national-park-closed/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=north-entrance-to-crater-lake-national-park-closed"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 3:40 a.m. The north entrance to Crater Lake National Park is now closed to allow firefighters on the Middle Fork Fire to prepare control lines about the North Entrance Road. A National Parks Service release said fire crews will reduce fuels along the north-south route creating a defensible zone to keep the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROCK SCALING WORK COMPLETED EARLY IN THE CANYONVILLE AREA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122368</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/rock-scaling-work-completed-early-in-the-canyonville-area/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rock-scaling-work-completed-early-in-the-canyonville-area"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 3:30 a.m. Crews with the Oregon Department of Transportation have finished rock scaling work along Interstate 5 ahead of schedule. Dan Latham of ODOT said the amount of work needed was less than anticipated. Latham said rolling slowdowns between mileposts 101 and 89 in the Canyonville area are no longer necessary this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG VA HEALTH CARE SYSTEM HOMELESS STAND DOWN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122365</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/roseburg-va-health-care-system-homeless-stand-down/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-va-health-care-system-homeless-stand-down"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 3:20 a.m. September 11th the Roseburg VA Medical Center will have its Homeless Stand Down event. A VA release said the resources are endless, from vaccines and dental checks to haircuts and massages. Dozens of services will be available for veterans. Vendor check-in and set up will be from 7:00 a.m. to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG LIBRARY CIRCULATION REACHES NEW RECORD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122362</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/roseburg-library-circulation-reaches-new-record/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-library-circulation-reaches-new-record"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Roseburg Public Library has set a new circulation record. A city release said nearly 11,000 items were checked out in the month of July. Physical items accounted for 71 percent of the checkouts with the library’s youth collection leading the way. Children’s and teen materials are about 42 percent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K9S IN THE GRAPEVINES EVENT IS SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122359</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/13/k9s-in-the-grapevines-event-is-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=k9s-in-the-grapevines-event-is-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 13, 2024 2:50 a.m. Friends of Umpqua Valley Police K9 Programs will hold its nineth “K9s in the Grapevines” event at Melrose Vineyards on Melqua Road this Sunday afternoon at 4:00 p.m. A release from the non-profit organization said this event will feature multi-agency teams that will talk about their programs, answer questions, provide...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dixon Fire Evacuation Update 8/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174492</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174492"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T03:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CURRENT EVACUATION NOTICES IN PLACE AS A RESULT OF THE DIXON FIRE
TILLER, Ore. - Evacuations remain in place for the Dixon Fire, previously referred to as the Tiller Trail Fire. The following is a summary of the current evacuation levels as of Monday, August 12, 2024. An interactive map reflecting these evacuation levels can be found online at www.dcso.com/evacuations. 

LEVEL 3 "GO!":
All residences on Crume Ranch Lane
All residences on Devil's Knob Road, also known as USFS Road #1610 
All residences on Tiller Trail Highway from the intersection of Devil's Knob (USFS 1610) south to milepost 31 on Tiller Trail Highway. This includes all residences between these two points. (UPGRADED 8/12)
 

LEVEL 2 "BE SET":
All residences on Tiller Trail Highway from milepost 31 to milepost 34. This incl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX EVACUATION DOWNGRADE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122357</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/diamond-complex-evacuation-downgrade/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-evacuation-downgrade"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T22:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 4:00 p.m.  In coordination with fire managers, the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office has downgraded the evacuation notice for all homes in the Slide Creek area downstream to the Soda Springs area to a Level 1 – Be Ready notice. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell said this is inclusive of all addresses between these two points....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diamond Complex Evacuation Downgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174488</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174488"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T22:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOKETEE, Ore. - In coordination with fire managers, the Douglas County Sheriff's Office is downgrading all homes in the Slide Creek area downstream to the Soda Springs area to a Level 1 - Be Ready Notice. This in inclusive of all addresses between these two points. These residences were previously on a Level 2 - Be Set notice as a result of the Pine Bench Fire, which is part of the Diamond Complex.
A LEVEL 1 - BE READY EVACUATION NOTICE means you should be aware of the danger that exists in the area, monitor emergency services websites and local media outlets for information. This is the time for preparation and precautionary movement of persons with special needs, mobile property and (under certain circumstances) pets and livestock. If conditions worsen, emergency services personnel may contact you via an emergency notification system.
Although the evacuation level has been reduced in this area, it is important to know that there is a significant forest closure which may include the above campgrounds. This forest closure is independent of the Sheriff's Office evacuation notice process. For current information on the status of the campgrounds and associated forest closure, please contact the United States Forest Service. 
An interactive evacuation map can be found on our website at https://www.dcso.com/evacuations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Traffic enforcement patrols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news174487</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news174487"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T21:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During August through the end of September the Roseburg Police Department will have some extra patrols out working traffic enforcement, with a specific focus on safety belt use, distracted driving and speeding.  These focused patrols are made available due to grants received from Oregon Impact and the Oregon Department of Transportation.
Seat belts have been proven to be one of the best ways to save your life in a crash. Yet many still don’t buckle up. Worse still, not wearing a seat belt is a habit that will pass on to impressionable youth, who in turn will think it’s safe to not buckle up.
Distracted driving is one of the fastest growing safety issues on the roads today. Distracted drivers aren’t just a threat to themselves: they’re a danger to everyone else on the road. The national distracted driving effort focuses on ways to change the behavior of drivers through legislation, enforcement, public awareness, and education.
Be on the lookout for specific enforcement campaigns over the next two months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Police Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 8.12.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122350</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/inside-douglas-county-8-12-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-8-12-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T20:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Representative Court Boice joins us live from central Oregon to cover a number of current topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIR QUALITY ALERT EXTENDED UNTIL 5:00 P.M. WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122347</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/air-quality-alert-extended-until-500-p-m-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=air-quality-alert-extended-until-500-p-m-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T18:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 11:40 a.m. The Oregon Department of Environmental Quality has extended an Air Pollution Advisory through at least 5:00 p.m. Wednesday. DEQ’s advisory is for eastern Douglas, northern Jackson, and Klamath and Lake counties due to wildfires burning in the region. The DEQ also expects intermittent smoke in southern Jackson County through this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX GROWS TO 4,151 ACRES, 14 PERCENT CONTAINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122345</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/homestead-complex-grows-to-4151-acres-14-percent-contained/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-grows-to-4151-acres-14-percent-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T18:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 11:20 a.m. The seven fires making up the Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, have grown to 4,151 acres, with containment remaining at 14 percent. A UNF update said the largest fire remains the 1,612 acre No Man Fire. Sunday, firefighters slowed growth toward dozer line in the southeastern corner...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX UP TO 8,466 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122343</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/diamond-complex-up-to-8466-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-up-to-8466-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T18:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 11:10 a.m. The Diamond Complex on the Umpqua National Forest, consisting of 27 fires, is up to 8,466 acres, with 743 people assigned. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 31 people assigned, but the Diamond Complex is sharing resources as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIXON FIRE TOPS 1,800 ACRES, ZERO PERCENT CONTAINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122339</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/dixon-fire-tops-1800-acres-zero-percent-contained/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dixon-fire-tops-1800-acres-zero-percent-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 10:50 a.m.  The Dixon Fire in the Tiller area is at 1,833 acres and is zero percent contained as of midday Monday. An update said the combination of erratic wind and dry fuels have driven fire growth and produced active fire behavior, including some spotting. The fire is now under joint command...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR THEFT/ROV VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122337</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-theft-rov-violation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-theft-rov-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for alleged theft and a restraining order violation on Saturday. An RPD report said on July 7th, officers received a report of a stolen phone. During the investigation, 39-year-old Christopher Coles was discovered to be a person of interest in the case. On Saturday Coles...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER ALLEGED DISTURBANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122335</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/roseburg-police-jail-man-after-alleged-disturbance-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-after-alleged-disturbance-3"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man after an alleged disturbance Friday afternoon. An RPD report said at 5:00 p.m. 36-year-old Morgan Wivel allegedly was in a disturbance was a victim in the 400 block of Northeast Cummins Street when a second victim tried to break up the fight. Wivel reportedly punched...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER REPORTED DISTURBANCE AT BUSINESS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122331</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/roseburg-police-jail-man-after-reported-disturbance-at-business/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-after-reported-disturbance-at-business"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man after a reported disturbance at a business Friday afternoon. The RPD report said at 2:45 p.m. officers responded to a restaurant in the 2700 block of Northwest Edenbower Boulevard after a witness said a man hit the manager in the head after being told to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE MAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED DISORDERLY CONDUCT AT FAIRGROUNDS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122329</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/riddle-man-jailed-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-at-fairgrounds/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riddle-man-jailed-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-at-fairgrounds"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 9:30 a.m. A Riddle man was jailed following alleged disorderly conduct at the Douglas County Fairgrounds Saturday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 11:30 p.m. the 20-year-old was called in after a caller said he was fighting with a security guard near the main gate and allegedly drinking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA TEEN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL AFTER SINGLE-VEHICLE WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122327</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/umpqua-teen-taken-to-hospital-after-single-vehicle-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-teen-taken-to-hospital-after-single-vehicle-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 9:20 a.m. An Umpqua teen was taken to the hospital following a single vehicle wreck on Friday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 6:30 p.m. the 16-year-old was traveling westbound in the 13000 block of Garden Valley and came around a corner at approximately 75 miles per hour. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 8.12.24.]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122321</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/morning-conversation-8-12-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-8-12-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National host Rich Valdes of America at Night with Rich Valdes joins us to cover a number of topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCSO DIXON FIRE UPDATE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122317</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/dcso-dixon-fire-update/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dcso-dixon-fire-update"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T13:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 6:00 a.m. In response to the Dixon Fire, the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office has evacuation notices remaining in place: *Level 3: GO – All residences on Crume Ranch Lane and Devil’s Knob Road, also known as USFS Road #1610, and the one residence in the area of Hamlin Prairie *Level 2: BE...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIR QUALITY ALERT THROUGH 3:00 P.M. MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122311</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/air-quality-alert-through-300-p-m-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=air-quality-alert-through-300-p-m-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T11:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024  4:00 a.m. The Oregon Department of Environmental Quality has issued an Air Pollution Advisory, in effect through at least 3:00 p.m. Monday for much of southern Oregon. The DEQ advisory is for central and eastern Douglas County, and Klamath and Lake counties, due to wildfires burning in the region. DEQ also expects...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIXON FIRE ESTIMATED AT 1,600 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122306</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/dixon-fire-estimated-at-1600-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dixon-fire-estimated-at-1600-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T11:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 3:40 a.m. The Dixon Fire, formerly the Tiller Trail Fire, is estimated to be about 1,600 acres as of Sunday. An Umpqua National Forest update said crews continue to work diligently to contain the fire and expand upon the hard work of initial attack resources. This includes extending, strengthening and tying in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG CITY COUNCIL WITH BUSY AGENDA FOR MONDAY NIGHT MEETING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122304</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/roseburg-city-council-with-busy-agenda-for-monday-night-meeting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-city-council-with-busy-agenda-for-monday-night-meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Roseburg City Council has a busy agenda for its meeting Monday night. Councilors will have a public hearing on an ordinance amending the Roseburg Urban Area Comprehensive Plan. Hearings will also be held on closing out a Community Development Block Grant for the regional housing rehabilitation project and on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGON 38 PAVING PROJECT BEGINS BETWEEN ELKTON AND DRAIN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122300</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/oregon-38-paving-project-begins-between-elkton-and-drain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregon-38-paving-project-begins-between-elkton-and-drain"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 3:20 a.m. Construction is starting this week on a project that will pave 12 miles of Oregon 38 between Elkton and Drain, and repair four bridges. An update from the Oregon Department of Transportation said pavement work and slide repairs will take place in several areas, mostly between the Elk Creek Tunnel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REGISTRATION CONTINUES FOR THRIVE UMPQUA’S LONGEST TABLE EVENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122298</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/registration-continues-for-thrive-umpquas-longest-table-event/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=registration-continues-for-thrive-umpquas-longest-table-event"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 3:05 a.m.  Registration continues for Thrive Umpqua’s Longest Table event. A Thrive Umpqua release said residents are invited to gather for a farm-to-table dinner, crafted by local chefs, at the scenic green bridge on Northwest Stewart Park Drive, on Saturday night August 24th. The evening is designed as a way for residents...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$125,000 IN EDUCATOR SUPPORT AVAILABLE FROM SELCO]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122295</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/12/125000-in-educator-support-available-from-selco/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=125000-in-educator-support-available-from-selco"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 12, 2024 2:50 a.m. As educators increasingly dip into their own pockets to pay for classroom-related expenses, SELCO Community Credit Union will soon begin accepting applications for two programs that will combine to offer as much as $125,000 in classroom support across Oregon. A SELCO release said part of SELCO Steps Up, these educator-oriented...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dixon Fire Update 08/11/24 3:45 pm (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174467</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174467"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T22:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CURRENT EVACUATION NOTICES IN PLACE AS A RESULT OF THE DIXON FIRE
TILLER, Ore. - Evacuations remain in place for the Dixon Fire, previously referred to as the Tiller Trail Fire. The following is a summary of the current evacuation levels as of Sunday, August 11, 2024, at 3:45 pm. An interactive map reflecting these evacuation levels can be found online at www.dcso.com/evacuations. 

LEVEL 3 "GO!":
All residences on Crume Ranch Lane 
All residences on Devil's Knob Road, also known as USFS Road #1610
The one residence in the area of Hamlin Prairie. 
 

LEVEL 2 "BE SET":
All residences on Tiller Trail Highway from the intersection of Devil's Knob (USFS 1610) south to milepost 31 on Tiller Trail Highway. This includes all residences between these two points. 
 

Level 1 “BE READY”:
All residen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER TRAIL FIRE NOW NAMED DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122289</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/11/tiller-trail-fire-now-named-dixon-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tiller-trail-fire-now-named-dixon-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T18:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 11, 2024 11:20 a.m. The Tiller Trail Fire has now officially been named the Dixon Fire due to multiple agency involvement. An update from the Douglas Forest Protective Association said night crews continued aggressively working on building lines on the estimated 1,600 to 2,000-acre fire and addressing some spot fires. DFPA Public Information Officer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX GROWS SLIGHTLY TO 8,256 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122286</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/11/diamond-complex-grows-slightly-to-8256-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-grows-slightly-to-8256-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 11, 2024 10:20 a.m.  The Diamond Complex on the Umpqua National Forest, consisting of 27 fires, has grown slightly to 8.256 acres, with 743 people assigned. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park, has 28 people assigned, but the Diamond Complex is sharing resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Falls Fire 25% contained, evacuation levels reduced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174464</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174464"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T17:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry Grove, Ore. – With yesterday’s progress on the Lee Falls Fire, structural firefighting task forces and law enforcement demobilized from the area yesterday. Oregon Department of Forestry’s (ODF) Type 3 Incident Management Team remains on the Lee Falls Fire to continue mop up operations in preparation for returning the fire to the local district.
Yesterday’s work made sufficient progress to increase confidence that the fire will stay within its current perimeter. After consultation with fire officials, that confidence led to the Washington County Sheriff’s Office reducing all Level 3 evacuation levels to Level 2—Be Set. Cherry Grove community members returning to their homes should remain vigilant and maintain readiness for future evacuations, should fire conditions significantly chan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX GROWS SLIGHTLY, CONTAINMENT AT 14 PERCENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122282</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/11/homestead-complex-grows-slightly-containment-at-14-percent/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-grows-slightly-containment-at-14-percent"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T16:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 11, 2024 9:45 a.m.  The seven fires making up the Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, have grown slightly to 3,841 acres, with containment remaining at 14 percent. A UNF update said Saturday on the 1,465-acre No Man and 239-acre Salmon 33 fires, crews and heavy equipment continued primary and indirect line...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local students graduate Linfield University]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fa5b0d78-566e-11ef-94e6-87506b5b811b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/local-students-graduate-linfield-university/article_fa5b0d78-566e-11ef-94e6-87506b5b811b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linfield University announced 505 graduates following the spring 2024 semester. The commencement ceremony was held in McMinnville on May 26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER  TRAIL FIRE AT 1,000-1,500 ACRES AS OF SATURDAY EVENING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122276</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/11/tiller-trail-fire-at-1000-1500-acres-as-of-saturday-evening/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tiller-trail-fire-at-1000-1500-acres-as-of-saturday-evening"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T13:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 11,  2024 6:30 a.m. Saturday at approximately 2:40 p.m., crews from the Douglas Forest Protective Association and over a dozen other agencies responded to a reported fire in the 28000 block of Tiller Trail Highway in the Tiller area. DFPA Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said upon arrival at the scene, an estimated 50-acre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local school districts receive grants for energy upgrades]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/91361494-56ac-11ef-b75c-c3d0163d74f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/local-school-districts-receive-grants-for-energy-upgrades/article_91361494-56ac-11ef-b75c-c3d0163d74f2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T04:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oregon Department of Education announced Monday that it will improve facilities as seven districts statewide, including Roseburg, Winston-Dillard and South Umpqua school districts in Douglas County.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX GROWS TO 8,129 ACRES, 738 PEOPLE ASSIGNED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122271</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/10/diamond-complex-grows-to-8129-acres-738-people-assigned/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-grows-to-8129-acres-738-people-assigned"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T17:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 10, 2024 10:15 a.m.   The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, has grown to 8,129 acres with 728 people assigned as of midday Saturday. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 28 people assigned, but the Diamond Complex is sharing resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAMOND COMPLEX GROWS TO 8,129 ACRES, 738 PEOPLE ASSIGNED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122271</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/10/damond-complex-grows-to-8129-acres-738-people-assigned/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=damond-complex-grows-to-8129-acres-738-people-assigned"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T17:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 10, 2024 10:15 a.m.   The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, has grown to 8,129 acres with 728 people assigned as of midday Saturday. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 28 people assigned, but the Diamond Complex is sharing resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX UP TO 3,726 ACRES, REMAINS 14 PERCENT CONTAINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122269</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/10/homestead-complex-up-to-3726-acres-remains-14-percent-contained/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-up-to-3726-acres-remains-14-percent-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T16:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 9:45 a.m.  The Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, is up to 3,726 acres, and remains 14 percent contained. A UNF update said the fire is being managed by Northwest Incident Management Team 8. Friday on the 1,334-acre No Man Fire, control line on the west flank continued to prevent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community protection continues on Lee Falls Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174450</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174450"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T16:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry Grove, Ore. – Oregon Department of Forestry’s (ODF) Type 3 Incident Management Team, along with a Type 3 Incident Management Team from structural firefighters and the Washington County Sheriff's Office, continue protecting the community of Cherry Grove today.
With over 175 personnel from ODF, contract, and crews of adults in custody from Coffee Creek and South Fork Forest Camp working to mop up the fire line today, some community members can return to their homes. Two task forces of structural firefighters remain to protect homes and structures.
The interior of the Lee Falls fire continues to burn slowly so residents will experience some smoke. With recent fire activity, snags present a hazard around some roads. Snags are dead or burned standing trees that may easily fall. Crews tod…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building community through volunteerism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e9652e24-5338-11ef-ba1d-7ff7dee19601</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/building-community-through-volunteerism/article_e9652e24-5338-11ef-ba1d-7ff7dee19601.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at JustServe we are all about building community. One way to do that is to work alongside our friends and neighbors for a good cause. Another way is to reach out to strangers and those we don’t know well…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JENNIFER COALWELL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrollment underway for Roseburg school district]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/69c839ae-54c8-11ef-9f14-8f387cb943be</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/enrollment-underway-for-roseburg-school-district/article_69c839ae-54c8-11ef-9f14-8f387cb943be.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enrollment process is underway for the 2024-25 school year at Roseburg school district.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY FAIR DAY FOUR ACTIVITIES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122266</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/10/douglas-county-fair-day-four-activities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-fair-day-four-activities"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 10, 2024 7:00 a.m. It’s day four of the Douglas County Fair. It’s Family Day at the fair, sponsored by Pepsi and Clint Newell Auto Group. Kids aged 12 and under are admitted for free sponsored by the Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Tribe of Indians. Teens get in for $2 off when they...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spirit Halloween returns to Roseburg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ccc20570-5677-11ef-beba-0b0e8966b826</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/spirit-halloween-returns-to-roseburg/article_ccc20570-5677-11ef-beba-0b0e8966b826.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spirit Halloween is coming soon to 444 SE Stephens St., the former Rite Aid location in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Falls Fire 100% lined]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174447</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174447"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T04:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry Grove, Ore. – Oregon Department of Forestry’s (ODF) Type 3 Incident Management Team, who took command of fire operations today, along with a Type 3 Incident Management Team from structural firefighters and the Washington County Sheriff's Office. Today’s suppression efforts achieved control lines around the fire’s perimeter, keeping it at 280 acres.
ODF, contract, and crews of adults in custody from South Fork Forest Camp continued dozer and hand lines with ground crews receiving support from three helicopters dropping water on the Lee Falls Fire most of the afternoon and evening. The fire is now 100% lined.
With control lines established around the fire, and many areas plumbed with fire hose, the arduous process of mop up begins. Mop up is the process of cooling the perimeter of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>