<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-12-10T03:00:11.940Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DILLARD MAN DIES IN MYRTLE CREEK SHOOTING, ROSEBURG MAN JAILED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126966</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/dillard-man-dies-in-myrtle-creek-shooting-roseburg-man-jailed/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dillard-man-dies-in-myrtle-creek-shooting-roseburg-man-jailed"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T21:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 1:30 p.m.  A Dillard man died in a shooting incident in Myrtle Creek on Saturday and a Roseburg man is in jail charged with the crime. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at about 1:35 p.m., deputies responded after a caller said there was a physical disturbance with shots fired at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 12.9.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126962</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/inside-douglas-county-12-9-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-12-9-24"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T21:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greater Douglas United Way Executive Director Bryan Trenkle talks about how they help over 30 local non-profit organizations, and how residents can support their current campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Killed in Myrtle Creek Shooting, Suspect in Custody]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news177298</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news177298"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T20:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK, Ore. – A 22-year-old Myrtle Creek man was arrested on suspicion of murder Saturday, December 7th, 2024, after a disturbance with shots fired at the Rivers West RV Park in Myrtle Creek.
At about 1:35 pm, deputies from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office responded to the area of the RV park, 333 Ruckles Drive, after receiving information about a physical disturbance and shooting.
Responders located a male suffering from multiple gunshot wounds just south of the park on Booth Ranch Road. He was later identified as Damion Sumner, 29, of Dillard. Deputies and a Myrtle Creek Police Officer provided Sumner aid, but he succumbed to his wounds and was declared deceased on scene.
Daniel Hetrick, 22, of Myrtle Creek was taken into custody nearby without incident. Hetrick has been charged with second-degree murder and unlawful use of a weapon and lodged at the Douglas County Jail.
The Douglas County Major Crimes Team was activated and continues to investigate. The team consists of detectives from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office, Roseburg Police Department, Oregon State Police, and members of the Douglas County District Attorney’s Office. Cow Creek Tribal Police is also assisting in the investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Higher Education is More Important than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8548</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/why-higher-education-is-more-important-than-ever/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T20:17:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By RICK BAILEY I’m going to start with a disclaimer. I am a university president, so I have an obvious affection for higher education. The university I serve is a regionally responsive, liberal arts institution, so I am admittedly partial to the advantages that come with a broad-based education. Am I biased? Absolutely. But even…
The post Why Higher Education is More Important than Ever appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari is wild for holidays events]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7d2aa402-b277-11ef-b056-dbff2040536e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/wildlife-safari-is-wild-for-holidays-events/article_7d2aa402-b277-11ef-b056-dbff2040536e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T19:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari's Wildlights takes place 5 to 8 p.m. Dec. 13-15. It includes light displays in the village, a train ride, keeper talks, cocoa and an opportunity for kids to meet with Santa Claus. Admission is $10, or $7 for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER ALLEGED HARASSMENT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126957</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/roseburg-police-jail-man-after-alleged-harassment-incident-6/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-after-alleged-harassment-incident-6"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T19:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9,. 2024 11:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man after an alleged harassment incident on Saturday. An RPD report said at 6:50 p.m. officers contacted the 64-year-old in the 1300 block of Southeast Stephens Street. The man allegedly had a half-full opened beer can next to him that he was drinking. The man then...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING REPORTED HARASSMENT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126955</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-harassment-incident-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-harassment-incident-3"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T19:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 11:15 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man following a reported harassment incident on Saturday night. An RPD report said at 8:50 p.m. officers contacted the 44-year-old after he allegedly punched a female in the face in front of a business in the 700 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway.  The man was taken...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126953</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-incident-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-incident-4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T19:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 11:05 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged harassment incident on Saturday night. An RPD report said at 7:50 p.m. officers contacted the 44-year-old at Walmart in the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway when he returned after being previously trespassed. He was taken into custody without issue and charged...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO JAILED, STOLEN VEHICLE RECOVERED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126951</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/two-jailed-stolen-vehicle-recovered-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-jailed-stolen-vehicle-recovered-2"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T18:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 10:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed two people when a stolen vehicle was recovered early Saturday. An RPD report said at approximately 2:15 a.m. an officer made a traffic stop on the vehicle near the intersection of Northwest Harvey Drive and Northwest Stewart Parkway. All occupants were detained without incident. During the investigation,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN ON SECOND-DEGREE THEFT CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126949</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/roseburg-police-jail-man-on-second-degree-theft-charge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-on-second-degree-theft-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T18:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 10: 20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man on a second-degree theft charge on Sunday night. An RPD report said at 10:45 p.m. officers responded after a caller said there had been a theft from Walmart in the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. The 25-year-old suspect had allegedly gotten into a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DILLARD MAN JAILED FOLLOWING REPORTED ROBBERY INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126947</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/dillard-man-jailed-following-reported-robbery-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dillard-man-jailed-following-reported-robbery-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T18:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 10:00 a.m.    A Dillard man was jailed following a reported robbery incident on Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 3:15 p.m. a victim claimed that she had been hit in the face and body multiple times by 48-year-old Kip McCoy, while they were in her car near...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WISH UPON A STAR 12.9.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126938</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/wish-upon-a-star-12-9-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wish-upon-a-star-12-9-24"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Rogue Credit Union, our first Wish Upon a Star wish is granted Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg hires new public works director]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/705f2e4a-b656-11ef-8c1b-d3ea9a470efd</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/roseburg-hires-new-public-works-director/article_705f2e4a-b656-11ef-8c1b-d3ea9a470efd.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Herinckx has taken over the helm of the Roseburg Public Works Department after being promoted to director, effective Dec. 1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG WOMAN TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL, FOLLOWING TWO-VEHICLE WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126943</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/roseburg-woman-taken-to-the-hospital-following-two-vehicle-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-woman-taken-to-the-hospital-following-two-vehicle-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 9:30 a.m. A Roseburg woman was taken to the hospital following a two-vehicle wreck on Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 9:50 a.m. the 55-year-old was turning onto Colonial Road from Laurel Oaks Drive in the Lookingglass area. She reportedly pulled out in front of a pickup. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Families in Lane, Linn, Benton, Douglas, Yamhill and Washington counties recognized for their forest management by Oregon Tree Farm System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news177291</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news177291"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ELKTON, Ore. - The Oregon Tree Farm System honored family forest landowners for the exceptional management of their forests at its annual meeting in November. Top honors went to Douglas County’s Kesterson family as Oregon’s Outstanding Tree Farmers of the Year for 2025.
Receiving a Silver Award at the Oregon Tree Farm’s Annual Meeting were Tom and Julia Tibbs of Washington County for their multi-resource management of their 300 forested acres near Buxton.
Others being recognized for exemplary management of their family forests included:

Rich Clark from Benton County
John and Alesanne Dugan from Lane County
Steve and Katie Kohl from Linn County, and 
Neil Schroeder and Laurie and Jim Marsh from Yamhill County 

The Kesterson family’s 2,200-acre property near Elkton in Douglas County has been in the family since 1905. Currently under the leadership of fifth-generation owner Gary Williamson, the property is managed for wood, recreation, wildlife and water quality.
The property has approximately nine miles of river frontage along the Umpqua River. Their Big K Guest Ranch offers fishing, rafting, and accommodations for family and corporate gatherings.
The family manages 1,500 acres of forest for timber and wildlife habitat, and approximately 700 acres of pasture and hay fields for a herd of 90 cows.
Wildlife habitat and water quality are a focus on both the forested and streamside areas.
With much to be proud of managing the property, Gary Williamson states that he is most proud, blessed, and honored to be a part of a family that has been caring for the property for five generations, with his children being part of the sixth.
Oregon joined the Tree Farm System in 1941 and has recognized and honored family forest landowners as Outstanding Tree Farmers of the Year every year since 1966, except in 2021 the first year of the COVID pandemic.
                                                # # #]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County family named Oregon's Outstanding Tree Farmers (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news177290</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news177290"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ELKTON, Ore. - The Oregon Tree Farm System honored family forest landowners for the exceptional management of their forests at its annual meeting in November. They selected Douglas County’s Kesterson family as Oregon’s Outstanding Tree Farmers of the Year for 2025.
The Kesterson family’s 2,200-acre property near Elkton has been in the family since 1905. Currently under the leadership of fifth-generation owner Gary Williamson, the property is managed for wood, recreation, wildlife and water quality.
The property has approximately nine miles of river frontage along the Umpqua River. Their Big K Guest Ranch offers fishing, rafting, and accommodations for family and corporate gatherings.
The family manages 1,500 acres of forest for timber and wildlife habitat, and approximately 700 acres of pasture and hay fields for a herd of 90 cows.
Wildlife habitat and water quality are a focus on both the forested and streamside areas.
With much to be proud of managing the property, Gary Williamson states that he is most proud, blessed, and honored to be a part of a family that has been caring for the property for five generations, with his children being part of the sixth.
Receiving a Silver Award at the Oregon Tree Farm’s Annual Meeting were Tom and Julia Tibbs of Washington County for their multi-resource management of their 300 forested acres near Buxton.
Others being recognized for exemplary management of their family forests included:

Rich Clark from Benton County
John and Alesanne Dugan from Lane County
Steve and Katie Kohl from Linn County, and 
Neil Schroeder and Laurie and Jim Marsh from Yamhill County 

Oregon joined the Tree Farm System in 1941 and has recognized and honored family forest landowners as Outstanding Tree Farmers of the Year every year since 1966, except in 2021 the first year of the COVID pandemic.
                                                                       # # #]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWNG ALLEGED TRESPASS/DISORDERLY CONDUCT INCIDENTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126941</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/sutherlin-police-jail-man-followng-alleged-trespass-disorderly-conduct-incidents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-followng-alleged-trespass-disorderly-conduct-incidents"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 9:20 a.m. Sutherlin Police jailed a man following an alleged trespass and disorderly conduct incidents on Saturday. An SPD report said 31-year-old Rusty McGill was allegedly found inside a business in the 900 block of West Central Avenue and was trespassed by the owner. After being trespassed from the property, McGill reportedly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winston Martial Arts prepares for "Season's Beatings"]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/09c44cba-b430-11ef-ba6c-c722994eb8c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/sports/community_sports/winston-martial-arts-prepares-for-seasons-beatings/article_09c44cba-b430-11ef-ba6c-c722994eb8c2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Damian Dantibo’s Winston Martial Arts studio held a demonstration Friday at the Roseburg Senior Center, featuring local athletes who will compete in the upcoming Rumble at the Roseland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PATRICK MOORE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DENSE FOG ADVISORY THROUGH 12:00 P.M. MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126933</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/dense-fog-advisory-through-1200-p-m-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dense-fog-advisory-through-1200-p-m-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T12:14:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 4:10 a.m.  A Dense Fog Advisory is in effect until 12:00 p.m. Monday for much of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said visibility of one quarter mile or less in dense fog is expected. The Advisory area includes central Douglas County, Josephine and Jackson counties and eastern Curry County....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WARMING CENTER TO BE ACTIVATED FOR MONDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126930</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/warming-center-to-be-activated-for-monday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=warming-center-to-be-activated-for-monday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T12:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 3:50 a.m.  The United Community Action Network will activate the Roseburg Warming Center for Monday night. It will be held in the gymnasium of St. Joseph’s Church on West Stanton Street. Guests must arrive between 5:30 p.m. and 9:00 p.m. for check-in. A warm meal will be served during this time. Those...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY COUNCIL WITH VARIED AGENDA MONDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126928</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/city-council-with-varied-agenda-monday-night-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-council-with-varied-agenda-monday-night-3"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T11:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 3:30 a.m.  The Roseburg City Council will have a varied agenda for its meeting Monday night. Councilors will have second reading and adoption of an annexation and zone change ordinance for just over 5 acres of property in the 200 block of Northeast General Avenue. The annexation will bring the parcel into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY OF ROSEBURG SEEKING MEMBERRS FOR PUBLIC WORKS COMMISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126926</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/city-of-roseburg-seeking-memberrs-for-public-works-commission/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-of-roseburg-seeking-memberrs-for-public-works-commission"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T11:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 3:20 a.m.  The City of Roseburg is seeking members for the Public Works Commission. A city release said the commission has two vacancies. It serves in an advisory capacity to the city council. People normally appointed to these volunteer positions serve a three-year term unless they are serving the remainder of a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY OF ROSEBURG SELECTS NEW PUBLIC WORKS DIRECTOR]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126924</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/city-of-roseburg-selects-new-public-works-director/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-of-roseburg-selects-new-public-works-director"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T11:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 3:05 a.m.  Ryan Herinckx has taken over the helm of the Roseburg Public Works Department after being promoted to director, effective December 1st. A city release said for four years, Herinckx served as Design/Construction Manager, overseeing public works construction projects from budget-planning and design through completion of construction – managing about $24...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THRIVE UMPQUA HOSTS HOLDAY LIGHT RIDE ON DECEMBER 17TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126914</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/09/thrive-umpqua-hosts-holday-light-ride-on-december-17th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=thrive-umpqua-hosts-holday-light-ride-on-december-17th"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T11:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9, 2024 2:50 a.m.  Thrive Umpqua will hold the Holiday Lights Community Bike Ride on Tuesday, December 17th. The festive family-friendly event will go through the Hucrest neighborhood of Roseburg. Community partners Bike Walk Roseburg, the Umpqua Velo Club, and the Umpqua Valley Tennis Center are helping Thrive Umpqua with the event. The leisurely...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRAVEL TRAILER A TOTAL LOSS, FOLLOWING SATURDAY NIGHT FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126912</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/08/travel-trailer-a-total-loss-following-saturday-night-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=travel-trailer-a-total-loss-following-saturday-night-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T23:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 8, 2024 3:20 p.m.  A travel trailer was a total loss, following a fire on Saturday night. Battalion Chief Mitch Doss of Central Douglas Fire & Rescue said just before 9:00 p.m. crews were dispatched to the fire in the 400 block Gregory Street in Winston. Doss said the first arriving engine reported a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County tries out league level axe throwing at The Blade Axe House]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c817c81c-b346-11ef-ad14-dfe22f85082d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/douglas-county-tries-out-league-level-axe-throwing-at-the-blade-axe-house/article_c817c81c-b346-11ef-ad14-dfe22f85082d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T20:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The people of Roseburg had the chance to try their hand at league-level axe throwing during the Winter League Experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Travel Trailer on Gregory St. in Winston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news177281</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news177281"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T18:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 8:57 Saturday evening Central Douglas Fire & Rescue (CDF&R) was dispatched to a travel trailer on fire on Gregory Street in Winston.  Crews responded and were updated that the trailer was fully engulfed. The first arriving engine reported a fully involved travel trailer with multiple nearby structures. 
 
Thanks to the efficient response of our firefighters, the fire was stopped from spreading and contained to the travel trailer. The travel trailer suffered significant damage and is considered a total loss.  No injuries were reported by the resident or the firefighters working at the scene.
 
CDF&R responded to this incident with two fire engines, one truck and one command unit, totaling 9 personnel. Due to the heavy fire damage, crews could not determine the cause of the fire. Crews at the scene were assisted by Winston Police Department and Douglas County Sheriff's Office.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Central Douglas Fire &amp; Rescue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDLEYLD PARK MAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED ASSAULT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126910</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/08/idleyld-park-man-jailed-for-alleged-assault-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=idleyld-park-man-jailed-for-alleged-assault-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T14:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 8, 2024 6:55 a.m.    An Idleyld Park was jailed following an alleged assault incident early Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 12:00 a.m. the victim had two people call in to claim the 25-year-old man had been physical with the victim in the 1100 block of Lake Drive in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U-HAUL REPORTEDLY CAUSES DAMAGE TO FENCE IN PRIOR INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126908</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/08/u-haul-reportedly-causes-damage-to-fence-in-prior-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=u-haul-reportedly-causes-damage-to-fence-in-prior-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T14:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 8,. 2024 6:40 a.m.  A U-Haul vehicle reportedly caused damage to a fence in a prior incident reported on Friday at 5:00 p.m. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said the victim told a deputy the incident occurred on November 30th in the 100 block of Tipton Road, south of Roseburg. The victim said...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ELECTRICAL FIRE DAMAGES ROSEBURG HOUSE ON SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126902</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/08/electrical-fire-damages-roseburg-house-on-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=electrical-fire-damages-roseburg-house-on-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T14:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 8, 2024 6:30 a.m.  A fire damaged a Roseburg house on Saturday. Fire Chief Tyler Christopherson of the Roseburg Fire Department said shortly after 12:00 p.m. personnel responded to the structure fire in the 400 block of Southeast Leland Street. Christopherson said the reporting party had noted the roof of the home was on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DENSE FOG ADVISORY THROUGH SUNDAY AT 1:00 P.M.]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126899</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/08/dense-fog-advisory-through-sunday-at-100-p-m/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dense-fog-advisory-through-sunday-at-100-p-m"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T13:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 8, 2024 5:30 a.m. A Dense Fog Advisory is in effect through 1:00 p.m. Sunday for most of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said visibility of one quarter mile or less in dense fog is expected. The Advisory area applies to southwest Oregon including central Douglas County, especially in valleys and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Residential Structure Fire - 431 SE Leland Street - 12-7-24 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news177278</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news177278"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T04:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 12:07 p.m. on December 7, 2024, Roseburg Fire Department personnel responded to a residential structure fire located at 431 SE Leland Street. The reporting party had noted the roof of the residential structure was on fire and all occupants were out of the home.  
Firefighters arrived on scene to find a two story residential structure with heavy smoke showing from both the roof vents and the vents in the gable ends. Firefighters found an active fire inside the attic of the two story structure. Firefighters completed a primary and secondary search of the home, extinguished the fire, and completed overhaul. Stop loss measures were taken to cover holes in the roof from impending weather.
A fire investigator was on scene. The cause of the fire was determined to be electrical in nature. The structure sustained structural, smoke, and water damage.
Fourteen firefighters assisted with firefighting operations.  Other agencies assisting with the fire included Umpqua Valley Ambulance, Roseburg Police Department, Avista Utilities, and Pacific Power.  
For the latest information regarding the City of Roseburg Fire Department, please visit our website at www.cityofroseburg.org or like us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/roseburgfire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Fire Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holiday Lights community bike ride set for Dec. 17]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3bddac60-b510-11ef-a46b-53fea8c30636</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/holiday-lights-community-bike-ride-set-for-dec-17/article_3bddac60-b510-11ef-a46b-53fea8c30636.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T02:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual Holiday Lights Community Bike Ride will take place at 6 p.m. Tuesday, Dec. 17. Riders of all ages and abilities are invited to join this family-friendly 3.3-mile ride through the festive Hucrest neighborhood in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ornament making class at Thrive Umpqua Dec. 11]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2ffef4e4-b510-11ef-b0d9-07f93f2ea690</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/ornament-making-class-at-thrive-umpqua-dec-11/article_2ffef4e4-b510-11ef-b0d9-07f93f2ea690.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T02:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happier Hour: Holiday Ornaments - Registration Required]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Myrtle Creek Elementary decorates town Christmas tree]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ca4f350c-b431-11ef-a84c-33d64171dca2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/myrtle-creek-elementary-decorates-town-christmas-tree/article_ca4f350c-b431-11ef-a84c-33d64171dca2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T00:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students from Myrtle Creek Elementary School spent the first week of December decorating the town’s Christmas tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sheep and Sip event brings Douglas County sheep farms and wineries together]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/92cf1222-b4e6-11ef-b688-277b44cf9ff7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/sheep-and-sip-event-brings-douglas-county-sheep-farms-and-wineries-together/article_92cf1222-b4e6-11ef-b688-277b44cf9ff7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-07T21:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This weekend, two agricultural industries in Douglas County—sheep breeding and viticulture—came together for a collaboration during the county-wide event Sheep and Sip, supporting one another in a celebration of local agriculture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COMMERCIAL DUNGENESS CRAB SEASON BEGINS DECEMBER 16TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126895</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/07/commercial-dungeness-crab-season-begins-december-16th-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=commercial-dungeness-crab-season-begins-december-16th-2"/>
        <updated>2024-12-07T19:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 7, 2024 11:30 a.m.  Oregon’s commercial Dungeness crab fishery opens December 16 from Cape Falcon at Oswald State Park to the California border. An announcement Friday from the Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife said pre-season testing in this area shows crab meat fill meets criteria and domoic acid is below the safety threshold....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADAPT awarded five star primary care home designation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f24ce974-b336-11ef-81c5-a762fb5c8871</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/adapt-awarded-five-star-primary-care-home-designation/article_f24ce974-b336-11ef-81c5-a762fb5c8871.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-07T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adapt Integrated Health Care achieved the five star Patient-Centered Primary Care Home designation, the highest recognition awarded by the Oregon Health Authority.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg fugitive reportedly arrested in Tennessee]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9116d010-b3ff-11ef-9c07-af67005cb08d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/court/roseburg-fugitive-reportedly-arrested-in-tennessee/article_9116d010-b3ff-11ef-9c07-af67005cb08d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Lee Thacker, 57, of Roseburg is reportedly in the Knox County Jail in Tennessee awaiting extradition to Douglas County, according to the Roseburg Police Department.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PATRICK MOORE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laundry Love event helps low-income people wash clothes for free]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1ba110e0-b29a-11ef-9dc0-93462f98861e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/laundry-love-event-helps-low-income-people-wash-clothes-for-free/article_1ba110e0-b29a-11ef-9dc0-93462f98861e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T23:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laundry Love is a neighboring movement that partners with groups, schools and local laundromats to wash the clothes and bedding of low-income and/or no-income families and person(s).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas Craft Fair returns to Douglas County over Dec. 6 weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c7e31778-b429-11ef-bd95-afef16222266</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/christmas-craft-fair-returns-to-douglas-county-over-dec-6-weekend/article_c7e31778-b429-11ef-bd95-afef16222266.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T23:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The parking lots at the Douglas County Fairgrounds overflowed with hundreds of cars as visitors flocked to the 51st annual Christmas Craft Fair, held Friday through Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 12.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126892</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/06/inside-douglas-county-12-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-12-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T22:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Bailey was live at the Douglas County Christmas Craft Fair at the fairgrounds, talking with staffer Ciera Keith and several vendors that are at the event through Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Give the gift of your time]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/dc553114-b1a9-11ef-b27b-47e56eb7d92e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/give-the-gift-of-your-time/article_dc553114-b1a9-11ef-b27b-47e56eb7d92e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T19:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you feel it? Whether or not you celebrate Christmas, there is a spirit of generosity and good will which accompanies the hustle and bustle of holiday events and the frantic search for perfect gifts. I find people are more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JENNIFER COALWELL For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REPRESENTATIVE GOODWIN, HOUSE GOP CAUCUS PRAISE U.S. SENATE LEGISLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126888</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/06/representative-goodwin-house-gop-caucus-praise-u-s-senate-legislation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=representative-goodwin-house-gop-caucus-praise-u-s-senate-legislation"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T19:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 6, 2024 11:00 a.m.  On Thursday, State Representative Christine Goodwin praised the U.S. Senate passage of the Federal Disaster Tax Relief Act. A release from the Oregon House Republican Caucus said Goodwin called the act, landmark legislation that builds upon her pioneering efforts in the Oregon State Legislature to protect disaster survivors from burdensome...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG CONCERT CHORALE PRESENTS DECEMBER DELIGHTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126886</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/06/roseburg-concert-chorale-presents-december-delights-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-concert-chorale-presents-december-delights-3"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T18:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 6, 2024 10:30 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Roseburg Concert Chorale presents December Delights: A Feast of Holiday Favorites, in the Whipple Fine Arts Center Friday night at 7:00 p.m. and Sunday afternoon at 3:00 p.m. The performance is directed by Dr. Jason Heald and accompanied by Tammy Finch-Johnson. It will include...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. MARSHALS SERVICE ASSIST ROSEBURG POLICE IN FUGITIVE APPREHENSION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126884</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/06/u-s-marshals-service-assist-roseburg-police-in-fugitive-apprehension/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=u-s-marshals-service-assist-roseburg-police-in-fugitive-apprehension"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T18:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 6, 2024 10:15 a.m.  The U.S. Marshals Service has assisted the Roseburg Police Department in apprehending a fugitive who failed to appear for a court date earlier this year. RPD Public Information Officer Sergeant Daniel Allen said in May of 2022, a Roseburg man, Jerry Lee Thacker, now age 57, was arrested on charges...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRAVEL TRAILER CONSIDERED A TOTAL LOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126878</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/06/travel-trailer-considered-a-total-loss/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=travel-trailer-considered-a-total-loss"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T18:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 6, 2024 9:50 a.m.  A travel trailer is considered a total loss following an early morning fire Friday. Nick Wecks of Central Douglas County Fire & Rescue said just before 2:25 a.m. crews were dispatched to the fire on Meadowood Drive in Winston. Wecks said the trailer, located right next to a house, was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Marshals Service assist Roseburg P.D. in fugitive apprehension effort.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news177257</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news177257"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T18:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May of 2022, Jerry Lee Thacker, now a 57-year-old Roseburg man, was arrested on charges of Rape, Sodomy, Unlawful Sexual Penetration and Sexual Abuse. The alleged victim was a 13-year-old juvenile female and Roseburg resident. On January 9, 2024, Thacker failed to appear for trial resulting in a warrant for his arrest. The Roseburg Police Department began an investigation into Thacker’s whereabouts at that time. Using intelligence gathered during that effort, investigators came to believe Thacker fled to Knoxville, Tennessee and was living with a family member. Our agency reached out to the U.S. Marshals Service in Oregon and requested assistance in apprehending Thacker. The U.S. Marshals Service agreed to take the case and within a short period of time, located Thacker and served the warrant by taking Thacker into custody in the Knoxville, Tennessee area. Thacker was lodged at the Knox County Jail in Tennessee pending extradition. The Roseburg Police Department is very appreciative for the assistance of The U.S. Marshals Service in this case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Police Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard Shoe Repair fires under investigation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d187b9aa-b104-11ef-ba27-d7390494e71c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/harvard-shoe-repair-fires-under-investigation/article_d187b9aa-b104-11ef-ba27-d7390494e71c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard Shoe Repair, a Roseburg staple for more than 30 years, is under investigation after a fire early Monday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KYLE BAILEY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard Show Repair fires under investigation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d187b9aa-b104-11ef-ba27-d7390494e71c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/harvard-show-repair-fires-under-investigation/article_d187b9aa-b104-11ef-ba27-d7390494e71c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard Shoe Repair, a Roseburg staple for more than 30 years, is under investigation after a fire early Monday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KYLE BAILEY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CHRISTMAS STORY IS NEARLY SOLD-OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126876</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/06/a-christmas-story-is-nearly-sold-out/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-christmas-story-is-nearly-sold-out"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T17:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 6, 2024 9:20 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Actors Community Theatre’s 14-show run of the production of A Christmas Story is nearly sold out, after opening Thursday night. Narrator Brian Simshauser said as of Friday, only around 50 tickets are still available. Many of those are for two fundraising performances on December...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 12.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126873</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/06/local-real-estate-today-12-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-12-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T17:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group of Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our weekly look at local real estate data:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Recreation Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/485b662c-b1f4-11ef-abe3-2b242cb791ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/douglas-county-recreation-report/article_485b662c-b1f4-11ef-abe3-2b242cb791ca.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T17:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FISHING REPORT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 12.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126868</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/12/06/morning-conversation-12-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-12-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T17:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Umpqua Actors Community Theatre, Brian Simshauser and Fisher McEnroe talk about the production of A Christmas Story, which is on stage through December 22nd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Travel Trailer Fire (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news177248</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news177248"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T15:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See the news release in the attached document below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Central Douglas Fire &amp; Rescue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tsunami warning turns into Reedsport drill]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/21913730-b373-11ef-8dfe-1fdc85060e60</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/public_safety/tsunami-warning-turns-into-reedsport-drill/article_21913730-b373-11ef-8dfe-1fdc85060e60.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By the end of Thursday's lunch hour, Reedsport was back to normal and experiencing unseasonably pleasant weather, barely an hour after the tsunami warning issued by the National Weather Service was canceled. Residents working at businesses along Highway 101 described…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PATRICK MOORE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: The many gifts of serviceberry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/98abb9ba-b0d2-11ef-a50e-370bb15d328f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/ask-a-master-gardener-the-many-gifts-of-serviceberry/article_98abb9ba-b0d2-11ef-a50e-370bb15d328f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I have a small yard. I only have room to add one shrub or compact tree that will provide interest and attract pollinators and birds. Is there one that can cover all those bases?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JULIE BURCHSTEAD For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magical winter escapes: European Christmas markets to visit in 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6b0a37dc-b264-11ef-8f3b-07e48215dccf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/magical-winter-escapes-european-christmas-markets-to-visit-in-2024/article_6b0a37dc-b264-11ef-8f3b-07e48215dccf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas markets in the United States and Europe are terrific places to get a taste of traditional foods, shop for unique gifts and soak up some holiday cheer. Here are just a few of the places you can explore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JANE GREEN For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Concert Chorale performs Dec. 6]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/20de248e-a4a9-11ef-908f-479ee1502454</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/life/roseburg-concert-chorale-performs-dec-6/article_20de248e-a4a9-11ef-908f-479ee1502454.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Roseburg Concert Chorale will perform December Delights: A Feast of Holiday Favorites on Dec. 6 at 7 p.m. and Dec. 8 at 3 p.m. in Jacoby Auditorium at Umpqua Community College.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>