<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-03-11T19:08:17.377Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon's Urban and Community Forestry Conference is moving to Eugene on June 27 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170608</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170608"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T18:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EUGENE, Ore. – Early registration is now open for Oregon’s largest Urban and Community Forestry Conference. The all-day conference, which has been held in Portland for the past several years in early June will be held this year on Thursday, June 27 at Venue 252 in downtown Eugene.  It is put on by the Oregon Department of Forestry and USDA Forest Service in collaboration with the non-profit organization Oregon Community Trees, whose board members organize and staff the event. 
The conference’s theme – More Housing, More Trees: Giving Oregonians Both – will bring together advocates for more housing, and greater density and infill in existing residential neighborhoods, with advocates for preserving and expanding urban forest canopy to ensure the health and well-being of city residents. 
Earl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAN CITED FOR ALLEGEDLY STEALING CAT FOOD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116607</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/man-cited-for-allegedly-stealing-cat-food/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=man-cited-for-allegedly-stealing-cat-food"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T18:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 11:05 a.m.  A Roseburg man was cited for allegedly stealing cat food on Saturday. An RPD report said at 10:30 a.m. the 72-year-old was caught by loss prevention at a store in the 2300 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway after he allegedly stole two cans of cat food. The man was cited...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TEXTING WHILE DRIVING LEADS TO THREE-VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116605</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/texting-while-driving-leads-to-three-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=texting-while-driving-leads-to-three-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T17:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 11:00 a.m. Roseburg Police responded to a three-vehicle crash at the intersection of Northwest Calkins Avenue and Northwest Lynwood Street on Sunday night, shortly after 8:35 p.m. After an investigation, it was determined that a 37-year-old woman was texting while driving and crashed her vehicle into two other vehicles which were unoccupied....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER DUMPSTER FIRE WAS SPOTTED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116603</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/roseburg-police-jail-man-after-dumpster-fire-was-spotted/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-after-dumpster-fire-was-spotted"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T17:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 10:45 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man after a dumpster fire was spotted early Sunday morning. An RPD report said at 3:00 a.m. officers responded to a business in the 1100 block of Northeast Stephens Street after a caller said there was a fire. A 34-year-old man was contacted as he was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CHARGE MAN FOR UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY INTO A VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116600</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/roseburg-police-charge-man-for-unauthorized-entry-into-a-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-charge-man-for-unauthorized-entry-into-a-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T17:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 10:30 a.m.    Roseburg Police arrested a man for unauthorized entry into a motor vehicle early Sunday. An RPD report said officers were contacted about a theft that had allegedly occurred. The victim tracked one of the items and discovered it was inside a business in the 800 block of Northwest Garden...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Ranked #2 in the nation for Firewise sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170590</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170590"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore.—With 290 Firewise USA sites in good standing, the Oregon Department of Forestry is proud that Oregon is ranked number two in the nation for number of Firewise USA sites. In 2023, Oregon added 39 new sites creating more fire-adapted communities. 
Along with being number two as a state in 2023, Oregon is also home to the number four and number five counties with the most sites in the nation: Jackson County with 75 sites and Deschutes County with 73 sites. These accomplishments would not have been possible without the dedication of community members and those that led the charge. 
What is Firewise USA? Firewise USA is a program that helps guide communities in the process of protecting their homes and neighborhood from wildfire. The program is run by the National Fire Protection As…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CHARGED WITH SECOND-DEGREE CRIMINAL TRESPASS ON SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116598</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/roseburg-man-charged-with-second-degree-criminal-trespass-on-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-charged-with-second-degree-criminal-trespass-on-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T17:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 10:20 a.m.  A Roseburg man was jailed by Roseburg Police on the charge of second-degree criminal trespass on Sunday. An RPD report said the 21-year-old had been trespassed from a location in the 900 block of Northwest Veterans Way numerous times. At 12:00 p.m. he was in the location again and was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116596</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-21/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-21"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T17:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged trespass incident on Friday night. An RPD report said at approximately 8:10 p.m. officers responded to the 1800 block of Northeast Stephens Street after a caller said there was an intoxicated man who was refusing to leave the property. When asked the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED PRIOR FRAUD INCIDENT/NEW CRIME]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116591</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/roseburg-man-jailed-for-alleged-prior-fraud-incident-new-crime/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-for-alleged-prior-fraud-incident-new-crime"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 9;50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged prior fraud incident on Saturday and for a new crime as well. An RPD report said on January 5th officers took a report regarding a wallet being stolen and an Oregon EBT Card from the wallet being used at three businesses in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116589</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-10/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-10"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged harassment incident early Friday. An RPD report said just before 3:45 a.m. officers responded to a disturbance in the 400 block of Northeast Winchester Street. A 45-year-old man stated that a victim had taken $1,000 from him and he had used physical...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE ARREST TWO PEOPLE FOR ALLEGED KIDNAPPING/ROBBERY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116585</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/roseburg-police-arrest-two-people-for-alleged-kidnapping-robbery/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-arrest-two-people-for-alleged-kidnapping-robbery"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 9:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police arrested two people for an alleged kidnapping incident early Friday. An RPD report said at 3:00 a.m. officers contacted 38-year-old Rushil Solay of Grants Pass and 30-year-old Aleida Santos of Medford in the 3100 block of Northwest Aviation Drive after they were called in for kidnapping a Medford...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regional Forest Practice Committee for southwest Oregon meets March 19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170589</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170589"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T15:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. – The Regional Forest Practice Committee for southwest Oregon will meet at 10 a.m. on Tuesday, March 19 at the Douglas Forest Protective Association, located at 1758 NE Airport Rd. in Roseburg. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda. To provide public comment, please email forestresources.committees@odf.oregon.gov. 
The committee’s agenda includes:

ODF updates and member training requirements
Updates and informing post-disturbance harvest rulemaking
HCP update
Planning and priority for guidance development
Forest Practice Technical Guidance comment review

The public may attend in-person or online via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 72 hours before the meeting by emailing forestresources.committees@odf.oregon.gov.
Regional Forest Practices Committees are panels of citizens – mandated under Oregon law – that advise the Oregon Board of Forestry on current forestry issues and forest management approaches. In 1971, the legislature enacted Oregon’s Forest Practices Act which includes three Regional Forest Practices Committees, serving the Eastern, Northwest, and Southwest regions of the state. Under Oregon law, a majority of the committees’ members must be private forest landowners and logging or forest operations companies.
Oregon’s forests are among the state’s most valued resources, providing a balanced mix of environmental, economic, and social benefits. View more information on the RFPC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public gets to know local K-9s at fundraising event]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ba83e826-df2e-11ee-8b8b-0f6af03c9655</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/public-gets-to-know-local-k-9s-at-fundraising-event/article_ba83e826-df2e-11ee-8b8b-0f6af03c9655.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eros tries to steal his handler's snacks and loves spinning around in circles. Buster embodies the boundless energy and exuberance of a toddler. Nike's the old man, with grey in his face and knowledge of what's expected of him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIND ADVISORY 11:00 A.M. TO 11:00 P.M. FOR HIGHER ELEVATIONS IN CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116580</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/wind-advisory-1100-a-m-to-1100-p-m-for-higher-elevations-in-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wind-advisory-1100-a-m-to-1100-p-m-for-higher-elevations-in-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T11:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 4:00 a.m.  A Wind Advisory is in effect Monday from 11:00 a.m. to 11:00 p.m. for elevated terrain in Central Douglas County, eastern Curry County and Josephine County. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said south winds of 15 to 25 miles per hour with gusts up to 45 miles per hour...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY STARTING MONDAY NIGHT FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116577</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/winter-weather-advisory-starting-monday-night-for-mountain-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-starting-monday-night-for-mountain-areas"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 24, 2024 3:50 a.m. A Winter Weather Advisory remains in effect from 5:00 p.m. Monday to 5:00 p.m. Tuesday for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said 5 to 10 inches of snow is expected with up to 14 inches at peaks and ridgetops. Winds gusting as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOLLOWING OVERNIGHT DISTURBANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116575</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/winston-police-jail-woman-following-overnight-disturbance/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-police-jail-woman-following-overnight-disturbance"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 22, 2024 3:40 a.m. Winston Police jailed a woman following an overnight disturbance early Sunday. A WPD report said at about 2:00 a.m. 25-year-old Lily Selzer, who was allegedly intoxicated, pushed her way uninvited into a residence in the 300 block of Southeast Park Street. Selzer reportedly refused to leave, attempted to steal a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG CITY COUNCIL TO GET UPDATE ON URBAN GROWTH BOUNDARY SWAP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116571</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/roseburg-city-council-to-get-update-on-urban-growth-boundary-swap/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-city-council-to-get-update-on-urban-growth-boundary-swap"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Roseburg City Council will get an update on a potential Urban Growth Boundary Swap as part of its meeting Monday night. The process began in 2018 when staff were approached by two property owners who have a significant amount of land within the UGB. The properties face substantial development...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW CITY RECORDER FOR ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116568</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/new-city-recorder-for-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=new-city-recorder-for-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 3:20 a.m. The City of Roseburg welcomed new City Recorder Amy Nytes last week. Nytes replaces Patty Hitt, who retired on February 29th. City Manager Nikki Messenger said, “We are excited to welcome Amy to the team”. Messenger said, “She has hit the ground running. She is a great addition to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN CITY COUNCIL MEETING MONDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116566</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/sutherlin-city-council-meeting-monday-night-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-city-council-meeting-monday-night-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 3:00 a.m. The Sutherlin City Council will vote on several resolutions at its meeting on Monday night. Those include a Workforce Housing & Homelessness Task Force, Surplus Property, Safe Routes to School and other topics. A presentation on the police officer of the year will be made. The meeting begins at 7:00...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FISH AND WILDLIFE COMMISSION TO MEET IN ROSEBURG THURSDAY/FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116564</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/11/fish-and-wildlife-commission-to-meet-in-roseburg-thursday-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fish-and-wildlife-commission-to-meet-in-roseburg-thursday-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T09:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 11, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Oregon Fish and Wildlife Commission will meet in Roseburg on Thursday and Friday. An ODFW release said Thursday’s meeting is a tour of local projects including Northwestern pond turtle conservation and oak restoration at Ford’s Pond, beaver restoration on working lands, and West Region’s Wildlife Research project looking at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON POLICE JAIL MAN ON DRIVING/DRUG CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116562</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/10/winston-police-jail-man-on-driving-drug-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-police-jail-man-on-driving-drug-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T20:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 10, 2024 1:20 p.m. Winston Police jailed a man on driving and drug charges on Friday night. A WPD report said at 7:20 p.m. officers stopped the 48-year-old in the 10000 block of Highway 99 South. His driver’s license was suspended at the misdemeanor level. Officers observed drug paraphernalia in the vehicle and took...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoyle secures $14.6M in funding appropriations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/43ff8fe0-de50-11ee-91c2-b7ef676845a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/hoyle-secures-14-6m-in-funding-appropriations/article_43ff8fe0-de50-11ee-91c2-b7ef676845a2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, U.S. Rep. Val Hoyle announced she secured over $14 million for 13 projects in Oregon’s 4th Congressional District in the House-passed Consolidated Appropriations Act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Lions Club to hold food drive Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fa0706d8-dd92-11ee-84d4-37b0fcd39108</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/sutherlin-lions-club-to-hold-food-drive-tuesday/article_fa0706d8-dd92-11ee-84d4-37b0fcd39108.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — The Sutherlin Lions Club is planning a food drive from 10 a.m. to 2 p.m. Tuesday at Shop Smart Grocery Store in an effort to curb food insecurity of families in the area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club News: Explore Brice Creek Trail on March 16]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/34d4e81c-dcb1-11ee-a2b5-171422661b32</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/club-news-explore-brice-creek-trail-on-march-16/article_34d4e81c-dcb1-11ee-a2b5-171422661b32.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Friends of the Umpqua Hiking Club hike is scheduled for March 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pawfect companions: bringing pets to work]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/eae0edc4-da7f-11ee-a004-b788508d0e98</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/pawfect-companions-bringing-pets-to-work/article_eae0edc4-da7f-11ee-a004-b788508d0e98.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bailey’s flowing, golden locks dusted along the floor of MasterCuts during her shift at work. Her owner, Sean Hudson, called her name as her four paws trotted along and she nuzzled her head into him for more pets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Gem and Mineral club meeting Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a4fde41a-dc0f-11ee-a2d5-8bc30ae464c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/umpqua-gem-and-mineral-club-meeting-wednesday/article_a4fde41a-dc0f-11ee-a2d5-8bc30ae464c2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Umpqua Gem and Mineral Club’s next meeting will be held Wednesday at Westside Christian Church, 2712 W. Harvard Ave., Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marriages: Feb. 26-March 1]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/75ac7938-db1a-11ee-850a-5b51e85cc0e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/marriages-feb-26-march-1/article_75ac7938-db1a-11ee-850a-5b51e85cc0e2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following marriage licenses were issued by the Douglas County Clerk's Office from Feb. 26 to March 1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg library building Spanish language collection]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/504ed390-dcb2-11ee-8990-2b6e6a0e339b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/roseburg-library-building-spanish-language-collection/article_504ed390-dcb2-11ee-8990-2b6e6a0e339b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish language readers now can get new, popular titles at Roseburg Public Library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KRIS WILEY Library News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Isabel Stribling named to honor roll]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/35319556-dbe6-11ee-9d37-8ffe65d62ef1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/isabel-stribling-named-to-honor-roll/article_35319556-dbe6-11ee-9d37-8ffe65d62ef1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Isabel Stribling, of Roseburg, made the dean's honor roll at the University of Wyoming's fall semester.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fifth Annual AT-TIES Together conference in Salem April 18-19]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/23a1db58-dcdf-11ee-ba15-43b6c0977383</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/fifth-annual-at-ties-together-conference-in-salem-april-18-19/article_23a1db58-dcdf-11ee-ba15-43b6c0977383.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Registration is open for the annual AT-TIES Together conference scheduled for April 18-19 at the Salem Convention Center. This conference is hosted by the Regional and Statewide Services for Students with Orthopedic Impairment and the Oregon Technology Access Program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOYLE SECURES $14.6 MILLION IN FUNDING APPROPRIATIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116557</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/09/hoyle-secures-14-6-million-in-funding-appropriations/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hoyle-secures-14-6-million-in-funding-appropriations"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T14:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 9, 2024 6:30 a.m. On Friday, U.S. Representative Val Hoyle announced that she secured over $14 million for 13 projects in Oregon’s 4th Congressional District in the House-passed Consolidated Appropriations Act. Projects in Douglas County include: *$500,000 for the Glide Revitalization Resource Center *$1 million for the Kellog Rural Fire District for the main...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIGH WIND WARNING FROM SATURDAY EVENING THROUGH 8:00 A.M. SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116554</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/09/high-wind-warning-from-saturday-evening-through-800-a-m-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=high-wind-warning-from-saturday-evening-through-800-a-m-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T14:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 9, 2024 6:00 a.m.  A High Wind Warning is in effect from 10:00 p.m. Saturday through 8:00 a.m. Sunday for the headlands and exposed areas of Highway 101 on the south central and Curry County coast. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said south winds of 45 to 55 miles per hour with gusts...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local first responders participate in winter training]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fd3a34e8-db75-11ee-8f9f-2fa01814c58e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local-first-responders-participate-in-winter-training/article_fd3a34e8-db75-11ee-8f9f-2fa01814c58e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lt. paramedic Josh McDonald, firefighter/EMT Hayley Wisener and officer Lt. John Tranter of Sutherlin Fire Department spent two days in February expanding their fire service knowledge at the annual Winter Fire School in Salem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Figure it out: Winter Fire School teaches fire service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fd3a34e8-db75-11ee-8f9f-2fa01814c58e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/figure-it-out-winter-fire-school-teaches-fire-service/article_fd3a34e8-db75-11ee-8f9f-2fa01814c58e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lt. paramedic Josh McDonald, firefighter/EMT Hayley Wisener and officer Lt. John Tranter of Sutherlin Fire Department spent two days in February expanding their fire service knowledge at the annual Winter Fire School in Salem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAFE HAVEN FUNDRAISER INCLUDES GOLDEN CORK DRAWING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116549</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/safe-haven-fundraiser-includes-golden-cork-drawing/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=safe-haven-fundraiser-includes-golden-cork-drawing"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 11:00 a.m. The non-profit has been serving the community for 32 years. The goal of the evening is to raise funds for its vital programs. Executive Director Evie Kumar said 25 percent of their annual budget comes from fundraising. The goal for the evening is to raise $90,000. While the event is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG PUBLIC LIBRARY TO HOST GEOLOGIST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116546</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/roseburg-public-library-to-host-geologist/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-public-library-to-host-geologist"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 10:40 a.m.  Roseburg Public Library will host geologist Larry Broeker on Thursday night March 21st at 6:30 p.m. His program is titled, “Mt. Eddy: Inhospitable Rock, Harsh Climes, Tenacious Flora”. Broeker is a retired geologist who worked at the Umpqua National Forest. He will discuss the geology and geobotany of north-central California’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE AND RELEASE MAN FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116544</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/roseburg-police-cite-and-release-man-for-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-and-release-man-for-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 1o:15 a.m.   Roseburg Police cited and released a man for a warrant on Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 11:50 a.m. officers contacted the 47-year-old in the 200 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. The warrant was out of Cottage Grove. The man was given a new court date to appear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MYRTLE CREEK MAN FOR DUII]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116542</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/roseburg-police-cite-myrtle-creek-man-for-duii/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-myrtle-creek-man-for-duii"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a Myrtle Creek man for an alleged DUII incident early Friday. An RPD report said at 2:20 a.m. officers stopped the 40-year-old near the intersection of West Harvard Avenue and West Madrone Street. The officer noticed signs of impairment. The driver consented to standard field sobriety tests...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN CITED FOR DUII INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116540</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/myrtle-creek-man-cited-for-duii-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-cited-for-duii-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 10:00 a.m. A Myrtle Creek man was cited by Roseburg Police for an alleged DUII incident on Thursday night. An RPD report said just after 10:00 p.m. officers observed the 25-year-old commit several traffic violations after leaving a business near the intersection of Northwest Kline Street and Northwest Hughwood Avenue. Officers stopped...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR PRIOR RESTRAINING ORDER VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116538</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-prior-restraining-order-violation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-prior-restraining-order-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T17:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a prior restraining order violation on Thursday evening. An RPD report said on February 27th the 57-year-old allegedly violated a restraining order by contacting a victim at her place of employment. At 9:30 p.m. deputies from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office contacted the man...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116536</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-7/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-7"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T17:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged theft on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 9:00 p.m. officers contacted the 39-year-old for allegedly stealing a pair of denim jeans from the store in the 1400 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. The woman reportedly admitted to the theft...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Schools negotiates new union contracts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1bf0bd32-dce1-11ee-b0eb-f35318d7eb9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/roseburg-public-schools-negotiates-new-union-contracts/article_1bf0bd32-dce1-11ee-b0eb-f35318d7eb9d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Schools approved new contracts with local unions at a special meeting held Tuesday night at the district office in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Fire Department to issue burn permits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c27cbea8-dcd2-11ee-9b5c-2bfda6afa1b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-fire-department-to-issue-burn-permits/article_c27cbea8-dcd2-11ee-9b5c-2bfda6afa1b6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Roseburg Fire Department will begin issuing 30 day residential burn permits April 15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Students, community members explore UCC for future opportunities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d4d6a8b4-da86-11ee-a74c-db6311399bbb</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/students-community-members-explore-ucc-for-future-opportunities/article_d4d6a8b4-da86-11ee-a74c-db6311399bbb.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — Nicole Kloha stood in line with her friends ahead of an Umpqua Community College mathematics booth trying to see what could be offered in post-secondary education and onward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falleni named Future First Citizen]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/eeaefa30-dd0f-11ee-81d8-0332a8fb665c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/falleni-named-future-first-citizen/article_eeaefa30-dd0f-11ee-81d8-0332a8fb665c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Massimo Falleni was declared the 2024 Future First Citizen at Thursday's Roseburg High School Foundation Scholarship Night at the Rose Theater.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funding secured to build veterans' home in Roseburg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d375fe0c-dd5b-11ee-ad86-27f2588e0997</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/funding-secured-to-build-veterans-home-in-roseburg/article_d375fe0c-dd5b-11ee-ad86-27f2588e0997.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM — Oregon will provide $35 million in matching funds for a veterans home to be built in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC student a guest at State of the Union]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b348898e-dd5a-11ee-b6f3-5f0ec1f4bbdd</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/ucc-student-a-guest-at-state-of-the-union/article_b348898e-dd5a-11ee-b6f3-5f0ec1f4bbdd.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Danielle Lisette Hubbard, a member of the Army National Guard and second-year nursing student at Umpqua Community College, attended the State of the Union address Thursday as a guest of U.S. Rep. Val Hoyle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SENATOR BROCK SMITH AND TEAM SECURE FUNDING FOR VETERANS’ HOME IN ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116529</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/senator-brock-smith-and-team-secure-funding-for-veterans-home-in-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=senator-brock-smith-and-team-secure-funding-for-veterans-home-in-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T12:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 4:10 a.m. State Senator David Brock Smith and his team have secured funding for Oregon’s third veterans’ home which will be built in Roseburg. Senate Bill 5701 included in Section 500, the State of Oregon’s match of $35 million dollars to move the project forward. Next is seeking a federal grant from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MASSIMO FALLENI NAMED FUTURE FIRST CITIZEN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116527</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/massimo-falleni-named-future-first-citizen/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=massimo-falleni-named-future-first-citizen"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 3:45 a.m.  The Roseburg High School Foundation has named Massimo Falleni as its Future First Citizen for 2024. The award was given out during an event at Roseburg High School on Thursday night. Falleni earned $10,000 toward tuition at the college of his choice. Massimo plans to major in physics and go...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOYLE WELCOMES ROSEBURG RESIDENT AS HER GUEST AT STATE OF THE UNION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116525</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/hoyle-welcomes-roseburg-resident-as-her-guest-at-state-of-the-union/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hoyle-welcomes-roseburg-resident-as-her-guest-at-state-of-the-union"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 3:35 a.m. Late Thursday U.S. Representative Val Hoyle announced that Danielle Lisette Hubbard, a member of the Army National Guard and second-year nursing student at Umpqua Community College was her guest at the State of the Union address. Hubbard lives in Roseburg and was inspired to join the Army National Guard after...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE ARREST MAN IN FRAUD CASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116523</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/roseburg-police-arrest-man-in-fraud-case/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-arrest-man-in-fraud-case"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 3:15 a.m. Roseburg Police arrested a man Wednesday while following up on a fraud case. An RPD report said officers contacted 43-year-old Jason Tatiano at 12:30 p.m. while he was in the 1300 block of Southeast Stephens Street. Tatiano was allegedly photo-shopping credit cards and using stolen card numbers. Tatiano was reportedly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116521</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-driving-while-suspended/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-driving-while-suspended"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 3:05 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for driving while suspended on Wednesday night. An RPD report said just after 11:00 p.m. the 49-year-old was pulled over in the 500 block of Northeast Winchester Street, because his vehicle was not registered. The man’s license was suspended at the misdemeanor level. He was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REGISTRATION OPEN FOR AT-TIES TOGETHER CONFERENCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116518</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/08/registration-open-for-at-ties-together-conference-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=registration-open-for-at-ties-together-conference-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 8, 2024 2:50 a.m. Regional and Statewide Services for Students with Orthopedic Impairment and Oregon Technology Access Program are hosting the fifth annual AT-TIES conference, April 18th and 19th at the Salem Convention. Drew Winkelmaier has more “Drew” Q: News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN Information provided by the Douglas Education Service District...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>