<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-10-29T16:14:44.847Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Forestry launches Prescribed Fire Liability Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176370</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176370"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore.— The Oregon Department of Forestry is happy to announce the launch of the Prescribed Fire Liability Program. This pilot program is intended to increase use of prescribed fire and cultural burning and support fire practitioners by providing liability coverage for enrolled burns.
Introducing periodic fire to fire-adapted landscapes and reducing forest fuels has been shown to lessen the potential for high-intensity wildfires and the large volume of smoke they produce. 
While the rates of escape and loss are very low due to the careful planning and preparation required for prescribed fire and cultural burning, there is always some residual risk when working with fire. This risk, and the resulting liability for damages due to escape if uninsured, can deter some practitioners from using beneficial fire.
Governor Kotek signed House Bill 4016 in 2024 establishing the pilot Prescribed Fire Liability Program. It authorizes claims covering certain losses arising from escaped prescribed fires and cultural burns. Participation in the program is voluntary.
For your burn to have liability coverage under the program, all the following conditions must be met: 

The burn is enrolled in the program prior to burning.
The burn is conducted or supervised by an appropriate party for the burn.
Ensure the burn follows all applicable laws related to the burn (obtain and follow any required permits/burn plan, make required notifications for Certified Burn Manager-led burns, additional paperwork/ submissions for Power Driven Machinery, etc.).
If the burn escapes, the fire must not be a result of willful, malicious, or negligent actions in the origin or subsequent spread.

Learn more about the program and apply at ODF’s Prescribed Fire Liability Program web page. 
For more information on prescribed fire and correlating programs, visit ODF’s Prescribed Fire web page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEARLY 32 PERCENT OF BALLOTS RETURNED IN DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125383</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/nearly-32-percent-of-ballots-returned-in-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nearly-32-percent-of-ballots-returned-in-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 32 percent of local ballots have been returned for the 2024 Douglas County November Presidential General Election, as of Monday evening. County Clerk Daniel Loomis said 31.54 percent, or 18,842 ballots have been received. Loomis said that lags 14.94 percent behind the participation rate for the same point in the previous 2020 Douglas County...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY COMMISSIONERS TO HONOR VETERANS/FAMILIES WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125381</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/county-commissioners-to-honor-veterans-families-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-commissioners-to-honor-veterans-families-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T10:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 29, 2024 3:30 a.m.  Douglas County Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman and Tom Kress will hold their next public meeting Wednesday morning. A county release said it will take place at 9:00 a.m. in room 216 of the Douglas County Courthouse. While the agenda is rather short, the board will be honoring veterans and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG LIBRARY TO HOST “AMERICANS AND THE HOLOCAUST” EXHIBITION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125378</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/roseburg-library-to-host-americans-and-the-holocaust-exhibition/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-library-to-host-americans-and-the-holocaust-exhibition"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T10:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 29, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Roseburg Public Library will host the “Americans and the Holocaust: A Traveling Exhibition for Libraries” starting soon. A city release said it will be on display between Thursday, November 7th and Thursday December 19th. Th exhibition examines American’s responses to Nazism, war and genocide in Europe during the 1930s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HIGH HOLDING FINANCIAL AID/ADMISSIONS SESSIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125376</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/roseburg-high-holding-financial-aid-admissions-sessions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-high-holding-financial-aid-admissions-sessions"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T10:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 29, 2024 3:05 a.m. Roseburg High School is holding financial aid and admissions sessions during Parent Teacher Conferences. They will take place: *November 6th at 6:00 p.m. and 7:00 p.m. *November 7th at 11:00 a.m., 2:00 p.m. and 6:00 p.m. Families can get one-one-one assistance creating their FAFSA account with Umpqua Community College Director...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RCA TRACK PROJECT IS UNDERWAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125373</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/rca-track-project-is-underway/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rca-track-project-is-underway"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T10:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 29, 2024 2:50 a.m. Roseburg Christian Academy has its RCA Track Project underway. It recently kicked off with a fundraising dinner, dessert and musical event. Head Coordinator Joyce Ann Perham said it is going to be a challenge to raise the $250,000 needed to replace the decades old track and make other upgrades to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIRE AT MEDICAL OFFICE UNDER INVESTIGATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125369</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/fire-at-medical-office-under-investigation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fire-at-medical-office-under-investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 29, 2024 2:15 p.m. A fire at a medical office on Sunday remains under investigation. A Roseburg Fire Department report said at approximately 3:50 p.m. personnel responded to a report of a structure fire in the 1700 block of West Harvard Avenue. Fire Chief Tyler Christopherson said the reporting party indicated that the fire...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commercial Structure Fire - 1739 W. Harvard Avenue - 10-28-24 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news176358</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news176358"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update - 2:19 p.m., 10/28/24 - Corrected time of incident listed below
 
At 3:52 p.m. on October 27, 2024, Roseburg Fire Department personnel responded to a reported commercial structure fire at 1739 W. Harvard Avenue.  The reporting party stated the fire was spreading up the exterior wall of the building and into the roof area. 
Firefighters arrived on scene to find a single story, commercial structure with light smoke showing from the roof and flames visible from the backside of the structure. Firefighters extinguished the exterior portion of the fire and checked for possible fire extension inside the structure.  Several doors were forced and access holes made to gain entry and extinguish the small portion that had spread to the interior portion of the structure.
The commercial structure sustained structural, smoke, and water damage. Firefighters remained on scene to complete overhaul.  There were no reported injuries.  A fire investigator was on scene and the cause of the fire is under investigation.  Thirteen firefighters assisted with firefighting operations.  Other agencies assisting with the fire included Central Douglas Fire & Rescue, Umpqua Valley Ambulance, Roseburg Police Department, Avista Utilities, and Pacific Power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Fire Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.28.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125361</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/inside-douglas-county-10-28-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-28-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T20:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican candidate for state representative in district 4 talks about his campaign and what he hopes to focus on if he is elected to the Oregon State Legislature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October rain brings the end of a record-breaking fire season (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176344</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176344"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore.—After a record-breaking year, all Oregon Department of Forestry districts have terminated fire restrictions, marking the end of the 2024 Oregon fire season declaration. With over 1.9 million acres burned across the state, firefighters and resources experienced extreme strain.  
“This season proved that wildfire in Oregon is not just one agency’s issue but effects ALL Oregonians from government agencies to private landowners to Oregon residents.” Kyle Williams, ODF Deputy Director of Fire Protection, said, “This is our reality, and we need to adjust in response to it.” 
Throughout May and June, the state experienced an average, even below average, season. However, early July brought the beginning of peak season with a heat wave followed by several lightning and wind events that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL 2 PEOPLE, CITE 41 FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125359</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/roseburg-police-jail-2-people-cite-41-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-2-people-cite-41-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed 2 people and cited 41 for prohibited camping, between Friday morning and Sunday morning, with two of them going to jail. An RPD report said the biggest group – 27 people – were cited Friday at 12:00 p.m. in the 500 block of Northeast Stephens Street because...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK PAIR JAILED FOR PAST CASES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125355</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/myrtle-creek-pair-jailed-for-past-cases/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-pair-jailed-for-past-cases"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Two residents of Myrtle Creek were arrested by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office following a traffic stop on Sunday afternoon. A DCSO report said at 3:45 p.m. a 28-year-old woman was located while hiding in a minivan, which was driven by a 32-year-old man. The deputy knew that other deputies...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR BEING A FELON IN POSSESSION OF A FIREARM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125353</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-being-a-felon-in-possession-of-a-firearm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-being-a-felon-in-possession-of-a-firearm"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 10:10 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for being a felon in possession of a firearm on Sunday. An RPD report said at 6:50 p.m. officers saw the 22-year-old walking on the sidewalk in the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard and knew he was wanted by his probation officer. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING REPORTED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125351</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-trespass-incident-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-trespass-incident-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 9:50 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man following a reported trespass incident on Sunday. An RPD report said at 6:00 p.m. the 40-year-old was contacted at his camp which was located on private property near the intersection of Northeast Shambrook Avenue and Northeast Winchester Street. His camp had a substantial amount of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED PRIOR RESTRAINING ORDER VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125349</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-prior-restraining-order-violation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-prior-restraining-order-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man Sunday for a reported prior restraining order violation. An RPD report said at 2:00 p.m. officers contacted the 57-year-old at the courthouse in the 1000 block of Southeast Douglas Avenue who allegedly drove by the protected party on Friday, honked his vehicle horn and flipped...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT AT STORE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125347</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-at-store/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-at-store"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 9:30 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged theft incident at a store on Friday afternoon. An RPD report said at 1:40 p.m. officers contacted the 66-year-old at Sherm’s Thunderbird Market in the 2500 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. Loss prevention employees claimed the man had tried to leave the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125345</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-30/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-30"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged trespass incident on Sunday night. An RPD report said at 10:50 p.m. officers responded to property in the 2700 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway after security personnel said the 69-year-old was refusing to leave. Officers game the man numerous opportunities to exit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.28.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125342</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/morning-conversation-10-28-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-28-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiffany Roddy of the Douglas County Chapter of Oregon Women in Timber talks about employment  in the forest products sector, and related topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adaptive Management Program Committee meets Nov. 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176338</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176338"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T15:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Adaptive Management Program Committee will meet at noon on Monday, Nov. 4 in the Clatsop Room, Building C, at the Oregon Department of Forestry headquarters, located at 2600 State St. in Salem. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes:

Discuss amphibians research questions
Discuss effectiveness monitoring strategy (Substantial decision item)
Wrap up & discuss AMPC member renewals for 2025 and upcoming AMPC Co-chair election

The meeting is open to the public to attend in person and online via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted near the start of the meeting. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting at 503-945-7200 or by email at adaptivemanagementprogram@odf.oregon.gov.
The 13-member committee The Adaptive Management Program Committee helps determine if forest practices are meeting their goals to protect natural resources through a science-based and transparent process. The committee sets the research agenda that the Independent Research and Science Team (IRST) implements. View more information on the AMPC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trunk or treat: Sutherlin community comes together to celebrate Halloween]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b14c2376-92f8-11ef-b909-bf435cbdbf97</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/trunk-or-treat-sutherlin-community-comes-together-to-celebrate-halloween/article_b14c2376-92f8-11ef-b909-bf435cbdbf97.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Zuree Roark said she planned to trunk or treat Saturday as the Disney character Stitch, but moments before the family left the house, the dog peed on the costume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WASHINGTON MAN INJURED AFTER DODGING DEER ON MOTORCYCLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125336</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/washington-man-injured-after-dodging-deer-on-motorcycle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=washington-man-injured-after-dodging-deer-on-motorcycle"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T10:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 3:45 a.m. A Washington man was injured after dodging a deer while on his motorcycle Friday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 2:00 p.m. the 82-year-old from Mount Vernon was riding in the 7000 block of Driver Valley Road in the Oakland area when a deer jumped out...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNCIL TO CONDUCT CITY MANAGER EVALUATION MONDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125334</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/council-to-conduct-city-manager-evaluation-monday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=council-to-conduct-city-manager-evaluation-monday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T10:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Roseburg City Council will conduct an evaluation of City Manager Nikki Messenger at its meeting Monday night. That evaluation will be during an Executive Session, which is not open to the public. Public input regarding the city manager will be taken prior to the council adjourning into the Executive...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIRE SEASON ENDS ON ODF SOUTHWEST OREGON DISTRICT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125332</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/fire-season-ends-on-odf-southwest-oregon-district-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fire-season-ends-on-odf-southwest-oregon-district-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T10:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 3:20 a.m. After 148 days, the Oregon Department of Forestry Southwest Oregon District officially declared an end to the 2024 fire season in Jackson and Josephine counties, effective on Sunday morning. Public Information Officer Natalie Weber said consistent rain across the district and incoming rain throughout the upcoming week, along with new,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG’S NEEWOLLAH PARADE HAPPENING THURSDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125330</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/roseburgs-neewollah-parade-happening-thursday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburgs-neewollah-parade-happening-thursday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T10:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 3:05 a.m. Roseburg’s Neewollah parade is happening Thursday night. A city release said hundreds of costumed tricksters are expected to prowl the pavement in the downtown area. Captain Jack Sparrow will return with his Black Pearl pirate ship and dancing witches will share their broomsticks. Other Halloween themed groups are expected. Roseburg...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXTENSION WORKSHOP ABOUT HERBAL TEAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125328</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/28/extension-workshop-about-herbal-teas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=extension-workshop-about-herbal-teas"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T10:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Oregon State University Extension Service and Master Food Preservers will have a workshop about growing, preserving and blending teas. The event is coming up on December 7th from 10:00 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. at the Extension Officer on Southeast Douglas Avenue, next to the courthouse. Master Gardeners will show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoobilee brings children and animals together to trick or treat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e5e0dba0-92f7-11ef-9342-bf55b6e61c92</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/zoobilee-brings-children-and-animals-together-to-trick-or-treat/article_e5e0dba0-92f7-11ef-9342-bf55b6e61c92.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T22:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Penelope Marusa was dressed as Leonardo, the Ninja Turtle, on Friday as her family trooped to Wildlife Safari to trick or treat and see the animals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRANTS PASS MAN JAILED FOLLOWING POLICE CHASE IN STOLEN VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125326</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/27/grants-pass-man-jailed-following-police-chase-in-stolen-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=grants-pass-man-jailed-following-police-chase-in-stolen-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T17:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 11:00 a.m. A Grants Pass man was jailed following a police chase in a stolen vehicle on Saturday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 5:00 p.m. the stolen pickup was spotted in Roseburg driving on Lookingglass Road. 15 minutes later a Winston Police Officer saw the vehicle near Brockway...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG WOMAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT AT A BAR]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125324</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/27/roseburg-woman-jailed-for-alleged-harassment-at-a-bar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-woman-jailed-for-alleged-harassment-at-a-bar"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T17:22:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 10:20 a.m.  A Roseburg woman was jailed for alleged harassment at a bar on Saturday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 9:00 p.m. the 21-year-old was inside the business in the 4500 block of Old Highway 99 South in Green. The woman had been previously trespassed from the location....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TENMILE MAN JAILED, CHARGED WITH INTERFERING WITH A FIREFIGHTER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125322</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/27/tenmile-man-jailed-charged-with-interfering-with-a-firefighter/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tenmile-man-jailed-charged-with-interfering-with-a-firefighter"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T17:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 28, 2024 10:10 a.m.  A Tenmile man was jailed Saturday afternoon on the charge of interfering with a firefighter. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at approximately 1:40 p.m. the Tenmile Rural Fire Department was investigating an illegal burn at a home in the 100 block of Charlene Lane in the Tenmile area....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN DIES IN MOTORCYCLE ACCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125320</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/27/roseburg-man-dies-in-motorcycle-accident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-dies-in-motorcycle-accident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T16:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 27, 2024 10:00 a.m.  A Roseburg man died in a motorcycle accident on Friday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 3:40 p.m. a caller said they had found a motorcycle crashed in a field in the 12000 block of Elkhead Road in the Oakland area. The caller went to render...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volunteers make differences Saturday across Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/482f456e-92f6-11ef-809d-63e22aa147b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/volunteers-make-differences-saturday-across-douglas-county/article_482f456e-92f6-11ef-809d-63e22aa147b6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the Roseburg High School’s U-Dub Club — a club with Greater Douglas United Way — spent their Saturday morning at Fir Grove Elementary School taking walnuts from squirrels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maple Corner Montessori hosts International Children Day]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/08ea3434-92f8-11ef-9765-478a164cacc4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/maple-corner-montessori-hosts-international-children-day/article_08ea3434-92f8-11ef-9765-478a164cacc4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — Maple Corner Montessori was a busy hub Friday as students learned about different countries in-depth through hands-on activities and learning stations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEARLY 21 PERCENT OF DOUGLAS COUNTY BALLOTS RETURNED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125318</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/26/nearly-21-percent-of-douglas-county-ballots-returned/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nearly-21-percent-of-douglas-county-ballots-returned"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T13:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon 26th, 2024 7:00 a.m.   Nearly 21 percent of ballots for the 2024 Douglas County November Presidential General Election have been returned as of Friday evening. Douglas County Clerk Daniel Loomis said 20.99 percent, or 18,842 ballots have been received. Loomis said that lags 16.9 percent behind the participation rate for the same point in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Tree of heaven]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/65f17760-9004-11ef-9a3c-47f189c79bd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/ask-a-master-gardener-tree-of-heaven/article_65f17760-9004-11ef-9a3c-47f189c79bd2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I’ve noticed these tall trees growing along the bridge across from Stewart Park. They have interesting seed pods. Can you tell me what they are and more about them?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bonnie Courter Master Gardener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg library to host 'Americans and the Holocaust' exhibition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9d799f04-8e5c-11ef-8559-771343260289</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/roseburg-library-to-host-americans-and-the-holocaust-exhibition/article_9d799f04-8e5c-11ef-8559-771343260289.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans and the Holocaust traveling exhibition is coming soon to Roseburg Public Library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley for the News review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know Douglas ESD: National Disability Employment Awareness Month]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e369169a-8fd6-11ef-9ef6-d7d84c947043</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/get-to-know-douglas-esd-national-disability-employment-awareness-month/article_e369169a-8fd6-11ef-9ef6-d7d84c947043.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October is more than a beautiful fall month. It also marks the 79th National Disability Employment Awareness Month, a time to celebrate the valuable contributions of individuals experiencing disabilities in the workforce. On a state level, Oregon is leading the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HEATHER VILLA for News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>