<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.roseburgscanner.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2025-07-21T19:13:25.928Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.roseburgscanner.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.roseburgscanner.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN JAILED ON WARRANTS, CITED FOR METH POSSESSION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135790</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/myrtle-creek-man-jailed-on-warrants-cited-for-meth-possession/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-jailed-on-warrants-cited-for-meth-possession"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T18:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 11:00 a.m.    A Myrtle Creek man was jailed for warrants and cited for meth possession on Sunday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 4:00 p.m. the 45-year-old was contacted while he was walking on Ardis Street in front of the Meadowlark Apartments. The deputy knew the man had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EATING PEANUTS LEADS TO TWO-VEHICLE CRASH ON SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135788</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/eating-peanuts-leads-to-two-vehicle-crash-on-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=eating-peanuts-leads-to-two-vehicle-crash-on-sunday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T17:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 10:45 a.m. Roseburg Police responded to a two-vehicle crash on Sunday evening at 6:30 p.m. An RPD report said the accident took place at the intersection of Northeast Stewart Parkway and Northeast Airport Road. After speaking to both drivers, it was determined that a 42-year-old from Utah ran the red light eastbound...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE PERSON DECEASED, MAJOR CRIMES TEAM INVESTIGATION IS UNDERWAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135783</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/one-person-deceased-major-crimes-team-investigation-is-underway/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=one-person-deceased-major-crimes-team-investigation-is-underway"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T17:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 10:30 a.m.    One person is deceased, and a Douglas County Major Crimes Team investigation is underway following a shooting in Sutherlin late Sunday night. A Sutherlin Police report said at approximately 11:40 p.m. officers and medical personnel were dispatched after a caller said a person had been shot at a residence...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR THIRD-DEGREE THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135781</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-third-degree-theft-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-third-degree-theft-2"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T17:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 10:15 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for the charge of third-degree theft incident on Friday. An RPD report said at 1:20 p.m. officers contacted the 49-year-old after he allegedly stole three beers, valued at $8.67 from a store in the 1100 block of Northeast Stephens Street. The man admitted to stealing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT, BURGLARY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135779</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-burglary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-burglary"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T17:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant, burglary and theft charges on Saturday. An RPD report said just after 3:50 p.m. officers conducted a traffic stop on a sedan in the 700 block of Northeast Garden Valley Boulevard after witnessing traffic violations. The driver, 25-year-old Rad Osburn, was contacted....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER REPORTED ELUDE INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135777</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/roseburg-police-jail-man-after-reported-elude-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-after-reported-elude-incident"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T17:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 9:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man after a reported elude incident early Saturday. An RPD report said at 1:00 a.m. officers attempted to stop a sedan for several traffic violations near the intersection of Southeast Douglas Avenue and Southeast Jackson Street, and the driver eluded. Officers pursued the vehicle over the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDER HOSPITALIZED FOLLOWING MOTORCYCLE VERSUS SEDAN CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135775</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/rider-hospitalized-following-motorcycle-versus-sedan-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rider-hospitalized-following-motorcycle-versus-sedan-crash"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T16:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 9:20 a.m.  A rider was hospitalized following a motorcycle versus sedan crash on Saturday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 7:40 p.m. a 22-year-old was taking his classic 1964 vehicle for a test drive with three passengers inside in the 2100 block of Elgarose Road in the Melrose area....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 7.21.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135771</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/morning-conversation-7-21-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-7-21-25"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T16:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Actors Community Theatre opens the summer musical, “Anastasia” on Thursday night in Jacoby Auditorium of Umpqua Community College.  UACT Executive Director Melody Schwegel talks about the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025]]></title>
        <id>687dc275cbfd6b0001f9f609</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/july-21-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T13:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COOLER MONDAY, NEAR NORMAL HIGH TEMPERATURES STARTING TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135767</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/cooler-monday-near-normal-high-temperatures-starting-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cooler-monday-near-normal-high-temperatures-starting-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T10:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 3:50 a.m.  Monday will see clouds and cooler conditions with warming to near normal temperatures beginning Tuesday in the Umpqua Valley. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that low pressure off the coast of California will lead to the change in conditions....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW FENCING BEING INSTALLED AT HAPPY TRAILS DOG PARK STARTING MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135764</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/new-fencing-being-installed-at-happy-trails-dog-park-starting-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=new-fencing-being-installed-at-happy-trails-dog-park-starting-monday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T10:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 3:30 a.m. The reopening of the Happy Tails Dog Park is about two weeks away as work to install the new fencing begins on Monday. Information from the City of Roseburg said a contractor will work to replace 730 feet of fencing that was mangled at the park, which is a one-acre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON-DILLARD SCHOOLS CONTINUE SUMMER MEALS PROGRAM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135760</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/winston-dillard-schools-continue-summer-meals-program/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-dillard-schools-continue-summer-meals-program"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T10:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 3:20 a.m. The Winston-Dillard School District is continuing its summer meal distribution through August 14th. Nutritious summer meals offer children the choice of a hot or cold meal, including fruit, vegetables and milk. Meals are available as a grab-n-go breakfast and lunch and are for kids up to age 18. They can...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UACT SUMMER MUSIC OPENS ON THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135756</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/uact-summer-music-opens-on-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uact-summer-music-opens-on-thursday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T10:29:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 3:05 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Actors Community Theatre is presenting its summer musical, “Anastasia.” beginning on Thursday night in Jacoby Auditorium at Umpqua Community College. Based on the animated movie from 20th Century Fox, “Anastasia” is described as both a heartwarming and heart-wrenching dive into one of history’s biggest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOYS & GIRLS CLUB ANNOUNCES 18TH ANNUAL CELEBRATE KIDS 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135753</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/21/boys-girls-club-announces-18th-annual-celebrate-kids-2025/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=boys-girls-club-announces-18th-annual-celebrate-kids-2025"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T10:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 2:50 a.m. The Boys & Girls Club of the Umpqua Valley has announced the return of Celebrate Kids, its 18th annual dinner and auction. A release said the evening will spotlight the incredible youth who represent the future of the community. This year’s event will take place on Saturday, September 13th from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8942</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/8942-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T23:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ready for Exit? Sooner or later, business owners arrive at a defining point in their lives regarding when and how to exit their business. One question articulated by most owners is: “Am I Ready for This to Happen?” The answer, of course, is ‘either you are, or are not’. As an owner, you get to choose the answer…
The post  appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personalized, Efficient, and On-Brand: The Human Bean’s Journey into AI]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8939</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/personalized-efficient-and-on-brand-the-human-beans-journey-into-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Medford, OR, June 12, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) — While artificial intelligence (AI) is the buzzword dominating conversations in every industry, The Human Bean is turning talk into action—leveraging AI not just for efficiency, but to elevate the customer experience, support franchisee partners, and infuse brand personality into every touchpoint. For The Human Bean, AI isn’t…
The post Personalized, Efficient, and On-Brand: The Human Bean’s Journey into AI appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Human Bean Continues Partnership with St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital® on Annual Giveback Day]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8936</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/the-human-bean-continues-partnership-with-st-jude-childrens-research-hospital-on-annual-giveback-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Medford, OR, June 17, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) — On Friday, June 20, The Human Bean will host its second annual St. Jude Giveback Day. On this special day, one dollar from every drink sold at drive-thru locations nationwide will be donated directly to St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital®. These contributions will help fund groundbreaking research…
The post The Human Bean Continues Partnership with St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital® on Annual Giveback Day appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Building Affordable Rental Housing Works in Oregon]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8934</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/how-building-affordable-rental-housing-works-in-oregon/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Communities across Oregon need more affordable rental housing options. Rents continue to increase faster than wages, while the cost of everyday life—groceries, utilities, car repairs, and childcare—continues to rise. Many of our neighbors, including families, older adults on fixed incomes, and even people with steady jobs, struggle to find affordable places to live.  To avoid…
The post How Building Affordable Rental Housing Works in Oregon appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dave’s Nuttz, Now Shipping Nationwide on www.davesnuttz.com]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8931</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/daves-nuttz-now-shipping-nationwide-on-www-davesnuttz-com/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave’s Nuttz is crazy excited to launch our website and begin delivering directly to your door, nationwide! We are proud to be made in the USA and I feel honored to provide our little pieces of joy, one bite at a time, whenever someone is feelin’ a lil’ nuttz!” — Space Cake Dave EUGENE, OR,…
The post Dave’s Nuttz, Now Shipping Nationwide on www.davesnuttz.com appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kairos Unveils ‘Sonata’ Residential Treatment Home, Expanding Youth Mental Health Services in Southern Oregon]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8928</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/kairos-unveils-sonata-residential-treatment-home-expanding-youth-mental-health-services-in-southern-oregon/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kairos opens Sonata, a new youth mental health treatment home in Medford, with a grand opening July 10 and plans for a future tiny home pilot project. Sonata is more than a house—it’s a place of healing, transformation, and hope.” — Jeremy HarleGRANTS PASS, OR, UNITED STATES, June 30, 2025 /EINPresswire.com/ — Kairos is proud to announce…
The post Kairos Unveils ‘Sonata’ Residential Treatment Home, Expanding Youth Mental Health Services in Southern Oregon appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New e-bike rules begin at Oregon State Parks and the ocean shore]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8926</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/new-e-bike-rules-begin-at-oregon-state-parks-and-the-ocean-shore/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Oregon—Electric-assist bicycles (e-bikes) are now allowed on trails where other bicycles are allowed unless specifically prohibited at Oregon State Parks.  E-bikes are also allowed on the ocean shore on wet sand except where specifically restricted. Previously, e-bikes were only allowed on trails that were at least 8 feet wide. Signs will be posted on…
The post New e-bike rules begin at Oregon State Parks and the ocean shore appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Secretary of State Audit Highlights Need for Improved Procurement and Contracting Oversight]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8924</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/oregon-secretary-of-state-audit-highlights-need-for-improved-procurement-and-contracting-oversight/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oregon Secretary of State (SOS) has released an audit of the Oregon Department of Administrative Services (DAS) and its State Procurement Services (SPS). DAS SPS is the central procurement authority for most executive branch agencies and provides services across state and local government. The audit identified the need for DAS to dedicate resources to a comprehensive…
The post Oregon Secretary of State Audit Highlights Need for Improved Procurement and Contracting Oversight appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Chief Information Officer Announces Agreement with InnovateUS to Provide Training to State Employees on Responsible Use of Generative Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8922</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/state-chief-information-officer-announces-agreement-with-innovateus-to-provide-training-to-state-employees-on-responsible-use-of-generative-artificial-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Information Services (EIS) has partnered with InnovateUS to launch a series of courses to train state of Oregon employees on the responsible use of generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) as part of our commitment to building an informed and capable public service workforce. InnovateUS, a leading provider of no-cost training, has developed courses that are specific to…
The post State Chief Information Officer Announces Agreement with InnovateUS to Provide Training to State Employees on Responsible Use of Generative Artificial Intelligence appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farm season is rolling — are you ready to share the road?]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8920</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/farm-season-is-rolling-are-you-ready-to-share-the-road/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From July through September, Oregon’s rural roads and highways become busier with more than just regular traffic—they’re filled with tractors, combines, and other slow-moving farm equipment essential to the state’s agricultural economy. The Oregon Department of Transportation (ODOT), Oregon Department of Agriculture (ODA), and Oregon Farm Bureau are teaming up to remind drivers: stay alert, slow…
The post Farm season is rolling — are you ready to share the road? appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TriAgenics Closes $3 Million Series B-1 Financing to support regulatory process for third molar prevention technology]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8918</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/triagenics-closes-3-million-series-b-1-financing-to-support-regulatory-process-for-third-molar-prevention-technology/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REDMOND, OR, UNITED STATES, July 16, 2025 /EINPresswire.com/ — TriAgenics, Inc., a privately held medical device company pioneering a non-surgical approach to third molar (wisdom tooth) prevention, today announced the closing of a $3 million Series B-1 financing round. The round was approved by shareholders and completed in partnership with Asclepius Ventures, a private investment firm focused…
The post TriAgenics Closes $3 Million Series B-1 Financing to support regulatory process for third molar prevention technology appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donations After Disaster: Why Monetary Donations Are Best]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8916</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/donations-after-disaster-why-monetary-donations-are-best/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T22:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEWS PROVIDED BY Oregon Department of Environmental Quality July 17, 2025, 16:20 GMT In the aftermath of a disaster, Oregonians often ask, “How can I help?” While offers of donated goods like clothing, food, and household items are heartfelt, they can create serious logistical challenges for emergency responders and community organizations already stretched thin. Unless…
The post Donations After Disaster: Why Monetary Donations Are Best appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kids Safety Day is returning on July 26, from 10 a.m. to 1 p.m., at Sherm's Thunderbird in Roseburg!]]></title>
        <id>687bd6f2cbfd6b0001f9f5e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/kids-safety-day-is-returning-on-july-26-from-10-a-m-to-1-p-m-at-sherms-thunderbird-in-roseburg/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T17:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kids Safety Day returns July 26, 10 a.m.–1 p.m. at Sherm’s Thunderbird in Roseburg. Enjoy a free family event with BBQ, prizes, and interactive safety activities hosted by local fire, police, and health organizations. Presented by CHI Mercy Health and Sherm’s Thunderbird.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE MAN JAILED ON OFFENSIVE LITTERING CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135751</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/19/canyonville-man-jailed-on-offensive-littering-charge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=canyonville-man-jailed-on-offensive-littering-charge"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 19, 2025 10:00 a.m. A Canyonville man was jailed on the charge of offensive littering Friday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 2:30 p.m. witnesses said a 63-year-old was putting items onto the sidewalk in the 100 block of Southwest Fifth Street in Canyonville. A video showing the suspect pushing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN JAILED FOLLOWING ALLEGED ELUDE, RECKLESS DRIVING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135749</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/19/myrtle-creek-man-jailed-following-alleged-elude-reckless-driving/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-jailed-following-alleged-elude-reckless-driving"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T16:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 9:30 a.m. A Myrtle Creek man was jailed following an alleged elude and reckless driving incident on Friday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 6:30 p.m. a deputy was called to a restaurant in the 100 block of Thompson Avenue in Winston after an employee said a man had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOME AND MULTIPLE VEHICLES A TOTAL LOSS IN WINSTON FIRE FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135744</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/19/home-and-multiple-vehicles-a-total-loss-in-winston-fire-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=home-and-multiple-vehicles-a-total-loss-in-winston-fire-friday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T13:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21, 2025 6:40 a.m. A home and multiple vehicles are a total loss following a fire in Winston early Friday morning. Battalion Chief Mitch Doss of Central Douglas Fire & Rescue said just after 4:50 a.m. crews responded to the report of a fully engulfed home on Southeast Theodore Street. Doss said initial reports...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODOT Launches $17 M Improvement Project on Oregon 42 Between Lookingglass Creek and I‑5]]></title>
        <id>687b2d33cbfd6b0001f9f5bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/odot-launches-17-m-improvement-project-on-oregon-42-between-lookingglass-creek-and-i-5/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T05:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Winston, OR – The Oregon Department of Transportation (ODOT) has begun a two‑year construction project to upgrade a five‑mile stretch of Oregon 42 from Lookingglass Creek through the Green District in Winston to the Interstate 5 interchange. The $17,058,426 project, awarded to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARRESTS MADE IN CHILD EXPLOITATION AND ANIMAL ABUSE INVESTIGATION]]></title>
        <id>687b2bcccbfd6b0001f9f5ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/arrests-made-in-child-exploitation-and-animal-abuse-investigation/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-19T05:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Sheriff’s detectives arrested Daniel Roy Phelps and Terah Danyle Crawford in a child exploitation and animal abuse probe. Warrants uncovered explicit materials involving two minors and a bestiality video. Charges include sodomy, sexual abuse, and related offenses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARRESTS MADE IN CHILD SEX CRIMES AND ANIMAL SEXUAL ABUSE CASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135740</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/arrests-made-in-child-sex-crimes-and-animal-sexual-abuse-case/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=arrests-made-in-child-sex-crimes-and-animal-sexual-abuse-case"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T23:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 4:00 p.m.   The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office has made two arrests in a child sex crimes and animal sexual abuse case. Undersheriff Brad O’Dell said in late June, detectives began a criminal investigation involving child exploitative material. O’Dell said during the investigation, detectives identified the 5-year-old victim depicted in photographs and videos...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Youth and dogs shine at Douglas County Pre-Fair Dog Showmanship Contest]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/384639b5-9441-42f0-a057-3c72c53bca05</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/youth-and-dogs-shine-at-douglas-county-pre-fair-dog-showmanship-contest/article_384639b5-9441-42f0-a057-3c72c53bca05.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T20:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fur was ﬂying on a hot July day at the Douglas County Fairgrounds as 4-H members from across the county showcased their skills and hard work during the annual pre-fair dog showmanship contest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelly Simonson For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 7.18.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135734</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/inside-douglas-county-7-18-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-7-18-25"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T20:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A two-segment program with Kasey Hovick of Umpqua Watersheds talking about Saturday’s River Appreciation Day and Smash the Trash River Cleanup, the Terry Brock joins us live from Central Park in Sutherlin to talk about the Sutherlin Throwdown event happening this weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135732</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-warrant-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-warrant-2"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T18:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 11:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for a warrant on Thursday night. An RPD report said just at approximately 11:50 p.m. officers contacted the 63-year-old in the 400 block of Northeast Winchester Street and learned he had a cite and released warrant out of RPD. He was cited and released on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE ONE DRIVER FOLLOWING TWO-VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135730</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/roseburg-police-cite-one-driver-following-two-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-one-driver-following-two-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T17:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18,  2025 10:45 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited one driver following a two-vehicle crash on Thursday. An RPD report said at 9:55 a.m. officers contacted two drivers after a wreck at the intersection of Southeast Washington Avenue and Southeast Stephens Street. A 22-year-old said he was turning right onto Southeast Washington and Southeast Stephens, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135728</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-trespass-incident-15/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-trespass-incident-15"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T17:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 10:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a reported trespass incident on Thursday. An RPD report said at 4:15 p.m. the 45-year-old was contacted at a business in the 200 block of Northeast Garden Valley Boulevard after he was advised of trespass early in the day by an RPD officer and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR SEVERAL WARRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135725</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-several-warrants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-several-warrants"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T17:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for several warrants on Thursday. AN RPD report said 5:50 p.m. officers stopped a vehicle for not having a front license plate and the driver allegedly provided identification that did not belong to her. The stop took place in the 1100 block of Northeast Stephens...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135721</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-thursday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T17:16:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 10:15 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report said a few minutes after 12:00 p.m. officers contacted the 25-year-old during a traffic stop in the 200 block of Southeast Stephens Street. Officers learned the man had a warrant for his arrest out of Clackamas...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED THEFTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135719</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-thefts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-thefts"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T17:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for reported thefts on Thursday. An RPD report said the 44-year-old allegedly stole items from a business in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street, valued at $54. At the time he was contacted, the man was also in possession of a shopping cart valued...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED MENACING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135717</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/sutherlin-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-menacing-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-menacing-incident"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 9:40 a.m. Sutherin Police jailed a woman Thursday night for an alleged prior menacing incident. An SPD report said a victim had confronted the 39-year-old about cleaning up her property which she left in her driveway in the 500 block of South State Street. The woman allegedly decided to stab the victim’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DRUG LAW VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135715</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-drug-law-violation-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-drug-law-violation-2"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 9:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for a drug law violation on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 8:20 pm. officers were communicating with the 53-year-old from Dillard, when he allegedly agreed to sell them drugs. The man agreed to meet officers in the parking lot of a business in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rural artists to gain visibility through Tiller Art Fair]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a31d4669-573b-4823-ac96-5f2e41c6bfc6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/rural-artists-to-gain-visibility-through-tiller-art-fair/article_a31d4669-573b-4823-ac96-5f2e41c6bfc6.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER — "Exposure" and "visibility" probably aren't the first words that come to mind when looking at the community of Tiller, a small community nestled in the woodsy hills of Southern Douglas County. This Saturday, all of that changes for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look back at Wildlife Safari's DreamNight]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1e33b1db-629a-4b66-95fc-85ff5c95a111</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/a-look-back-at-wildlife-safaris-dreamnight/article_1e33b1db-629a-4b66-95fc-85ff5c95a111.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Each year, Wildlife Safari’s DreamNight gives local children with chronic or terminal illnesses their own free night at the safari.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Reynolds The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 7.18.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135712</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/local-real-estate-today-7-18-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-7-18-25"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeannie Haacke from the Mary Gilbert Group of Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our weekly local at real estate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fascinating world of bonsai]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4a2f0d33-f33e-44db-8ef6-226521478a14</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/life/the-fascinating-world-of-bonsai/article_4a2f0d33-f33e-44db-8ef6-226521478a14.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: Bonsai trees have always fascinated me, however, they also look very intimidating to grow. Do you have any tips on how to properly choose and care for these unique little trees?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mackenzi Hall Master Gardner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 7.18.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135706</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/morning-conversation-7-18-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-7-18-25"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Conor Davenport is one of the new family medicine residents at Aviva Health.  He talks about his background and what is ahead for him at Aviva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s up with Douglas County Parks?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a91665f0-5973-4344-b36a-e926b457005f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/what-s-up-with-douglas-county-parks/article_a91665f0-5973-4344-b36a-e926b457005f.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas County Parks Department champions a story of success — one that leadership falls back on when speaking and their Public Information Officers (PIOs) infuse into marketing materials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Dapp The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K9s in the Grapevines returns in September]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a5196820-84cb-4282-9366-75b9b19a50af</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/k9s-in-the-grapevines-returns-in-september/article_a5196820-84cb-4282-9366-75b9b19a50af.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MELROSE — Friends of Umpqua Valley Police K9 Programs will host K9s in the Grapevines on Sept. 5 and tickets are now available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025]]></title>
        <id>687a4ef4cbfd6b0001f9f44d</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/july-18-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T14:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yoncalla Public Library builds birdhouses, prepares to wrap up summer reading program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b02ba0a6-fd73-49d7-b42a-af08ede38810</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/yoncalla-public-library-builds-birdhouses-prepares-to-wrap-up-summer-reading-program/article_b02ba0a6-fd73-49d7-b42a-af08ede38810.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YONCALLA — Caroline Luke has read enough books so far this summer to fill four reading logs for the summer reading program at Yoncalla Public Library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLM reopens Lone Pine Group Campground]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e7594318-fafa-40fd-b46e-bf54638e73c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/blm-reopens-lone-pine-group-campground/article_e7594318-fafa-40fd-b46e-bf54638e73c6.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — The Bureau of Lane Management Roseburg District will reopen the Long Pine Group Campground in Glide on July 25 for individual site rental for the summer and fall season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE MORE DAY OF ABOVE NORMAL TEMPERATURES FOR FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135701</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/one-more-day-of-above-normal-temperatures-for-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=one-more-day-of-above-normal-temperatures-for-friday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T11:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 4:15 a.m. One more day of above normal temperatures is expected for Friday in the Umpqua Valley, before cooler conditions impact the region. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that highs in the low 90s are forecast. 86 degrees is the normal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COMMISSIONERS ISSUE PROCLAMATION FOR PARKS AND RECREATION MONTH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135697</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/commissioners-issue-proclamation-for-parks-and-recreation-month/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=commissioners-issue-proclamation-for-parks-and-recreation-month"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T11:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 4:00 a.m. Douglas County Commissioners Tim Freeman, Tom Kress, and Chris Boice issued a proclamation at their weekly business meeting on Wednesday, calling upon citizens to observe July as Parks and Recreation Appreciation Month. A county release said the proclamation was presented by Commissioner Boice and acknowledged that, “We recognize that Douglas...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLM TO REOPEN LONE PINE GROUP CAMPGROUND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135695</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/blm-to-reopen-lone-pine-group-campground/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=blm-to-reopen-lone-pine-group-campground"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T10:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 3:55 a.m.  The Bureau of Land Management Roseburg District will reopen Lone Pine Group Campground on July 25th. A BLM release said it is located approximately 10 miles from Glide and will be open for individual site rentals for the summer and fall 2025 season. Lone Pine Group Campground is adjacent to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTH UMPQUA FALLS CAMPGROUND SHORT-TERM CLOSURE THROUGH MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135690</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/south-umpqua-falls-campground-short-term-closure-through-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=south-umpqua-falls-campground-short-term-closure-through-monday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T10:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 3:50 a.m. The Umpqua National Forest has temporarily closed South Umpqua Falls Campground on the Tiller Ranger District through Monday. A UNF release said the closure is to accommodate the annual Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Tribe of Indians 2025 Pow Wow. South Umpqua Falls Campground will reopen to first-come, first-serve visitors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIVERBEND LIVE! WITH COWBOY POETRY AND WESTERN MUSIC FRIDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135688</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/riverbend-live-with-cowboy-poetry-and-western-music-friday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riverbend-live-with-cowboy-poetry-and-western-music-friday-night"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T10:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 3:45 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Riverbend Live! has its annual evening of cowboy poetry and western music on Friday night at 7:00 p.m. at Winston’s Riverbend Park. The evening will feature singer/songwriter Brenn Hill and cowboy poet and humorist Andy Nelson. Both are well known with lengthy careers and have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN THROWDOWN SATURDAY AND SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135686</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/sutherlin-throwdown-saturday-and-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-throwdown-saturday-and-sunday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T10:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 3:40 a.m. Sutherlin Throwdown is happening Saturday and Sunday. Events include a barbecue competition, Brewfest, cornhole competition, live music and more. It will be held at Central Park in downtown Sutherlin, starting at 10:00 a.m. each day. Barbecue sampling and the beer and wine festival will take place from 10:00 a.m. to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER ART FAIR HAPPENING ON SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=135683</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/07/18/tiller-art-fair-happening-on-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tiller-art-fair-happening-on-saturday"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T10:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 18, 2025 3:30 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Tiller Art Fair is taking place on Saturday from 11:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m. in downtown Tiller. Held at the South Umpqua Church, the event includes live music with food available for purchase. A number of artists will have their work on display and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hear ye, hear ye: Umpqua Community College to host Renaissance Faire]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3a961727-8f51-431b-8164-8213b24cf87f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/hear-ye-hear-ye-umpqua-community-college-to-host-renaissance-faire/article_3a961727-8f51-431b-8164-8213b24cf87f.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Break out the chainmail and sharpen the swords; On Saturday, Umpqua Community College (UCC) is inviting people to step back into the past and immerse themselves in the world as it was centuries ago with the school’s very first Renaissance…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg, beautified: Experience Roseburg wraps up mural works final pieces are completed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2ce5a517-b293-4b34-9e04-20e332382cfd</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/roseburg-beautified-experience-roseburg-wraps-up-mural-works-final-pieces-are-completed/article_2ce5a517-b293-4b34-9e04-20e332382cfd.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For nearly three years, artists from near and far have beautified downtown Roseburg with a series of murals for the Experience Roseburg Mural Project, all varying in size, style and subject.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drift smoke currently affecting Douglas District]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cd37d7b5-077e-4897-b221-111294de09d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/drift-smoke-currently-affecting-douglas-district/article_cd37d7b5-077e-4897-b221-111294de09d6.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T14:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — With a wind-shift, drift smoke has moved over the Douglas District.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Umpqua Falls Campground closed for weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9fde57b4-90c4-41dc-8ec1-a79037cb6a21</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/south-umpqua-falls-campground-closed-for-weekend/article_9fde57b4-90c4-41dc-8ec1-a79037cb6a21.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T14:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER — South Umpqua Falls Campground, located in the Tiller Ranger District, will be closed Friday-Monday for the annual Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Tribe of Indians 2025 Pow Wow, a press release from Umpqua National Forest said. The closure…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Reynolds The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Float the river and clean up for River Appreciation Day]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9be795c2-70d7-436f-b894-504b8c95d18c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/float-the-river-and-clean-up-for-river-appreciation-day/article_9be795c2-70d7-436f-b894-504b8c95d18c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Watersheds has been inviting the community to celebrate River Appreciation Day for almost 40 years now and this year is no different.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trade showcase, barbecue, brews and cornhole arrives in Sutherlin this weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/282397c5-9127-4860-bce6-29c031a011e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/trade-showcase-barbecue-brews-and-cornhole-arrives-in-sutherlin-this-weekend/article_282397c5-9127-4860-bce6-29c031a011e1.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Vanessa Slater graduated in June from Sutherlin High School and is well on her way to attend college in a financially responsible way — applying for as many scholarships as she can.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>