<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-09-07T13:13:33.447Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level 3 - GO NOW! Wildfire Evacuation Notices Issued for Devils Knob Fire, Tiller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175079</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175079"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T03:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER, Ore. - This is a wildfire emergency alert from the Douglas County Sheriff's Office. This is an UPGRADE from a Level 1 to a Level 3 – GO NOW! for the following areas: East side of Tiller Trail Hwy 34000 to 36760 block. Also, Tison Road, Diamond Elk Road, Joe Hall area.

Level 3 – GO NOW means leave without delay, it is unsafe to stay and threatens the safety of you, your family, and emergency responders.
Emergency services personnel may not be available to help you if you choose to stay.
• Do not stop to gather your belongings or protect your home. Follow your emergency plan.
• Leave as fast as safely possible. Drive carefully. Turn on your headlights. Follow traffic safety warnings and instructions from local authorities.
 
Use TripCheck.com (Road & Weather Conditions Map | TripCheck - Oregon Traveler Information) or call 511 for road closure information.
After you evacuate:
• Do not return to the area until public safety officials announce the area is safe. • Continue to check for updates through local city and county websites, social media, TV, and radio.
• An interactive wildfire evacuation map can be located at: www.dcso.com/evacuations
• Once you are safe, check with friends and family.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Committee for Family Forestlands meets on Sept. 12]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175076</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175076"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T22:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Committee for Family Forestlands will meet virtually on Thursday, Sept. 12 from 9 a.m. to 2 p.m. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda. 
The committee’s agenda includes:

Forest Resources Division update
Discuss vacant industry representative position
Small Forestland Investment in Stream Habitat Program (SFISH) one-pager
Protection Division update
Protection messaging and prevention
Board of Forestry update
Discuss upcoming meeting schedule and agenda topics

The meeting is open to the public to attend online via Zoom. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 24 hours before the meeting by emailing committee.of.family.forestlands@odf.oregon.gov.
The 13-member committee researches policies that affect family forests, natural resources and forestry benefits. Based on its findings, the committee recommends actions to the Oregon Board of Forestry and the State Forester. View more information on the CFF webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 9.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123423</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/inside-douglas-county-9-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-9-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T20:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Back to School series continues with Superintendent Erika Bare of the South Umpqua School District.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South County fire updates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0d5156ba-6c7e-11ef-93ab-7bc0727cec5c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/south-county-fire-updates/article_0d5156ba-6c7e-11ef-93ab-7bc0727cec5c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decreased temperatures limited fire activity and spread of the Devils Knob fire in Tiller.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEVILS KNOB FIRE/MILEPOST 98 FIRE UPDATES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123421</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/devils-knob-fire-milepost-98-fire-updates/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=devils-knob-fire-milepost-98-fire-updates"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T18:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 11:20 a.m.  Decreased temperatures throughout the night limited fire activity and spread on the Devils Knob Fire, burning in the Tiller area. Douglas Forest Protective Association Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said the fire is estimated between 1,200 and 1,500 acres as of midday Friday. Pope said crews continue to engage in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EAST HALF OF HOMESTEAD COMPLEX FIRES VERY ACTIVE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123418</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/east-half-of-homestead-complex-fires-very-active/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=east-half-of-homestead-complex-fires-very-active"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T18:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 11:00 a.m. The fires on the east half of the Homestead Complex were very active on Thursday and are expected to remain active An Umpqua National Forest update said firefighters began tactical burnout operations on the Horse Heaven Creek Fire Thursday. As the firing progressed, some spot fires crossed over the 3831...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGON STATE POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER DEER SHOT FROM ROADWAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123416</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/oregon-state-police-jail-man-after-deer-shot-from-roadway/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregon-state-police-jail-man-after-deer-shot-from-roadway"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T17:48:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 10:40 a.m.  Oregon State Police jailed a man for a wildlife incident on Thursday night. An OSP report said just before 10:30 p.m. a trooper responded to the 100 block of West Sixth Avenue in Sutherlin after a caller said a buck deer had been shot from the roadway. Sutherlin Police Department...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEVEL 1 BE READY WILDFIRE EVACUATION NOTICE ISSUED FOR DEVILS KNOB FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123414</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/level-1-be-ready-wildfire-evacuation-notice-issued-for-devils-knob-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=level-1-be-ready-wildfire-evacuation-notice-issued-for-devils-knob-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T17:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 10:30 a.m. The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office issued a Level 1 Be Ready evacuation notice for the Devils Knob Fire at 10:00 a.m. Friday. It is for the east side of Tiller Trail Highway between the 3400 and 36760 block. It also applies to Tison Road, Diamond Elk Road, and the Joe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR LITTER/CAMPING CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123412</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-litter-camping-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-litter-camping-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T17:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for litter and camping charges on Thursday. An RPD report said at 1:40 p.m. a 50-year-old man was found with a large 10-foot by 10-foot pile of trash and debris next to the east entrance of the Roseburg Police Library on Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level 1-BE READY Wildfire Evacuation Notices Issued for Devils Knob Fire, Tiller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175050</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175050"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T17:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER, Ore. - This is a wildfire emergency alert from Douglas County Sheriff's Office. Level 1 BE READY to evacuate from the following areas: East side of Tiller Trail Hwy 3400 to 36760 block. Also Tison Road, Diamond Elk Road, Joe Hall area.
 Level 1 - BE READY to evacuate means:
Be aware of danger in your area and stay informed. Check local city and county websites, social media, TV, and radio for updates. View wildfire information map at www.dcso.com/evacuations

Make plans and prepare to evacuate. Gather necessary supplies for health, safety, and identification.
Act early if you are older, have children, disabilities, or limited access to transportation. Consider moving pets and livestock early.
Plan possible evacuation routes. Use TripCheck.com or call 511 for road closure information.
 
If you can do so safely, check with your neighbors and share information. Ask for help if you need it. Offer help if you can give it.

This may be the only notice you receive. Don’t wait to evacuate if you feel unsafe. If conditions change, you may receive a Level 2 - BE SET or Level 3 - GO NOW evacuation notice. You do not need to wait for another evacuation notice. Make the best decision for your safety.
An interactive wildfire evacuation map can be located at: www.dcso.com/evacuations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE TWO IN SHOPPING CART INCIDENTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123410</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/roseburg-police-cite-two-in-shopping-cart-incidents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-two-in-shopping-cart-incidents"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police cited two people in separate shopping cart incidents on Thursday. An RPD report said at 3:00 p.m. a 70-year-old man was contacted in the 1400 block of West Harvard Avenue, with a shopping cart belonging to Big Lots. The man had been warned multiple times that he was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123408</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-22/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-22"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:47:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for alleged disorderly conduct on Thursday. An RPD report said just after 1:30 p.m. officers contacted the 41-year-old after a caller said he was screaming and nude near a business in the 1200 block of West Harvard Avenue. The man had been reported three times...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL FUGITIVE THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123406</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-thursday-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-thursday-2"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a fugitive on Thursday. An RPD report said at 7:40 a.m. officers contacted the 69-year-old in the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard for urinating in public. He was found to have a serviceable warrant out of Salem Municipal Court. The man was taken into custody...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 9.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123403</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/local-real-estate-today-9-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-9-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group powered by Place at Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our weekly look at local real estate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 9.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123399</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/morning-conversation-9-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-9-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Garrison Knowles is being promoted to the position of Club Golf Pro at the Roseburg Country Club.  He talks about his role at the club and his love for golf.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildfire Evacuation Notices Issued]]></title>
        <id>http://WWW.DCSO.COM/EVACUATIONS/638612175410000000</id>
        <link href="http://www.dcso.com/EVACUATIONS"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current interactive wildfire evacuation map for Douglas County, OR]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas County Sheriff, OR - Alert Center</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife benefits from unique state agency partnership to enhance critical habitat (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175046</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175046"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veneta, Ore.-- Purple martins, bats, bees and other common and uncommon wildlife are seeing benefits of a high-elevation meadow in the Oregon Coast Range established by a joint effort between the Oregon Department of Foresty (ODF) and the Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife (ODFW).
The four-acre Walker Meadows site is located about 13 miles west of Veneta and is at an elevation of 2,300 feet. 
“It’s at the top of Walker Point where there are three communication towers and an ODF smoke detection camera,” said Randy Smith, ODF Wildlife Biologist.  “The 2020 wildfires prompted discussion for options to remove timber to reduce fire risk and also limit damage to infrastructure from falling trees from the 84-yar old timber stand on the point.”
The local district office and area biologists cam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Army Corps of Engineers listening session]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ebeb7766-6c65-11ef-b675-9b2eb02126f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/army-corps-of-engineers-listening-session/article_ebeb7766-6c65-11ef-b675-9b2eb02126f9.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Portland District – Regulatory Branch, is hosting two listening session Sept. 23 at the Roseburg Public Library.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DTO hosts breakfast meeting]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ac168a90-6c65-11ef-a0c8-d7e6c12eea41</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/dto-hosts-breakfast-meeting/article_ac168a90-6c65-11ef-a0c8-d7e6c12eea41.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Douglas Timber Operators will have their monthly meeting for September at a different location.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DINT finds 5 illegal grow sites, more than 240,000 marijuana plants]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/beafd8d0-6c5d-11ef-8420-37ec5ccafcea</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/dint-finds-5-illegal-grow-sites-more-than-240-000-marijuana-plants/article_beafd8d0-6c5d-11ef-8420-37ec5ccafcea.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Detectives with the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team executed five search warrants in recent weeks, leading to the seizure of over 240,000 marijuana plants from illegal production sites in Douglas County and eight arrests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two new wildfires start in south Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/11a64e30-6bfe-11ef-bcb4-273149e31249</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/two-new-wildfires-start-in-south-douglas-county/article_11a64e30-6bfe-11ef-bcb4-273149e31249.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A vehicle crash resulted in a wildfire around 5:15 p.m. Thursday in the southbound lanes of Interestate 5 around milepost 98 in Canyonville.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DINT FINDS 5 ILLEGAL GROW SITES, OVER 240,000 MARIJUANA PLANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123387</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/dint-finds-5-illegal-grow-sites-over-240000-marijuana-plants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dint-finds-5-illegal-grow-sites-over-240000-marijuana-plants"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T13:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 6:50 a.m. Detectives with the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team executed 5 search warrants in recent weeks, leading to the seizure of over 240,000 marijuana plants from massive illegal production sites in Douglas County and 8 arrests. DINT Commander Lieutenant Rick McArthur said on August 15th detectives went to a property in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG SETS RECORD HIGH TEMPERATURE THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123382</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/roseburg-sets-record-high-temperature-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-sets-record-high-temperature-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T11:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 4:10 a.m. Roseburg set a record high temperature for the date on Thursday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the mercury reached 105 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport. The previous record high for September 5th was 104 degrees, set 80 years ago...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEAT ADVISORY EXTENDED THROUGH FRIDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123379</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/heat-advisory-extended-through-friday-night-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=heat-advisory-extended-through-friday-night-2"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 4:00 a.m. The National Weather Service has extended a Heat Advisory through 10:00 p.m. Friday for much of southern Oregon. Forecasters said afternoon high temperatures between 100 and 105 degrees are expected. The Advisory area includes central Douglas, Josephine, Jackson and eastern Curry counties. Forecasters said hot temperatures and high humidity may...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA/UNF DEAL WITH FIRES IN DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123372</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/dfpa-unf-deal-with-fires-in-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-unf-deal-with-fires-in-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 3:50 a.m.  Crews with the Douglas Forest Protective Association, the Umpqua National Forest and other agencies are dealing with two fires in Douglas County. At about 2:10 p.m. Thursday, firefighters from several agencies responded to a fire located near Devils Knob Road and north of Joe Hall Creek in the Tiller area....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCAMMERS PREYING ON COMMUNITY MEMBERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123370</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/scammers-preying-on-community-members/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=scammers-preying-on-community-members"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 3:30 a.m. Scammers are posing as officials from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office in an effort to scam community members out of money. A DCSO release said deputies have once again begun receiving reports from people contacted by phone by individuals posing as DCSO employees. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell said the scammer will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARMY CORPS OF ENGINEERS LISTENING SESSIONS COMING TO ROSEBURG LIBRARY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123368</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/army-corps-of-engineers-listening-sessions-coming-to-roseburg-library/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=army-corps-of-engineers-listening-sessions-coming-to-roseburg-library"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Douglas County Board of Commissioners are inviting residents to attend two Listening Sessions hosted by the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Portland District – Regulatory Branch, on Monday September 23rd. A county release said these sessions provide a platform for the community to engage directly with the Corps regarding...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDE THE RIM AT CRATER LAKE NEXT TWO SATURDAYS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123366</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/ride-the-rim-at-crater-lake-next-two-saturdays/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ride-the-rim-at-crater-lake-next-two-saturdays"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 3:05 a.m. Crater Lake National Park, in partnership with the Friends of Crater Lake and Discover Klamath, will host the tenth annual Ride the Rim days on September 7th and September 14th. A National Park Service release said on these two consecutive Saturdays, East Rim Drive from North Junction to Park Headquarters...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS TIMBER OPERATORS HAVING MEETING SEPTEMBER 26TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123364</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/06/douglas-timber-operators-having-meeting-september-26th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-timber-operators-having-meeting-september-26th"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 6, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Douglas Timber Operators will have their monthly meeting for September at a different location. DTO’s event will be held on Thursday. September 26th at 8:00 a.m. in the Cascade Hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds. The guest speaker will be Roseburg Resources President Scott Folk. His presentation is titled,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fire Near Milepost 98 Results in Evacuation Notices (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175043</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175043"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T02:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wildfire has started near Milepost 98 on Interstate 5, which has resulted in the following evacuation notices. 
LEVEL 3 - GO NOW! Evacuate immediately is in effect for the following areas:
* All homes in the 100-7000 block of Ritchie Road, Canyonville.
Level 3 - GO NOW means Leave Immediately!
There is extreme danger in your area - evacuate now. Leave without delay, it is unsafe to stay and threatens the safety of you, your family, and emergency responders. Your life could be in great danger. Emergency services personnel may not be available to help you if you choose to stay.
• Do not stop to gather your belongings or protect your home. Follow your emergency plan.
• Leave as fast as safely possible. Drive carefully. Turn on your headlights. Follow traffic safety warnings and instructions from local authorities.
• Use TripCheck.com or call 511 for road closure information.
****
LEVEL 2 - BE SET to evacuate from the following areas:
* All homes in the 100-950 block of Canyon Creek Road, Canyonville
Level 2 - BE SET to evacuate means:
• There is significant danger in your area - be ready to leave at a moment’s notice.
• Time to act - follow your emergency plan. Grab your go-kit of essential supplies for health, safety, and identification.
 
An interactive evacuation map can be found at ww.dcso.com/evacuations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marijuana Cases (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6255#news175021</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6255#news175021"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T23:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past two weeks the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT) has executed search warrants at several massive illegal marijuana production sites in Douglas County.  As stated in previous reports, it's important to explain there are legal ways to produce and consume marijuana in Oregon.  However, in recent years Oregon has been overrun with massive illegal grow sites that have been devastating to our local environment and water supply.  Many of these sites are operated and staffed by foreign organized crime organizations.  
 
These organizations have demonstrated a complete disregard for our local laws, and environmental protections, creating incalculable damage to our local ecosystems.  It is common to see improper use of toxic chemicals or in many cases using banned chemicals, unp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 9.5.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123357</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/inside-douglas-county-9-5-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-9-5-24"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T20:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Out Back to School series continues with Oakland School District Superintendent Jeff Clark:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TACTICAL BURNOUT OPERATIONS ON HOMESTEAD COMPLEX]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123355</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/tactical-burnout-operations-on-homestead-complex/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tactical-burnout-operations-on-homestead-complex"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T18:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 11:00 a.m. The Homestead Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, remains 60 percent contained and at 5,926 acres. A UNF update said the predicted hotter and drier weather has arrived and fire managers are taking advantage of the opportunity to conduct tactical burnout operations on the northernmost fire on the complex,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX UP TO 81 PERCENT CONTAINMENT, 11,141 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123352</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/diamond-complex-up-to-81-percent-containment-11141-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-up-to-81-percent-containment-11141-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T17:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 10:40 a.m.   The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, is now 81 percent contained, and listed at 11,141 acres. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in Crater Lake National Park is 58 percent contained and at 5,286 acres. The North Entrance to Crater Lake National Park is closed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENT JAILED FOR REPORTED RECKLESS BURNING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123350</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/transient-jailed-for-reported-reckless-burning-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transient-jailed-for-reported-reckless-burning-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T17:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 10:30 a.m. A transient was jailed for a reported reckless burning incident on Tuesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 8:30 p.m. fire crews responded to a brush fire outside a business in the 24000 block of North Umpqua Highway in Idleyld Park. When firefighters arrived, they located...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fire Season is not over]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175017</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175017"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, OR— The Oregon Department of Forestry wants to remind Oregonians that with weather fluctuating across the state, fire is still on the landscape and fire season is still in effect. Oregon is still experiencing one of the worst seasons we’ve seen in the past decade, and the department warns the public against complacency. 
“East winds are very common around this time of year, making now the time to prevent the next large wildfire. There is still potential for more fire starts and the season isn’t over yet.” Chris Cline, Fire Protection Division Chief, said. “The fewer human caused fires we have, the less strained our resources will be.”
East winds come to the Pacific Northwest every year around the end of August and last through the fall months. They occur from the crest of the Cascad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL CENTRAL POINT MAN FOLLOWING ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123348</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/roseburg-police-jail-central-point-man-following-alleged-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-central-point-man-following-alleged-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T17:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 10:15 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a Central Point man following an alleged trespass incident on Wednesday. An RPD report said the 42-year-old was discharged from CHI Mercy Medical Center on Northwest Stewart Parkway but refused to leave. The man reportedly became combative with security and had to be restrained on the floor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123346</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-incident-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-incident-3"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T17:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police Jailed a man for an alleged harassment incident on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 1:00 p.m. a victim was working at a business in the 2000 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway when he was punched by a 43-year-old transient, for no apparent reason. Officers watched video of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POILCE JAIL TRANSIENT FOLLOWING ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123344</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/roseburg-poilce-jail-transient-following-alleged-theft-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-poilce-jail-transient-following-alleged-theft-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 204 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a transient following an alleged theft incident on Wednesday. An RPD report said 24-year-old Kendell Holbrook was allegedly seen on video surveillance in the secure area of the Roseburg Public Safety Center on Southeast Douglas Avenue. Holbrook reportedly stole a bike from the secure area and fled...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOLLOWING REPORTED ASSAULT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123342</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/sutherlin-police-jail-woman-following-reported-assault/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-woman-following-reported-assault"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 9:30 a.m. Sutherlin Police jailed a woman following a reported assault incident on Tuesday night. An SPD report said at 9:10 p.m. the 27-year-old trespassed at a residence in the 200 block of West Third Avenue. She reportedly fought with a juvenile, causing damage to his airway. The woman left prior to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STATE POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOLLOWING DUII CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123340</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/state-police-jail-woman-following-duii-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=state-police-jail-woman-following-duii-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 9:20 a.m. Troopers with Oregon State Police jailed a woman following a DUII crash on Wednesday afternoon. An OSP report said at approximately 1:10 p.m. troopers responded to the wreck about 2 miles west of Winston. The 67-year-old operator of a westbound pickup had lost control of the vehicle at a high...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 9.5.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123337</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/morning-conversation-9-5-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-9-5-24"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fire Information Officer Trish Boles has an update on the Diamond Complex fires.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two new businesses open in Reedsport]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a5ffeaa2-6b98-11ef-830a-d358d838ddb4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/two-new-businesses-open-in-reedsport/article_a5ffeaa2-6b98-11ef-830a-d358d838ddb4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REEDSPORT — The Wooden Indian Boutique and Stillwagon Distillery will be celebrating their grand openings and ribbon cuttings during the First Friday Vendor Market this Friday in Old Town Reedsport.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crater Lake to host annual Ride the Rim]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b03d76ac-6b97-11ef-9a69-d3743994be2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/crater-lake-to-host-annual-ride-the-rim/article_b03d76ac-6b97-11ef-9a69-d3743994be2f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T15:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRATER LAKE — The 10th annual Ride the Rim days will be held Saturday and Sept. 14 at Crater Lake National Park, in partnership with the Friends of Crater Lake and Discover Klamath.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers impersonating sheriff's office]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/55813b14-6b96-11ef-bce6-0f1c4cce5ff7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/scammers-impersonating-sheriffs-office/article_55813b14-6b96-11ef-bce6-0f1c4cce5ff7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — People are posing as officials with the Douglas County Sheriff's Office to scam community members out of money, a press release from the sheriff's office said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers Preying on Community Members]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175009</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175009"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T14:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY, Ore. - Scammers are posing as officials from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office (DCSO) in an effort to scam community members out of money. Deputies have once again begun receiving reports from people contacted by phone by individuals posing as DCSO employees. 
The scammer will tell the intended victim they have missed some court appearance, failed to appear for jury duty, they owe fines or have a warrant for their arrest and eventually demands payment. The victim is often directed to immediately make payment or they face consequences including arrest. These are tactics that are never utilized by legitimate law enforcement agencies. 
It is critically important for our community to be aware of these tactics and to share them with their friends and family members, especially those who may be vulnerable to falling victim to the scams, such as the elderly members of the community. However, we also wish to remind the community not to focus too much on specific scam tactics; scammers often change their methods over time:

Scammers can easily obtain new phone numbers and will change them often.
Scammers may use “spoof” programs to make the Caller ID show an agency’s actual phone number.  
Scammers may use the names of actual DCSO employees to make the call seem legitimate.  
Scammers may obtain personal information about a victim online including their name, address, phone number, and the names of others in the home. 
Scammers may initially contact victims by mail, email, or through social media.

Due to the technology used in the scam – and the fact that scammers can be located anywhere in the world – it is virtually impossible to track the scammers or to get money back.
“If anyone has any question about a possible scam call, they should call dispatch at (541) 440-4471 and ask to speak to a deputy,” said Lieutenant Brad O'Dell.  “The most important thing is to not send any money or agree to meet someone to make payment.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austin Farm awarded Century Farm designation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bf141468-6b03-11ef-83f5-f719ab0ca234</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/austin-farm-awarded-century-farm-designation/article_bf141468-6b03-11ef-83f5-f719ab0ca234.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even over the phone, the emotion could be heard in Bruce Austin’s voice as he explained the process of certifying the family farm of five generations and counting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New sign in Drain places four-way stop on Highway 38]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b3e0804c-6b01-11ef-a4d1-1306e2f6350a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/new-sign-in-drain-places-four-way-stop-on-highway-38/article_b3e0804c-6b01-11ef-a4d1-1306e2f6350a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Transportation announced an additional stop sign would be installed Thursday on Oregon Highway 38 West at North Cedar Street in Drain. The sign will result in a permanent four-way stop in an effort to improve traffic safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacific Northwest Power Equipment comes to Sutherlin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c4052ffa-6a33-11ef-bd25-e7c5665d5e80</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/pacific-northwest-power-equipment-comes-to-sutherlin/article_c4052ffa-6a33-11ef-bd25-e7c5665d5e80.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin — Krystal Hammer, Brett Hammer and Andrea Stromberg opened Pacific Northwest Power Equipment on Aug. 12 at 1550 South Comstock Road in Sutherlin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEAT ADVISORY THURSDAY 12:00 P.M. TO 10:00 P.M. FOR MUCH OF REGION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123332</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/heat-advisory-thursday-1200-p-m-to-1000-p-m-for-much-of-region/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=heat-advisory-thursday-1200-p-m-to-1000-p-m-for-much-of-region"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 4:10 a.m.  A Heat Advisory remains in effect for Thursday from 12:00 p.m. to 10:00 p.m. for much of the region. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said afternoon high temperatures between 100 and 105 degrees are expected. The Advisory area includes Douglas, Josephine, Jackson and eastern Curry counties. Forecasters said hot...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN JAILED ON FELONY STRANGULATION/ASSAULT CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123330</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/myrtle-creek-man-jailed-on-felony-strangulation-assault-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-jailed-on-felony-strangulation-assault-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 4:00 a.m. A Myrtle Creek man was jailed, charged with felony counts of strangulation and 4th degree assault Tuesday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said a victim requested contact at the Myrtle Creek Police Department regarding an alleged past assault between her and 38-year -old Patrick Beard. She advised that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LINE PAINTING HAPPENING THURSDAY IN REEDSPORT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123328</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/line-painting-happening-thursday-in-reedsport/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=line-painting-happening-thursday-in-reedsport"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 3:50 a.m.   Covering coastal Douglas County: A contractor for the City of Reedsport will be completing line painting on various roads throughout the community on Thursday. Public Works Director Kimberly Clardy said this will include Port Dock Road, 22nd Street, Frontage Road, Longwood, and Ranch Road from Longwood to Regents Place. Clardy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIRE DANGER LEVEL INCREASES TO EXTREME IN JACKSON & JOSEPHINE COUNTIES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123325</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/fire-danger-level-increases-to-extreme-in-jackson-josephine-counties/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fire-danger-level-increases-to-extreme-in-jackson-josephine-counties"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 3:30 a.m. Due to dry vegetation, hot conditions, and numerous active fires in the region, the fire danger level on lands protected by the Oregon Department of Forestry in Jackson and Josephine counties will increase to Extreme on Friday. A release from the Oregon Department of Forestry said these regulations impact 1.8...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORDS POND COMMUNITIY PARK GRAND OPENING FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123321</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/fords-pond-communitiy-park-grand-opening-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fords-pond-communitiy-park-grand-opening-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 3:20 a.m. The City of Sutherlin is having the grand opening of Ford’s Pond Community Park on Friday. A city release said a ribbon cutting ceremony will be held at 2:00 p.m. with refreshments provided.  The event will continue until 4:00 p.m. The 202-acre park now features a completely paved 1.7-mile path...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC PRESENTS MUSIC EDUCATORS EXTRAVAGANZA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123319</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/ucc-presents-music-educators-extravaganza-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-presents-music-educators-extravaganza-3"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 3:05 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Community College Performing and Visual Arts presents a Music Educators Extravaganza on Sunday afternoon at 3:00 p.m. in the Swanson Amphitheatre on the UCC campus. Local secondary school music educators will perform live with the UCC music faculty. This will include band and choir...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNITED WAY DAVE JOHNSON MEMORIAL GOLF TOURNAMENT NEXT WEEK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123317</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/05/united-way-dave-johnson-memorial-golf-tournament-next-week/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=united-way-dave-johnson-memorial-golf-tournament-next-week"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 5, 2024 2:50 a.m. Greater Douglas United Way has their 42nd annual Dave Johnson Memorial Golf Tournament happening next Thursday. The event returns to Bar Run Golf Course west of Roseburg. Proceeds will benefit GDUW’s annual fundraising campaign thanks to generous loyal sponsors, enthusiastic golfers, volunteers and United Way staff. The tournament is sponsored...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIKE WINTERS LAWN AND GARDEN SHOW 9.4.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123314</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-9-4-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-9-4-24"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T00:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County’s Commissioner of Dirt, Mike Winters, has our weekly local lawn and garden show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogs show tricks, obedience and skill]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cddcd782-6b12-11ef-9607-a78357729500</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/dogs-show-tricks-obedience-and-skill/article_cddcd782-6b12-11ef-9607-a78357729500.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T23:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jacque Keller's dachshund Inky Ball will drive a battery-operated car in the expert level trick dog testing competition at the Umpqua Valley Kennel Club's dog show at the Douglas County Fairgrounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 9.4.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123306</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/inside-douglas-county-9-4-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-9-4-24"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T20:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our annual Back to School series begins with Superintendent Jared Cordon of Roseburg Public Schools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DUII INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123304</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-duii-incident-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-duii-incident-3"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T18:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 11:10 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for a DUII incident Tuesday evening. An RPD report said at approximately 10:15 p.m. officers responded to the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard after a witness reported seeing a pickup speeding and swerving on the roadway. Officers contacted the driver, a 21-year-old man,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123302</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-7/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-7"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T18:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 11:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged theft incident on Tuesday evening. An RPD report said at 6:30 p.m. officers contacted 46-year-old William Cantwell near the Public Safety Center on Southeast Douglas Avenue. Cantwell was reportedly captured on camera tampering with a security camera before it was disconnected and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR VIOLATING STALKING ORDER AT SCHOOL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123300</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-violating-stalking-order-at-school/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-violating-stalking-order-at-school"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 10:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for violating a stalking order at a school on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 3:30 p.m. the 31-year-old from Broadbent went to Hucrest Elementary School in the 1800 of Northwest Kline Street to visit a family member. There is a stalking order against the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX CREWS ANTICIPATE HOTTER DRIER WEATHER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123298</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/homestead-complex-crews-anticipate-hotter-drier-weather/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-crews-anticipate-hotter-drier-weather"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 10:30 a.m. The Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest is still at 5,918 acres and remains 60 percent contained. A UNF update said the predicated hotter and drier weather the next few days may bring with it opportunities to conduct planned tactical burnout operations on the north flank of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN MAYOR PRESENTING MEET THE AUTHOR EVENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123296</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/sutherlin-mayor-presenting-meet-the-author-event/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-mayor-presenting-meet-the-author-event"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 10:10 a.m. City of Sutherlin Mayor Michelle Sumner will present a Meet the Author event this Saturday afternoon at 2:00 p.m. at the C. Giles Hunt Memorial Public Library on East Central Avenue. Author Kenda Elliot will be the guest. Elliot has sold twelve million books, hit the Wall Street Journal top...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COOLING CENTER OPEN THURSDAY AFTERNOON/EARLY EVENING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123292</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/cooling-center-open-thursday-afternoon-early-evening/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cooling-center-open-thursday-afternoon-early-evening"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Due to the afternoon forecast high temperature of over 100 degrees, a cooling center will be open at Saint George Episcopal Church in downtown Roseburg from 3:00 p.m. to around 8:00 p.m. on Thursday. The center will be overseen by Jacob Schlueter. Schlueter said the church is helping by providing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR OVERNIGHT TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123290</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-overnight-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-overnight-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T16:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 9;40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an overnight trespass incident early Tuesday. An RPD report said just after 12:10 a.m. the 31-year-old was contacted within the exclusion zone within his exclusion period, in the 700 block of Southeast Jackson Street. The man was also found with an open can of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERSECTION AT OREGON 38/CEDAR STREET WILL BECOME FOUR-WAY STOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123286</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/intersection-at-oregon-38-cedar-street-will-become-four-way-stop/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=intersection-at-oregon-38-cedar-street-will-become-four-way-stop"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T16:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 9:30 a.m. The Intersection of Oregon 38 and Cedar Street in Drain will become a permanent four-way stop on Thursday. Dan Latham of the Oregon Department of Transportation said the new sign is being installed in an effort to improve traffic safety in Drain. Latham said for several decades, the intersection has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 9.4.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123280</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/morning-conversation-9-4-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-9-4-24"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T16:12:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nikol Hansen from the Roseburg VA Medical Center talks about several upcoming events for veterans and the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former college coach sentenced to federal prison]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/93fa7a7a-6acb-11ef-9515-2f9219cfd239</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/former-college-coach-sentenced-to-federal-prison/article_93fa7a7a-6acb-11ef-9515-2f9219cfd239.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Portland man who served as the head men’s basketball coach at Mt. Hood Community College in Gresham was sentenced to federal prison Tuesday for persuading a child to send him sexually explicit images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diamond Complex is 11,141 acres, 78% contained]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e2b8db08-6a43-11ef-bfd8-4bd5380f2ae2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/diamond-complex-is-11-141-acres-78-contained/article_e2b8db08-6a43-11ef-bfd8-4bd5380f2ae2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas Forest Protective Association increased the fire danger level to high and the Industrial Fire Precaution Level to level 3, effective Wednesday, because of high temperatures in the forecast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEAT ADVISORY IN EFFECT FOR THURSDAY IN MUCH OF SOUTHERN OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123274</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/heat-advisory-in-effect-for-thursday-in-much-of-southern-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=heat-advisory-in-effect-for-thursday-in-much-of-southern-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T10:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4. 2024 4:00 a.m.  A Heat Advisory is in effect from 12:00 p.m. to 10:00 p.m. Thursday in much of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heat index values of around 100 degrees are expected. The Advisory area includes Douglas, Josephine, Jackson and eastern Curry counties. Afternoon high temperatures near 105...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER COLLEGE COACH SENTENCED TO FEDERAL PRISION – GLIDE HIGH CAMP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123272</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/former-college-coach-sentenced-to-federal-prision-glide-high-camp/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=former-college-coach-sentenced-to-federal-prision-glide-high-camp"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T10:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 3:40 a.m.  A Portland man who served as the head men’s basketball coach at Mt. Hood Community College in Gresham, was sentenced to federal prison Tuesday for persuading a child to send him sexually explicit images. A release from the U.S. Attorney’s Office – District of Oregon, said 38-year-old Nathan Ezell Bowie...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA CHANGE TO LEVEL 3 EFFECTIVE WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123269</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/dfpa-change-to-level-3-effective-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-change-to-level-3-effective-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T10:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 3:30 a.m. Effective Wednesday, the Douglas Forest Protective Association changed the Industrial Fire Precaution Levels to LEVEL 3 for all private, county, state and Bureau of Indian Affairs lands within the Douglas District. Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said the Roseburg District of the Bureau of Land Management is in cluded in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GARDEN VALLEY BOULEVARD MAINTENANCE THIS WEEKEND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123267</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/garden-valley-boulevard-maintenance-this-weekend/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=garden-valley-boulevard-maintenance-this-weekend"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T10:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 3:20 a.m. Drivers should use caution and expect detours and delays when road maintenance will close a short section of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard in Roseburg starting this Saturday. A city release said the Roseburg Public Works Department has hired a contractor to repair the road base on a 100-foot section of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC PERFORMING & VISUAL ARTS PRESENTS PIANIST JOHN NILSEN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123265</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/ucc-performing-visual-arts-presents-pianist-john-nilsen/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-performing-visual-arts-presents-pianist-john-nilsen"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T10:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4, 2024 3:05 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Community College Performing & Visual Arts presents pianist John Nilsen in concert on Friday night at 7:00 p.m. in the Whipple Fine Arts Center. A release said it will be an evening that evokes peaceful yet exciting visions of locations around the world, childhood...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY REPUBLICANS WITH FREEDOM GALA SEPTEMBER 12TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=123263</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/09/04/douglas-county-republicans-with-freedom-gala-september-12th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-republicans-with-freedom-gala-september-12th"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T10:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 4,  2024 2:50 a.m.  The Douglas County Republican Central Committee will have their fall fundraising event on September 12th. The Freedom Gala, also known as the Trump/Reagan dinner, will be held at Melrose Vineyards on Melqua Road. Doors will open at 4:45 p.m. The featured speaker is House Republican Leader State Representative Jeff Helfrich,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man stabs another man in Stewart Park, nicking his artery]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/326423a6-6a53-11ef-a3c9-8b5efb234ad7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/man-stabs-another-man-in-stewart-park-nicking-his-artery/article_326423a6-6a53-11ef-a3c9-8b5efb234ad7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[William Edward Wasyluk, 48, of Roseburg, stabbed a man in the knee with a knife, nicking an artery following an altercation around 1 p.m. Sunday at Stewart Park pavilion in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA to issue pasture burn permits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/42bb7c64-6a0c-11ef-afc7-c7b5c54b2907</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/dfpa-to-issue-pasture-burn-permits/article_42bb7c64-6a0c-11ef-afc7-c7b5c54b2907.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — Douglas Forest Protective Association will start issuing prescribed pasture burn permits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran's War Memorial to be rededicated following repairs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/51a496e0-6483-11ef-9335-6375e5fc8acd</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/veterans-war-memorial-to-be-rededicated-following-repairs/article_51a496e0-6483-11ef-9335-6375e5fc8acd.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A rededication ceremony for Douglas County’s Veteran’s War Memorial is scheduled for 10 a.m. Sept. 18 at the Douglas County Courthouse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homestead Complex nearly 6,000 acres, 60% contained]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0d0ad922-6a00-11ef-8200-ab921a3a86d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/homestead-complex-nearly-6-000-acres-60-contained/article_0d0ad922-6a00-11ef-8200-ab921a3a86d0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T14:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Homestead Complex, burning about 30 miles outside of Glide in the Umpqua National Forest, was 60% contained, with slight growth to 5,918 acres as of midday Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slide repair project to impact traffic near Elkton]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9705ad92-69ff-11ef-9dcc-5fd1754fead7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/slide-repair-project-to-impact-traffic-near-elkton/article_9705ad92-69ff-11ef-9dcc-5fd1754fead7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T14:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motorists on Oregon Highway 138 West, between Elkton and Sutherlin, can expect delays for most of September due to a slide repair project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Woman taken to hospital after ATV wreck]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3d9fe01a-69ff-11ef-b6c1-171729c72f28</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/woman-taken-to-hospital-after-atv-wreck/article_3d9fe01a-69ff-11ef-b6c1-171729c72f28.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T14:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — A Canyonville woman was taken to the hospital following an ATV wreck Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YMCA reopens after improvements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bff6c1ec-69fe-11ef-922a-ef7ad4921e69</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/ymca-reopens-after-improvements/article_bff6c1ec-69fe-11ef-922a-ef7ad4921e69.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The YMCA of Douglas County reopened Tuesday after a weeklong closure due to facility enhancements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>