<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-02-18T13:09:54.650Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Bank closing downtown Roseburg branch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cf9d03d6-ccf6-11ee-a9b3-83e0f3521e41</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/u-s-bank-closing-downtown-roseburg-branch/article_cf9d03d6-ccf6-11ee-a9b3-83e0f3521e41.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-18T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After many decades in downtown Roseburg, U.S. Bank has announced that its location at 619 Southeast Main Street will be closing soon. A sign outside the bank on Thursday said the branch would permanently close as of April 29.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE MAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED ASSAULT/BURGLARY/KIDNAPPING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115834</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/18/three-man-jailed-for-alleged-assault-burglary-kidnapping-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=three-man-jailed-for-alleged-assault-burglary-kidnapping-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-02-18T01:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 17, 2024 5:00 p.m.  Three Roseburg men were arrested Friday afternoon following an alleged assault, burglary and kidnapping incident in Riddle. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at about 10:00 a.m. 911 dispatchers received a report of a disturbance in the 200 block of Maple Street. O’Dell said callers indicated...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg men arrested for burglary, kidnapping]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4eae9402-cde5-11ee-81e0-4b083d801d1d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-men-arrested-for-burglary-kidnapping/article_4eae9402-cde5-11ee-81e0-4b083d801d1d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T22:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE — Three Roseburg men were arrested Friday on numerous charges, including burglary and assault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Roseburg Men Arrested for Burglary and Kidnapping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170130</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170130"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T22:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE, Ore. - Three Roseburg men were arrested Friday afternoon for Burglary, Kidnapping and a number of other crimes. 
On Friday, February 16, 2024, around 10:00 a.m., 9-1-1 dispatchers received a report of a disturbance in the 200-block of Maple Street in Riddle. Callers were reporting a physical disturbance where three men were assaulting another. One caller reported that the men were applying zip-ties to the male to restrain him. 
Deputies arrived on scene and were able to determine that 25-year-old Justin Daniel Devlaeminck, 53-year-old Daniel Terrance Devlaeminck, and 26-year-old Austin Lee Lyman broke into a residence in an effort to “evict” the 22-year-old victim. Justin Devlaeminck pointed a firearm at the victim and Daniel Devlaeminck broke a window to the residence. All three suspects entered the home and began to assault the male victim who tried to escape, but was pulled back. At one point, the victim was able to break away and flee outside where the three suspects captured him and continued their assault and eventually used zip ties to restrain him. 
The victim was transported to Mercy Medical Center by ambulance for treatment of his injuries. 
All three suspects were taken into custody and transported to the Douglas County Jail where they were lodged on the following charges: 
Daniel Devlaeminck: Burglary I, Kidnapping I, Assault IV, Criminal Mischief II
Justin Devlaeminck: Burglary I, Kidnapping I, Assault IV, Menacing, Pointing a Firearm at Another
Austin Lyman: Burglary I, Kidnapping I, Assault IV
The Sheriff's Office was assisted by the Myrtle Creek Police Department, Umpqua Valley Ambulance and Riddle Fire Department.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers Posing as DCSO Employees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170129</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170129"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T21:52:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY, Ore. - Scammers are posing as officials from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office (DCSO) in an effort to scam community members out of money. Deputies have once again begun receiving reports from people contacted by phone by individuals posing as DCSO employees such as Lt. Brad O'Dell and Retired Lt. Mike Root. 
The scammer will tell the intended victim they have missed some court appearance, owe fines or have a warrant for their arrest and then demands payment. The victim is often directed to immediately make payment or they face consequences including arrest. These are tactics that are never utilized by legitimate law enforcement agencies. 
It is critically important for our community to be aware of these tactics and to share them with their friends and family members, especially those who may be vulnerable to falling victim to the scams, such as the elderly members of the community. However, we also wish to remind the community not to focus too much on specific scam tactics; scammers often change their methods over time:

Scammers can easily obtain new phone numbers and will change them often.
Scammers may use “spoof” programs to make the Caller ID show an agency’s actual phone number.  
Scammers may use the names of actual DCSO employees to make the call seem legitimate.  
Scammers may obtain personal information about a victim online including their name, address, phone number, and the names of others in the home. 
Scammers may initially contact victims by mail, email, or through social media.

Due to the technology used in the scam – and the fact that scammers can be located anywhere in the world – it is virtually impossible to track the scammers or to get money back.
“If anyone has any question about a possible scam call, they should call dispatch at (541) 440-4471 and ask to speak to a deputy,” said Lieutenant Brad O'Dell.  “The most important thing is to not send any money or agree to meet someone to make payment.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. BANK CITES MIGRATION TO DIGITAL FOR BRANCH CLOSURE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115831</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/17/u-s-bank-cites-migration-to-digital-for-branch-closure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=u-s-bank-cites-migration-to-digital-for-branch-closure"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T20:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 19, 2024 12:20 p.m. In the KQEN Business Spotlight: An official with U.S. Bank is citing changes to client’s banking preferences as part of the reason for the upcoming closure of the downtown Roseburg branch. Regional Communications Manager Jake Holtrop told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the shift includes a rapid...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg to continue pipeline replacement project]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1092c77a-cdd0-11ee-a9ad-c39556a235d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/roseburg-to-continue-pipeline-replacement-project/article_1092c77a-cdd0-11ee-a9ad-c39556a235d5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T20:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Starting Monday, natural gas pipeline replacements will resume on Stewart Parkway before continuing onto Garden Valley Boulevard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari celebrates the birth of critically endangered tamarin babies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4a9fbeb6-cc2f-11ee-9f7f-bb4d81795dea</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/wildlife-safari-celebrates-the-birth-of-critically-endangered-tamarin-babies/article_4a9fbeb6-cc2f-11ee-9f7f-bb4d81795dea.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari announced the birth of two cotton top tamarin babies to proud parents Bey and Colonel Mustard in the Wildlife Safari Village.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Holeman Wildlife Safari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tow truck drivers hear Jagraj Singh Sidhu plead not guilty in court]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8d8be224-cd18-11ee-87b1-3f44a85dcfd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/tow-truck-drivers-hear-jagraj-singh-sidhu-plead-not-guilty-in-court/article_8d8be224-cd18-11ee-87b1-3f44a85dcfd2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tow trucks lined up on Southeast Fowler Street near the Douglas County Courthouse, while a man charged with criminal negligent homicide pleaded not guilty for his role in the death of Henry Alan Lichtwald.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY and ABIGAIL ADKINS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Birth Announcements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a7971dee-ca9a-11ee-b42e-3fb290e80c29</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/birth-announcements/article_a7971dee-ca9a-11ee-b42e-3fb290e80c29.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MERCY MEDICAL CENTER, ROSEBURG]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marriages: Feb. 5-9]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4d04a28e-ca9a-11ee-a51b-0ff29d4b72f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/marriages-feb-5-9/article_4d04a28e-ca9a-11ee-a51b-0ff29d4b72f8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas County Clerk’s Office issued these licenses Feb. 5-9.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recommendations for contemporary mysteries]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bfbd3858-cd02-11ee-816c-27f823534872</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/recommendations-for-contemporary-mysteries/article_bfbd3858-cd02-11ee-816c-27f823534872.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love mysteries with compelling characters and a strong sense of place, and these contemporary new releases fit the bill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KRIS WILEY For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg High School closet closed during lunch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/dbcf5712-cb7f-11ee-811b-0345fa52daab</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/roseburg-high-school-closet-closed-during-lunch/article_dbcf5712-cb7f-11ee-811b-0345fa52daab.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rachel Jackson, the Key Club advisor, had to close the RHS Campus Closet during lunch on Thursdays because students were causing issues in the unsupervised Heritage building.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEIRA LEE For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canyonville Middle School honor roll]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4ec24c0e-cc9b-11ee-b5ce-978c703dd6ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/canyonville-middle-school-honor-roll/article_4ec24c0e-cc9b-11ee-b5ce-978c703dd6ce.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE — Canyonville Middle School released its honor roll for the second quarter of the 2023-24 year. Students named to the president's list posted a 4.0 GPA, while high honors students have a GPA between 3.86-3.5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Literary Council’s poster contest winners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8ba1f9c4-cbe9-11ee-9ade-8bf8aa435f55</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/umpqua-literary-council-s-poster-contest-winners/article_8ba1f9c4-cbe9-11ee-9ade-8bf8aa435f55.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Literacy Council held its annual poster contest for elementary school students.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UVA OFFERING SPRING BREAK YOUTH ART CAMP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115827</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/uva-offering-spring-break-youth-art-camp/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uva-offering-spring-break-youth-art-camp"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T18:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 10:50 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Valley Arts kicks off the spring break with a Youth Art Spring Break Camp. Foraging Wild Colors will take place Tuesday March 26th through Friday March 29th from 1:00 p.m. to 4:00 p.m. Through this camp, young artists will gain tools to identify and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN ARRESTED FOR DUII INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115825</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/roseburg-man-arrested-for-duii-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-arrested-for-duii-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T18:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 10:25 a.m.  A Roseburg man was arrested by Roseburg Police for driving under the influence of intoxicants early Friday. An RPD report said at 2:30 a.m. an officer stopped the 48-year-old after he left a business in the 900 block of Southeast Stephens Street and pulled out in front of a semi-truck,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg man still missing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0335ed52-cb76-11ee-9ee0-0f78f25014d7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/roseburg-man-still-missing/article_0335ed52-cb76-11ee-9ee0-0f78f25014d7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Tykerrious "Ty" Ray has been reported missing to the Roseburg Police Department.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG WOMAN CITED FOR OFFENSIVE LITTERING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115822</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/roseburg-woman-cited-for-offensive-littering/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-woman-cited-for-offensive-littering"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T18:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 10:10 a.m. A Roseburg woman was cited by Roseburg Police for offensive littering Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 8:00 a.m. officers contacted the 41-year-old during camp clean ups in the 1400 block of Southeast Miccelli Street. The woman’s camp was not cleaned up and the suspect had allegedly spread out...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICLE JAIL FUGITIVE FOLLOWING TRAFFIC STOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115820</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/roseburg-policle-jail-fugitive-following-traffic-stop/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-policle-jail-fugitive-following-traffic-stop"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T18:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 9:50 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a fugitive following a traffic stop Thursday night. An RPD report said at approximately 10:50 p.m. 37-year-old Jered Koser was stopped for traffic violations in the 300 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. During the stop, Koser allegedly gave the officer his brother’s name. Officers later identified...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING REPORTED ASSAULT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115818</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-assault/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-assault"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T17:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 9;30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man following a reported assault incident on Thursday evening. An RPD report said at 6:00 p.m. 48-year-old Mark Bennett was contacted in the 600 block of Southeast Jackson Street for allegedly assaulting and physically harassing the victims during the incident in their home. The victims reportedly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115816</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-9/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-9"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T17:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 9:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for alleged disorderly conduct on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report said at 12:20 p.m. officers responded after callers said the woman was standing in the middle of the street, blocking traffic and spitting at vehicles. This was at the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Desantiago guilty of punching his defense attorney]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ebc53b56-cc69-11ee-8ffc-2f70e0fc2b3d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/desantiago-guilty-of-punching-his-defense-attorney/article_ebc53b56-cc69-11ee-8ffc-2f70e0fc2b3d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 12-person jury found Savino David Desantiago guilty Thursday of second-degree assault for punching his defense attorney, Donald L. Scales, on April 13, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thrive Umpqua establishes school wellness program in Glide]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fb7b2170-cb72-11ee-92cf-3bcbdc9fa4fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/thrive-umpqua-establishes-school-wellness-program-in-glide/article_fb7b2170-cb72-11ee-92cf-3bcbdc9fa4fd.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not just a name — Thrive Umpqua has established a local program, this time in the Glide School District, with hopes teachers and staff will learn and continue to truly thrive in their health and wellness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. BANK CLOSING DOWNTOWN ROSEBURG BRANCH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115812</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/u-s-bank-closing-downtown-roseburg-branch/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=u-s-bank-closing-downtown-roseburg-branch"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T12:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 4:10 a.m.  In the KQEN Business Spotlight: After many decades in downtown Roseburg, U.S. Bank has announced that its location at 619 Southeast Main Street will be closing soon. A sign outside the bank on Thursday said the branch would permanently close as of April 29th. Headquartered in Minneapolis, Minnesota, U.S. Bank...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLM HAS PROJECT FUNDING FOR WESTERN OREGON PROJECTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115810</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/blm-has-project-funding-for-western-oregon-projects/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=blm-has-project-funding-for-western-oregon-projects"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T11:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 3:35 a.m.  The Bureau of Land Management has funding for projects that maintain and improve public lands across western Oregon. A BLM release said agency leaders are encouraging individuals, organizations, and local governments to submit funding applications for consideration. Roseburg District Manager Heather Whitman said, “Title II funds are used to make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FREE FISHING WEEKEND SATURDAY/SUNDAY IN OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115808</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/free-fishing-weekend-saturday-sunday-in-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=free-fishing-weekend-saturday-sunday-in-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T11:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife has a Free Fishing Weekend in the state on Saturday and Sunday. An ODFW release said no fishing/shellfish licenses or tags are required for those two days of President’s Day weekend. Both Oregon residents and nonresidents can fish for free. All other fishing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELEBRATION OF LITERACY SIGNATURE EVENT IS SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115806</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/celebration-of-literacy-signature-event-is-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=celebration-of-literacy-signature-event-is-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T11:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Celebration of Literacy has its signature event on Saturday at Wildlife Safari in Winston. Magic in Books is the theme. It will take place from 10:00 a.m. to 3:00 p.m. in the Safari Village. Activities will include a book walk, book exchange, story time, crafts, face painting, origami making...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PACIFIC POWER FILES GENERAL RATE CASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115804</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/16/pacific-power-files-general-rate-case/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pacific-power-files-general-rate-case"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T11:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 16, 2024 2:50 a.m. Pacific Power has filed a general rate case and a Transition Adjustment Mechanism update with the Oregon Public Utility Commission. A release from the utility said the combined rate actions would result in a 16.9 percent rate adjustment, or roughly $304 million, and would support continued investments in wildfire risk...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New countywide resource guide available]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6db022d4-cc33-11ee-8ba7-9bdc15708dee</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/new-countywide-resource-guide-available/article_6db022d4-cc33-11ee-8ba7-9bdc15708dee.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County has created an updated resource guide intended to help individuals and families experiencing homelessness, dealing with substance abuse, or anyone else seeking support during a crisis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Community College faculty art show open until March 13]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/834bcafa-cc54-11ee-b664-d767377f79eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/umpqua-community-college-faculty-art-show-open-until-march-13/article_834bcafa-cc54-11ee-b664-d767377f79eb.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T22:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — For the first time in seven years, the Umpqua Community College visual art faculty are hosting a show at the Whipple Fine Arts center on campus, bringing together sculptures, photography, mixed media and everything in between for a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WILL GESCHKE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missing snowmobiler found Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b9c8d19a-cc3b-11ee-9711-0315f4c4a4ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/missing-snowmobiler-found-tuesday/article_b9c8d19a-cc3b-11ee-9711-0315f4c4a4ec.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T19:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A missing snowmobiler was found near Crater Lake late Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE RESPOND TO FOUR DUII INCIDENT IN 17 HOURS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115800</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/roseburg-police-respond-to-four-duii-incident-in-17-hours/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-respond-to-four-duii-incident-in-17-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T19:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 11:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police responded to four DUII incidents in 17 hours between Wednesday morning and early Thursday. An RPD report said just after 8:20 a.m. officers responded to the intersection of Northwest Broad Street and Northwest Edenbower Boulevard regarding a sedan that was stalled in a lane of travel. The 19-year-old...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR RESTRAINING ORDER VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115798</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-restraining-order-violation-8/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-restraining-order-violation-8"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 10:45 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a restraining order violation on Wednesday afternoon. An RPD report said at 4:00 p.m. officers contacted the 39-year-old after he called to turn himself in on a previous case. Officers met with man near the entrance to corrections where he admitted to violating a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115796</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 10:35 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged harassment incident on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 7:00 p.m. officers responded to the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard after a caller said there had been a physical disturbance. They learned that a 29-year-old man had allegedly punched a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR TRESPASS/MISCHIEF INCIDENTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115794</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-trespass-mischief-incidents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-trespass-mischief-incidents"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 204 10:25 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man following two incidents Wednesday morning. An RPD report said at 7:30 a.m. 38-year-old Jonathan Rios allegedly went back to a location which he had been previously trespassed from in the 3200 block of West Shasta Avenue. Rios reportedly left several hundred dollars on top of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLLEGE WITH JAZZ EVENT IN MARCH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115792</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/college-with-jazz-event-in-march/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=college-with-jazz-event-in-march"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 10:10 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Community College will have a jazz themed show on March 8th. Jazz virtuoso Dan Balmer will perform with the Umpqua Singers and the Big Horn Jazz Band at 7:00 p.m. in Jacoby Auditorium. Balmer is fresh off a European tour with Pink Martini. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON HAS WALK ON THE WILD SIDE SET FOR JUNE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115789</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/winston-has-walk-on-the-wild-side-set-for-june/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-has-walk-on-the-wild-side-set-for-june"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T18:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 10:00 a.m.  The City of Winston has scheduled its Walk on the Wild Side event for June 22nd. It will take place from 3:00 p.m. to 7:00 p.m. at Civic Wayside Park. $35 entry tickets provide participants with entrance to a wine garden, 3 tasting vouchers, 1 wine glass to paint, 3...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MISSING SNOWMOBILER FOUND LATE TUESDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115787</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/missing-snowmobiler-found-late-tuesday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=missing-snowmobiler-found-late-tuesday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T17:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 9:40 a.m.  A missing snowmobiler was found near Crater Lake late Tuesday. A report from the Klamath County Sheriff’s Office said on Tuesday at 4:30 p.m. Klamath County Search and Rescue responded after a man went missing after being separated from his group while riding in Crater Lake National Park.  The man...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing the love: seniors receive Valentine's Day cards]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/56cbffe0-cb69-11ee-b4f0-bbe27e7e9298</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/sharing-the-love-seniors-receive-valentines-day-cards/article_56cbffe0-cb69-11ee-b4f0-bbe27e7e9298.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dennis Sox, a resident at Avamere at Oak Park, spent his first Valentine’s Day without his partner of 17 years Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Truck of fraudulent investor seized in Canyonville]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0e478c02-cc19-11ee-b765-6f3dadf6a9da</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/truck-of-fraudulent-investor-seized-in-canyonville/article_0e478c02-cc19-11ee-b765-6f3dadf6a9da.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE — A vehicle purchased by John Harder and stored at his home in Canyonville was seized by the U.S. Attorney's Office for the District of Oregon on Jan. 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drazan hosts roundtable in Roseburg concerning wildfires]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2c2b49c2-cba9-11ee-b8db-4fa24db2044c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/drazan-hosts-roundtable-in-roseburg-concerning-wildfires/article_2c2b49c2-cba9-11ee-b8db-4fa24db2044c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People sitting around the table Wednesday at the Douglas County Courthouse mostly seemed to agree on one common problem concerning wildfires in Oregon — the lack of management on federal lands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community invited to Heart Health Fair on Feb. 23]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3af3222a-cb7e-11ee-8505-dfd39be3f4c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/community-invited-to-heart-health-fair-on-feb-23/article_3af3222a-cb7e-11ee-8505-dfd39be3f4c6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All things heart related will be the focus Feb. 23, when CHI Mercy Health observes American Heart Month with a free event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adapt's opioid treatment program to relocate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/79f54850-cb69-11ee-9878-5fe1a8b0188b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/adapts-opioid-treatment-program-to-relocate/article_79f54850-cb69-11ee-9878-5fe1a8b0188b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Adapt Integrated Health Care's opioid treatment program will relocate to 406 NE Winchester Street in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING THROUGH THURSDAY EVENING ABOVE 5,000 FEET]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115783</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/winter-storm-warning-through-thursday-evening-above-5000-feet/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-through-thursday-evening-above-5000-feet"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T11:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2025 3:50 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning is in effect through 11:00 p.m. Thursday above 5,000 feet for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected with additional accumulations of 5 to 20 inches. Winds will gust as high as 45 miles per...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY GOVERNMENT TO CLOSE ON MONDAY, WITH EXCEPTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115780</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/county-government-to-close-on-monday-with-exceptions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-government-to-close-on-monday-with-exceptions"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T11:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 3:35 a.m. Douglas County government will close Monday, but there will be exceptions. A County release said Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman and Tom Kress would like to remind residents that offices at the Courthouse, Justice Building, County Annex in Reedsport, museum, fairgrounds, landfill and transfer stations, and all external government offices...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HIGH BAND BINGO NIGHT THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115778</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/roseburg-high-band-bingo-night-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-high-band-bingo-night-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T11:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 3:25 a.m. Thursday night, the Roseburg High School Band will have its annual Band Bingo Night. The fundraiser will be held in the RHS Student Center. A $5 bingo card is good for the entire night, but many people purchase several cards to help to increase their odds of winning. Several prize...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ART OF PREVENTION CONTEST SEEKING YOUNG ARTISTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115776</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/art-of-prevention-contest-seeking-young-artists/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=art-of-prevention-contest-seeking-young-artists"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T11:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 3:15 a.m. The Prevention and Education Program of Adapt Integrated Health Care is seeking young artists for its Art of Prevention art contest. An Adapt release said it’s an opportunity for youth to express their understanding and experiences of substance misuse, suicidal ideation/self-harm, problem gambling/gaming, and/or resilience through artwork, utilizing the medium...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CASCADE-SISKIYOU NATIONAL MONUMENT ACCEPTING ARTIST-IN-RESIDENCE APPLICATIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115774</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/cascade-siskiyou-national-monument-accepting-artist-in-residence-applications/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cascade-siskiyou-national-monument-accepting-artist-in-residence-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T11:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Bureau of Land Management has announced that applications are open for the annual Artist-in-Residence program. A release said the selected artist receives a one-to-two-week residency at CSNM in the month of June. Artists will create work while immersed in a beautiful environment and share their art with the public....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WYDEN, MERKLEY, COLLEAGUES URGE EDUCATION DEPARTMENT TO ADDRESS FAFSA ISSUES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115772</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/15/wyden-merkley-colleagues-urge-education-department-to-address-fafsa-issues/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wyden-merkley-colleagues-urge-education-department-to-address-fafsa-issues"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T11:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 15, 2024 2:50 a.m. On Wednesday, Senators Ron Wyden, Jeff Merkley and Senate colleagues called on the U.S. Department of Education to urgently address the operational issues with the new Free Application for Federal Student Aid form that impacts many students in Oregon and nationwide. The senators wrote, “We are supportive of the Department’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>