<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-05-08T23:11:38.781Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Forests Advisory Committee hosts tour May 16, meets May 17 in Forest Grove]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news172130</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news172130"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. – An Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) state forests advisory group will host a tour of forestland in portions of the Tillamook and Clatsop State Forests on May 16 and meet on May 17 in Forest Grove, and the meeting will have a virtual option via Zoom.
The public is welcome at both events, hosted by the State Forests Advisory Committee (SFAC). The meeting agenda will be posted on the SFAC webpage. 
Details
Forest Tour: Meets at 8:30 a.m. on May 16 at the Hornshuh Creek fire Station #14 at 49021 NW Sunset Highway in Banks. The tour will visit the Wolf Creek Target Shooting Lanes, a partial cut harvest for habitat development, and a stop at Reehers Camp to hear and see the Salmonberry trail project. RSVP is requested for the forest tour so that attendees can be provided safety …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 5.8.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118541</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/inside-douglas-county-5-8-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-5-8-24"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shannon Sebastian and son Garrett Weaver talk about Shannon’s grandson Owen, who suffered a life-changing brain injury in  a car accident following an Oregon State football game last fall.  They talk about a benefit golf tournament happening June 1st at the Roseburg Country Club to help with the family’s expenses and other aspects of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accounting firm announces new partner]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/08ba2eee-0ca0-11ef-b358-2755d052eb0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/accounting-firm-announces-new-partner/article_08ba2eee-0ca0-11ef-b358-2755d052eb0b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T18:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wicks Emmett Certified Public Accountants in Roseburg has announced that Erica Aitken is now a partner in the firm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHI MERCY MEDICAL CENTER ADDRESSES SPILL ON TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118539</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/chi-mercy-medical-center-addresses-spill-on-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=chi-mercy-medical-center-addresses-spill-on-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T17:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHI Mercy Medical Center is addressing a spill which took place on Tuesday. Information from Mercy shared on their Facebook page said during a routine generator test early Tuesday morning on the Mercy campus, a system deficiency was identified. That resulted in the emergency equipment fuel overflowing from the basin on campus near the grounds...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN LIONS HOSTING PUBLIC SAFETY OPEN HOUSE/BBQ]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118534</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/sutherlin-lions-hosting-public-safety-open-house-bbq/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-lions-hosting-public-safety-open-house-bbq"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T17:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 10:20 a.m.   The Sutherlin Lions Club will host a Public Safety Open House and Appreciation BBQ on Thursday night from 5:00 p.m. to 7:00 p.m. It will be held at the Sutherlin Fire Station, on South State Street. It is an opportunity to meet first responders and say thank you for always...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TEEN CITED FOR MINOR IN POSSESSION OF MARIJUANA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118532</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/teen-cited-for-minor-in-possession-of-marijuana/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=teen-cited-for-minor-in-possession-of-marijuana"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a teen for minor in possession of marijuana while operating a motor vehicle on Tuesday night. An RPD report said at 10:40 p.m. the 18-year-old male was stopped for a traffic violation at the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and Northeast Shambrook Avenue. He was allegedly found...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PAIR CITED FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118530</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/pair-cited-for-prohibited-camping-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pair-cited-for-prohibited-camping-2"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 9:50 a.m.   Two people were cited by Roseburg Police for prohibited camping on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 8:20 a.m. officers contacted a 60-year-old man and a 55-year-old woman in the 2000 block of West Harvard Avenue. The pair was camping in a tent next to the Stewart Parkway Bridge. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR OFFENSIVE LITTERING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118528</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-offensive-littering-6/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-offensive-littering-6"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 9:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for offensive littering on Tuesday morning. An RPD report said just after 11:30 a.m. the 46-year-old was contacted in the 700 block of Southeast Stephens Street because he had trash and other debris spread across three parking spaces on a city lot. The man had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR LITTERING/RESISTING ARREST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118526</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-littering-resisting-arrest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-littering-resisting-arrest"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for depositing trash within 100 yards of a waterway, resisting arrest, and prohibited camping on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 8:30 a.m. the 33-year-old was contacted at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. She was found in a heap of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR PAROLE VIOLATION TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118524</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-parole-violation-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-parole-violation-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 9:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a parole violation on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 3:15 p.m. officers contacted the 48-year-old at Charles Gardiner Park in the 2600 block of Northwest Edenbower Boulevard after he was seen sitting on a bench drinking a beer. Officers learned the man was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 5.8.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118520</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/morning-conversation-5-8-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-5-8-24"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg School District Superintendent Jared Cordon talks about Teacher Appreciation Week – happening this week:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public invited to comment on Forestry strategic plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news172114</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news172114"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore. — The Oregon Board of Forestry and Department of Forestry are inviting public comment on the final draft of their new shared strategic plan, the Vision for Oregon’s Forests, through May 24.
The board and department have been working together on this plan—which will replace the Forestry Program for Oregon—for the past two years. The Vision for Oregon’s Forests will provide the strategic direction that will guide both the board and department’s work for the next several years. 
Comments can be submitted online or by mail to: ODF Public Affairs, 2600 State St., Salem, OR 97310. Comments will be shared with the board prior to their June 7 vote to adopt the plan. 
Throughout the remainder of 2024 and into 2025, the board and department will continue to build upon the foundation provided by the Vision for Oregon’s Forests through developing associated progress measures. ODF will also build out its process for development of action plans to achieve the goals identified in the Vision for Oregon’s Forests. Engagement with department and board advisory committees, Tribes, key state and federal agencies, stakeholders, other partners, and local communities to identify actions will be a core component of the planning process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County schools place at state championships]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2459a464-0c90-11ef-a2c7-c32621e8e246</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/douglas-county-schools-place-at-state-championships/article_2459a464-0c90-11ef-a2c7-c32621e8e246.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CORVALLIS — Sutherlin High School choir placed third and Douglas High School took fourth at the Class 3A 2024 Choir State Championships, held at Oregon State University last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giving people a reason to smile: Mercy's oral health program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0417e620-0bc8-11ef-b11e-ab11de5d26c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/giving-people-a-reason-to-smile-mercys-oral-health-program/article_0417e620-0bc8-11ef-b11e-ab11de5d26c0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In keeping with our goal to reduce health disparities and take the next step in furthering our outreach from children to adults, our hospital based oral health program is making a difference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LISA PLATT For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Education in nature: Roseburg students attend Eastwood Nature Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e71cf938-0cbd-11ef-a136-b7d27aeb85dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/education-in-nature-roseburg-students-attend-eastwood-nature-days/article_e71cf938-0cbd-11ef-a136-b7d27aeb85dc.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Children learned to use binoculars to see birds, find matching scents like salmon can and learned how beavers build dams Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thrive Umpqua: Love your neighborhood]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e9ea2e22-0bca-11ef-8c80-5bcb4185cbd6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/thrive-umpqua-love-your-neighborhood/article_e9ea2e22-0bca-11ef-8c80-5bcb4185cbd6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago, a company-wide layoff coinciding with the end of my car’s lease forced me to slow down. Meandering through neighborhoods, now on foot or by bike, I reminisce about the various neighborhoods I’ve called home over the years…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>REBECCA WARREN For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swindler, Jennings will get separate murder trials]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a154381a-0cc4-11ef-bad9-e36de0b02c7a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/swindler-jennings-will-get-separate-murder-trials/article_a154381a-0cc4-11ef-bad9-e36de0b02c7a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to tell whether it’s a twisted love story or an angry boyfriend — those are the two sides being argued so far. Whichever the case might be, it resulted in the death of 34-year-old Joshua Lynn Alexander.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FALLEN OFFICERS HONORED DURING ANNUAL MEMORIAL CEREMONY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118518</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/fallen-officers-honored-during-annual-memorial-ceremony/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fallen-officers-honored-during-annual-memorial-ceremony"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T12:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 6:00 a.m.  A ceremony held Tuesday in Salem commemorated law enforcement officers who have died in the line of duty in Oregon. A release from the Oregon Department of Public Safety Standards and Training said hundreds gathered for the Oregon Law Enforcement Memorial Ceremony to honor the state’s fallen officers and those...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOTTEST TEMPERATURES OF THE YEAR SO FAR LATER THIS WEEK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118511</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/hottest-temperatures-of-the-year-so-far-later-this-week/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hottest-temperatures-of-the-year-so-far-later-this-week"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 4:00 a.m. The Umpqua Valley should see the hottest temperatures of the year so far later this week. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the mercury reached 80 degrees on April 2nd. So far, that has been the warmest day in 2024. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BALLOTS TRICKING IN FOR THE MAY PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY ELECTION IN DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118509</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/ballots-tricking-in-for-the-may-presidential-primary-election-in-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ballots-tricking-in-for-the-may-presidential-primary-election-in-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 3:50 a.m.  Ballots are beginning to trickle in for the 2024 May Presidential Primary Election in Douglas County. County Clerk Daniel Loomis said 0.92 percent, or 827 ballots have been returned as of late Tuesday. Loomis said that lags 1.84 percent behind the participation rate for the same point in the 2020...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MONIQUE DESPAIN ANNOUNCES LAW ENFORCEMENT ENDORSEMENTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118505</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/monique-despain-announces-law-enforcement-endorsements/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=monique-despain-announces-law-enforcement-endorsements"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 3:40 a.m.  On Tuesday, Republican candidate for Congress Monique DeSpain held a press conference to address the issue of public safety and announced key law enforcement endorsements in her race for Oregon’s Fourth Congressional District. A release said DeSpain is the only candidate in the race to receive endorsements from law enforcement...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN NAMES BARTRAM AND HAMILTION FIRST CITIZENS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118503</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/sutherlin-names-bartram-and-hamiltion-first-citizens/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-names-bartram-and-hamiltion-first-citizens"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 3:30 a.m. Dan Bartram and Debbie Hamilton were named as Sutherlin’s man and woman of the year for 2023, on Sunday. The 68th annual First Citizens Banquet had a western theme and took place at Workman’s Bar & Smokehouse in Green. Other winners were: *Jack Chostner – Inspirational of the Year *Beth...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REPUBLICAN CENTRAL COMMITTEE ENDORSES JOHN HANLILN FOR SHERIFF]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118501</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/local-republican-central-committee-endorses-john-hanliln-for-sheriff/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-republican-central-committee-endorses-john-hanliln-for-sheriff"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Douglas County Republican Central Committee has announced its endorsement of John Hanlin for Douglas County Sheriff. A DCRCC release said after careful consideration and thorough evaluation, “we proudly stand behind Sheriff Hanlin as the most qualified and dedicated candidate for this crucial role. Mr. Hanlin brings with him a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STEAM EXTRAVAGANZA HAPPENING SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118496</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/steam-extravaganza-happening-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=steam-extravaganza-happening-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 3:05 a.m. The STEAM Extravaganza is happening on Saturday May 18th at Umpqua Community College. The annual event presented by the Umpqua Valley STEAM Hub is designed to provide an opportunity to show some of the activities and connections that people in the county are making in the fields of science, technology,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A WORLD OF FOLK SONGS PERFORMED BY UCC CONCERT BAND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118494</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/08/a-world-of-folk-songs-performed-by-ucc-concert-band/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-world-of-folk-songs-performed-by-ucc-concert-band"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 8, 2024 2:50 a.m.   In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Community College Performing and Visual Arts presents “A World of Folk Songs” performed by the UCC Concert Band on May 20th. The concert will be held at 7:00 p.m. in the Jacoby Auditorium on the school’s campus. A variety of family-friendly music will take...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 5.7.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118491</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/true-wealth-5-7-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-5-7-24"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Littlejohn Financial, David Littlejohn and Matt Dickson have our weekly local financial program:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheers to Oregon Wine Month]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a980e7be-0c96-11ef-a70a-4fa479bc46d3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/life/cheers-to-oregon-wine-month/article_a980e7be-0c96-11ef-a70a-4fa479bc46d3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The beginning of May kicked off Oregon Wine Month and there is no better place to pay homage to the grape than in the Umpqua Valley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 5.7.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118487</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/inside-douglas-county-5-7-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-5-7-24"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:21:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Fire Division Chief of Training and Volunteer Coordinator Brandon McGarr and Volunteer Lieutenant Josh McDonald talk about the need for volunteer firefighters in Sutherlin:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DEPOSITING TRASH NEAR WATERWAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118484</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-depositing-trash-near-waterway/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-depositing-trash-near-waterway"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for depositing trash within 100 yards of a waterway on Monday. An RPD report said at 7:30 a.m. the 54-year-old was contacted at The Point in Deer Creek Park in the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street where he was staying in a large camp....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[J.E. Schroeder Seed Orchard contracts Kevin Barnes to propagate improved trees for Oregon's forests (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news172094</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news172094"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST. PAUL, Ore. – The Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) contracted Kevin Barnes, grafting specialist, to propagate improved Douglas fir, western hemlock, western larch, and ponderosa pine trees for the J.E. Schroeder Seed Orchard. Barnes plays a crucial role in propagating improved tree varieties that will produce seeds for replanting clearcuts and areas affected by fire in Oregon.
At the J.E. Schroeder Seed Orchard, geneticist Don Kaczmarek uses traditional breeding methods to develop trees for Oregon with characteristics such as increased growth rates, climate adaptability, and resistance to insects and disease. Barnes grafts material from parent trees to a rootstock that provides water and nutrients for growth. “It’s a specialized profession and not a lot of people do what we do,” Barn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE THIRTEEN PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118482</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/roseburg-police-cite-thirteen-people-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-thirteen-people-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 10:45 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited thirteen people for prohibited camping on Monday. An RPD report said eleven contacts were made, all in either the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street, or the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. Those contacted were all allegedly in violation of at least one part of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CITED FOR DUII]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118480</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/roseburg-man-cited-for-duii/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-cited-for-duii"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 10:30 a.m.  A Roseburg man was cited by Roseburg Police for DUII on Monday. An RPD report said just after 5:50 p.m. officers responded to the 1400 block of Northwest Mulholland Drive after a caller said there was a disturbance between two drivers. Officers arrived on scene and contacted the 34-year-old who...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118478</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-24"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 224 10:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged trespass incident on Monday. An RPD report said just before 5:30 p.m. officers contacted the 20-year-old at a business in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street because he was refusing to leave. The man had been trespassed from that same location...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR UNLAWFUL USE OF A VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118476</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-unlawful-use-of-a-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-unlawful-use-of-a-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 10:10 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for unlawful use of a vehicle and for first-degree theft, early Tuesday. An RPD report said the 28-year-old had been developed as a suspect for a previous stolen vehicle case. Officers located him in the parking lot of a recreation facility in the 1200 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE DRIVER EXTRICATED FOLLOWING TWO VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118474</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/one-driver-extricated-following-two-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=one-driver-extricated-following-two-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 10:00 a.m. One driver had to be extricated following a two-vehicle crash on Monday in Roseburg. A Roseburg Police report said just after 1:45 p.m. a pickup driver was heading south in the 400 block of Southeast Stephens Street when a second vehicle pulled out of a parking lot, without yielding. Both...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOODWIN ENDORSES TRUMP FOR PRESIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118472</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/goodwin-endorses-trump-for-president/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=goodwin-endorses-trump-for-president"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 9:30 a.m.    State Representative Christine Goodwin, candidate for State Senate in District 2, has announced her endorsement for Donald Trump for President in the 2024 election. Goodwin said, “Republicans, Democrats and every in-between knows Joe Biden’s presidency has been a complete and utter disaster. I saw it first-hand on your visit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 5.7.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118468</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/morning-conversation-5-7-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-5-7-24"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Public Transportation District General Manager Cheryl Cheas talks about upcoming changes in routes, ride costs and more:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg man denied release in murder case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ccbc5990-0c08-11ef-99d4-bb56fe37d1e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-man-denied-release-in-murder-case/article_ccbc5990-0c08-11ef-99d4-bb56fe37d1e8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After hours of testimony and debate, Gauge Douglas James Main was not granted release in his alleged murder case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riddle City Councils asks DCSO about contract]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/792abcc2-0c08-11ef-8679-8784da7f0cd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/riddle-city-councils-asks-dcso-about-contract/article_792abcc2-0c08-11ef-8679-8784da7f0cd4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE — Douglas County Sheriff’s Office Sgt. Dan Schwenn, Sheriff John Hanlin and Undersheriff Jeff Frieze answered Riddle City Council’s questions regarding its contract Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Gardeners hold Plant Expo]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/921a1b4c-0bf4-11ef-ad0f-37e76bdc0208</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/master-gardeners-hold-plant-expo/article_921a1b4c-0bf4-11ef-ad0f-37e76bdc0208.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plants, flowers and everything you may need for a garden was available at the Douglas County Master Gardeners’ 37th annual Plant Expo on Saturday in the exhibit hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Movies in the Park returns in June]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e2b035c0-0bcf-11ef-bc9e-9746dd158677</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/movies-in-the-park-returns-in-june/article_e2b035c0-0bcf-11ef-bc9e-9746dd158677.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Movies in the Park returns in June to the Nichols Band Shell in Stewart Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA VALLEY TO SEE RAPID RAMP UP IN TEMPERATURES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118460</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/umpqua-valley-to-see-rapid-ramp-up-in-temperatures/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-valley-to-see-rapid-ramp-up-in-temperatures"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T11:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 4:10 a.m. The Umpqua Valley will see a rapid ramp up in high temperatures later this week, with near record high conditions possible by Saturday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that high pressure will begin increasing Wednesday and is expected to peak on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BALLOTS COMING IN FOR THE 2024 MAY PRIMARY ELECTION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118458</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/ballots-coming-in-for-the-2024-may-primary-election/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ballots-coming-in-for-the-2024-may-primary-election"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 3:40 a.m.   Ballots for the 2024 Douglas County May Primary Election went out last week and are beginning to be returned to the Office of the County Clerk. Clerk Daniel Loomis has some reminders for voters: *Ballots must be cast no later than 8:00 p.m. on May 21st *Voters can use the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALMON HARBOR SETS SIGHTS ON NEWS MASTER PLAN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118455</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/salmon-harbor-sets-sights-on-news-master-plan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=salmon-harbor-sets-sights-on-news-master-plan"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 3:30 a.m.  Douglas County Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman, and Tom Kress along with Salmon Harbor Director James Zimmer and staff at Salmon Harbor Marina, have announced that they have started development of a new master plan exclusively for Salmon Harbor Marina and the Waterfront. A County release said master plans provide...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST HAS VOLUNTEER OPPORTUNITIES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118453</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/umpqua-national-forest-has-volunteer-opportunities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-national-forest-has-volunteer-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 3:20 a.m. There are volunteer opportunities in the Umpqua National Forest this month. A UNF release said volunteers play a crucial role in maintaining the delicate balance of the ecosystem. That includes working to protect sensitive areas, reduce environmental impact and promote responsible outdoor recreation. The release said volunteers provide an opportunity...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADAPT ANNUAL CLOSURE NOTICE FOR MEMORIAL DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118451</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/adapt-annual-closure-notice-for-memorial-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=adapt-annual-closure-notice-for-memorial-day"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 3:05 a.m. Adapt Integrated Health Care will be closed for services May 27th for Memorial Day. An Adapt release said this is for all non-crisis, non-residential services and sites in Douglas, Coos, Curry, and Josephine counties. This will be a full-day closure with services resuming on May 28th. 24/7 Crisis Support Services...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC STUDENT ART EXHIBITION OPENS MAY 13TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118448</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/07/ucc-student-art-exhibition-opens-may-13th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-student-art-exhibition-opens-may-13th"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 7, 2024 2:50 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Art Gallery at Umpqua Community College presents the annual Student Art Exhibition, “On the Rise” on display from May 13th through June 5th. A UCC release said a reception will take place on Thursday, May 16th from 12:00 p.m. to 1:00 p.m. Visual fine...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE EIGHT FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING FRIDAY-SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118446</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/roseburg-police-cite-eight-for-prohibited-camping-friday-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-eight-for-prohibited-camping-friday-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 3:45 p.m.  Roseburg Police cited eight people for prohibited camping between Friday and Sunday including one man was cited twice. An RPD report said citations took place in the 400 block of Southeast Stephens Street, the 700 block of Southeast Stephens Street, the 1400 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway, the 1000 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CITED AFTER DUII CRASH EARLY SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118444</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/roseburg-man-cited-after-duii-crash-early-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-cited-after-duii-crash-early-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 2:45 p.m.  Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office cited and released a Roseburg man for DUII and reckless driving after an accident early Sunday. A DCSO report said at 1:30 a.m. the 19-year-old was reported to have been in a single vehicle, single occupant accident on Colonial Road near the intersection...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITED THREE, AND JAIL ONE FOR DUII INCIDENTS OVER THE WEEKEND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118437</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/roseburg-police-cited-three-and-jail-one-for-duii-incidents-over-the-weekend/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cited-three-and-jail-one-for-duii-incidents-over-the-weekend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 11:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited three people and jailed one for DUII incidents between early Saturday and early Sunday. An RPD report said officers contacted a 25-year-old Sutherlin woman after observing several traffic violations just after 12:40 a.m. Saturday in the 1400 block of Northeast Stephens Street. During the contact with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hike scheduled May 11]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/401e2904-097a-11ef-b965-9fef69f4e051</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/hike-scheduled-may-11/article_401e2904-097a-11ef-b965-9fef69f4e051.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Friends of the Umpqua Hiking Club hike is scheduled for May 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118435</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-theft-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-theft-2"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 11:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged theft incident on Sunday. An RPD report said at 6;00 pm. officers responded to the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway after a caller said a woman had been shoplifting. Officers learned the female had left the area on foot. She was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE MAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118435</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/roseburg-police-mail-woman-for-alleged-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-mail-woman-for-alleged-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 11:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged theft incident on Sunday. An RPD report said at 6;00 pm. officers responded to the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway after a caller said a woman had been shoplifting. Officers learned the female had left the area on foot. She was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118433</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 10:50 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a reported disorderly conduct incident on Saturday night. An RPD report said at 8:20 p.m. officers responded to the 1100 block of Northeast Stephens Street after a caller said a man was running into traffic. Officers found the 55-year-old in the bus stop at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walk and Roll to school on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bb030984-0bd0-11ef-819f-4393a2883312</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/walk-and-roll-to-school-on-wednesday/article_bb030984-0bd0-11ef-819f-4393a2883312.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Four schools in the Roseburg school district and one school in north county are participating in Walk and Roll to School Day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED ASSAULT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118431</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-assault-incident-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-assault-incident-3"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 10:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged assault incident on Friday night. An RPD report said just after 7:40 p.m. officers responded to a disturbance between a 38-year-old man and a victim in the 1600 block of Southeast Cobb Street. During the disturbance, the suspect reportedly threw a shovel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSP RESPONDS TO VEHICLE DOWN AN EMBANKMENT ACCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118429</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/osp-responds-to-vehicle-down-an-embankment-accident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=osp-responds-to-vehicle-down-an-embankment-accident"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Troopers with Oregon State Police responded after a vehicle left Highway 138 East, a few miles east of Steamboat on Saturday night. An OSP report said just after 9:30 p.m. a westbound pickup hit a boulder which was in the lane of travel. The 30-year-old driver from Ridgefield, Washington lost...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamilton, Bartram named Sutherlin's Citizens of the Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b0da67c2-0bbc-11ef-bd7a-8fad118a7a16</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/hamilton-bartram-named-sutherlins-citizens-of-the-year/article_b0da67c2-0bbc-11ef-bd7a-8fad118a7a16.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debbie Hamilton and Dan Bartram were named Sutherlin's woman and man of 2023 at Sunday's 68th annual First Citizen Banquet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EARLY MONDAY CRASH ON INTERSTATE FIVE NORTHBOUND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118427</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/early-monday-crash-on-interstate-five-northbound/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=early-monday-crash-on-interstate-five-northbound"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Troopers from the Oregon State Police responded to a single vehicle accident on Interstate 5 early Monday. An OSP report said just after 2:00 a.m. a sedan was headed northbound near the Scotts Valley/Elk Creek interchange when the 27-year-old driver from Federal Way, Washington, said he hit an alternator that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 5.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118423</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/morning-conversation-5-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-5-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saving Grace Pet Adoption Center Executive Director Jennifer Barta talks about the Empty the Shelter event underway, and about Barks and Recreation happening later this month:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media Advisory Only: 2024 media access to natural disasters training now available]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news172049</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news172049"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T15:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual training required for journalists to gain unescorted access natural disaster scenes is now available. The free, one-hour online training course is provided by the Oregon Department of Forestry. Training credentials need to be renewed every year by completing the training. 
New for this year: Training credentials will be generated automatically after passing the quiz at the end of the course and available immediately. Journalists are encouraged to print two copies of their credentials—one to display in their vehicle and another to keep in their wallet—and to save an electronic copy to their phone or computer, just in case.
House Bill 4087 (2022) granted journalists access to certain natural disaster scenes even if a public safety organization escort is unavailable. The bill’s access provisions apply specifically to natural disaster scenes on non-federal public lands that are also closed to the public due to the disaster. The HB 4087 guidelines created by a joint committee of public safety and media representatives provide additional important information including personal protective equipment requirements and circumstances when access may be denied.
For more information about HB 4087 and media access to natural disasters in Oregon, check out these resources from the Safe Media Access to Disaster Sites Committee and the Oregon Chapter of the Society of Professional Journalists. 
If you have problems accessing the training or questions about media access, contact Joy Krawczyk, ODF’s Public Affairs Director, at joy.p.krawczyk@odf.oregon.gov or April Ehrlich with OPB at aehrlich@opb.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Family Fair: Bringing entertainment, joy to Jerry Bruce Community Campus]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/062c24f6-0bbb-11ef-af01-63c87586dd86</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/spring-family-fair-bringing-entertainment-joy-to-jerry-bruce-community-campus/article_062c24f6-0bbb-11ef-af01-63c87586dd86.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Families and nonprofit organizations came together for a day of fun Saturday at the Spring Family Fair on the Jerry Bruce Community Campus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY COUNTY PLANNING COMMISSIONS MEETING ON LAND SWAP PROPOSAL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118416</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/city-county-planning-commissions-meeting-on-land-swap-proposal/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-county-planning-commissions-meeting-on-land-swap-proposal"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 3:40 a.m. The City of Roseburg Planning Commission and the Douglas County Planning Commission will have a joint meeting Monday night at 6:00 p.m. to discuss a proposed urban growth boundary swap. The meeting will be held in the city’s council chambers on Southeast Douglas Avenue. A City release said Roseburg seeks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODOT CONTINUES EXIT 125 NORTHBOUND OFF-RAMP PROJECT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118414</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/odot-continues-exit-125-northbound-off-ramp-project/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=odot-continues-exit-125-northbound-off-ramp-project"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 3:30 a.m.  A contractor for the Oregon Department of Transportation is continuing work on the Exit 125 Northbound Off-Ramp project at Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. To improve safety and ease congestion at Exit 125, a dedicated right-turn lane is being added to the northbound off-ramp. The project will also replace the traffic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UHI INVESTS OVERALL $500,000 IN 31 LOCAL HEALTH IMPROVEMENT PROGRAMS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118412</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/uhi-invests-overall-500000-in-31-local-health-improvement-programs/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uhi-invests-overall-500000-in-31-local-health-improvement-programs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 3:20 a.m. Umpqua Health Alliance committed over $500,00 to 31 different Community Health Improvement Programs in Douglas County in 2024. UHI Chief Executive Officer Brent Eichman said, “Umpqua Health Alliance is committed to investing in programs and services that make a real impact on the health and well- being of our members...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACCOUNTING FIRM ANNOUNCES NEW PARTNER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118409</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/accounting-firm-announces-new-partner/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=accounting-firm-announces-new-partner"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 3:05 a.m. In the KQEN Business Spotlight: Wicks Emmett Certified Public Accountants in Roseburg has announced that Erica Aitken is now a partner in the firm. A company release said, “Erica has been an integral part of Wicks Emmett for quite some time, consistently providing a deep commitment to our clients and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WALK AND ROLL TO SCHOOL ON WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=118407</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/05/06/walk-and-roll-to-school-on-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=walk-and-roll-to-school-on-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 6, 2024 2:50 a.m. Four schools in the Roseburg School District and one school in north county are participating in Walk and Roll to School Day later this week. A Douglas Education Service District release said Oregon Safe Routes to School promotes the event as a way to enhance the health of families through...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>