<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-03-05T19:08:04.655Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rulemaking advisory committee on update to statewide wildfire hazard map meeting series starting March 7 via Zoom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170462</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170462"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T19:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore.—A series of three meetings of a rulemaking advisory committee on updating the statewide wildfire hazard map have been scheduled. 
The committee’s focus will be to provide input on whether irrigation for farmland and agricultural crops might be incorporated into the calculations for wildfire hazard assessments. 
The first meeting is set for Thursday, March 7 from 9 a.m.–noon via Zoom. Two additional meetings are scheduled for March 28 and April 18—also from 9 a.m.–noon. All meetings will be held virtually and are open to the public.
Anyone can access the Zoom meeting at the following link: https://odf.zoom.us/j/8829567607?omn=94409353162. A post-meeting recording will be posted on the ODF YouTube channel at https://www.youtube.com/c/oregondepartmentofforestry. For special accomm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WYDEN MAKES STATEMENT ON NEW CONCESSIONAIRE CONTRACT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116399</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/wyden-makes-statement-on-new-concessionaire-contract/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wyden-makes-statement-on-new-concessionaire-contract"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T18:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 10:50 a.m.   On Monday, Senator Ron Wyden released a statement after the National Park Service announced Aramark’s concessionaire contract to manage Crater Lake National Park is in the process of being transferred to a new operator. Wyden said, “I want to thank National Park Service Director Chuck Sams for his leadership and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING THROUGH 4:00 P.M. TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116396</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/winter-storm-warning-through-400-p-m-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-through-400-p-m-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T18:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 10:30 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect until 4:00 p.m. Tuesday above 1,500 feet in central Douglas County and its eastern foothills. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said wet snow is expected with additional snow accumulations of 1 to 3 inches. This includes the passes on Interstate 5, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[26-YEAR OLD WOMAN HOSPITALIZED AFTER INJURY CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116394</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/26-year-old-woman-hospitalized-after-injury-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=26-year-old-woman-hospitalized-after-injury-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T18:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 10:20 a.m.  A 26-year-old woman was hospitalized after a single-vehicle crash on Monday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 9:30 p.m. a deputy was dispatched to the accident in the 11000 block of Garden Valley Road, west of Roseburg. The female was being transported to CHI Mercy Medical Center...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DUII ALCOHOL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116390</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-duii-alcohol-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-duii-alcohol-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T18:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for driving under the influence of intoxicants-alcohol on Monday night. An RPD report said at 8:15 p.m. an officer conducted a traffic stop after observing a traffic violation near the intersection of Northeast Airport Road and Northeast Stewart Parkway. The driver was identified as a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER OVERNIGHT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116388</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/roseburg-police-jail-man-after-overnight-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-after-overnight-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T17:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 6, 2024 9:50 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed man after an overnight incident early Tuesday. An RPD report said at 2:20 a.m. officers responded to Micelli Park in the 1400 block of Southeast Micelli Street after a caller said a woman was screaming in that area. The 61-year-old was taken into custody on RPD warrants....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN AFTER INVESTIGATION OF SUSPICIOUS PEOPLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116386</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/roseburg-police-jail-woman-after-investigation-of-suspicious-people/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-after-investigation-of-suspicious-people"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T17:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a warrant after an incident on Monday night. An RPD report said just before 7:30 p.m. officers were dispatched to the 2000 block of Northeast Stephens Street after a caller said a group of suspicious people were at that location. During the contact, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116384</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-3"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T17:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for warrants after contacted him on Monday. An RPD report said at 2:00 p.m. officers conducted a traffic stop on a sedan for numerous traffic violations in the 1300 block of West Harvard Avenue. The 43-year-old driver had two warrants for his arrest and was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED FRAUD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116382</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-fraud/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-fraud"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T17:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 9:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged fraud incident on Monday afternoon. An RPD report said the 43-year-old was developed as a suspect in a fraud case last month and officers located him at 4:00 p.m. in the 1300 block of West Harvard Avenue. He admitted to using a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter wonderland: Douglas County covered in snow]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6f8acff4-db02-11ee-b64b-f7da1b6cb144</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/winter-wonderland-douglas-county-covered-in-snow/article_6f8acff4-db02-11ee-b64b-f7da1b6cb144.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A blanket of snow covered Douglas County on Tuesday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Tennis Center hosts open house with Thrive Umpqua]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/569910dc-d72e-11ee-9217-0bc0b56113c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/umpqua-valley-tennis-center-hosts-open-house-with-thrive-umpqua/article_569910dc-d72e-11ee-9217-0bc0b56113c6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From 10 a.m. to 2 p.m. on Saturday the public is invited to drop in for the Umpqua Valley Tennis Center's Open House in partnership with Thrive Umpqua.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHANGES FOR TUESDAY DUE TO WEATHER CONDITIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116363</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/changes-for-tuesday-due-to-weather-conditions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=changes-for-tuesday-due-to-weather-conditions"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 4:00 a.m. Winter weather in some areas is leading to some changes for Tuesday morning. *Camas Valley Charter School is on a two-hour delay. Pre-school is canceled. Listen to News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN and check www.541radio.com to stay connected with updated storm impact information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY/WINTER STORM WARNING FOR TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116361</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 4:00 a.m. A Winter Weather Advisory is in effect through 10:00 a.m. Tuesday above 500 feet with a Winter Storm Warning in place until 4:00 p.m. Tuesday above 1,500 feet. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said for the Advisory, wet snow is expected above 500 feet with accumulations of up to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING THROUGH 4:00 P.M. TUESDAY IN MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116358</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/winter-storm-warning-through-400-p-m-tuesday-in-mountain-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-through-400-p-m-tuesday-in-mountain-areas"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 3:50 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect through 4:00 pm. Tuesday in mountain areas of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected. Total snow accumulations of 4 to 12 inches above 3,000 feet in the Douglas County foothills and between 20 and 28 inches...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVIVA HEALTH TO OPEN NEW SUTHERLIN CLINIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116355</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/aviva-health-to-open-new-sutherlin-clinic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=aviva-health-to-open-new-sutherlin-clinic"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 3:40 a.m. Avivia Health is opening its new Sutherlin Clinic, at 775 Taylor Street on Monday, April 1st. An Aviva release said the non-profit Federally Qualified Health Center’s previous Sutherlin office was just north of the Apple Peddler Restaurant on Ponderosa Drive. Last year the clinic building that Aviva was leasing was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHAMBER ORCHESTRA/CONCERT CHOIR PERFORMING TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116353</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/chamber-orchestra-concert-choir-performing-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=chamber-orchestra-concert-choir-performing-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 3:30 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Umpqua Community College Fine and Performing Arts Department presents the Umpqua Chamber Orchestra and UCC Chamber Choir, under the direction of Dr. Jason Heald, in concert Tuesday night at 7:00 p.m. at First Presbyterian Church in Roseburg. The concert will feature music spanning four...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GLENDALE WOMAN ARRESTED FOR REPORTED ASSAULT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116350</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/glendale-woman-arrested-for-reported-assault/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=glendale-woman-arrested-for-reported-assault"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 3:20 a.m. A Glendale Woman was arrested for a reported assault incident early Monday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 1:00 a.m. deputies responded after a caller said there had been an incident at an apartment complex in the 500 block of Pacific Avenue in Glendale. Upon arrival deputies...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOUR PEOPLE TAKEN TO HOSPITAL AFTER HEAD-ON COLLISION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116347</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/four-people-taken-to-hospital-after-head-on-collision/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=four-people-taken-to-hospital-after-head-on-collision"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 3:10 a.m. Four people were taken to the hospital after a head-on collision on Friday afternoon. An Oregon State Police report said at 4:40 p.m. troopers responded to the crash on Highway 42, about five miles west of Camas Valley. The driver of a sedan was heading east when he lost traction...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BENTZ URGES WSDOT TO RECONSIDER DAM BREACHING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116345</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/05/bentz-urges-wsdot-to-reconsider-dam-breaching/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=bentz-urges-wsdot-to-reconsider-dam-breaching"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 5, 2024 3:00 a.m. Congressman Cliff has joined a group of Pacific Northwest colleagues in raising concerns with Washington State Department of Transportation Secretary Roger Millar regarding the economic fallout of breaching the lower Snake River dams. Bentz said, “This scheme by WSDOT and the Biden Administration is a direct attack on clean energy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDLEYLD PARK MAN JAILED AFTER MONTHS LONG INVESTIGATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116343</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/idleyld-park-man-jailed-after-months-long-investigation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=idleyld-park-man-jailed-after-months-long-investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T00:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 4:00 p.m.  On Friday, detectives with the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team wrapped up a month’s long investigation that began in early December by arresting an Idleyld Park man on 16 charges. Captain Kurt Sorenson said the investigation focused on the alleged sale of methamphetamine by 40-year-old Kyle Vatland. McArthur said over the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DINT Meth Arrest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6255#news170439</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6255#news170439"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T23:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, March 1st, 2024, detectives with the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT) wrapped up a months long investigation that began in early December.  
 
The investigation focused on the alleged sales of methamphetamine by 40 year old Kyle Vatland, of Idleyld Park.  Over the course of the investigation detectives were able to generate evidence of multiple sales of methamphetamine by Vatland, all occurring at various locations in the Glide area.  
 
On Friday, March 1st, detectives concluded the investigation by arresting Vatland during a traffic stop in the 20,000 block of N. Umpqua Hwy in Glide, with the help of a deputy from the Douglas County Sheriff's Office.  Vatland was taken into custody without incident and detectives immediately executed a search warrant on Vatland's vehi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE DEAL WITH FOUR DUII INCIDENTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116341</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/roseburg-police-deal-with-four-duii-incidents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-deal-with-four-duii-incidents"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T22:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 2:45 p.m. Roseburg Police dealt with four DUII incidents between early Friday and early Sunday. Information from RPD said Friday just after 12:20 a.m. officers contacted a 55-year-old man in the 200 block of Southeast Jackson Street during a traffic stop and noticed signs of impairment. The man consented to standard field...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four people transported to hospital following crash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/83883cca-da68-11ee-9e72-17e5fdd7f59a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/four-people-transported-to-hospital-following-crash/article_83883cca-da68-11ee-9e72-17e5fdd7f59a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T20:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMAS VALLEY — Oregon State Police officers responded to an injury crash around 4:40 p.m. Friday on Highway 42, near milepost 51 about five miles west of Camas Valley, which resulted in the highway to be closed briefly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New royalty: Audrey Van Houten and Kendyl-Rae Bartz win titles at Miss Douglas County and Miss Douglas County Outstanding Teen Competition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9bf735ea-da40-11ee-8d38-0fcf4f7a9a10</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/new-royalty-audrey-van-houten-and-kendyl-rae-bartz-win-titles-at-miss-douglas-county/article_9bf735ea-da40-11ee-8d38-0fcf4f7a9a10.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — Audrey Van Houten had just been crowned the new Miss Douglas County when her sister came across the stage to give her a hug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas Electric hosts annual meeting]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/22ee15f6-da5e-11ee-b9f1-1327443e8e78</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/douglas-electric-hosts-annual-meeting/article_22ee15f6-da5e-11ee-b9f1-1327443e8e78.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T19:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Douglas Electric Cooperative is hosting its annual meeting April 6 at the Community Conference Hall of the Douglas County Fairgrounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CHARGE MAN WITH RESTRAINING ORDER VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116339</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/roseburg-police-charge-man-with-restraining-order-violation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-charge-man-with-restraining-order-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:49:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Police charged a man with a restraining order violation on Friday. An RPD report said the 43-year-old was contacted at 8:00 a.m. while he was already in jail on another matter. The suspect was a respondent in a restraining order with the victim being the petitioner. The man had allegedly written the victim a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED AFTER REPORTED BATHROOM TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116337</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/roseburg-man-jailed-after-reported-bathroom-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-after-reported-bathroom-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 10:40 a.m.  A Roseburg man was jailed by Roseburg Police after a reported trespass incident on Sunday. An RPD report said at 2:30 p.m. a business in the 1500 block of Northeast Stephens Street said a man had been in the store’s bathroom for over an hour. Officers contacted the 63-year-old, who...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116335</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-20/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-20"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged trespass incident on Sunday afternoon. An RPD report said at approximately 3:20 p.m. officers were dispatched to the Roseburg Regional Airport on Northwest Aviation Drive after a caller said a man was climbing the barbed wire fence. Officers contacted the 37-year-old who...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116333</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-9/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-9"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for alleged harassment on Saturday evening. An RPD report said just before 5:30 p.m. officers responded to CHI Mercy Medical Center on Northwest Stewart Parkway regarding a man that was allegedly attacking an employee. Officers contacted the 31-year-old who said he punched the victim because...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HITT RETIRES AS CITY RECORDER FOLLOWING CAREER IN PUBLIC SERVICE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116330</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/hitt-retires-as-city-recorder-following-career-in-public-service/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hitt-retires-as-city-recorder-following-career-in-public-service"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 9:50 a.m.  On Thursday, Roseburg City Recorder Patty Hitt retired following a year of working for the city. City Manager Nikki Messenger said, “The entire management team has really enjoyed working with Patty. Even though she was only here a short time, she has a lot of great experience and was able...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSBORNE SAID DRUG RECRIMINALIZATION BILL IS NOT ENOUGH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116328</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/osborne-said-drug-recriminalization-bill-is-not-enough/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=osborne-said-drug-recriminalization-bill-is-not-enough"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T17:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 9:30 a.m.   State Representative Virgile Osborne said HB 4002 is a step in the right direction, but it is not enough. Last week, the Oregon State Legislature, with a bipartisan vote, passed the legislation out of both chambers. Osborne said it was a noteworthy rollback of Measure 110, recriminalizing the possession of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County bridge replacements and fairgrounds improvements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/5d840480-d81c-11ee-bf14-3f37dd19d109</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/douglas_county/douglas-county-bridge-replacements-and-fairgrounds-improvements/article_5d840480-d81c-11ee-bf14-3f37dd19d109.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County had a busy 2023 improving infrastructure around the county. While traffic has been impacted by various bridge replacement projects, Douglas County Fairgrounds have received some needed improvements to allow for more events year round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHANGES FOR MONDAY DUE TO WEATHER CONDITIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116316</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/changes-for-monday-due-to-weather-conditions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=changes-for-monday-due-to-weather-conditions"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 4:00 a.m. Wintry weather conditions in some areas are leading to a few changes for Monday. *Camas Valley Charter School is on a two-hour delay. Pre-school is canceled. *Winston-Dillard School District has morning buses on snow routes. Routes 15 and 18 will be on snow routes while Route 20 Bryson Creek students...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING ABOVE 1800 FEET IN CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116314</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/winter-storm-warning-above-1800-feet-in-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-above-1800-feet-in-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:55 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning is in effect through 4:00 p.m. Tuesday above 1,800 feet for central Douglas County and its eastern foothills. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected with accumulations of 2 to 6 inches with up to 12 inches above 3,000 feet in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNINGS FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS OF SOUTHERN OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116311</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/winter-storm-warnings-for-mountain-areas-of-southern-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warnings-for-mountain-areas-of-southern-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:45 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning is in effect through 4:00 p.m. Tuesday for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected with accumulations of 20 to 30 inches. The Warning area is for the south-central Oregon Cascades including Crater Lake, Diamond...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR REPORTED DISORDERLY CONDUCT/MISUSE OF 911]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116309</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/winston-police-jail-woman-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-misuse-of-911/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-police-jail-woman-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-misuse-of-911"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:40 a.m. Winston Police jailed a woman for a reportedly disorderly conduct incident early Sunday. Sergeant Mike Miller said at about 3:20 a.m. 45-year-old Angela Osburn allegedly called 911. Miller said Osburn reportedly rambled and yelled at dispatchers with no emergency. When officers responded to her residence, she allegedly acted in a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K9 EROS TRACKS DOWN STOLEN VEHICLE SUSPECT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116306</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/k9-eros-tracks-down-stolen-vehicle-suspect/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=k9-eros-tracks-down-stolen-vehicle-suspect"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:30 a.m. Douglas County Sheriff’s Office K9 Eros tracked down a stolen vehicle suspect on Friday. Information from DCSO and the Sutherlin Police Department said officers located a stolen vehicle being driven in the 1000 block of West Central Avenue near Ponderosa Drive shortly after 2:30 p.m. The suspect failed to stop...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON CITY COUNCIL WILL NOT MEET MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116304</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/winston-city-council-will-not-meet-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-city-council-will-not-meet-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:20 a.m. Due to a lack of agenda items, Winston City Council will not meet Monday evening. City Recorder Cindy Sarti said the next scheduled meeting is March 18th at 7:00 p.m. For more information about the City of Winston, go to: www.winstoncity.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS HALL HETS NEW ROOF/HVAC SYSTEM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116301</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/douglas-hall-hets-new-roof-hvac-system/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-hall-hets-new-roof-hvac-system"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:05 a.m.  Douglas County Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman and Tom Kress have announced that work has officially been completed on the roof replacement and new HVAC system project on Douglas Hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds. A County release said the project began in 2023 and took about nine months to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGON SENATE RECRIMINALIZES HARD DRUGS IN HISTORIC VOTE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116299</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/oregon-senate-recriminalizes-hard-drugs-in-historic-vote/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregon-senate-recriminalizes-hard-drugs-in-historic-vote"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 2:50 a.m. On Friday, the Oregon Senate voted to turn the page on Oregon’s drug decriminalization experiment by passing HB 4002. A release from the Senate Republican Caucus said the bipartisan proposal will give law enforcement, district attorneys, and local government leaders many of the tools they need to get people off...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANTA ROSA MAN RESCUED BY SAR AFTER FOLLOWING GPS DIRECTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116294</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/03/santa-rosa-man-rescued-by-sar-after-following-gps-directions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=santa-rosa-man-rescued-by-sar-after-following-gps-directions"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T22:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 3, 2024 2:00 p.m.   A Santa Rosa, California man was rescued by Douglas County Search and Rescue after he followed Global Positioning System directions when he encountered a weather- related delay on Interstate 5. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said on Saturday just after 12:00 a.m. 911 dispatchers received a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man rescued after getting stuck in snow, while following GPS]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c1cb7e64-d993-11ee-904e-7b3704e2dc8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/man-rescued-after-getting-stuck-in-snow-while-following-gps/article_c1cb7e64-d993-11ee-904e-7b3704e2dc8f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AZALEA — A 34-year-old man was rescued by Douglas County Search and Rescue after he got stuck in the snow following his GPS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santa Rosa Man Rescued by SAR After Following GPS to Avoid Travel Delays (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170408</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170408"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T18:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AZALEA, Ore. - On March 2, 2024, shortly after midnight, Douglas County 9-1-1 received a text-to-911 from an individual stating he had gotten stuck in snow after following his GPS and was in need of assistance.
Deputies learned 34-year-old Juan Carlos Torres-Esquivel of Santa Rosa, California had purchased a 1996 Ford F150 in Corvallis and was enroute to his residence in Santa Rosa when he encountered weather related delays on I-5. Google maps recommended a detour which he selected that instructed him to take exit 88, drive east on Upper Cow Creek for approximately 13 miles, and turn south onto Snow Creek Rd.
Torres-Esquivel made it approximately 5 miles up Snow Creek Road before sliding the passenger side of the vehicle into a deep ditch and getting the vehicle stuck in approximately 24" of snow. He was unprepared for the conditions and was unsuccessful in attempting to dig the vehicle out without a shovel.
Douglas County Search and Rescue was activated and responded to assist. SAR responded and was unable to make it to his location with the Snowcat due to a U-Haul truck being abandoned approximately 2 or 3 miles up Snow Creek Rd in the middle of the roadway. Members of the 4x4 team were able to maneuver around the U-Haul after airing down their tires and retrieved Torres-Esquivel.
Deputies provided Torres-Esquivel a courtesy ride to Seven Feathers.
The Sheriff's Office would like to remind drivers of the dangers of blindly following GPS devices.
"GPS devices are often set to direct drivers through the fastest route to their destination. Oftentimes, this means direction through non-maintained road systems, including forest roads," Lt. Brad O'Dell said. "Blindly following GPS navigation can potentially lead to dangerous situations and have serious consequences. Although travel delays can be disruptive, it is best to remain on routes that are maintained."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY/WINTER STORM WARNING FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116292</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/03/winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T14:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March, 2024 6:40 a.m. A Winter Weather Advisory remains in effect until Sunday evening at 10:00 p.m. above 1,500 feet with a Winter Storm Warning from 10:00 a.m. Monday through 4:00 p.m. Tuesday for central Douglas County and its eastern foothills above 1,800 feet. For the Advisory, an additional 3 to 7 inches of snow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY/WINTER STORM WARNING FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116289</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/03/winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-mountain-areas-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-mountain-areas-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T14:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 3, 2024 6:20 a.m.  A Winter Weather Advisory remains in effect through Sunday evening at 10:00 p.m. with a Winter Storm Warning from 10:00 a.m. Monday through 4:00 p.m. Tuesday for mountain areas of southern Oregon. For the Advisory, an additional 4 to 9 inches of snow is expected. Winds will gust as high...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homes and gardens need upgrades, too]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/099a65b6-d8ef-11ee-b402-771fd10f312e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/homes-and-gardens-need-upgrades-too/article_099a65b6-d8ef-11ee-b402-771fd10f312e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For homeowners wondering about how to modernize their carpets or which massage chair is the best to buy, the Home & Garden Show was the perfect weekend activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merkley fields questions about the Winchester Dam, mental health in town hall]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/70fff4f4-d913-11ee-bd90-1788db7cc549</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/merkley-fields-questions-about-the-winchester-dam-mental-health-in-town-hall/article_70fff4f4-d913-11ee-bd90-1788db7cc549.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley braved the weather to appear in Douglas County for his first town hall of the year Saturday night at the Southern Oregon Wine Institute at Umpqua Community College.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K-9 Eros tracks down suspect]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8f463bf0-d8da-11ee-a352-7f809482119d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/k-9-eros-tracks-down-suspect/article_8f463bf0-d8da-11ee-a352-7f809482119d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — A Roseburg man was arrested Friday with the assistance of Douglas County Sheriff’s Office K-9 Officer Eros.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K-9 Eros tracks down suspect]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8f463bf0-d8da-11ee-a352-7f809482119d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/k-9-eros-tracks-down-suspect/article_8f463bf0-d8da-11ee-a352-7f809482119d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — A Roseburg man was arrested Friday with the assistance of Douglas County Sheriff's Office K-9 Officer Eros.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marriages: Feb. 19-23]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2ad2436a-d4e5-11ee-b870-573fe5d90e62</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/marriages-feb-19-23/article_2ad2436a-d4e5-11ee-b870-573fe5d90e62.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T20:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas County Clerk’s Office issued these licenses Feb. 19-23]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K9 Eros Tracks Down Stolen Vehicle Elude Suspect (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170404</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170404"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T20:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND, Ore. - On Friday, March 1, 2024, shortly after 2:30 p.m., Sutherlin Police Department attempted to stop a stolen 2017 Nissan Rogue on W. Central Avenue near Ponderosa Drive in Sutherlin. The suspect failed to stop and attempted to elude officers in the stolen vehicle.
The suspect crashed and fled on foot in the 600-block of Fawn Ridge Drive in Oakland. A perimeter was established and a Sheriff’s Office K9 was requested to respond to the scene.
K9 Eros responded and began to track the suspect from his last known location. During the track, Eros located clothing that had been worn by the suspect. K9 Eros eventually lead officers to a red pump house indicating the suspect was inside. Deputies began giving announcements that the suspect had been located by the K9 and should surrender. The suspect, 50-year-old Kevin Wade Davison of Roseburg, opened the door to the pump house and gave up without further incident.
Davison was taken into custody and lodged at the Douglas County Jail by Sutherlin Police Officers on their case.
K9 Eros, a 4.5-year-old German Shepherd, has been with the Douglas County Sheriff's Office since November 2021. He was purchased by an anonymous donor in the community and gifted to the agency. The Sheriff's Office K9 program, consisting of three Patrol K9 teams and 1 narcotics K9 team, is supported financially by private donations and the Friends of Umpqua Valley Police K9 Programs, a non-profit organization whose mission is to support local police K9 teams. Bailey's Veterinary Clinic provides medical care and some food for the Sheriff's Office K9 program while Coastal Farm and Home Supply provides all other food. The agency’s current K9 program has been highly active since 2013.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bailey discusses prescribed fire burns in fire management presentation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/708af21a-d794-11ee-9785-d34724342ff3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/bailey-discusses-prescribed-fire-burns-in-fire-management-presentation/article_708af21a-d794-11ee-9785-d34724342ff3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — Fire and what fuels them was the hot topic Thursday night when John Bailey gave a presentation on fire management to about 50-70 people sitting in Umpqua Community College's Jacoby Auditorium.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116287</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/winter-weather-advisory-for-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-for-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T18:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 10:20 a.m.  A Winter Weather Advisory is in effect until 10:00 a.m. Sunday above 2,000 feet for central Douglas County. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said additional accumulations of 3 to 6 inches are expected. The Advisory area includes Canyon Creek Pass on Interstate 5. Up to 1 inch of snow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116284</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/winter-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas-16/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas-16"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T18:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 10:00 a.m.  A Winter Weather Advisory is in effect through 10:00 p.m. Sunday for mountain areas in southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said additional accumulations of 6 to 10 inches of snow are expected. Winds will gust up to 30 miles per hour over exposed terrain. The Advisory area...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRAFFIC CRASH CLAIMS LIFE OF RIDDLE TEEN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116282</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/traffic-crash-claims-life-of-riddle-teen/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=traffic-crash-claims-life-of-riddle-teen"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T17:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 9:30 a.m.  A Riddle teenager died Friday evening in a single vehicle crash. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at approximately 10:30 p.m. dispatchers received a report of the wreck in the 15000 block of North Myrtle Road in the Myrtle Creek area. O’Dell said deputies arrived on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riddle teen dies in crash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6d8185b2-d8ba-11ee-866d-afb34d038014</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/riddle-teen-dies-in-crash/article_6d8185b2-d8ba-11ee-866d-afb34d038014.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T17:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — A Riddle teenager died Friday in a single vehicle accident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fatal Traffic Crash Claims Life of Riddle Teen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170401</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170401"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T17:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK, Ore. - A Riddle teenager died Friday evening in a single vehicle crash.
On March 1, 2024, at approximately 10:30 pm, 9-1-1 dispatchers received a report of a single vehicle crash with injuries in the 15000-block of North Myrtle Road in Myrtle Creek.
Deputies arrived on scene to find a 2006 Mazda sedan which had been traveling westbound at a high rate of speed in poor weather conditions. The driver, 17-year-old Brooke Leeann Dubuc of Myrtle Creek, lost control of the vehicle which rolled several times before striking a tree. A passenger, 17-year-old Jonathan Wylie Rosenstiel of Riddle, was ejected from the vehicle and trapped under the car when it came to rest. Rosenstiel was pronounced deceased at the scene by EMS. A second passenger, 19-year-old Canyonville resident Avorie Dunsmore, was able to self-extricate from the vehicle. Both Dubuc and Dunsmore were transported to Mercy Medical Center by Ambulance.
The investigation is ongoing at this time. Anyone with information related to the actions of the individuals involved prior to the crash is asked to contact the Douglas County Sheriff's Office at (541) 440-4471 referencing case #24-1140.
The Sheriff's Office was assisted by the Myrtle Creek Police Department, Douglas County District Attorney's Office, Umpqua Valley Ambulance, Myrtle Creek Fire Department and Joe's Towing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCSO SEEKING SEDAN FOLLOWING REPORTED ELUDE INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116280</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/dcso-seeking-sedan-following-reported-elude-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dcso-seeking-sedan-following-reported-elude-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T17:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 9:00 a.m.  The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office is seeking a sedan following a reported eluding incident early Thursday. A DCSO report said just after 1:20 a.m. a deputy saw the vehicle commit multiple traffic violations in an attempt to get away while traveling southbound on Interstate 5 near Canyonville. The deputy caught...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES JAIL MAN FROM GREEN FOLLOWING ALLEGED DUII INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116278</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/deputies-jail-man-from-green-following-alleged-duii-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-jail-man-from-green-following-alleged-duii-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 8:50 a.m.   Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a man from Green, following an alleged DUII incident Friday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said shortly before 8:50 a.m. the 47-year-old went to a residence in the 2200 block of Castle Street to yell at the homeowner. A deputy arrived...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Searchers find pickup, driver not located]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4386b854-d8b5-11ee-8408-3b6dddb4b18f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/searchers-find-pickup-driver-not-located/article_4386b854-d8b5-11ee-8408-3b6dddb4b18f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — Friday afternoon, searchers located a pickup that crashed into the North Umpqua River east of Glide on Thursday, but the body of the driver was not located.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Christian students celebrate reading]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cb15a024-d80a-11ee-bca0-9759c3aff968</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/umpqua-valley-christian-students-celebrate-reading/article_cb15a024-d80a-11ee-bca0-9759c3aff968.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eggs were flipped, fish were counted and Whos were heard Friday when Umpqua Valley Christian School celebrated National Read Across America Day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New year, new books at Roseburg library]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b04a98ce-d7f8-11ee-8021-3716bfbf8184</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/new-year-new-books-at-roseburg-library/article_b04a98ce-d7f8-11ee-8021-3716bfbf8184.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library regularly adds new books to the collection, including these recently published titles that we recommend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AURORA ROPP AND KRIS WILEY For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Blackberry Festival adds scholarship]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bddd0da6-d6cb-11ee-a2f0-df8679f1e858</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/sutherlin-blackberry-festival-adds-scholarship/article_bddd0da6-d6cb-11ee-a2f0-df8679f1e858.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Blackberry Festival expanded its scholarship program for 2024 and are is introducing a new-this-year Returning/Second Year Student Trades Scholarship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Registration open for 2024 North Douglas dodgeball tournament]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7c831d5a-d680-11ee-b133-27f2a851f101</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/registration-open-for-2024-north-douglas-dodgeball-tournament/article_7c831d5a-d680-11ee-b133-27f2a851f101.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team registration is open until March 11 for the second annual North Douglas Travel Club’s Dodgeball Tournament.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEARCHERS FIND PICKUP BUT DRIVER NOT LOCATED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116275</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/searchers-find-pickup-but-driver-not-located/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=searchers-find-pickup-but-driver-not-located"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T15:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 7:00 a.m. Friday afternoon searchers located a pickup that crashed into the North Umpqua River east of Glide on Thursday, but the body of the driver was not located. Captain Kyle Kennedy of the Oregon State Police said a 1995 GMC pickup, believed to have been operated by 27-year-old Rachel Merchant-Ly was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to parent in a digital world presentation Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c07765c4-d67c-11ee-aeeb-b76e79ac3114</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/how-to-parent-in-a-digital-world-presentation-thursday/article_c07765c4-d67c-11ee-aeeb-b76e79ac3114.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pastor and certified Family Life Coach Jana Lee will present on how to parent in a digital world Thursday at the Roseburg Christian Academy, 1653 NW Troost St., Roseburg. The free seminar will begin with a light dinner at 6…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg library starts year strong]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e241776c-d75d-11ee-8859-d32051169e30</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/roseburg-library-starts-year-strong/article_e241776c-d75d-11ee-8859-d32051169e30.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library is rocking in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KRIS WILEY Library News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC nursing instructors stay local with tuition-free master’s degree]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e2d86de0-d594-11ee-9447-532af8e76ad7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/ucc-nursing-instructors-stay-local-with-tuition-free-master-s-degree/article_e2d86de0-d594-11ee-9447-532af8e76ad7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Community College nursing faculty members Rivka Spain Butler and Mary Barron are taking advantage of a new grant program enabling them to earn a master’s degree without leaving the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SUZI PRITCHARD For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Lions Club sells candy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6a90b002-d744-11ee-9f10-0f01cdd3f7e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/roseburg-lions-club-sells-candy/article_6a90b002-d744-11ee-9f10-0f01cdd3f7e4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Roseburg Lions Club will be selling See's Candy from March 15-30 from a yellow trailer in the northwest corner of the Sherm's Thunderbird Marketplace parking lot, 2553 NW Stewart Parkway, Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County recreation report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7129bd8c-d802-11ee-93f3-c3685f5f730c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/douglas-county-recreation-report/article_7129bd8c-d802-11ee-93f3-c3685f5f730c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FISHING REPORT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING/WEATHER ADVISORY FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116270</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/winter-storm-warning-weather-advisory-for-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-weather-advisory-for-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 6:00 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect until 10:00 a.m. Saturday above 2,000 feet with a Winter Weather Advisory in place until 4:00 p.m. Sunday above 800 feet for central Douglas County. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said for the Warning, heavy snow is expected with additional accumulations of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING/WEATHER ADVISORY FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116267</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/winter-storm-warning-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T13:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 5:30 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect until 10:00 a.m. Saturday with a Winter Weather Advisory in place from 10:00 a.m. Saturday through 4:00 p.m. Sunday for mountain areas in southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said for the Warning, heavy snow is expected with additional accumulations of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>