<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-10-17T13:20:37.166Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RAIN STAYS SOUTH WEDNESDAY, LIGHT SHOWERS THURSDAY FOR ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124953</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/17/rain-stays-south-wednesday-light-showers-thursday-for-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rain-stays-south-wednesday-light-showers-thursday-for-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 17, 2024 3;50 a.m. Light rain that had been expected didn’t materialize on Wednesday with no precipitation measured at the Roseburg Regional Airport. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that moisture remained south of the Sexton Summit. In contrast to the Umpqua Valley, the Medford Airport...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FINAL PUBLIC STARGAZING EVENT FRIDAY NIGHT AT MORGAN OBSERVATORY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124950</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/17/final-public-stargazing-event-friday-night-at-morgan-observatory/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=final-public-stargazing-event-friday-night-at-morgan-observatory"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 17, 2024 3:40 a.m. The Paul Morgan Observatory at Umpqua Community College will have its final public stargazing event of 2024 on Friday night from 6:30 p.m., to 8:00 p.m. Attendees of all ages can join UCC astronomers to see a new comet and more. Bring folding chairs or blankets to watch on the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGON EMPLOYMENT SITUATION SEES LITTLE CHANGE IN SEPTEMBER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124948</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/17/oregon-employment-situation-sees-little-change-in-september/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregon-employment-situation-sees-little-change-in-september"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:17:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 17, 2024 3;30 a.m. Oregon’s unemployment rate was 4.0 percent in August and September and has been in a tight range between 4.0 percent and 4.2 percent since October 2023. An Oregon Employment Department release said the U.S. unemployment rate was little changed at 4.1 percent in September in 4.2 percent in August. State...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESIDENTIAL LEAF PICKUPS TO START IN ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124946</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/17/residential-leaf-pickups-to-start-in-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=residential-leaf-pickups-to-start-in-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 17, 2024 3:20 a.m. Roseburg Public Works will offer leaf collection service for homeowners starting later this month. A city release said from the week of Monday, October 28th through Friday, January 3rd, Public Works crews will pick up leaves from residents inside the city limits. Dump trucks of free leaves may soon be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HIGH SCHOOL MARCHING ENSEMBLE GETS SECOND IN COMPETITION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124944</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/17/roseburg-high-school-marching-ensemble-gets-second-in-competition/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-high-school-marching-ensemble-gets-second-in-competition"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 17, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Roseburg High School Marching Ensemble recently competed at the annual Pride of the Northwest marching competition at Grants Pass High School. Taking place last Saturday, October 12th, the competition brought together 12 high school marching bands from all over Oregon and northern California. RHS took home the 2nd place...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TERROR OFF CENTRAL HAUNTED HOUSE IN SUTHERLIN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124941</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/17/terror-off-central-haunted-house-in-sutherlin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=terror-off-central-haunted-house-in-sutherlin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 17, 2024 2:50 a.m. Sutherlin Downtown Development will have Terror Off Central coming soon. The event will feature a haunted house located at 103 West Central Avenue. It will be open Saturday October 26th from 4:00 p.m. to 8:00 p.m. and Wednesday October 30th from 6:00 p.m. to 8:00 p.m. The haunted house will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIKE WINTERS LAWN AND GARDEN SHOW 10.16.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124938</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-10-16-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-10-16-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T00:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County’s Commissioner of Dirt, Mike Winters, has the weekly local lawn and garden program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Forests Advisory Committee meets Oct. 25]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176068</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176068"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The State Forests Advisory Committee will meet in the Tillamook Room, Building C, Oregon Department of Forestry, 2600 State Street in Salem on Friday, Oct. 25 at 9 a.m. A virtual option will be available via Zoom video conference, which can be found on the agenda. To provide public comment, please contact Emily Shook at 503-945-7363.
Agenda topics include:

Fiscal Year 2024 accomplishment reports
Fiscal Year 2025 Annual Operations Plan (AOP) public comments summary
Implementation Plan (IP) revisions
Forest Management Plan (FMP) modeling scenarios
Peer Support Program
Charter review
Appointment renewals and recruitments

The meeting is open to the public to attend in-person or virtually via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted near the start of the meeting. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 72 hours before the meeting by contacting Emily Shook at 503-945-7363.
The State Forests Advisory Committee (SFAC) includes citizens and representatives of timber, environmental and recreation groups. SFAC provides a forum to discuss issues, opportunities and concerns, and offer guidance to ODF on the implementation of the Northwest Oregon State Forests Management Plan. The plan provides guidance for managing 616,000 acres within the Tillamook, Clatsop and Santiam State Forests, and several scattered state-owned forest tracts in Benton, Polk, Lincoln and Lane counties through a balanced approach to generate revenue while preserving environmental and social benefits. View more information on the SFAC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.16.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124929</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/inside-douglas-county-10-16-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-16-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Commissioner Tom Kress talks about a revenue shortfall to maintain safe county roads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAWMAKERS ANNOUNCE $25 MILLION IN FUNDING-PORT OF COOS BAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124926</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/lawmakers-announce-25-million-in-funding-port-of-coos-bay/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lawmakers-announce-25-million-in-funding-port-of-coos-bay"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 11:10 a.m.   On Wednesday, U.S. Representative Val Hoyle and Senators Ron Wyden and Jeff Merkley, announced over $25 million in federal funding for the Pacific Coast Intermodal Port Terminal Planning Project. A joint release from the lawmakers said the investment comes from the U.S. Department of Transportation’s Nationally Significant Multimodal Freight and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON POLICE RESPOND TO SINGLE VEHICLE CRASH IN A FIELD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124924</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/winston-police-respond-to-single-vehicle-crash-in-a-field/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-police-respond-to-single-vehicle-crash-in-a-field"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 10:40 a.m. Winston Police dealt with a single vehicle crash Wednesday morning. A WPD report said just before 7:10 a.m. officers responded to the wreck in the field next to Douglas High School on Highway 42. Officers learned that the driver had fallen asleep and had driven his vehicle off the road....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY FAIR BOARD HOLDING SPECIAL MEETING THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124922</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/douglas-county-fair-board-holding-special-meeting-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-fair-board-holding-special-meeting-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 10:30 a.m.  The Douglas County Fair Board is holding a special meeting on Thursday morning at 9:00 a.m. in rooms 216 and 220 of the Douglas County Courthouse. An Executive Session, not open to the public, will be held to interview applicants for the fairgrounds director position. Current Director Dan Hults will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Famed string quarter comes to The Chapel]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2e4db394-8a52-11ef-817d-47c3721bf3b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/famed-string-quarter-comes-to-the-chapel/article_2e4db394-8a52-11ef-817d-47c3721bf3b1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexander String Quarter will perform at 3 p.m. Sunday, Nov. 17, at The Chapel, 2837 W. Harvard Ave. in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA DROPS FIRE DANGER – PUR TO LOW, IFPL TO 1]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124919</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/dfpa-drops-fire-danger-pur-to-low-ifpl-to-1/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-drops-fire-danger-pur-to-low-ifpl-to-1"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 1o:15 a.m.  Effective Wednesday at 9:00 a.m. Public Use Restriction Levels changed to LOW for all private, county, state, and Bureau of Indian Affairs lands within the Douglas District, which imposes certain fire restrictions on the public to help prevent wildfires. Douglas Forest Protective Association Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIDESPREAD RAIN ALLOWS FOR DECREASES IN PUBLIC/INDUSTRIAL FIRE DANGER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124916</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/widespread-rain-allows-for-decreases-in-public-industrial-fire-danger/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=widespread-rain-allows-for-decreases-in-public-industrial-fire-danger"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:05:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 9:50 a.m. Recent fall-like weather and widespread rain has made it possible to ease off on some public and industrial fire prevention regulations on lands protected by the Oregon Department of Forestry Southwest Oregon District. Effective Wednesday at 9:00 a.m. the public fire danger has decreased to low, and the industrial fire...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO PEOPLE TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWNG SINGLE VEHICLE WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124913</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/two-people-taken-to-hospital-followng-single-vehicle-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-people-taken-to-hospital-followng-single-vehicle-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 9:30 a.m. Two people were taken to the hospital following a single vehicle wreck Tuesday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 3:50 p.m. dispatchers were notified of a crash in roughly the 30000 block of Cow Creek Road in the Glendale area. By the time units arrived at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE INVESTIGATING IN-CUSTODY DEATH AT COUNTY JAIL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124911</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/roseburg-police-investigating-in-custody-death-at-county-jail/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-investigating-in-custody-death-at-county-jail"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 9:20 a.m. A Sutherlin woman died Monday of an apparent suicide while in custody at the Douglas County Jail. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at approximately 5:40 p.m., a deputy discovered a female adult unresponsive in a holding cell from an apparent suicide attempt. Deputies immediately summoned emergency services and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.16.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124907</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/morning-conversation-10-16-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-16-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christie Glen-Knutson is running for the office of mayor in Winston. She talks about her campaign and her hopes for the future of Winston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In-Custody Death Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news176057</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news176057"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG, Ore. – A Sutherlin woman died of an apparent suicide while in custody at the Douglas County Jail.
On Monday, October 14, 2024, at approximately 5:40 pm, a deputy discovered a female adult in custody (AIC) unresponsive in a holding cell from an apparent suicide attempt. Deputies immediately summoned emergency services and began life saving efforts. The AIC, identified as 38-year-old Katrina Nicole Robertson of Sutherlin, was transported by ambulance but could not be revived.
“My heartfelt condolences are extended to Ms. Robertson’s family,” Sheriff Hanlin said. “The safety and security of those in our custody is of utmost importance to me as Sheriff. In the interest of providing an independent investigation into this tragedy, I have requested the assistance of an outside agency. I wish to thank the Roseburg Police Department for assuming this investigation and conducing a thorough review of the facts.”
Any further information will be released by the Roseburg Police Department.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Christian Academy performs musical for annual fundraiser]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ff1436e2-8b6a-11ef-9a9d-4705f9a03ef9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/roseburg-christian-academy-performs-musical-for-annual-fundraiser/article_ff1436e2-8b6a-11ef-9a9d-4705f9a03ef9.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Christian Academy students are gearing up with last minute rehearsals and final touches to present their musical “The American Revolution” on Thursday and through the weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STATE LAND BOARD ESTABLISHES ELLIOT STATE RESEARCH FOREST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124899</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/state-land-board-establishes-elliot-state-research-forest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=state-land-board-establishes-elliot-state-research-forest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 4:00 a.m. Oregon’s first state forest is officially its first research forest. A release from the Oregon Department of State Lands said on Tuesday the State Land Board approved the Elliot State Research Forest Management Plan, which establishes the forest as a nationally important center for forest science and management that also...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY OF ROSEBURG LISTS CAMPAIGN SIGNS RULES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124897</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/city-of-roseburg-lists-campaign-signs-rules/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-of-roseburg-lists-campaign-signs-rules"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:35:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 3:40 a.m.  With the November General Election approaching, the City of Roseburg has reminders regarding campaign sign rules. A city release said signs must not be placed on sidewalks or any other public right-of-way, which is generally the area from the street to the property line and can include sidewalks, grass, gravel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY URGES RESIDENTS, BUSINESSES TO ALLOW ONLY RAIN DOWN STORM DRAINS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124895</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/city-urges-residents-businesses-to-allow-only-rain-down-storm-drains/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-urges-residents-businesses-to-allow-only-rain-down-storm-drains"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Roseburg Public Works Department encourages residents and businesses to protect local waterways and prevent street flooding by allowing only rain down storm drains this fall. A city release said streets and storm drains are designed to enable rain to drain directly to nearby creeks and rivers instead of flooding...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WILDLIFE SAFARI BOOS AND BREWS HAPPENING SATURDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124892</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/wildlife-safari-boos-and-brews-happening-saturday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wildlife-safari-boos-and-brews-happening-saturday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 3:20 a.m. Wildlife Safari’s Boos and Brews Halloween themed event is happening Saturday night. The 21 and older event features a costume contest with prizes for the scariest, funniest and most creative costumes. There will also be dancing, a variety of local beers, ciders, and wines, and a haunted house. Guests can...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FESTIVAL OF LIGHTS PREPARES FOR ITS 32ND SEASON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124890</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/festival-of-lights-prepares-for-its-32nd-season/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=festival-of-lights-prepares-for-its-32nd-season"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 16, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Umpqua Valley Festival of Lights is preparing for its 32nd season. A festival release said organized by the Roseburg Rotary Club it will launch on November 24th, showcasing 500,000 lights and 90 displays at River Forks Park, west of Roseburg. Visitors will be excited for the return of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEXANDER STRING QUARTET IN CONCERT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124887</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/16/alexander-string-quartet-in-concert/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=alexander-string-quartet-in-concert"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 2:50 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Umpqua Symphony Association will present The Alexander String Quartet will be in concert on Sunday, November 17th at 3:00 p.m. The event will be at The Chapel, at 2837 West Harvard Avenue in Roseburg. The group has performed globally, having presented concerts in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 10.15.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124884</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/true-wealth-10-15-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-10-15-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T00:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littlejohn Financial, David Littlejohn and Matt Dickson have our weekly local financial program]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Oregon District terminates regulated-use closure; fire season remains in effect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176037</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176037"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T21:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRINEVILLE, Ore. – Oregon Department of Forestry’s Central Oregon District will terminate regulated-use closure at 12:01 a.m., Wednesday, Oct. 16, 2024. Fire season remains in effect across the Central Oregon District.
“We caution the public to be mindful of activities which could start a fire as we continue to slowly ease into winter. Periods of dry windy weather are possible and can be a threat into November,” says Brandon Ferguson, Forest Resources Manager for the John Day Unit. “While fire danger has lessened with cooler nights and increased humidity, we can still have rapidly spreading fires during the heat of the day.”
Wildland fuels, including live vegetation and down wood material are extremely dry. Limited precipitation, combined with long-term drought conditions continue to elevate the risk of fire ignition and increase fire behavior in wildland fuels. Fire managers regularly evaluate conditions to determine current fire danger and necessary restrictions to limit impacts from wildfires.
During fire season backyard debris burning, including burn barrels is allowed by permit only. Many counties have burn bans in place prohibiting debris burning at this time. Check restrictions in your local area to help prevent wildfires.
With the termination of regulated-use closure, chainsaw use and mowing restrictions are lifted and small warming/recreational fires may be allowed on ODF-protected lands unless restricted locally.
Failure to follow fire season restrictions can result in citations, fines, and liability for costs associated with putting fires out. Wildfires impact public health, water quality, soil productivity, landowners, and local communities and businesses.
For additional information on ODF’s Central Oregon District, including regulated-use closure restrictions and contact information, please visit www.ODFcentraloregon.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DINT ARRESTS TWO FOLLOWING A MONTH-LONG INVESTIGATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124881</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/dint-arrests-two-following-a-month-long-investigation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dint-arrests-two-following-a-month-long-investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 1:50 p.m.  On Monday, detectives with the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team were assisted by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office in bringing to conclusion a month-long investigation into suspected drug trafficking. DINT Commander Lieutenant Rick McArthur said at approximately 8:30 p.m. a deputy initiated a traffic stop on a vehicle on Interstate 5...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VA Awareness Fair shows veterans what resources are available]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fd8e7842-8b32-11ef-be4c-33cc4f907818</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/va-awareness-fair-shows-veterans-what-resources-are-available/article_fd8e7842-8b32-11ef-be4c-33cc4f907818.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deena Lockhart, of Roseburg, said she uses Roseburg VA Medical Center for medical needs. She volunteers in the clothing area, but she learned about new resources during Tuesday's Veteran's Health and Awareness Fair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.15.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124875</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/inside-douglas-county-10-15-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-15-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angela Wilhelms, president of Oregon Business and Industry talks about her group’s opposition to Ballot Measure 118.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DINT makes arrests in meth investigation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/efb8d82c-8b21-11ef-b45d-5755c2f38357</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/dint-makes-arrests-in-meth-investigation/article_efb8d82c-8b21-11ef-b45d-5755c2f38357.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team detectives brought a months-long investigation into suspected drug trafficking to a conclusion Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meth Arrest (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6255#news176024</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6255#news176024"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, October 14th, detectives with the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT) were assisted by the Douglas County Sheriff's Office in bringing to conclusion a month long investigation into suspected drug trafficking.  
At approximately 8:30 PM, a Douglas County Sheriff's Deputy initiated a traffic stop on a vehicle on I-5 at milepost 161 near Curtin, at the request of DINT detectives.  Two persons were detained:  45 year old Jeffrey Bell, and 45 year old Annie Randles, both of Roseburg.
During a search of the vehicle, detectives found approximately 2 pounds of suspected methamphetamine.  Detectives followed up with a search of a residence in the 900 block of Shoestring Road in Riddle where they found more evidence of drug trafficking.  
Jeff Bell was lodged at the Douglas County Jail on charges of Possession, Manufacturing, and Delivery of Methamphetamine.  
Annie Randles was cited and released on charges on Unlawful Possession and Delivery of Methamphetamine.
 
The Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT) is a multi-jurisdictional narcotics task force that identifies, disrupts, and dismantles local, multi-state, and international drug trafficking organizations using an intelligence-driven, multi-agency prosecutor-supported approach.  DINT is supported by the Oregon-Idaho High-Intensity Drug Trafficking Area (HIDTA) and is composed of members from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office, Roseburg Police Department, Oregon State Police, Douglas County District Attorney’s Office, and the Bureau of Land Management.
The Oregon-Idaho HIDTA program is an Office of National Drug Control Policy (ONDCP) sponsored counterdrug grant program that coordinates with and provides funding resources to multi-agency drug enforcement initiatives, including DINT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPTD SELECTS TOP APPLICANT FOR INTERIM GM POSITION, BOARD MEMBER RESIGNS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124871</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/uptd-selects-top-applicant-for-interim-gm-position-board-member-resigns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uptd-selects-top-applicant-for-interim-gm-position-board-member-resigns"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 11:10 a.m. The Board of Directors of the Umpqua Public Transportation District has selected Ben Edtl as the top applicant for the position of interim general manager. Chair/Executive Director Position 2 Michaela Hammerson said the decision was reached by a vote of 4 in favor, 2 against and 1 abstention. Hammerson said...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Bruce Campus hosts trunk or treat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/592cd28c-8a54-11ef-b8e4-6f0bb1788c94</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/jerry-bruce-campus-hosts-trunk-or-treat/article_592cd28c-8a54-11ef-b8e4-6f0bb1788c94.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Jerry Bruce Community Campus partner organizations including the FISH Food Pantry and Aviva Health, are holding a trunk-or-treat for families Saturday, Oct. 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124869</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-17/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-17"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 10:40 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for drinking in public Monday evening. An RPD report said at 6:50 p.m. a 63-year-old man was contacted because he was sitting on the sidewalk in the 200 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard and was drinking a can of malt liquor. He was released...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE 5 PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124867</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-police-cite-5-people-for-prohibited-camping-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-5-people-for-prohibited-camping-4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited 5 people for prohibited camping between Monday morning and early Tuesday morning. An RPD report said contacts were made at camps in the corner of Northwest Stewart Parkway and Northwest Renann Street, in the 1400 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive, in the 200 block of Northwest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR CRIMINAL TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124865</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-criminal-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-criminal-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a criminal trespass incident on Monday. An RPD report said at 10:30 a.m. the 41-year-old was contacted in the 700 block of Southeast Jackson Street. Officers learned the man was a city expulsion violator on his third warning and that his parole officer wanted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN ARRESTED BY BOTH RPD AND DCSO FOLLOWING ELUDE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124863</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-man-arrested-by-both-rpd-and-dcso-following-elude/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-arrested-by-both-rpd-and-dcso-following-elude"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 10:00 a.m. A Roseburg man was arrested by both the Roseburg Police Department and the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office following an eluding incident on Monday night. Reports from both agencies indicate that 25-year-old Blake Van Norman was called in for driving recklessly in the area of West Godeck Avenue in Roseburg at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOTH DRIVERS CITED IN HUCREST TWO-VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124861</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/both-drivers-cited-in-hucrest-two-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=both-drivers-cited-in-hucrest-two-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 9:30 a.m. Both drivers were cited after a two-vehicle crash in the Hucrest neighborhood on Monday afternoon. A Roseburg Police report said at 5:30 p.m. officers responded to the accident at the intersection of Northwest Calkins Road and Northwest Troost Street. An 18-year-old driver said she did not stop at the stop...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.15.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124858</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/morning-conversation-10-15-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-15-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rebecca Marshall of the American Red Cross talks about the disaster relief work she has been doing in Tennessee, and the other places the non-profit is currently assisting around the nation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Halloween events throughout Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a24512fe-8211-11ef-9eb2-6b318c22e8d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/health/halloween-events-throughout-douglas-county/article_a24512fe-8211-11ef-9eb2-6b318c22e8d0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October brings with it fall weather and ghastly sights as Douglas County sets up for spooky times in the name of Halloween.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BEGINNING OF SIGNIFICANT CHANGE TO WEATHER IN THE UMPQUA VALLEY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124855</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/beginning-of-significant-change-to-weather-in-the-umpqua-valley/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=beginning-of-significant-change-to-weather-in-the-umpqua-valley"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T11:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 4:10 a.m. Tuesday will see the beginning of a significant change to the weather in the Umpqua Valley. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that Tuesday and Wednesday will see light showers with .10 inches of rain between the two days. Thursday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEAGUE OF WOMEN VOTERS TO HOST TOWN HALL FOR CITY COUNCIL CANDIDATES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124853</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/league-of-women-voters-to-host-town-hall-for-city-council-candidates/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=league-of-women-voters-to-host-town-hall-for-city-council-candidates"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 3:40 a.m. The League of Women Voters of the Umpqua Valley will host a town hall for Roseburg City Council candidates on Wednesday, October 23rd. For the first time in many years, there are two candidates running for all four council positions which are up a vote. Organizers say the event will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAST DAY TO REGISTER AS A NEW OREGON VOTER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124851</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/last-day-to-register-as-a-new-oregon-voter/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=last-day-to-register-as-a-new-oregon-voter"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 3:30 a.m. Tuesday is the last day to register as a new Oregon voter, ahead of the November General Election. Douglas County Clerk Daniel Loomis said current voters can make changes in their status up to election day. Loomis said to get registered, go to a link on the Oregon Secretary of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COMMUNITY HELP NEEDED FOR WREATHS ACROSS AMERICA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124848</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/community-help-needed-for-wreaths-across-america/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=community-help-needed-for-wreaths-across-america"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 3:20 a.m. Community help is needed for this year’s Wreaths Across America wreath laying ceremony on Saturday December 14th. Douglas County Commissioner Chris Boice has been working closely with location coordinator John Pierson. Pierson is battling terminal cancer, but his goal for many years has been to raise enough money to place...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTH DOUGLAS COUNTY LIBRARIES WITH FOOD DRIVE CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124846</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/south-douglas-county-libraries-with-food-drive-challenge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=south-douglas-county-libraries-with-food-drive-challenge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 3:05 a.m. The libraries in south Douglas County have launched a collaborative food drive challenge in support of the South Douglas Food Bank. The initiative aims to gather non-perishable food items to assist families in need within the community. The food drive challenge will run through December 15th. It also introduces a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN HOSPITALIZED/CITED FOLLOWING SINGLE VEHICLE ACCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124844</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-man-hospitalized-cited-following-single-vehicle-accident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-hospitalized-cited-following-single-vehicle-accident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 2:50 a.m. A Roseburg man was hospitalized and cited following a single-vehicle wreck early Monday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 1:20 a.m. the 21-year-old was driving west on Happy Valley Road in the Green area. He drifted out of his lane to the right and his vehicle struck...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari plans for African painted dogs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c237549c-8a8a-11ef-9d15-dfd122400431</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/wildlife-safari-plans-for-african-painted-dogs/article_c237549c-8a8a-11ef-9d15-dfd122400431.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T00:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Wildlife Safari's annual benefit dinner raised more than $200,000 to help fund the upcoming African painted dog exhibit, which will be located in the lion loop of the drive-through area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA CREWS DEAL WITH KENT CREEK FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124841</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/dfpa-crews-deal-with-kent-creek-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-crews-deal-with-kent-creek-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T22:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:00 p.m.  Crews with the Douglas Forest Protective Association dealt with the Kent Creek Fire on Sunday. Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said at approximately 3:20 p.m. DFPA, Central Douglas Fire & Rescue and Lookingglass Rural Fire District responded to a natural cover fire near the 200 block of Kent Creek Road...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.14.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124834</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/inside-douglas-county-10-14-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-14-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T20:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Commissioner Chris Boice talks about this year’s Wreaths Across America event at the Roseburg VA Cemetery and the community help that is needed to lay 7,000 wreaths.  Residents can sign up to help here:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE 14 PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124832</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/roseburg-police-cite-14-people-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-14-people-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T18:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 11:10 a.m. Roseburg Police cited 14 people for prohibited camping between Saturday afternoon and Sunday morning. An RPD report said the camps were located in the 1400 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive, at Deer Creek Park in the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street, at the corner of Southeast Cass Avenue...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE MAN JAILED FOR DISORDERLY CONDUCT/RESISTING ARREST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124830</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/riddle-man-jailed-for-disorderly-conduct-resisting-arrest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riddle-man-jailed-for-disorderly-conduct-resisting-arrest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 10:50 a.m.  A Riddle man was charged with second-degree disorderly conduct and resisting arrest following an incident Saturday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 11:00 p.m. deputies responded after a caller said there was a disturbance in the 300 block of East Fifth Avenue. When the first deputy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED FOR DUII WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124828</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/roseburg-man-jailed-for-duii-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-for-duii-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 10:20 a.m. A Roseburg man was jailed for a DUII wreck late Sunday morning. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 12:00 p.m. the 37-year-old wrecked his pickup in the 2000 block of South Deer Creek Road in Green. He was contacted by a nearby resident who believed that the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YONCALLA MAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED STRANGULATION INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124825</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/yoncalla-man-jailed-for-alleged-strangulation-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=yoncalla-man-jailed-for-alleged-strangulation-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 10:00 a.m.   A Yoncalla man was jailed for an alleged strangulation incident on Sunday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 8:00 p.m. a deputy responded to the 100 block of Birch Street. A victim had an injury to her neck area and legs. The victim stated that the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING HIGH-SPEED CHASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124823</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/winston-police-jail-man-following-high-speed-chase/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-police-jail-man-following-high-speed-chase"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2023 9:50 a.m.  Winston Police jailed a man following a high-speed chase that started late Sunday night. A WPD report said just before 12:00 a.m. Monday, officers attempted a stop on a motorcycle near the intersection of Brockway Road and Lookingglass Road for traffic violations.  The driver, later identified as 44-year-old Roy Abbot,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING REPORTED DISTURBANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124821</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/sutherlin-police-jail-man-following-reported-disturbance-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-following-reported-disturbance-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 9:30 a.m.    Sutherlin Police jailed a man following a reported disturbance on Friday night. An SPD report said just after 8:40 p.m. 25-year-old Corbin Christy and a victim were allegedly involved in the incident at a motel in the 1400 block of Hospitality Way. Neighbors reported loud yelling and physical fighting....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN ON DRUG AND WEAPON CHARGES SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124817</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/sutherlin-police-jail-man-on-drug-and-weapon-charges-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-on-drug-and-weapon-charges-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 9:20 a.m. Sutherlin Police jailed a man on drug and weapon charges on Saturday. An SPD report said just after 1:00 a.m. 36-year-old Miles Yohai allegedly agreed to see a half ounce of methamphetamine for $110. When Yohai arrived at Ford’s Pond at the agreed upon time, he was taken into custody...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.14.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124814</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/morning-conversation-10-14-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-14-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiffany Roddy of the Douglas County Chapter of the Oregon Women in Timber talks about the educational program OWIT offers for young people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Board of Forestry to meet on Oct. 16 and 17 in Pendleton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175999</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175999"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T15:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Oregon Board of Forestry will meet in Pendleton for their fall retreat on Oct. 16 and 17. The retreat’s two-day itinerary will include an executive session, field tour, and public social on Wednesday, Oct. 16, and an executive session and public meeting on Thursday, Oct. 17. Both executive sessions will be closed to the public, except for members of the press. The field tour and social event that will take place on Oct. 16 are open to the public for in-person participation, and recordings of highlights will be posted on the board’s meeting page afterward. The public meeting that will take place on Oct. 17 will be open for in-person observation and livestreamed on the department’s YouTube channel.
The board’s agenda for the retreat’s public meeting includes:

State of the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pink in Paradise show to honor breast cancer survivors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4fd632e8-88ea-11ef-b879-7b05756aebf4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/health/pink-in-paradise-show-to-honor-breast-cancer-survivors/article_4fd632e8-88ea-11ef-b879-7b05756aebf4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Vanessa Cummings visited her doctor for a routine mammogram in August 2022, they found a speck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ELDERLY MAN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING HEAD-ON CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124805</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/elderly-man-taken-to-hospital-following-head-on-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=elderly-man-taken-to-hospital-following-head-on-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 4:00 a.m. An elderly man was taken to the hospital following a head-on crash on Saturday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 1:50 p.m. a 22-year-old driver was traveling north in his sedan on old Highway 99 North near Del Rio Road when he failed to maintain his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WOMAN JAILED ON 28 CHARGES: THEFT IN UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124803</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/woman-jailed-on-28-charges-theft-in-umpqua-national-forest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=woman-jailed-on-28-charges-theft-in-umpqua-national-forest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:50 a.m. A Myrtle Creek woman was jailed on 28 charges for alleged theft incidents in the Umpqua National Forest on Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 5:45 p.m. a 45-year-old was stopped while driving a sedan on Highway 230 in the Tree Lakes Snow Park/Diamond Lake area. She...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLUMBUS DAY/INDIGENOUS PEOPLE’S DAY MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124801</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/columbus-day-indigenous-peoples-day-monday-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=columbus-day-indigenous-peoples-day-monday-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:40 a.m. Monday is Columbus Day, a federal holiday. However approximately 29 states and Washington D.C. do not celebrate it. In Oregon, Monday is Indigenous People’s Day and is a state holiday. With the two observances, federal and state offices will be closed. Regular mail will not be delivered. Banks and credit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY COUNCIL TO CONSIDER DOWNTOWN PARKING ENFORCEMENT OPTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124799</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/city-council-to-consider-downtown-parking-enforcement-options/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-council-to-consider-downtown-parking-enforcement-options"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Roseburg City Council will consider downtown parking enforcement options as part of its meeting Monday night. The city has had a contract with ACE Parking Enforcement since the start of 2022. However, ACE has failed to generate enough revenue to cover the cost of its contract. The council has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VETERAN’S HEALTH & AWARENESS FAIR ON TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124795</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/veterans-health-awareness-fair-on-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=veterans-health-awareness-fair-on-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3;20 a.m. The Roseburg VA Medical Center is presenting the 2024 Veteran’s Health & Awareness Fair on Tuesday. A VA release said the event is being held to help raise awareness as October is National Breast Cancer Awareness Month and National Domestic Violence Awareness Month. An Awareness Walk will begin at 11:00...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JERRY BRUCE CAMPUS NON-PROFIT PARTNERS TO HOLD TRUNK-OR-TREAT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124793</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/jerry-bruce-campus-non-profit-partners-to-hold-trunk-or-treat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=jerry-bruce-campus-non-profit-partners-to-hold-trunk-or-treat"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:05 a.m. Jerry Bruce Community Campus partner organizations Family Development Center, the FISH Food Pantry, Umpqua Homes, United Community Action Network and Aviva Health are holding a truck-or-treat for local families this Saturday October 19th. It will take place from 12:00 p.m. to 3:00 p.m. in the Aviva Health parking lot on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPOUSAL AND SURVIVORS BENEFITS EDUCATIONAL SEMINAR]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124790</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/spousal-and-survivors-benefits-educational-seminar-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spousal-and-survivors-benefits-educational-seminar-3"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024, 2:50 a.m.  Associates of Vietnam Veterans of America will have a Spousal and Survivor Benefits Educational Seminar coming soon. The event will be held on Saturday, November 2nd from 10:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. at Garden Valley Church, at 3047 Garden Valley Road, west of Roseburg. Those attending can learn about the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helmets for Hope hands out headware to bikers, skaters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/47a9ae78-88dc-11ef-b20f-a768cab92343</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/court/helmets-for-hope-hands-out-headware-to-bikers-skaters/article_47a9ae78-88dc-11ef-b20f-a768cab92343.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noel Crownover organized Helmets for Hope to help prevent head injuries among skaters in Douglas County, as his community project for Douglas County H.O.P.E. Drug Court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A paw-sitively good time at Howl-O-Ween in Sutherlin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c06ec9ac-88db-11ef-8dc2-278e151eb33f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/a-paw-sitively-good-time-at-howl-o-ween-in-sutherlin/article_c06ec9ac-88db-11ef-8dc2-278e151eb33f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Richard Atkinson brought his two heelers, 4-year-old Cricket and 5-year-old Bobo, to Sutherlin’s Central Park on Saturday to socialize at the 2024 Howl-O-Ween carnival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hope for Helmets hands out headware to bikers, skaters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/47a9ae78-88dc-11ef-b20f-a768cab92343</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/court/hope-for-helmets-hands-out-headware-to-bikers-skaters/article_47a9ae78-88dc-11ef-b20f-a768cab92343.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noel Crownover organized Helmets for Hope to help prevent head injuries among skaters in Douglas County, as his community project for Douglas County H.O.P.E. Drug Court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>