<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-08-11T23:10:11.394Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dixon Fire Update 08/11/24 3:45 pm (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174467</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174467"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T22:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CURRENT EVACUATION NOTICES IN PLACE AS A RESULT OF THE DIXON FIRE
TILLER, Ore. - Evacuations remain in place for the Dixon Fire, previously referred to as the Tiller Trail Fire. The following is a summary of the current evacuation levels as of Sunday, August 11, 2024, at 3:45 pm. An interactive map reflecting these evacuation levels can be found online at www.dcso.com/evacuations. 

LEVEL 3 "GO!":
All residences on Crume Ranch Lane 
All residences on Devil's Knob Road, also known as USFS Road #1610
The one residence in the area of Hamlin Prairie. 
 

LEVEL 2 "BE SET":
All residences on Tiller Trail Highway from the intersection of Devil's Knob (USFS 1610) south to milepost 31 on Tiller Trail Highway. This includes all residences between these two points. 
 

Level 1 “BE READY”:
All residen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER TRAIL FIRE NOW NAMED DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122289</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/11/tiller-trail-fire-now-named-dixon-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tiller-trail-fire-now-named-dixon-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T18:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 11, 2024 11:20 a.m. The Tiller Trail Fire has now officially been named the Dixon Fire due to multiple agency involvement. An update from the Douglas Forest Protective Association said night crews continued aggressively working on building lines on the estimated 1,600 to 2,000-acre fire and addressing some spot fires. DFPA Public Information Officer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX GROWS SLIGHTLY TO 8,256 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122286</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/11/diamond-complex-grows-slightly-to-8256-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-grows-slightly-to-8256-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 11, 2024 10:20 a.m.  The Diamond Complex on the Umpqua National Forest, consisting of 27 fires, has grown slightly to 8.256 acres, with 743 people assigned. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park, has 28 people assigned, but the Diamond Complex is sharing resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Falls Fire 25% contained, evacuation levels reduced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174464</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174464"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T17:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry Grove, Ore. – With yesterday’s progress on the Lee Falls Fire, structural firefighting task forces and law enforcement demobilized from the area yesterday. Oregon Department of Forestry’s (ODF) Type 3 Incident Management Team remains on the Lee Falls Fire to continue mop up operations in preparation for returning the fire to the local district.
Yesterday’s work made sufficient progress to increase confidence that the fire will stay within its current perimeter. After consultation with fire officials, that confidence led to the Washington County Sheriff’s Office reducing all Level 3 evacuation levels to Level 2—Be Set. Cherry Grove community members returning to their homes should remain vigilant and maintain readiness for future evacuations, should fire conditions significantly chan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX GROWS SLIGHTLY, CONTAINMENT AT 14 PERCENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122282</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/11/homestead-complex-grows-slightly-containment-at-14-percent/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-grows-slightly-containment-at-14-percent"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T16:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 11, 2024 9:45 a.m.  The seven fires making up the Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, have grown slightly to 3,841 acres, with containment remaining at 14 percent. A UNF update said Saturday on the 1,465-acre No Man and 239-acre Salmon 33 fires, crews and heavy equipment continued primary and indirect line...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local students graduate Linfield University]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fa5b0d78-566e-11ef-94e6-87506b5b811b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/local-students-graduate-linfield-university/article_fa5b0d78-566e-11ef-94e6-87506b5b811b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linfield University announced 505 graduates following the spring 2024 semester. The commencement ceremony was held in McMinnville on May 26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TILLER  TRAIL FIRE AT 1,000-1,500 ACRES AS OF SATURDAY EVENING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122276</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/11/tiller-trail-fire-at-1000-1500-acres-as-of-saturday-evening/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tiller-trail-fire-at-1000-1500-acres-as-of-saturday-evening"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T13:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 11,  2024 6:30 a.m. Saturday at approximately 2:40 p.m., crews from the Douglas Forest Protective Association and over a dozen other agencies responded to a reported fire in the 28000 block of Tiller Trail Highway in the Tiller area. DFPA Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said upon arrival at the scene, an estimated 50-acre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local school districts receive grants for energy upgrades]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/91361494-56ac-11ef-b75c-c3d0163d74f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/local-school-districts-receive-grants-for-energy-upgrades/article_91361494-56ac-11ef-b75c-c3d0163d74f2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T04:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oregon Department of Education announced Monday that it will improve facilities as seven districts statewide, including Roseburg, Winston-Dillard and South Umpqua school districts in Douglas County.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX GROWS TO 8,129 ACRES, 738 PEOPLE ASSIGNED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122271</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/10/diamond-complex-grows-to-8129-acres-738-people-assigned/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-grows-to-8129-acres-738-people-assigned"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T17:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 10, 2024 10:15 a.m.   The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, has grown to 8,129 acres with 728 people assigned as of midday Saturday. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 28 people assigned, but the Diamond Complex is sharing resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAMOND COMPLEX GROWS TO 8,129 ACRES, 738 PEOPLE ASSIGNED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122271</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/10/damond-complex-grows-to-8129-acres-738-people-assigned/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=damond-complex-grows-to-8129-acres-738-people-assigned"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T17:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 10, 2024 10:15 a.m.   The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, has grown to 8,129 acres with 728 people assigned as of midday Saturday. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 28 people assigned, but the Diamond Complex is sharing resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX UP TO 3,726 ACRES, REMAINS 14 PERCENT CONTAINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122269</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/10/homestead-complex-up-to-3726-acres-remains-14-percent-contained/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-up-to-3726-acres-remains-14-percent-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T16:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 9:45 a.m.  The Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, is up to 3,726 acres, and remains 14 percent contained. A UNF update said the fire is being managed by Northwest Incident Management Team 8. Friday on the 1,334-acre No Man Fire, control line on the west flank continued to prevent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community protection continues on Lee Falls Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174450</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174450"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T16:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry Grove, Ore. – Oregon Department of Forestry’s (ODF) Type 3 Incident Management Team, along with a Type 3 Incident Management Team from structural firefighters and the Washington County Sheriff's Office, continue protecting the community of Cherry Grove today.
With over 175 personnel from ODF, contract, and crews of adults in custody from Coffee Creek and South Fork Forest Camp working to mop up the fire line today, some community members can return to their homes. Two task forces of structural firefighters remain to protect homes and structures.
The interior of the Lee Falls fire continues to burn slowly so residents will experience some smoke. With recent fire activity, snags present a hazard around some roads. Snags are dead or burned standing trees that may easily fall. Crews tod…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building community through volunteerism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e9652e24-5338-11ef-ba1d-7ff7dee19601</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/building-community-through-volunteerism/article_e9652e24-5338-11ef-ba1d-7ff7dee19601.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at JustServe we are all about building community. One way to do that is to work alongside our friends and neighbors for a good cause. Another way is to reach out to strangers and those we don’t know well…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JENNIFER COALWELL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrollment underway for Roseburg school district]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/69c839ae-54c8-11ef-9f14-8f387cb943be</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/enrollment-underway-for-roseburg-school-district/article_69c839ae-54c8-11ef-9f14-8f387cb943be.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The enrollment process is underway for the 2024-25 school year at Roseburg school district.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY FAIR DAY FOUR ACTIVITIES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122266</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/10/douglas-county-fair-day-four-activities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-fair-day-four-activities"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 10, 2024 7:00 a.m. It’s day four of the Douglas County Fair. It’s Family Day at the fair, sponsored by Pepsi and Clint Newell Auto Group. Kids aged 12 and under are admitted for free sponsored by the Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Tribe of Indians. Teens get in for $2 off when they...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spirit Halloween returns to Roseburg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ccc20570-5677-11ef-beba-0b0e8966b826</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/spirit-halloween-returns-to-roseburg/article_ccc20570-5677-11ef-beba-0b0e8966b826.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spirit Halloween is coming soon to 444 SE Stephens St., the former Rite Aid location in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Falls Fire 100% lined]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174447</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174447"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T04:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry Grove, Ore. – Oregon Department of Forestry’s (ODF) Type 3 Incident Management Team, who took command of fire operations today, along with a Type 3 Incident Management Team from structural firefighters and the Washington County Sheriff's Office. Today’s suppression efforts achieved control lines around the fire’s perimeter, keeping it at 280 acres.
ODF, contract, and crews of adults in custody from South Fork Forest Camp continued dozer and hand lines with ground crews receiving support from three helicopters dropping water on the Lee Falls Fire most of the afternoon and evening. The fire is now 100% lined.
With control lines established around the fire, and many areas plumbed with fire hose, the arduous process of mop up begins. Mop up is the process of cooling the perimeter of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 8.09.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122262</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/inside-douglas-county-8-09-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-8-09-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T20:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Senator David Brock Smith is in studio to cover a number of topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suppression efforts continue on the Lee Falls Fire (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174433</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174433"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T20:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry Grove, Ore. – The Oregon Department of Forestry, Gaston Rural Fire District and Washington County Sheriff's Office are working together in response to the Lee Falls Fire to protect the community of Cherry Grove and surrounding areas. The fire was reported Thursday, August 8, around 11 a.m. and is now estimated to be over 280 acres and is 75% lined. 
Oregon Department of Forestry firefighters, alongside multiple structural fire agencies from several counties, local landowners, crews of adults in custody from South Fork Forest Camp, and contractors worked diligently overnight on suppression efforts. ODF, contract, and South Fork crews will continue work to line the fire today. Multiple aviation resources are on standby and will be deployed as needed to support ground operations. 
The …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX UP TO 3,548 ACRES, 14 PERCENT CONTAINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122260</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/homestead-complex-up-to-3548-acres-14-percent-contained/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-up-to-3548-acres-14-percent-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T18:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 11:30 a.m. The Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, is up to 3,548 acres, with an overall containment of 14 percent. A UNF update said the fire is being managed by Northwest Incident Management Team 8. On Thursday, the 1,334 acre No Man Fire was active in the southeast corner...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX HOLDS AT 7,629 ACRES, 728 PEOPLE ASSIGNED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122258</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/diamond-complex-holds-at-7629-acres-728-people-assigned/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-holds-at-7629-acres-728-people-assigned"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T17:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 10:50 a.m. The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, is holding at approximately 7,629 acres, with 728 people assigned as of mid-day Friday. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire, in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 31 people assigned. The Diamond Complex is sharing resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OR230 REDUCED TO ONE LANE FOR TEN MILES NEAR OR138]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122256</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/or230-reduced-to-one-lane-for-ten-miles-near-or138/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=or230-reduced-to-one-lane-for-ten-miles-near-or138"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T17:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 10:45 a.m.   The Oregon Department of Transportation has announced that OR-230, Diamond Lake Highway, is reduced to one lane for ten miles. Julie Denney of ODOT said this is between mileposts 13 and 23, near the intersection with the North Umpqua Highway, also known as Highway 138E. Denny said pilot cars are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PRIOR HIT AND RUN INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122254</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prior-hit-and-run-incident-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prior-hit-and-run-incident-2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T17:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man Thursday for a prior hit and run incident. An RPD report said the 32-year-old was identified as the suspect from a hit and run which occurred on January 30th. The man admitted to dozing off at the wheel which allowed his vehicle to drift into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122252</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-alleged-harassment-incident-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-alleged-harassment-incident-3"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T17:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for an alleged harassment on Thursday. An RPD report said at 10:00 a.m. the 69-year alleged poked a victim in the face after a brief verbal argument in the 2700 block of Southeast Douglas Avenue. The victim had video footage in which the suspect was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED BURGLARY/ASSAULT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122250</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-alleged-burglary-assault-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-alleged-burglary-assault-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T17:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Police jailed a man following an alleged burglary and assault incident early Friday. An SPD report at approximately 2:15 a.m. 21-year-old Derek Moss alleged entered a home in the 700 block of Northwest Tanglewood Drive. Moss reportedly assaulted a victim, causing enough injury that the victim had to be transported to CHI Mercy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DOWNTOWN TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122248</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-downtown-trespass-incident-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-downtown-trespass-incident-2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T16:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man Thursday following a downtown trespass incident. An RPD report said at 11:00 a.m. the 67-year-old was contacted within the exclusion zone near the intersection of Southeast Washington Avenue and Southeast Rose Street. The man was still within his exclusion period. He was charged with second-degree...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS/WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122246</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T16:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged trespass incident on Thursday. An RPD report said just before 11:15 a.m. officers contacted the 44-year-old at CHI Mercy Medical Center on Northwest Stewart Parkway. The man had been medically discharged but refused to leave after being asked to by staff. He...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 8.9.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122243</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/local-real-estate-today-8-9-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-8-9-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T16:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Powered by Place at Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our local real estate update:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 8.9.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122237</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/morning-conversation-8-9-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-8-9-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T16:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Farmers Market Manager Meg Williams talks about National Farmers Market Week and special things happening at the Roseburg Farmer’s Market on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forestry Program for Oregon Subcommittee meets Aug. 15]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174418</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174418"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T15:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Forestry Program for Oregon Subcommittee will meet virtually on Thursday, Aug. 15 from 8 to 9 a.m. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda. 
The subcommittee’s agenda includes:

Review of current draft for Vision of Oregon’s Forests

Accommodations for people with disabilities, and special materials, services, or assistance can be arranged by calling ODF’s Public Affairs Office at least 72 hours in advance of the meeting at 503-945-7200 or by email at forestryinformation@odf.oregon.gov.
Subcommittee purpose: Collaborative work forum for board and agency leadership to advance efforts to jointly develop a modern Forestry Program for Oregon (FPFO). Read more information about the subcommittee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The circus comes to the Douglas County Fair]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/545661b0-50ed-11ef-b248-9bb917d919b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/the-circus-comes-to-the-douglas-county-fair/article_545661b0-50ed-11ef-b248-9bb917d919b3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ringmaster Caton Raintree-Hegwer and Costumier Carolina Raintree-Hegwer invited children from the audience to become the stars of circus Thursday at the Douglas County Fair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua National Forest adjusts closures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/32a6eac2-5605-11ef-920b-e3b289d7025b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/umpqua-national-forest-adjusts-closures/article_32a6eac2-5605-11ef-920b-e3b289d7025b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua National Forest adjusted the forest closure effective Thursday, which impacts all of the Cottage Grove Ranger District, most of the Diamond Lake District and parts of the Tiller and North Umpqua Ranger Districts in response to fire activity in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Saving seeds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7fa3157e-535a-11ef-9d5a-2f79618d53c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/ask-a-master-gardener-saving-seeds/article_7fa3157e-535a-11ef-9d5a-2f79618d53c0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I would like to try and save my own seeds for next year’s garden. Can you give me some tips on how to do that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mackenzi Hall Master Gardener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extension spotlight: Smoothies are great on hot summer days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/612db9b2-543d-11ef-b8df-7fa1bbf8c2ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/extension-spotlight-smoothies-are-great-on-hot-summer-days/article_612db9b2-543d-11ef-b8df-7fa1bbf8c2ee.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’re looking for an easy meal on a hectic day or a refreshing beverage when the temperature soars, there’s nothing quite like an ice cold smoothie. But just how did this delicious drink come about? Most countries in the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATHY BATES For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WEATHER PATTERN CHANGE LEADING TO CLOSER TO NORMAL TEMPERATURES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122232</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/weather-pattern-change-leading-to-closer-to-normal-temperatures/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=weather-pattern-change-leading-to-closer-to-normal-temperatures"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T11:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 4:10 a.m. A change in the weather pattern is forecast to bring the Umpqua Valley closer to normal temperatures through the weekend, with below normal temperatures expected for much of next week. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that highs should be in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEARCH FOR MISSING WOMAN ACTIVE AND ONGOING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122230</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/search-for-missing-woman-active-and-ongoing/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=search-for-missing-woman-active-and-ongoing"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T10:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 4:00 a.m. The search for a missing McMinnville woman is active and ongoing. Detective Kevin Taggart of the Myrtle Creek Police said 69-year of Kathleen Wilson has not been found. Taggart said the woman left Myrtle Creek early Monday morning on her way to Chiloquin. Wilson’s 2012 Chevrolet Cruze with Oregon license...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST ADJUSTS CLOSURE ORDER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122228</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/umpqua-national-forest-adjusts-closure-order/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-national-forest-adjusts-closure-order"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 3:50 a.m. Thursday evening, the Umpqua National Forest adjusted a closure order. A UNF update said it includes some exceptions from the previous closure order. This closure, which still impacts all the Cottage Grove Ranger District, most of the Diamond Lake Ranger District, and parts of the Tiller and North Umpqua Ranger...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVIVA HEALTH VACCINE MANAGER WINS BIG AWARD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122225</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/aviva-health-vaccine-manager-wins-big-award/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=aviva-health-vaccine-manager-wins-big-award"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T10:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 3:40 a.m.  Aviva Health’s Community Health Vaccine Manager Sallie Dean has won a big award. On Thursday, the Association of Immunization Managers announced that Sallie Dean is the recipient of its 2024 AIM Champion Award. An Aviva release said according to AIM, “the annual award honors up to one champion from each...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY FAIR DAY THREE ACTIVITIES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122222</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/douglas-county-fair-day-three-activities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-fair-day-three-activities"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T10:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 3:30 a.m. It’s day three of the Douglas County Fair. Admission is free with “Dress a Veggie” at the main gate from 10:00 a.m. to 1:00 p.m. sponsored by True North Restoration. Kids aged 12 and under are admitted for free all day, every day, sponsored by the Cow Creek Band of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOOKINGGLASS ROAD MAINTENANCE STARTS MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122219</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/lookingglass-road-maintenance-starts-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lookingglass-road-maintenance-starts-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T10:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 3:20 a.m. Drivers should use caution and expect delays when three days of maintenance to extend the life of Lookingglass Road begins next week in southwest Roseburg, weather permitting. A city release said starting Monday, August 12th, road maintenance crews from City of Roseburg and Douglas County will apply a chip-seal surface...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG VA OFFERS WHOLE HEALTH TO WELLNESS CLASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122216</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/roseburg-va-offers-whole-health-to-wellness-class/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-va-offers-whole-health-to-wellness-class"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T10:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Roseburg VA Medical Center is an Introduction to Whole Health & Wellness Class for Veterans that asks, “What Matters to You?”. A VA release said the class is part of the Whole Health & Wellness initiative and is an opportunity for veterans to focus on their well-being and personal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WYDEN, SENATORS URGE DOJ TO RESCHEDULE MARIJUANA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122214</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/09/wyden-senators-urge-doj-to-reschedule-marijuana/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wyden-senators-urge-doj-to-reschedule-marijuana"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 9, 2024 2:50 a.m. U.S. Senator Ron Wyden has announced that he and six other senators have sent a letter to Attorney General Merrick Garland and Drug Enforcement Administrator Anne Milgram, expressing their strong support for the DEA’s proposal to transfer marijuana from Schedule I to Schedule III of the Controlled Substances Act. Wyden’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 8.8.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122209</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/08/inside-douglas-county-8-8-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-8-8-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T20:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at 4-H and FFA live from the Douglas County Fair with Roseburg Rotary Auction Chair Rebekah Melton, and participants  Josh Hawley, Hunter Smith, Katelynn Simpson and Ryley Schneider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man who admitted to decade of rape to be released from jail]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7450ab68-55bd-11ef-897b-637c154f0737</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/man-who-admitted-to-decade-of-rape-to-be-released-from-jail/article_7450ab68-55bd-11ef-897b-637c154f0737.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T19:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A man who admitted to raping and sexually abusing a girl for nearly a decade could be released from jail Monday after spending a week in custody at the Douglas County Jail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE FUGITIVE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122207</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/08/roseburg-police-cite-fugitive/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-fugitive"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 8, 2024 11:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a fugitive early Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 12:15 a.m. officers contacted a 26-year-old woman who was setting up camp in an unauthorized location in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Drive. Dispatch advised that the woman had a cite and release warrant for her...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOVERNOR KOTEK INVOKES CONFLAGRATION ACT- TOWN GULCH FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122205</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/08/governor-kotek-invokes-conflagration-act-town-gulch-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=governor-kotek-invokes-conflagration-act-town-gulch-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T17:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 8, 2024 10:50 a.m.  Governor Tina Kotek has authorized the Emergency Conflagration Act in response to the Town Gulch Fire in Baker County. The Baker County Fire Defense Board requested assistance with life, safety, and structural fire protection and the state fire marshal concurred with that request. Kotek said, “Firefighters on the ground have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR PROBATION VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122203</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/08/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-probation-violation-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-probation-violation-4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T17:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 8, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman on a probation violation early Thursday. An RPD report said at 3:00 a.m. the 35-year-old was contacted in the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard, as the officer knew the woman’s probation officer wanted her detained. She was taken into custody without incident and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VEHICLES WRECK ON GARDEN VALLEY BOULEVARD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122200</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/08/vehicles-wreck-on-garden-valley-boulevard/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=vehicles-wreck-on-garden-valley-boulevard"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T17:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 8, 2024 10:20 a.m.   Two vehicles got into a wreck on Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard on Wednesday afternoon. A Roseburg Police report said at 2:10 p.m. a 24-year-old Tenmile man was driving a pickup eastbound in the 700 block and looked down temporarily. When he looked back up, the traffic light was red. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX GROWS BY 1,000 ACRES, 702 PEOPLE ASSIGNED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122196</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/08/diamond-complex-grows-by-1000-acres-702-people-assigned/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-grows-by-1000-acres-702-people-assigned"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T17:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 8, 2024 9:50 a.m.    The Diamond Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, has grown by 1,000 acres to 7,629 acres as of mid-day Thursday. A UNF update said 702 people are assigned to the fire. The Middle Fork Fire, in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 28 people assigned,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX HAS GROWN TO 3,384 ACRES, CONTAINMENT STILL AT 14 PERCENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122192</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/08/homestead-complex-has-grown-to-3384-acres-containment-still-at-14-percent/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-has-grown-to-3384-acres-containment-still-at-14-percent"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T16:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 8, 2024 9:30 a.m.  The Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, has grown to 3,384, with containment remaining at 14 percent. A UNF update said 455 people are working on the fire. It is being managed by Northwest Incident Management Team 8. Wednesday on the 1,269-acre No Man Fire, all lines are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC begins design of Medical Careers Hub and Welcome Center]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4e163146-554c-11ef-b968-cb6ec806e41f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/ucc-begins-design-of-medical-careers-hub-and-welcome-center/article_4e163146-554c-11ef-b968-cb6ec806e41f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Community College has started to make plans for its Medical Careers Hub and Welcome Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Country Financial hosts neighborhood cleanup]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a33c5700-54d8-11ef-8b45-9f13dc65c39d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/country-financial-hosts-neighborhood-cleanup/article_a33c5700-54d8-11ef-8b45-9f13dc65c39d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Rusty Mentes County Financial will host a Diamond Lake Boulevard clean up event 9-11 a.m. Aug. 24. Participants will meet up at the office at 2776 Diamond Lake Blvd. in Roseburg to be assigned an area and clean…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fair time is competition time for animals and children]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/5bc0ec20-5513-11ef-a7dd-77b03c389f6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/fair-time-is-competition-time-for-animals-and-children/article_5bc0ec20-5513-11ef-a7dd-77b03c389f6e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Eric Horton joined South Umpqua FFA about eight or nine months ago, he didn't expect to find himself showing a market goat Wednesday at the Douglas County Fair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forest service grants open for private forest landowners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d6059794-4f5d-11ef-b422-cfa6d31e90f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/forest-service-grants-open-for-private-forest-landowners/article_d6059794-4f5d-11ef-b422-cfa6d31e90f1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UNITED STATES — The U.S. Department of Agriculture's Forest Service has $190 million available to help private forest landowners adapt and mitigate the impacts of climate change to retain working forestlands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smoke diminishes air quality while fires keep raging]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/09c10a6e-54e0-11ef-8bb4-ef87201adc6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/smoke-diminishes-air-quality-while-fires-keep-raging/article_09c10a6e-54e0-11ef-8bb4-ef87201adc6f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intermittent smoke is expected through at least Friday afternoon in multiple counties including eastern Douglas County, according to the Oregon Department of Environmental Quality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slaughter and Great White rock on into the night]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8a996068-5545-11ef-a945-b7d0607459b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/slaughter-and-great-white-rock-on-into-the-night/article_8a996068-5545-11ef-a945-b7d0607459b1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sky above the Douglas County Fairgrounds cleared of the drift smoke to kick off of the Douglas County Fair concert series with a Wednesday night line up of Slaughter followed by Great White.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK POLICE CONTINUE SEARCH FOR MISSING WOMAN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122186</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/08/myrtle-creek-police-continue-search-for-missing-woman/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-police-continue-search-for-missing-woman"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T11:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 8, 2024 4:15 a.m. Myrtle Creek Police are continuing their search for a McMinnville woman who went missing after leaving Myrtle Creek Monday morning. Detective Kevin Taggart said as of early Thursday, neither 69-year-old Kathleen Wilson nor her vehicle have been located. The woman had spent a short time staying at the Mill Site...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>