<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-01-30T15:58:15.436Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tino's Tacos finds its permanent home]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/89dd9e96-bf04-11ee-b986-e39393d1785f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/tinos-tacos-finds-its-permanent-home/article_89dd9e96-bf04-11ee-b986-e39393d1785f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laurentino “Tino” Flores spent two weeks commuting between Springfield and Roseburg when he first opened his food truck Tino’s Tacos in May 2004. On Monday he celebrated his chance at “stability,” at a permanent location on Northeast Stephens Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driver injured after single vehicle crash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2f9f2fc6-bf86-11ee-ada8-1b1606c0bc45</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/driver-injured-after-single-vehicle-crash/article_2f9f2fc6-bf86-11ee-ada8-1b1606c0bc45.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A 41-year-old woman was injured in a single-vehicle crash Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Umpqua superintendent finalists meet with the community]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/19b5cdec-bf26-11ee-9b52-3fd13307238a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/south-umpqua-superintendent-finalists-meet-with-the-community/article_19b5cdec-bf26-11ee-9b52-3fd13307238a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TRI CITY — School staff and parents sat in the wooden chairs in the library at South Umpqua High School, intent on the words spoken by three candidates for the superintendent position at the district.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement to continue search for missing scuba diver]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4529a95a-bf83-11ee-8db5-2fc8642b0b11</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/law-enforcement-to-continue-search-for-missing-scuba-diver/article_4529a95a-bf83-11ee-8db5-2fc8642b0b11.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER BAY — Law enforcement officers are continuing the search for a Eugene man who went missing in the Umpqua River near the mouth of the Pacific Ocean.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIND ADVISORY FROM TUESDAY AFTERNOON THROUGH WEDNESDAY EVENING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115362</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/30/wind-advisory-from-tuesday-afternoon-through-wednesday-evening/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wind-advisory-from-tuesday-afternoon-through-wednesday-evening"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 30, 2024 7:00 a.m.  A Wind Advisory is in effect from 1:00 p.m. Tuesday through 7:00 p.m. Wednesday for parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said the Advisory area includes central Douglas County and its eastern foothills, along with Curry and Josephine counties. It applies to areas above 2000 feet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEARCH CONTINUES FOR MISSING SCUBA DIVER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115359</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/30/search-continues-for-missing-scuba-diver/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=search-continues-for-missing-scuba-diver"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 30, 2024 6:55 a.m.  The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office is continuing the search for a scuba diver who went missing on Sunday. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell said shortly before 3:00 p.m. dispatchers received a call from a woman reporting that her friend, 47-year old Jeffery Scott Harris of Eugene, had gone missing after scuba diving...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER MAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED MYRTLE CREEK BURGLARY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115357</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/30/winchester-man-jailed-for-alleged-myrtle-creek-burglary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winchester-man-jailed-for-alleged-myrtle-creek-burglary"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 30, 2024 6:50 a.m. A Winchester man was jailed for an alleged burglary in the Myrtle Creek area Sunday afternoon. A report from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at 4:45 p.m. a nearby resident called and said she had noticed a light and television on inside a residence in the 1100 block of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN JAILED FOR BEING A FELON IN POSSESSION OF A FIREARM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115355</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/30/myrtle-creek-man-jailed-for-being-a-felon-in-possession-of-a-firearm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-jailed-for-being-a-felon-in-possession-of-a-firearm"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 30, 2024 6:50 a.m. A Myrtle Creek man was jailed for being a felon in possession of firearms, following an incident early Sunday. A report from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at 4:15 a.m. a deputy was dispatched to a disturbance involving the victim and 29-year old Anthony Smith in the 100 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRIVER INJURED AFTER SINGLE-VEHICLE WRECK ON SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115353</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/30/driver-injured-after-single-vehicle-wreck-on-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=driver-injured-after-single-vehicle-wreck-on-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 30, 2024 6:30 a.m.  The driver was injured after a single-vehicle crash on Sunday. A report from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at 4:35 p.m. the 41-year old was traveling west in the 2000 block of Del Rio Road when her vehicle left the opposite side of the road, crashing through a mailbox...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search Continues for Missing Scuba Diver (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news169679</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news169679"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T04:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER BAY, Ore. - A Eugene man who went scuba diving in the Umpqua River near the mouth of the Pacific Ocean is considered missing after he did not surface. 
On Sunday, January 29, 2024, shortly before 3:00 p.m., 9-1-1 dispatchers received a call from a female reporting her friend, 47-year-old Jeffery Scott Harris of Eugene, missing. Harris had gone scuba diving in the Umpqua River near the mouth of the Pacific Ocean in Winchester Bay at approximately 12:30 p.m. Sunday afternoon. Harris, who had previous diving experience, had not returned prompting the call to emergency personnel. 
The Douglas County Sheriff's Office, along with the United States Coast Guard (USCG), began a large-scale search for Harris. Two USCG Boats along with a helicopter searched the water. The Sheriff's Office Search and Rescue unit searched by land with K9 teams and ATVs until dark. 
On Monday, searchers resumed their efforts by water and ground. Dive Rescue teams from Douglas County and Lane County attempted to dive in the morning during low tide but had to abort efforts due to dangerous diving conditions. The USCG helicopter assisted in searching throughout the morning. 
“We have been in communication with Jeffrey's family and have kept them updated as to the efforts that are being made. We are doing everything we can to assist them in locating Jeffrey,” Lt. Brad O'Dell said. “Deputies will return Tuesday to patrol the area by land. We are also coordinating with outside agencies to determine if specialized underwater searching equipment can be utilized in the conditions.”
The Sheriff's Office has been assisted by the United States Coast Guard, Oregon State SAR Coordinator, CAHOOTS of Eugene, Lane County Search and Rescue, Douglas County Marine Patrol and Douglas County Search and Rescue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Editor's Note: Dedicated to bringing you the news]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4542a58e-beef-11ee-bc93-9f2eccd4d370</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/editors-note-dedicated-to-bringing-you-the-news/article_4542a58e-beef-11ee-bc93-9f2eccd4d370.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lotus Media, the Roseburg company that owns The News-Review, was hacked and held ransom. We have tech experts working on retrieving as much data as possible, but it means there will be no print newspaper Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jungle Things Oregon celebrates grand opening]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/be6183bc-bd79-11ee-a869-87c10183392e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/jungle-things-oregon-celebrates-grand-opening/article_be6183bc-bd79-11ee-a869-87c10183392e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entering Jungle Things Oregon feels like walking into an actual jungle, as the store is kept in a constant state of humid warmth for the various species of snakes, lizards, turtles and other reptiles that call the store home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HAS RECORD HIGH FOR THE DATE ON SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115350</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/29/roseburg-has-record-high-for-the-date-on-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-has-record-high-for-the-date-on-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T12:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 29, 2024 4:00 a.m. Roseburg had a record high for the date on Sunday. Data from the National Weather Service said the mercury reached 68 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport. The previous record high for January 28th was 64 degrees, which happened in 1998. Roseburg is expected to see a high in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DENSE FOG ADVISORY THROUGH 9:00 A.M. MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115347</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/29/dense-fog-advisory-through-900-a-m-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dense-fog-advisory-through-900-a-m-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 29, 2024 3:40  a.m. A Dense Fog Advisory is in effect through 9:00 a.m. Monday for central Douglas County. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said visibility is less than a quarter of a mile in dense fog. This applies to the central Umpqua Valley from Canyonville to Curtin. Forecasters said driving conditions are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTH UMPQUA SCHOOL BOARD HOLDING FINALIST FORUM MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115343</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/29/south-umpqua-school-board-holding-finalist-forum-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=south-umpqua-school-board-holding-finalist-forum-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 29, 2024 3:30 a.m. The South Umpqua District School Board recently named the finalists to be the district’s next superintendent and is holding a Finalist Forum on Monday. The finalists are: *Erika Bare, current assistant superintendent in the Ashland School District *Brad Capener, current superintendent for the Jefferson School District in Jefferson, Oregon *Carl...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODF SOUTHWEST OREGON DISTRICT NOW HIRING FOR 2024 SEASON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115341</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/29/odf-southwest-oregon-district-now-hiring-for-2024-season/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=odf-southwest-oregon-district-now-hiring-for-2024-season"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 29, 2024 3:10 a.m. The Oregon Department of Forestry Southwest Oregon District is recruiting for multiple positions for the upcoming fire season, including entry-level and experienced firefighters, dispatchers and detection specialists, totaling approximately 130 jobs in Josephine and Jackson counties. Natalie Weber of the ODF said these seasonal positions generally span from June through...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FREE PLANT CLINIC IN ROSEBURG TO EXPAND HOURS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115339</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/29/free-plant-clinic-in-roseburg-to-expand-hours/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=free-plant-clinic-in-roseburg-to-expand-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 29, 2024 3:00 a.m. Beginning in February, the Oregon State University Master Gardener Plant Clinic will be open Mondays, Wednesdays and Fridays from 1:00 p.m. to 4:00 p.m. Master Gardener Cheryl Caplan said the Plant Clinic is a free service to the public where master gardeners work to solve gardening questions from the public....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DANCING FRIENDS OF ROSEBURG WITH TWO STEP DANCE CLASSES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115337</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/29/dancing-friends-of-roseburg-with-two-step-dance-classes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dancing-friends-of-roseburg-with-two-step-dance-classes"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 29, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Dancing Friends of Roseburg will offer learn to dance “Two Step” classes starting this Thursday night. Weekly classes will run through May 23rd from 6:00 p.m. to 8:00 p.m. at the Buckaroo Barn on Northeast Stephens Street between Costco and Winchester. Couples and singles are welcome. Open enrollment will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENT JAILED FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT IN DRAIN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115335</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/28/transient-jailed-for-alleged-trespass-incident-in-drain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transient-jailed-for-alleged-trespass-incident-in-drain"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T22:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 28, 2024 3:00 p.m.  A transient was jailed for an alleged trespass incident in Drain early Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 1:30 a.m. a deputy responded to the 100 block of East B Avenue. A victim advised that a 61-year old man would not leave her residence after being told...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG WOMAN CHARGED WITH MENACING AND HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115331</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/28/roseburg-woman-charged-with-menacing-and-harassment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-woman-charged-with-menacing-and-harassment"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T22:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 28, 2024 2:40 p.m.  A Roseburg woman was charged with menacing and harassment early Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 12:30 a.m. the 35-year allegedly hit a victim across the chest with a metal broom, punched him in the nose and swung a machete around the home with children present, in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCSO JAILS TRANSIENT FOR 13 WARRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115329</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/28/dcso-jails-transient-for-13-warrants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dcso-jails-transient-for-13-warrants"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T22:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 28, 2024 2:20 p.m. The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a transient who had 13 warrants for this arrest on Friday. A DCSO report said at 5:20 p.m. a deputy contacted 20-year old Taylor Pennington in the 5000 block of Elkhead Road in Yoncalla. A resident said a new couple was staying at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YONCALLA MAN ARRESTED FOLLOWING BURGLARY INVESTIGATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115327</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/28/yoncalla-man-arrested-following-burglary-investigation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=yoncalla-man-arrested-following-burglary-investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T21:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 28, 2024 1:50 p.m. A Yoncalla man was arrested following a burglary investigation by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office on Friday. A DCSO report said a deputy had been the investigating the incident at a storage unit facility in the 2500 block of Eagle Valley Road in Yoncalla since January 18th. The deputy had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENT JAILED FOR WARRANT, CITED FOR VIOLATION AMOUNT OF METHAMPHETAMINE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115325</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/28/transient-jailed-for-warrant-cited-for-violation-amount-of-methamphetamine/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transient-jailed-for-warrant-cited-for-violation-amount-of-methamphetamine"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 28, 2024 1:30 p.m.  A deputy with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a transient for a warrant and cited him on a drug charge early Friday. A DCSO report said at 12:45 a.m. the 34-year was spotted during a security check under the Exit 106 overpass at Weaver Road near Myrtle Creek. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club News: Hobbit Trail hike scheduled for Feb. 3]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7f1ae02c-bb9e-11ee-8c75-7b40745ee646</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/club-news-hobbit-trail-hike-scheduled-for-feb-3/article_7f1ae02c-bb9e-11ee-8c75-7b40745ee646.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Friends of the Umpqua Hiking Club hike is scheduled for Feb. 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plant clinic expands hours]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/5d023b24-bc94-11ee-a4ad-5f0d14846431</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/plant-clinic-expands-hours/article_5d023b24-bc94-11ee-a4ad-5f0d14846431.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Starting in February, the Oregon State University Extension Master Gardener Plant Clinic will be open 1-4 p.m. Monday, Wednesday and Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I-5 GARDEN VALLEY BOULEVARD OFF-RAMP TO CLOSE AT NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115322</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/27/i-5-garden-valley-boulevard-off-ramp-to-close-at-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=i-5-garden-valley-boulevard-off-ramp-to-close-at-night"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T17:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 27, 2024 9:20 a.m. The Interstate north-bound off-ramp at Exit 125, Garden Valley Boulevard in Roseburg, will be close Sunday, Monday and Tuesday nights, January 28th-30th, for construction. Dan Latham of the Oregon Department of Transportation said a three-mile detour will be provided for the 8:00 p.m. to 6:00 a.m. closures. Latham said northbound...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamper Korner RV Center merges with Wagers RV Center & Consignment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/512197ba-b707-11ee-8fa4-6f9128c672a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/kamper-korner-rv-center-merges-with-wagers-rv-center-consignment/article_512197ba-b707-11ee-8fa4-6f9128c672a8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamper Korner RV Center entered a merger with Wagers RV Center & Consignment, a 50-year-old Salem-based parts and service dealership, with changes starting in February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reading year off to a good start]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/14407306-bbd1-11ee-b584-138d651a0338</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/reading-year-off-to-a-good-start/article_14407306-bbd1-11ee-b584-138d651a0338.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only resolution I make every new year involves reading. This year I promised myself I would do my best to read 200 books, which would be a record.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley for The News Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does the 4-H clover represent?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/78249bae-bb09-11ee-88c1-6f1866f63b7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/what-does-the-4-h-clover-represent/article_78249bae-bb09-11ee-88c1-6f1866f63b7d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What qualities does 4-H represent? In 1911, club leaders in Washington D.C. adopted the current 4-H design; a green four-leaf clover with a single “H” on each leaf with the stem facing right. Who knew that the start of this…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATIE BAXTER For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farm Bureau announces scholarships]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4160b2be-b94d-11ee-835c-cf441cf7c180</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/farm-bureau-announces-scholarships/article_4160b2be-b94d-11ee-835c-cf441cf7c180.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Farm Bureau will be awarding up to five $1,000 scholarships for the 2024-2025 school year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to Know Douglas ESD: Empowering youth through mental health support]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6dfe8f60-baf8-11ee-a5b9-63b7fbf04fba</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/get-to-know-douglas-esd-empowering-youth-through-mental-health-support/article_6dfe8f60-baf8-11ee-a5b9-63b7fbf04fba.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erin Payne hit the ground running. She’s a Douglas Education Service District behavior interventionist at Days Creek Charter School District.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HEATHER VILLA For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New secure entrance at Roseburg schools]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b2412520-bc06-11ee-8c37-1fd7ac8dc4eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/new-secure-entrance-at-roseburg-schools/article_b2412520-bc06-11ee-8c37-1fd7ac8dc4eb.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several schools in the Roseburg Public School District are in the process of receiving security upgrades to entry ways. Right now, these upgrades are in the form of new secure entrances, called vestibules, being built in the entry building to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Christian Schools hosts First Pitch dinner]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/41ddbdb0-ba6d-11ee-b5c7-bbdb2295fd87</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/umpqua-valley-christian-schools-hosts-first-pitch-dinner/article_41ddbdb0-ba6d-11ee-b5c7-bbdb2295fd87.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Christian School is hosting a First Pitch dinner fundraiser for its baseball team at 6 p.m. Feb. 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Board approves storage building at Roseburg High School]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/34e406ba-bcc9-11ee-ad30-ebe1df5191f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/board-approves-storage-building-at-roseburg-high-school/article_34e406ba-bcc9-11ee-ad30-ebe1df5191f2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T04:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new performing arts storage building will come to Roseburg High School.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>