<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-04-06T19:07:55.055Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRANTS PASS WOMAN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING EARLY SATURDAY MORNING CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117414</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/06/grants-pass-woman-taken-to-hospital-following-early-saturday-morning-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=grants-pass-woman-taken-to-hospital-following-early-saturday-morning-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T16:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 9:15 a.m. A Grants Pass woman was taken to the hospital following a single vehicle wreck early Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 2:30 a.m. units responded to the accident in the 2800 block of Bilger Creek Road near Glendale.  Upon arrival they found the 44-year-old driver in her...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COTTAGE GROVE MEN JAILED FOR FREEWAY DUII]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117412</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/06/cottage-grove-men-jailed-for-freeway-duii/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cottage-grove-men-jailed-for-freeway-duii"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T15:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April April 6, 9:00 a.m. Two Cottage Grove men were jailed for an alleged DUII incident early Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 12:00 a.m. a deputy stopped a pickup on Interstate Five about a mile north of the Yoncalla/Drain interchange due to speed and seeing a beer can being thrown...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FRIDAY FIRE CLAIMS LIFE OF ROSEBURG MAN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117409</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/06/friday-fire-claims-life-of-roseburg-man/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=friday-fire-claims-life-of-roseburg-man"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T15:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 8:00 a.m. A residential structure fire Friday night claimed the life of a Roseburg man. Fire Chief Tyler Christopherson of the Roseburg Fire Department said just after 7:50 p.m. personnel responded to the fire with a known rescue in the 700 block of West Wharton Street. Christopherson said firefighters arrived on the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fatal Residential Structure Fire - 737 W. Wharton Street - 4-5-24 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news171318</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news171318"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T14:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 7:53 p.m. on April 5, 2024, Roseburg Fire Department personnel responded to a residential structure fire with a known rescue at 737 W. Wharton Street.  Firefighters arrived on scene to find a single-family residential structure with heavy fire and smoke coming from the left, front corner of the home with smoke alarms sounding. Upon arrival, a female resident informed fire crews that her husband was still inside the structure near the front of the home.
Fire crews entered the single-family residence in rescue mode. Crews were able to quickly locate the seventy-one year old male resident near the front of the home and found him to be unconscious.  Crews quickly removed the victim through the front door of the home.  The patient was transported to a nearby hospital, where the victim succumbed to his injuries and was pronounced deceased.  Crews extinguished the fire and completed overhaul of the structure. 
The single-family residence sustained structural, smoke, and water damage.  A fire investigator was on scene and the exact cause of the fire is under investigation. Sixteen firefighters assisted with firefighting operations.  Other agencies assisting with the fire included Umpqua Valley Ambulance, Douglas County Fire District #2, Roseburg Police Department, Avista Utilities, and Pacific Power. 
The Roseburg Fire Department would like to remind everyone of the importance of working smoke alarms and ensuring you have the appropriate number of smoke alarms installed in the home.  Remember to make sure you have working smoke alarms on every level of your home, outside each sleeping area and in every bedroom.  Roseburg Fire Department recommends that homeowners consider a home fire sprinkler system for increased protection.
For the latest information regarding the City of Roseburg Fire Department, please visit our website at www.cityofroseburg.org or like us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/roseburgfire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Fire Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STABBING SUSPECT ARRESTED AND JAILED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117407</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/06/stabbing-suspect-arrested-and-jailed/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=stabbing-suspect-arrested-and-jailed"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T14:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 7:30 a.m.  The suspect in an early morning stabbing in Roseburg on Thursday was arrested Friday afternoon. Sergeant Daniel Allen of Roseburg Police said 20-year-old Zane Everett Johnston was contacted by detectives in a parking lot in the 100 block of Sunshine Road at approximately 1:50 p.m. and arrested without incident. Johnston...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRAFFIC STOP LEADS TO SEIZURE OF FENTANYL AND METH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117402</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/06/traffic-stop-leads-to-seizure-of-fentanyl-and-meth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=traffic-stop-leads-to-seizure-of-fentanyl-and-meth"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 7:00 a.m. A recent traffic stop on Interstate 5 near Rice Hill led to the seizure of large quantities of methamphetamine and fentanyl which had been headed for the streets of Portland. An Oregon State Police report said on April 1st at 9:00 a.m. a trooper stopped a northbound sedan for a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friends of the Umpqua Hiking Club visits Goodman Creek]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d196fa16-f2c1-11ee-9918-27dea5c7064a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/friends-of-the-umpqua-hiking-club-visits-goodman-creek/article_d196fa16-f2c1-11ee-9918-27dea5c7064a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Friends of the Umpqua Hiking Club will be hiking Goodman Creek on April 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing our love of books and reading]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/af46e3b0-f1fc-11ee-9ddd-ab0752a79ba2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/sharing-our-love-of-books-and-reading/article_af46e3b0-f1fc-11ee-9ddd-ab0752a79ba2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a fun and easy way to get book recommendations, try one of Roseburg Public Library’s book groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley for The News Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County recreation report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/842f018e-f2a7-11ee-87d4-5340ab00305e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/douglas-county-recreation-report/article_842f018e-f2a7-11ee-87d4-5340ab00305e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FISHING REPORT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The greatness grind: Striving for success at state convention]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3057f1f4-f2c2-11ee-8b4f-dbc474998272</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/the-greatness-grind-striving-for-success-at-state-convention/article_3057f1f4-f2c2-11ee-8b4f-dbc474998272.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REDMOND — Over 3,000 FFA members were ready to compete, make new friends, and explore their leadership capabilities, as they gathered at the Redmond Expo Center on March 21 for the 96th Annual State Convention.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HAILEY HOLGATE For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cascade Community Credit Union ranked No. 2 in the nation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4126271e-f2c0-11ee-89ba-8fa455840c38</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/cascade-community-credit-union-ranked-no-2-in-the-nation/article_4126271e-f2c0-11ee-89ba-8fa455840c38.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cascade Community Credit Union has received top rankings through the nationally recognized S&P Global Market Intelligence list, achieving the rank of No. 1 credit union in Oregon and No. 2 in the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elkton FFA prepares for annual spring sale]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/11bfac32-f2b3-11ee-a1c2-ab21255c1fe4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/elkton-ffa-prepares-for-annual-spring-sale/article_11bfac32-f2b3-11ee-a1c2-ab21255c1fe4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T00:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ELKTON — Hanging flower bowls, plants, vegetable starts and metal art will be available for the greater community in about two weeks through Elkton FFA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE WOMAN DIES IN VEHICLE VERSUS PEDESTRIAN CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117400</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/canyonville-woman-dies-in-vehicle-versus-pedestrian-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=canyonville-woman-dies-in-vehicle-versus-pedestrian-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T21:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 2:30 p.m.  A Canyonville woman died in a vehicle versus pedestrian crash early Thursday morning. An Oregon State Police report said at 3:00 a.m. troopers responded to the accident on Interstate Five northbound in the Canyonville area. Captain Kyle Kennedy said a preliminary investigation indicated that the pedestrian, 82-year-old Sally Kaye Bidlake,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON WOMAN ARRESTED FOR ANIMAL ABUSE AND NEGLECT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117398</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/winston-woman-arrested-for-animal-abuse-and-neglect/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-woman-arrested-for-animal-abuse-and-neglect"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T21:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Winston woman has been arrested on charges of animal abuse and neglect. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said deputies began an investigation early this week after receiving a tip of a horse that was being mistreated at a property in the 600 block of Longhorn Lane in the Melrose area....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winston Woman Arrested for Animal Abuse and Neglect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news171306</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news171306"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T20:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG, Ore. - A Winston woman has been arrested on charges of animal abuse and neglect.
Douglas County Sheriff's Office Animal Control deputies began an investigation early this week after receiving a tip of a horse that was reported to be mistreated at a property in the 600-block of Longhorn Lane. During the investigation, deputies learned the horse and property owner had no connection.
Deputies discovered a 3-year-old mixed breed horse, named Ace, who was found to be severely malnourished and in neglectful conditions. Ace's owner, 24-year-old Morgan Faith Fowler of Winston, surrendered the horse to deputies on Wednesday who took it to a veterinary hospital for examination and later to Strawberry Mountain Rescue and Rehabilitation Center. Overnight, Ace's condition declined to the point that euthanasia was necessary for humane care.
Deputies contacted Fowler Thursday afternoon and took her into custody for Animal Neglect I and Animal Abuse II. She was transported to the Douglas County Jail where she was booked on those charges.
"This is a very severe case of neglect and abuse," Sheriff John Hanlin said. "The Douglas County Sheriff's Office is continuing its investigation and will provide all relevant facts to the Douglas County District Attorney's Office."
Anyone who may have information regarding this case is encouraged to contact the Douglas County Sheriff's Office at 541-440-4471 referencing case #24-1522.
Sheriff Hanlin expressed his thanks to Bailey Veterinary Clinic, Strawberry Mountain Rescue and Rehabilitation Center and to the deputies and volunteers who worked to save Ace and are now working on holding Fowler accountable. "These cases are never easy and I cannot thank those who have been involved enough," the Sheriff remarked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deputies arrest mounted posse member on horse neglect and abuse charges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6cda4898-f38a-11ee-89d1-2f846b36fee4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/deputies-arrest-mounted-posse-member-on-horse-neglect-and-abuse-charges/article_6cda4898-f38a-11ee-89d1-2f846b36fee4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T20:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Oregon equestrian and member of the Douglas County Mounted Posse has been arrested on allegations she neglected and abused a horse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Alderman NW Horse Report</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR ALLEGED PRIOR THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117394</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-alleged-prior-theft-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-alleged-prior-theft-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T17:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 10:50 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a woman for an alleged prior theft incident on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report said around 4:50 p.m. officers contacted the 42-year-old in the 900 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. She had been observed on video stealing nearly $300 in merchandise from a business in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE ARREST WOMAN FOR ALLEGED CRIMINAL TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117391</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/roseburg-police-arrest-woman-for-alleged-criminal-trespass/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-arrest-woman-for-alleged-criminal-trespass"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T17:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 10:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police arrested a woman for alleged criminal trespass on Thursday. An RPD report said at 8:00 a.m. the 45-year returned to a business in the 1800 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard after being trespassed from the location less than an hour earlier. She was charged with second-degree criminal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL TWO MYRTLE CREEK RESIDENTS FOR UNLAWFUL USE OF A VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117389</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/roseburg-police-jail-two-myrtle-creerk-residents-for-unlawful-use-of-a-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-two-myrtle-creerk-residents-for-unlawful-use-of-a-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T17:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 9:50 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed two Myrtle Creek residents for unlawful use of a motor vehicle early Friday. An RPD report said a victim reported that his pickup was stolen from the parking lot of a business in the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. The vehicle left the area and came back...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BURN PERMITS AVAILABLE STARTING SOON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117387</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/burn-permits-available-starting-soon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=burn-permits-available-starting-soon"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T16:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 9:30 a.m. The City of Roseburg Fire Department will begin issuing residential burn permits soon. Permits are only available between April 15th and May 15th. Permits will be issued for seven days at a cost of $75. Residential yard waste is the only material that may be burned. Prohibited items include standing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jammin' out at the Oregon Oldtime Fiddlers' convention]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/14709112-f114-11ee-859a-9318ec5916ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/jammin-out-at-the-oregon-oldtime-fiddlers-convention/article_14709112-f114-11ee-859a-9318ec5916ee.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — A small group of people inside the Winston Assembly of God were enjoying a jam session.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A rainy start to the Sutherlin Farmers' Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/adec92a8-f116-11ee-b15e-8b3f85757127</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/a-rainy-start-to-the-sutherlin-farmers-market/article_adec92a8-f116-11ee-b15e-8b3f85757127.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Customers trickled in slowly as did the rain at the opening day of the Sutherlin Farmers’ Market on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C&D Lumber Co. announces permanent closure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/89b96ea2-f2dc-11ee-af42-834ca82fa1b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/c-d-lumber-co-announces-permanent-closure/article_89b96ea2-f2dc-11ee-af42-834ca82fa1b4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE — C&D Lumber Co. announced its permanent closure Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say farewell to Oakland bridge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/046779c2-f35b-11ee-906d-930e2bf8ae6b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/history/say-farewell-to-oakland-bridge/article_046779c2-f35b-11ee-906d-930e2bf8ae6b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T14:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — The city of Oakland is encouraging residents from all over Douglas County to celebrate the Historic Oakland Bridge with a Sunday Stroll.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Road to close for construction]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c5660aee-f2c0-11ee-86b1-8707cf20e941</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/road-to-close-for-construction/article_c5660aee-f2c0-11ee-86b1-8707cf20e941.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — Green Valley Road is scheduled to close at the Old Highway 99 intersection in Oakland from 7 a.m. to 5 p.m. Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Worms in the garden]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ba0a5df4-f03f-11ee-8afb-436cc16ad197</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/ask-a-master-gardener-worms-in-the-garden/article_ba0a5df4-f03f-11ee-8afb-436cc16ad197.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I am a home gardener and have recently seen vermicomposting gaining more and more popularity. I am looking to start my own bin, but I’m not sure where to start? Can you please tell me more about using worms…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MACKENZI HALL Master Gardener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County will see partial solar eclipse Monday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e47aade4-f2c1-11ee-a8d6-536962ea655f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/douglas-county-will-see-partial-solar-eclipse-monday/article_e47aade4-f2c1-11ee-a8d6-536962ea655f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A total eclipse will cover parts of North America on Monday as the moon attempts to hides the sun. Douglas County, and most of Oregon in general, will not be in the direct path, but there will still be opportunities…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UVA hosts open house for exhibits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/183c16c4-f2d9-11ee-84a8-67d0654ae89c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/uva-hosts-open-house-for-exhibits/article_183c16c4-f2d9-11ee-84a8-67d0654ae89c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — An open house at Umpqua Valley Arts will welcome five new exhibits from 4-7 p.m. Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C&D LUMBER ANNOUNCES PERMANENT CLOSURE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117381</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/cd-lumber-announces-permanent-closure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cd-lumber-announces-permanent-closure"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T11:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 5, 2024 4:00 a.m. In the KQEN Business Spotlight: After over 130 years, a local timber company is closing. On Thursday, Riddle based C&D Lumber issued a release which said, “It is with profound regret that the board of directors of C&D Lumber Co. announces the permanent closure of our operations”. Founded in 1890...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED PRIOR MENACING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117379</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/deputies-jail-man-for-alleged-prior-menacing-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-jail-man-for-alleged-prior-menacing-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T10:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 5, 2024 3:30 a.m. Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a Roseburg man Wednesday for crimes associated with an alleged prior menacing incident. A DCSO report said at on March 10th at approximately 11:15 a.m. two victims went to a residence in the 5000 block of Little River Road in the Glide...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUNDAY STROLL ON OAKLAND BRIDGE SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117377</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/sunday-stroll-on-oakland-bridge-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sunday-stroll-on-oakland-bridge-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T10:18:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 5, 2024 3:20 a.m. The City of Oakland is encouraging residents from all over Douglas County to celebrate the Historic Oakland Bridge with a Sunday Stroll this weekend. With demolition of the 99-year-old bridge set to begin later this month, the event is happening so people can walk on the bridge and enjoy the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOLAR ECLIPSE MONDAY AT UCC’S MORGAN OBSERVATORY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117375</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/solar-eclipse-monday-at-uccs-morgan-observatory/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=solar-eclipse-monday-at-uccs-morgan-observatory"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T10:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 5, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Paul Morgan Observatory at Umpqua Community College will hold a public watch party for the solar eclipse on Monday. A UCC release said that the rare event will occur as the moon passes over the sun for a few minutes. The next total solar eclipse will not occur in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOOD WASTE PREVENTION WEEK AND BEYOND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117373</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/05/food-waste-prevention-week-and-beyond/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=food-waste-prevention-week-and-beyond"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T10:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 5, 2024 2:50 a.m. A collaborative effort of several Douglas County organizations has announced a series of events for this year’s National Food Waste Prevention Week. Events will continue throughout the month. Organizations involved include Thrive Umpqua, Umpqua Valley Farm to School, HealTerra, Umpqua Valley Farmer’s Market, the City of Roseburg and Douglas County...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circus is coming to Sutherlin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/44e1ba7c-f201-11ee-a803-57b0d65d99e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/circus-is-coming-to-sutherlin/article_44e1ba7c-f201-11ee-a803-57b0d65d99e1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T21:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — The Culpepper and Merriweather Circus is coming to Lauren Young Park in Sutherlin with two shows May 20.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inspection delays slows move for forest service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f9a1beb2-f2bf-11ee-bb36-63a6c8c12bb4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/inspection-delays-slows-move-for-forest-service/article_f9a1beb2-f2bf-11ee-bb36-63a6c8c12bb4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T20:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — An inspection delay has slowed the move of the Umpqua National Forest Service staff relocating to the new Roseburg Interagency Office at 777 NW Garden Valley Blvd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PORTLAND WOMAN CHARGED WITH THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117367</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/portland-woman-charged-with-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=portland-woman-charged-with-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T18:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 11:00 a.m.  A Portland woman was charged with third degree theft by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office on Wednesday. A DCSO report said at approximately 5:15 p.m. two people were contacted in a pickup near the intersection of Toketee Rigdon Road and Thorn Prairie Road in the Umpqua National Forest. The woman,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PROSPECT MAN CHARGED WITH DUII]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117365</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/prospect-man-charged-with-duii/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=prospect-man-charged-with-duii"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T17:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 10:30 a.m.  A Prospect man was charged with DUII by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office late Wednesday. A DCSO report said at 11:00 p.m. a deputy responded to a non-injury crash in the 300 block John Long Road in the Oakland area. The 55-year-old driver showed signs of impairment. He refused standard...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED ASSAULT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117363</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/deputies-jail-man-for-alleged-assault-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-jail-man-for-alleged-assault-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T17:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 10:15 a.m.  Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a man following an alleged assault incident early Tuesday. A DCSO report said at 6:50 a.m. 40-year-old Joshua Harding was detoxing from methamphetamine and acted out due to a perceived lack food being in the house at a residence in the 100...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES JAIL PAIR FOR SOUTH COUNTY ASSAULT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117361</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/deputies-jail-pair-for-south-county-assault/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-jail-pair-for-south-county-assault"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T16:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 9:50 a.m.   Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed two people following an alleged incident in south county on Wednesday night. A DCSO report the female suspect and the victim had both taken items from each other on prior incidents. Just after 10:30 p.m. the woman and the male suspect, both...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DWS/DRIVING UNINSURED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117359</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-dws-driving-uninsured/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-dws-driving-uninsured"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T16:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for driving while suspended and driving uninsured on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 10:20 p.m. officers stopped the 47-year-old for driving with no lights on Northeast Walnut Street near Northeast Garden Valley Boulevard. He was released after the citations were issued.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR LITTERING, CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117357</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-littering-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-littering-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T16:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man on littering and camping charges on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 11:00 a.m. officers contacted the 55-year-old at his camp in the 900 block of Northwest Rowe Street. The camp was on the bike path over the old train trestle. The contents of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT FOLLOWING DISTRUBANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117355</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-following-distrubance/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-following-distrubance"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T16:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 9:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant following a disturbance on Wednesday. An RPD report said just before 12:00 p.m. officers contacted the 44-year-old following a disturbance at Stewart Park in the 2000 block of Stewart Park Drive. The man was known to have a warrant for his arrest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Forestry names Pendleton as Oregon Tree City of the Year (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171265</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171265"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T16:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PENDLETON, Ore. – The Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) has named Pendleton as Oregon’s Tree City of the Year. It’s an unusual honor given that the town in northeast Oregon is surrounded by rolling grasslands and was largely treeless except along the Umatilla River when Pendleton was laid out in 1868. Early city residents wasted no time planting trees to buffer the winds and offer shade from the area’s hot summers.
That tree-planting tradition has continued to this day. In partnership with the Umatilla National Forest and the volunteer-led Tree Commission, the city annually distributes free trees to residents during an Arbor Day celebration, giving away 250 last year and nearly 700 over the past 4 years.
A city of more than 16,000 people, Pendleton has maintained its status as a Tree Cit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compliance Monitoring Program Committee meets April 11]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171263</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171263"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T15:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Compliance Monitoring Program Committee will hold a virtual meeting Thursday, April 11, from 9 to 11 a.m. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes:

Mount Hood Environmental presentation – Pilot study development

The meeting is open to the public to attend online via Zoom. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours before the meeting by emailing marta.l.friasbedolla@odf.oregon.gov.
The CMP Committee assists efforts to monitor compliance with Forest Practices Rules. The committee advises ODF regarding monitoring projects and procedures. View more information on the CMPC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Realtors association hosting free fair housing webinar]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8cff7d66-f117-11ee-950a-17093ec904bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/realtors-association-hosting-free-fair-housing-webinar/article_8cff7d66-f117-11ee-950a-17093ec904bf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Douglas County Association of Realtors is sponsoring a webinar on fair housing and equitable service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urban Health Chiropractic opens Monday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d77df99e-f1cb-11ee-a30e-6f78972ac3ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/urban-health-chiropractic-opens-monday/article_d77df99e-f1cb-11ee-a30e-6f78972ac3ff.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Urban Health Chiropractic, a new chiropractic clinic in Roseburg, will be opening its doors to patients starting Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Hunters Banquet takes place this weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e10e697c-f111-11ee-9946-a78166f7978d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/oregon-hunters-banquet-takes-place-this-weekend/article_e10e697c-f111-11ee-9946-a78166f7978d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE — Oregon Hunters Association’s Umpqua chapter is taking its fundraising efforts by the horns at its 24th annual banquet Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas Electric Cooperative hosting annual meeting]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1f43b83e-f1f1-11ee-a429-e37081ef8c4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/douglas-electric-cooperative-hosting-annual-meeting/article_1f43b83e-f1f1-11ee-a429-e37081ef8c4f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once a year, Douglas Electric Cooperative members have the chance to hear a rundown of how the cooperative’s year went and actively make suggestions for the year to come — and snag a free lunch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silent disco returns to Millsite Park]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2b06197e-f1c8-11ee-9d18-8721661fce6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/silent-disco-returns-to-millsite-park/article_2b06197e-f1c8-11ee-9d18-8721661fce6d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — Friends of the Myrtle Creek Library and Myrtle Creeks Elks Lodge No. 1943 are presenting a silent disco event April 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg High opens its gates to the public, incoming students]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2762a31c-f224-11ee-a9ed-c375b24d72b1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/roseburg-high-opens-its-gates-to-the-public-incoming-students/article_2762a31c-f224-11ee-a9ed-c375b24d72b1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eighth graders and their families arrived at Roseburg High School on Wednesday evening to view the school they will become a part of at the start of next school year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waste not want not: National Food Waste Prevention Week is here]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/004ccb8a-f10d-11ee-afc4-c37a1554035e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/waste-not-want-not-national-food-waste-prevention-week-is-here/article_004ccb8a-f10d-11ee-afc4-c37a1554035e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's National Food Waste Prevention Week and it comes with events, activities and ideas to guide communities on how to cut down on food waste.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN VALLEY ROAD WILL CLOSE AT OLD HIGHWAY 99 IN OAKLAND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117348</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/green-valley-road-will-close-at-old-highway-99-in-oakland/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=green-valley-road-will-close-at-old-highway-99-in-oakland"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 6:00 a.m. Green Valley Road is scheduled to close at the Old Highway 99 intersection in Oakland from 7:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. on Monday, April 8th. A release from the Oregon Department of Transportation said the closure is due to paving work near the north end of the new Oakland Bridge....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HIGH DROPS 28 DEGREES ON WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117345</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/roseburg-high-drops-28-degrees-on-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-high-drops-28-degrees-on-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T11:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 2024 4:00 p.m.  Roseburg’s high temperature dropped 28 degrees on Wednesday, in comparison to the high recorded on Tuesday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said the mercury reached just 52 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport. That compares with a high of 80 degrees which was set on Tuesday. Rainy conditions are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG VA WOMEN VETERAN’S TOWN HALL TUESDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117343</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/roseburg-va-women-veterans-town-hall-tuesday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-va-women-veterans-town-hall-tuesday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T10:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 3:50 a.m. The Roseburg VA Health Care System will have a Women Veterans Town Hall on Tuesday night. It will take place from 5:30 p.m.to 6:30 p.m. in the Roseburg VA Medical Center Auditorium. Those attending will hear from VA leadership and have an opportunity to get their questions answered. For more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CASCADE RANKED #2 CREDIT UNION IN THE NATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117340</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/cascade-ranked-2-credit-union-in-the-nation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cascade-ranked-2-credit-union-in-the-nation"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T10:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 3:30 a.m. In the KQEN Business Spotlight: Cascade Community Credit Union has received top rankings through the nationally recognized S&P Global Market Intelligence list, achieving the rank of #1 credit union in Oregon, and #2 of 4,900 credit unions in the United States, for 2023. Cascade Marketing Director Shelby Beattie said according...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSPECTION DELAY SLOWS MOVE TO NEW ROSEBURG INTERAGENCY OFFICE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117335</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/inspection-delay-slows-move-to-new-roseburg-interagency-office/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inspection-delay-slows-move-to-new-roseburg-interagency-office"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T10:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 4, 2024 3:05 a.m. An inspection delay has slowed the move of the Umpqua National Forest Service staff relocating to the new Roseburg Interagency Office at 777 Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. A UNF post said this delay does not impact services to the public. The front lobby of the new building is open weekdays...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MUCHAS GRACIUS TO OPEN ROSEBURG LOCATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117331</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/04/muchas-gracius-to-open-roseburg-location/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=muchas-gracius-to-open-roseburg-location"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T10:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo credits: Will Geschke April 4, 2024 2:50 a.m. In the KQEN Business Spotlight: Muchas Gracius will open a location in Roseburg next month. Using the corporate name Jerifam, Inc, the company is getting ready to open the store on West Harvard Avenue, in the former location of a Kentucky Fried Chicken, Long John Silvers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STABBING INVESTIGATION CONTINUING, SUSPECT NOT LOCATED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117327</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/stabbing-investigation-continuing-suspect-not-located/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=stabbing-investigation-continuing-suspect-not-located"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T19:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 12:50 p.m.  A stabbing investigation in Roseburg is continuing, with the suspect still being sought. Sergeant Daniel Allen from the Roseburg Police said Wednesday morning at approximately 6:00 a.m. RPD officers responded to the 900 block of Northeast Willow Street regarding a reported stabbing. Allen said when officers arrived, they found that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stabbing Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news171249</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news171249"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T18:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 3, 2024 at approximately 6:00 AM, the Roseburg Police Department responded to the 900 block of NE Willow Street regarding a reported stabbing. When officers arrived, they found a 50 year old Roseburg man was injured due to a stab wound and immediately began life-saving efforts. The injured male was transported to Mercy Medical Center, then later transferred out of the area for additional treatment.
 A suspect in this case, a 20 year old Roseburg man, fled the scene and has not been located despite efforts from multiple assisting agencies and a DCSO K9 track; investigators found the victim and suspect are known to each other. Roseburg Police detectives, Douglas County Sheriff’s Office detectives, DCSO deputies and Oregon State Police responded to assist and will continue to investigate the matter with assistance from the Douglas County District Attorney’s Office. At this time, there is no known ongoing threat to the general public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Police Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CITED BY ROSEBURG POLICE FOLLOWING DUII INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117323</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-man-cited-by-roseburg-police-following-duii-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-cited-by-roseburg-police-following-duii-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 204 10:50 a.m. A Roseburg man was cited by Roseburg Police following a DUII incident early Wednesday. An RPD report said at 2:20 a.m. officers saw 41-year-old Robert Wilkerson leave the parking lot of an establishment in the 900 block of Southeast Stephens Street. An officer got behind his vehicle and saw it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CITED FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117321</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/three-cited-for-prohibited-camping-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=three-cited-for-prohibited-camping-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 10:30 a.m.   Three people were cited by Roseburg Police for prohibited camping on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 9:50 a.m. the group was contacted at their camp in the 500 block of Southeast Spruce Street after receiving numerous complaints about their camp. The two men and one woman, ranging in age...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR DRUGS/LITTERING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117319</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-drugs-littering-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-drugs-littering-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 10:15 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman following a littering incident on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 10:30 a.m. officers responded to the former Visitor’s Center building in the 400 block of Southeast Spruce Street after getting numerous reports of litter along the riverbank. The 57-year-old was contacted at her camp,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117317</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-9/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-9"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for drinking in public on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 2:10 p.m. officers contacted the 52- year-old at the intersection of Northeast Winchester Street and Northeast Shambrook Avenue where he was allegedly sitting and drinking an alcoholic beverage. The man was cited. and his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOLLOWING TRAFFIC STOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117315</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-police-cite-man-following-traffic-stop-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-following-traffic-stop-3"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man following a traffic stop on Tuesday. An RPD report said at approximately 10:50 a.m. officers stopped a pickup for a traffic violation near the intersection of Northeast Lincoln Street and Northeast Beulah Drive in Roseburg. The driver, 36-year-old Chad Woods returned with a suspended license...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Muchas Gracias set to open Roseburg location]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cebc9f62-f113-11ee-990f-3b06fe6c51d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/muchas-gracias-set-to-open-roseburg-location/article_cebc9f62-f113-11ee-990f-3b06fe6c51d5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Muchas Gracias is moving into the former Kentucky Fried Chicken/Long John Silver’s building on West Harvard Avenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSU Extension offers events for forest landowners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6dd8e768-f1c8-11ee-840a-33dee72f0acf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/osu-extension-offers-events-for-forest-landowners/article_6dd8e768-f1c8-11ee-840a-33dee72f0acf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The public is invited to attend the many forestry and natural resources programs offered by Oregon State University Extension in Douglas County this spring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Gem and Mineral show coming in May]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c6890966-f1c7-11ee-97d4-133faa4ea1db</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/umpqua-gem-and-mineral-show-coming-in-may/article_c6890966-f1c7-11ee-97d4-133faa4ea1db.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The annual event will take place May 4 and 5 in Douglas Hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forestry department invites public comment on state forest management activities&nbsp;]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171244</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171244"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore. -- The Oregon Department of Forestry is inviting public comment on planned projects, timber sales and other management activities in state-owned forests in fiscal year 2025.    
 From April 3 through 5 p.m. May 17, Oregonians can weigh in on draft Annual Operations Plans (AOPs) for state forests on the Astoria, Forest Grove, Klamath Falls, North Cascade, Tillamook, West Oregon, and Western Lane Districts. These plans lay out on-the-ground activities expected to take place in the coming fiscal year.  
 State forests by law must provide economic, environmental, and social benefits to Oregonians. To achieve that legal mandate, these lands are managed to create healthy productive forests, high-quality habitat for native fish and wildlife, clean water, timber, revenues to rural comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG TIES FOR HOTTEST DAY OF 2024, JUST MISSES RECORD HIGH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117310</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-ties-for-hottest-day-of-2024-just-misses-record-high/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-ties-for-hottest-day-of-2024-just-misses-record-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T11:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 4:00 a.m. The high temperature in Roseburg Tuesday tied for the hottest day of the year, but just missed a record high for the date. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said the mercury reached 80 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport. That tied with the 80-degree mark set on March 18th....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CROSS COUNTRY SKIER RESCUED BY DCSO SEARCH & RESCUE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117304</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/cross-country-skier-rescued-by-dcso-search-rescue/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cross-country-skier-rescued-by-dcso-search-rescue"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 3:45 a.m.  A cross country skier was rescued after falling and injuring her ankle on Sunday afternoon. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at approximately 1:30 p.m. 911 dispatchers received a report of a 57-year-old woman who fell and injured her ankle while cross country skiing near Mt....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Family friendly employer summit this Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c6a6d85a-f114-11ee-8a7f-6318dbaddc41</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/family-friendly-employer-summit-this-thursday/article_c6a6d85a-f114-11ee-8a7f-6318dbaddc41.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Business Champions for KIDs will host the Family Friendly Employer Summit from 8:30 a.m. to 3 p.m. Thursday in the conference space of Aviva Health a the nonprofit's campus on Northeast Kenneth Ford Drive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Family friendly employer summer this Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c6a6d85a-f114-11ee-8a7f-6318dbaddc41</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/family-friendly-employer-summer-this-thursday/article_c6a6d85a-f114-11ee-8a7f-6318dbaddc41.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Business Champions for KIDs will host the Family Friendly Employer Summit from 8:30 a.m. to 3 p.m. Thursday in the conference space of Aviva Health a the nonprofit's campus on Northeast Kenneth Ford Drive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODOT hosts open house]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f1bca3ba-f10c-11ee-8640-8b7e5dffc0db</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/odot-hosts-open-house/article_f1bca3ba-f10c-11ee-8640-8b7e5dffc0db.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Oregon Department of Transportation is hosting an open house from noon to 6 p.m. April 9 at the Roseburg headquarters on 3500 NW Stewart Parkway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONGRESSMAN BENTZ TO HOLD LISTENING SESSION ON WOLVES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117302</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/congressman-bentz-to-hold-listening-session-on-wolves/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=congressman-bentz-to-hold-listening-session-on-wolves"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 3:30 a.m. Congressman Cliff Bentz will hold a listening session on wolves with members of the ranching community and staff from the U.S. Department of Agriculture, U.S. Forest Service and Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife on Thursday in Pendleton. The event is open to the public and begins at 2:30 p.m....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSU EXTENSION OFFERS MANY FREE EVENTS FOR FOREST LANDOWNERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117300</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/osu-extension-offers-many-free-events-for-forest-landowners/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=osu-extension-offers-many-free-events-for-forest-landowners"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 3:20 a.m. The public is invited to attend the many forestry and natural resources programs offered by Oregon State University Extension in Douglas County this spring. An Extension release said the classes cover a variety of topics which are sure to be of interest to a wide range of landowners. Each of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SILENT DISCO EVENT IN MYRTLE CREEK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117297</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/silent-disco-event-in-myrtle-creek/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=silent-disco-event-in-myrtle-creek"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 3:05 a.m. Friends of the Myrtle Creek Library and the Myrtle Creeks Elks Lodge No. 1943 are presenting a Silent Disco event on Friday April 19th. Organizers said the unique experience will allow participants to get lost in the music with wireless headphones, from 6:00 p.m. to 11:00 p.m. at the Elks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA GEM AND MINERAL SHOW COMING IN MAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117294</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/umpqua-gem-and-mineral-show-coming-in-may/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-gem-and-mineral-show-coming-in-may"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Umpqua Gem and Mineral Show is coming in May. The annual event will take place on Saturday and Sunday May 4th and 5th in Douglas Hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds. Enjoy gem and mineral displays, vendor booths, demonstrations, prizes, rock hunts and more. Show hours are 9:00 a.m....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>