<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-11-15T16:14:49.703Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Days Creek Charter School first quarter honor roll]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f6a12f0a-a20e-11ef-a986-03fdfcce2b53</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/days-creek-charter-school-first-quarter-honor-roll/article_f6a12f0a-a20e-11ef-a986-03fdfcce2b53.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAYS CREEK — These are the students who qualified for the honor roll at Days Creek Charter School in the first quarter of the 2024-25 school year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WATCH STARTS SUNDAY FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126085</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/15/winter-storm-watch-starts-sunday-for-mountain-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-watch-starts-sunday-for-mountain-areas"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T11:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 15, 2024 3:40 a.m.  A Winter Storm Watch is in effect from Sunday afternoon through Monday evening for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is possible with accumulations between 5 and 20 inches possible. Winds could gust as high as 40 miles per hour....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY EMPLOYERS ADD 230 JOBS IN SEPTEMBER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126083</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/15/douglas-county-employers-add-230-jobs-in-september/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-employers-add-230-jobs-in-september"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T11:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 15, 2024 3:30 a.m.  Douglas County’s seasonally adjusted payroll employment rose by 230 jobs in September after a gain of 100 in August and a loss of 110 in July. A State of Oregon Employment Department release said in the not seasonally adjusted private-sector industries in September, there were relatively large gains of 40...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SENATORS ANNOUNCE $5.4 MILLION FOR PROJECTS TO REDUCE WILDFIRE RISK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126081</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/15/senators-announce-5-4-million-for-projects-to-reduce-wildfire-risk/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=senators-announce-5-4-million-for-projects-to-reduce-wildfire-risk"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T11:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 15, 2024 3:20 a.m. On Thursday, Oregon’s U.S. Senators Jeff Merkley and Ron Wyden announced that just over $5.4 million is coming to Oregon from the Inflation Reduction Act – the largest investment in clean energy and climate action ever – for hazardous fuels transportation projects across the state, including in Douglas County. A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTHEAST STEPHENS STREET WATER MAIN PROJECT UNDERWAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126078</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/15/southeast-stephens-street-water-main-project-underway/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=southeast-stephens-street-water-main-project-underway"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T11:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 15, 2024 3:05 a.m. A water main replacement project on Southeast Stephens Street in Roseburg is underway, leading to a daytime closure that could impact traffic heading into downtown. A City of Roseburg release said portions of one northbound lane on Stephens Street will be closed from Southeast Sykes Street to Southeast Oak Avenue...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA RIVER LIGHTHOUSE DISPLAY DEBUTS NOVEMBER 24TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126076</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/15/umpqua-river-lighthouse-display-debuts-november-24th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-river-lighthouse-display-debuts-november-24th"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T11:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 15, 2024 2:50 a.m. A new light display featuring the Umpqua River Lighthouse is being added to the Umpqua Valley Festival of Lights for its 32nd season. A release said the popular annual holiday drive-through event opens Sunday, November 24th at River Forks Park. Festival of Lights Chair Tabitha Layman said designers and fabricators...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter weather advisory in effect until Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/db170c9a-a322-11ef-85c4-477252148fa2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/winter-weather-advisory-in-effect-until-tuesday/article_db170c9a-a322-11ef-85c4-477252148fa2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T07:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A winter weather advisory is in effect until 10 a.m. Tuesday above 5,000 feet for mountain areas in southern Oregon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Board of Forestry hosts virtual special meeting on Nov. 22]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176765</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176765"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T23:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Oregon Board of Forestry will meet for a virtual special meeting starting at 9 a.m. on Friday, Nov. 22, 2024. The purpose of this meeting will be to review the Western Oregon State Forests Draft Forest Management Plan (FMP) scenarios. The board will direct the department on the next steps in the development of the FMP.
Members of the public are welcome to view the special meeting on the ODF's YouTube channel.
Please note: There will not be time allotted for live testimony during the special meeting. Written testimony may be submitted by emailing boardofforestry@odf.oregon.gov prior to the meeting date. To account for the time board members need to review the written testimony, consider sending written testimony at least 72 hours prior to the meeting start time. If submitted after this window of time the testimony will be entered into the public record but may not be viewed by the board until after the meeting. Written testimony for the Nov. 22 meeting will continue to be accepted until Dec. 6. Submissions should include the meeting date and agenda item number/topic header with the written submission. 
The agenda is available on the board’s webpage. 
Accommodations for people with disabilities, and special materials, services, or assistance can be arranged by calling ODF’s Public Affairs Office at least 72 hours in advance of the meeting at 503-945-7200 or by email at forestryinformation@odf.oregon.gov.
The Oregon Board of Forestry consists of seven citizens nominated by the Governor and confirmed by the Oregon Senate. Responsibilities include appointing the State Forester, setting management direction for state-owned forests, adopting rules governing timber harvest and other practices on private forestland, and promoting sustainable management of Oregon’s 30 million-acre forestland base. Read more information about the board.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE 3 PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING ON WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126073</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/roseburg-police-cite-3-people-for-prohibited-camping-on-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-3-people-for-prohibited-camping-on-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T21:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 1:45 p.m.   Roseburg Police cited 3 people for prohibited camping on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 11:10 a.m. officers contacted a 39-year at her camp near the intersection of Northwest Stewart Parkway and Northwest Renann Avenue. She was in her tent which was next to the sidewalk. There was trash covering...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR REPORTED HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126071</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-reported-harassment-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-reported-harassment-3"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T21:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 1:30 p.m.  Roseburg Police cited a woman for a reported harassment incident on Wednesday night. An RPD report said just before 5:40 p.m. officers contacted the 71-year-old at CHI Mercy Medical Center on Northwest Stewart Parkway, after she allegedly spit on a nurse. The woman was cited and released at Mercy so...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126069</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-alleged-theft-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-alleged-theft-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T21:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 1:20 p.m.   Roseburg Police cited a woman for an alleged theft incident on Wednesday night. An RPD report said just before 7:30 p.m. officers contacted the 28-year-old after she allegedly walked out of WinCo Foods in the 2700 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway, with an armful of items.  The items were recovered,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 11.14.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126066</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/inside-douglas-county-11-14-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-11-14-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T21:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Senator David Brock Smith reacts to legislative races in Oregon in the General Election, talks about his plans for the next session of the legislature and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC hosts Nov. 16 performance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/62f9a7f8-9c7a-11ef-9b23-db5b09c86249</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/ucc-hosts-nov-16-performance/article_62f9a7f8-9c7a-11ef-9b23-db5b09c86249.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Umpqua Community College fine and performing arts department presents the Umpqua Singers and Kirby Shaw Singers at 7 p.m. Saturday, Nov. 16, at the Whipple Fine Arts Center on the UCC campus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The News Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Notice - Central Douglas Fire & Rescue Authority Regular Board Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news176751</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news176751"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T18:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CENTRAL DOUGLAS FIRE & RESCUE AUTHORITY REGULAR BOARD MEETING NOTICE
The Board of Directors of Central Douglas Fire & Rescue Authority will hold its Regular Board meeting at its headquarters located at 250 SE Main St. Winston, OR 97496 on Monday November 18, 2024, at 5:30 p.m.  To comply with House Bill 2560, those that wish to participate can attend through videoconferencing or telephonically. If you plan on attending the meeting, please call the business office at 541-673-5503 during normal business hours prior to 4:00 p.m. on Monday November 18, 2024, for instructions.
The Board agenda to include but not limited to:          

Monthly Financials
Resolution 2025-02: Resolution Authorizing Authority Credit Card and Signer
Board Practices Assessment Impressions and Recommendations
Chief’s Report

 
The meeting location is accessible to persons with disabilities. A request for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or for other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours before the meeting to administration at 541-673-5503.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Central Douglas Fire &amp; Rescue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Notice - Douglas County Fire District No. 2 Regular Board Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news176748</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news176748"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T18:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOARD REGULAR MEETING NOTICE
The Board of Directors of Douglas County Fire District No. 2 will hold its Regular Board meeting at its headquarters located at 250 SE Main St. Winston, OR 97496 on Monday November 18, 2024, at 5:30 pm. To comply with House Bill 2560, those that wish to participate can attend through videoconferencing or telephonically. If you plan on attending the meeting, please call the business office at 541-673-5503 during normal business hours prior to 4:00 p.m. on Monday November 18, 2024, for instructions. 
 
The Board agenda to include but not limited to:                    

Monthly Financials

 
The meeting location is accessible to persons with disabilities. A request for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or for other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours before the meeting to DCFD #2 at 541-673-5503.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Central Douglas Fire &amp; Rescue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Notice - Winston-Dillard Fire District No. 5 Regular Board Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news176747</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news176747"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T18:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOARD REGULAR MEETING NOTICE
The Board of Directors of Winston-Dillard Fire District No. 5 will hold its Regular Board meeting at WDFD Fire Station at 250 SE Main St., Winston, OR on Monday, November 18, 2024, at 5:30 p.m. To comply with House Bill 2560, those that wish to participate can attend through videoconferencing or telephonically. If you plan on attending the meeting, please call the business office at 541-679-8721 during normal business hours prior to 4:00 p.m. on Monday, November 18, 2024, for instructions.
The Board agenda to include but not limited to:
  1. Monthly Financial Report
 
The meeting location is accessible to person with disabilities. A request for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or for other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours before the meeting to Winston-Dillard Fire District No. 5 at 541-679-8721]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Central Douglas Fire &amp; Rescue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HELFRICH TO NOT SEEK RE-ELECTION AS HOUSE GOP LEADER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126062</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/helfrich-to-not-seek-re-election-as-house-gop-leader/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=helfrich-to-not-seek-re-election-as-house-gop-leader"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T18:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 10:20 a.m.  This week Oregon House Republican Leader Jeff Helfrich made an announcement. Helfrich said, “Today, I am announcing my intention to not seek re-election as leader of the Oregon House Republican caucus”. Helfrich said, “This week, as I laid my father to rest, I found myself contemplating what truly matters in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FREE FISHING DAYS NOVEMBER 29TH/30TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126060</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/free-fishing-days-november-29th-30th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=free-fishing-days-november-29th-30th"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T18:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 10:20 a.m.  The Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife is offering free fishing days right after Thanksgiving on November 29th and 30th. An ODFW release said that offer also applies to clamming and crabbing as well. No fishing/shellfish licenses or tags are required those two days. Both Oregon residents and nonresidents can...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOREST SERVICE OFFERING SAW CLASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126058</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/forest-service-offering-saw-class/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=forest-service-offering-saw-class"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T18:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 10:00 a.m.  The U.S. Forest Service will offer a saw class that covers the basics of bucking for trail maintenance, for both chainsaw and crosscut saws, on Saturday and Sunday, December 7th and 8th, at the Diamond Lake Ranger Station. Trails and Wilderness Technician & Volunteer Coordinator Lauren Hack said attendees will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMELESS COMMISSION MEETING NEXT WEEK HAS BEEN CANCELED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126056</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/homeless-commission-meeting-next-week-has-been-canceled/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homeless-commission-meeting-next-week-has-been-canceled"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T17:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 9:50 a.m.  The City of Roseburg Homeless Commission scheduled for next Monday, November 18th, has been canceled. No reason was given for the cancelation. The next regular meeting date is to be determined. For more information about the City of Roseburg, go to: www.cityofroseburg.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN MAN JAILED FOLLOWING ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126054</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/sutherlin-man-jailed-following-alleged-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-man-jailed-following-alleged-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T17:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 9:40 a.m.  A Sutherlin man was jailed following an alleged trespass incident on Wednesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 8:00 p.m. the 35-year-old was called in for allegedly harassing customers and threatening employees at a business on John Long Road in Rice Hill. He reportedly refused to leave...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRAIN TEEN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING TWO-VEHICLE CRASH WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126052</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/drain-teen-taken-to-hospital-following-two-vehicle-crash-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=drain-teen-taken-to-hospital-following-two-vehicle-crash-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T17:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 9:30 a.m.  A Drain teen was taken to the hospital following a two-vehicle accident on Wednesday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 2:50 p.m. an Oakland man was driving east on Stearns Lane near Crystal Lane in the Oakland area when the 17-year-old male -made a left-hand turn in front...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SLOW VEHICLE LEADS TO 4-VEHICLE CRASH, WEST OF ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126050</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/slow-vehicle-leads-to-4-vehicle-crash-west-of-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=slow-vehicle-leads-to-4-vehicle-crash-west-of-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T17:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 9:15 a.m. A slow vehicle led to a 4-vehicle crash west of Roseburg on Wednesday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 2:00 p.m. a pickup had its flashers on while traveling on Garden Valley Road near Gypsy Lane. A pickup following a Jeep and an SUV got into a chain...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 11.14.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126047</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/morning-conversation-11-14-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-11-14-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T17:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zachary Stocks of Oregon Black Pioneers talks about a Douglas County Historical Society presentation on Saturday at the Douglas County Museum regarding Letitia Carson, a formerly enslaved black women who came to Oregon in 1845.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kellogg volunteer fire scores modern asset with grant]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6f03ff46-a1c8-11ef-889d-17ac6fc2b6f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/kellogg-volunteer-fire-scores-modern-asset-with-grant/article_6f03ff46-a1c8-11ef-889d-17ac6fc2b6f8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T14:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In their annual community meeting Tuesday the Kellogg Rural Fire District was joined by the National Volunteer Fire Council and State Farm Insurance, that announced the district was one of 100 volunteer fire departments in the nation to receive a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PATRICK MOORE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIGHEST ONE DAY RAINFALL AMOUNT IN MONTHS FOR ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126040</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/highest-one-day-rainfall-amount-in-months-for-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=highest-one-day-rainfall-amount-in-months-for-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T11:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 3:40 a.m. The Umpqua Valley saw the highest one-day rainfall amount in months on Wednesday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that 1.23 inches of rain was recorded at the Roseburg Regional Airport. That compares with 0.94 inches of precipitation measured on November 1st....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SECURE RURAL SCHOOLS LEGISLATION PASSES U.S. SENATE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126038</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/secure-rural-schools-legislation-passes-u-s-senate/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=secure-rural-schools-legislation-passes-u-s-senate"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T11:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 3:30 a.m. A bipartisan bill to reauthorize the U.S. Forest Service’s Secure Rural Schools and Self-Determination Program through 2026, was unanimously approved by the U.S. Senate on Monday night. A release from Senators Ron Wyden and Jeff Merkley said the legislation was introduced by Wyden and Idaho Senator Mike Crapo. Wyden and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOYLE VOTES YES ON SOCIAL SECURITY FAIRNESS ACT OF 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126036</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/hoyle-votes-yes-on-social-security-fairness-act-of-2023/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hoyle-votes-yes-on-social-security-fairness-act-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T11:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 3:20 a.m. On Wednesday, 4th District Congresswoman Val Hoyle voted in support of H.R. 28, the Social Security Fairness Act of 2023, which would expand Social Security’s benefits for over 2.7 million Americans. A release from Hoyle said the legislation would help increase Social Security benefits by eliminating the Windfall Elimination Program...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KEVIN HEATLEY SELECTED AS SUPERINTENDENT OF CRATER LAKE NATIONAL PARK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126030</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/kevin-heatley-selected-as-superintendent-of-crater-lake-national-park/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=kevin-heatley-selected-as-superintendent-of-crater-lake-national-park"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T11:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 3:05 a.m. The National Park Service has selected Kevin Heatley to serve as the superintendent of Crater Lake National Park beginning in January 2025. An NPS release said Heatley currently serves as deputy chief of the Bureau of Land Management’s NEPA, Planning and Decision Support Division in Washington D.C. He previously worked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCAN/ST. JOSEPH’S CHURCH SEEKING WARMING CENTER VOLUNTEERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126028</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/ucan-st-josephs-church-seeking-warming-center-volunteers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucan-st-josephs-church-seeking-warming-center-volunteers"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T10:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 14, 2024 2:50 a.m.  The Umpqua Community Action Network and St. Joseph’s Church are seeking volunteers to help them operate the Roseburg Warming Center when it is needed during periods of cold weather this winter. A UCAN release said as temperatures drop, the two organizations are stepping up to offer warmth and safety to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIKE WINTERS LAWN AND GARDEN SHOW 11.13.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126025</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/14/mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-11-13-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-11-13-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-14T01:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County’s Commissioner of Dirt, Mike Winters, has our weekly local lawn and garden program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG STABBING INVESTIGATION UPDATE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126023</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/roseburg-stabbing-investigation-update/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-stabbing-investigation-update"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T22:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2025 2:45 p.m.  Roseburg Police have provided an update on a stabbing investigation, from an incident that took place Tuesday night. Public Information Officer Sergeant Daniel Allen said at approximately 8:30 p.m. RPD along with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office responded to an area referred to as “The Point”, in the 200 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stabbing Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news176730</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news176730"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T22:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 12, 2024 at approximately 8:30 PM, the Roseburg Police Department, along with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office, responded to the 200 block of SE Pine Street, an area referred to as “The Point,” regarding a reported stabbing. When officers arrived, they found 31-year-old Jesse Otha Thomas lying on the bike path with multiple stab wounds. Thomas was transported to Mercy Medical Center by Umpqua Valley Ambulance, with non-life threatening injuries and later released.
The suspect in this case, 45-year-old Joshua Daniel Saunders, fled the scene but was located along the South Umpqua riverbank with the use of a FLIR thermal imaging device.  After a multi-hour standoff, Saunders was tased and taken into custody without further incident.  Saunders was lodged at the Douglas County Jail for Assault 1 and Unlawful Use of a Weapon.
The Roseburg Police Department would like to thank the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office and Umpqua Valley Ambulance for their assistance.
No further details are being released at this time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Police Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 11.13.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126018</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/inside-douglas-county-11-13-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-11-13-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T21:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg area resident Donda King has been an American Red Cross volunteer for nearly 40 years. She talks about the work she has done to help others in their time of need, and some of the things she has experienced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT, CITE & RELEASE FOR OTHER CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126014</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-warrant-cite-release-for-other-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-warrant-cite-release-for-other-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T19:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a man for a warrant following a traffic stop early Wednesday. An SPD report said just after 3:00 a.m. an officer observed the 41-year-old near the intersection of East Fourth Avenue and Mardonna Way. The officer knew the man had a suspended driving status in Oregon and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CAMAS VALLEY MAN REPORTS PRIOR HIT AND RUN INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126012</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/camas-valley-man-reports-prior-hit-and-run-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=camas-valley-man-reports-prior-hit-and-run-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T18:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 10:40 a.m.  A Camas Valley man reported a prior hit and run incident on Tuesday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 6:00 p.m. a deputy contacted the 18-year-old regarding a hit/run that occurred on Monday night at approximately 7:30 p.m. in the 1600 block of Brockway Road. The victim said...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Forestry announces top forest operator for NW Oregon in 2024 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176719</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176719"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T18:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAINIER, Ore. – R.D. Reeves Construction, based in Rainier in Columbia County, has been chosen as Operator of the Year for Northwest Oregon. A regional advisory committee to the Oregon Board of Forestry selected the logging company earlier this fall. R.D. Reeves will be recognized in Salem at the January meeting of the Board along with two other regional honorees:

Eastern Oregon – BTO Forestry Solutions, owned by Mike Wiedeman and based in Enterprise in Wallowa County. View a video of the company’s work at https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZcE22ZAA8I8
Southwest Oregon – D & H Logging, based in Coos Bay. View video about D & H’s work at https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A1eTDEcXQiY

The award recognizes forest operators who, while harvesting timber or doing other forestry work, protect natural…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Forestry announces SW Oregon's top forest operator for 2024 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176718</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176718"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T18:23:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COOS BAY, Ore. – D and H Logging Company of Coos Bay has been chosen as Operator of the Year for Southwest Oregon. A regional advisory committee to the Oregon Board of Forestry selected the company earlier this fall. 
D and H Logging will be recognized in Salem at the January meeting of the Board along with the two other regional Oregon honorees:

Eastern Oregon – BTO Forestry Solutions, owned by Mike Wiedeman, and based in Enterprise in Wallowa County. Watch a video of the firm’s work at https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZcE22ZAA8I8
Northwest Oregon – R.D. Reeves Construction, based in Rainier, Ore. in Columbia County. Watch a video of the firm’s work at https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EUsBwxBZiEo

The Operator of the Year award recognizes forest operators who, while harvesting timber or do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Forestry announces top forest operator in Eastern Oregon for 2024 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176717</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176717"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T18:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ENTERPRISE, Ore. – BTO Forestry Solutions, based in Enterprise, has been chosen as Operator of the Year for Eastern Oregon. A regional advisory committee to the Oregon Board of Forestry earlier this fall selected the logging company for the honor. The firm and its owner, Mike Wiedeman, will be recognized in Salem at the January meeting of the Board along with honorees from northwest and southwest Oregon. Those are:

Northwest Oregon – R.D. Reeves Construction, Inc., based in Rainier, Ore. in Columbia County
Southwest Oregon – D & H Logging Company, based in Coos Bay

The Operator of the Year award recognizes forest operators who, while harvesting timber or doing other forestry work, protect natural resources at a level that consistently meets or goes above and beyond requirements of the Or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE MAN JAILED FOR WARRANT FOLLOWING TWO-VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126010</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/riddle-man-jailed-for-warrant-following-two-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riddle-man-jailed-for-warrant-following-two-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T18:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 10:10 a.m.  A Riddle man was jailed for a warrant, following a two-vehicle crash on Tuesday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 7:15 a.m. the 44-year-old was traveling in the 200 block of Pruner Road in the Riddle area. A vehicle pulled out in front of him, causing his pickup...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Forestry announces state's top forest operators for 2024 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176716</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176716"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T18:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. – Three loggers have been chosen as Operator of the Year for their respective region of Oregon. Three regional advisory committees to the Oregon Board of Forestry selected the trio earlier this fall. The recipients will be recognized in Salem at the January meeting of the Board. The honorees are:

Eastern Oregon – BTO Forestry Solutions, owned by Mike Wiedeman and based in Enterprise in Wallowa County
Northwest Oregon – R.D. Reeves Construction, based in Rainier, Ore. in Columbia County
Southwest Oregon – D & H Logging based in Coos Bay

The award recognizes forest operators who, while harvesting timber or doing other forestry work, protect natural resources at a level that consistently meets or goes above and beyond requirements of the Oregon Forest Practices Act *. That law r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All-State choir qualifiers receive scholarships from local organization]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ce5714a8-a17b-11ef-b0b9-d31c9e7e6d05</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/all-state-choir-qualifiers-receive-scholarships-from-local-organization/article_ce5714a8-a17b-11ef-b0b9-d31c9e7e6d05.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choir members from various Roseburg schools who qualified for the 2025 Oregon Music Education Association All-State choir got together Tuesday evening to receive scholarships for their trip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR REPORTED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126008</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-reported-theft-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-reported-theft-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T17:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a reported theft incident on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 4:15 p.m. the 32-year-old was allegedly seen on camera stealing a pair of paints from a business near the corner of Northeast Winchester Street and Northeast Rowe Avenue. Officers contacted the woman later,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED CRIMINAL TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126006</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-criminal-trespass-incident-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-criminal-trespass-incident-2"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T17:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged criminal trespass incident on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 2:00 p.m. dispatch received several calls regarding the 41-year-old walking around a business with his pants down in the 2000 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. Officers located the man sitting up against one...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING STABBING, STAND OFF]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=126004</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-stabbing-stand-off/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-stabbing-stand-off"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T17:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 9:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man following and lengthy stand-off, which began on Tuesday night. An RPD report said at 8:25 p.m. numerous officers and deputies from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office responded to Deer Creek Park in the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street, after a caller said there had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Forestry announces that two Lane County logging firms have earned Awards of Merit (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176712</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176712"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T17:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EUGENE, Ore. – Two Lane County logging firms – Card Logging of Eugene and Weyerhaeuser’s Springfield Tree Farm logging and road-building crews – have each earned an Award of Merit for difficult timber harvests done in the aftermath of last January’s devastating ice storm. 
The companies were selected from among nominations submitted to the Oregon Dept. of Forestry (ODF). The Northwest Regional Forest Practices Committee, which advises the Oregon Board of Forestry on forest practice matters, chose the two companies to receive Awards of Merit as part of the annual Operator of the Year program administered by ODF.
Details of what each company did to earn the awards are below:

Card Logging Company, Inc., based in Eugene. The firm earned its award for harvesting an ice-storm-damaged stand of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 11.13.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125998</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/morning-conversation-11-13-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-11-13-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T17:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg High School Theatre teacher Troy Pennington talks about their upcoming production of “Something Like a Christmas Carol”, in December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missing 5-year-old boy from Coos County found deceased.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cc56a926-a1de-11ef-b0c2-2f9ba1cc3417</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/missing-5-year-old-boy-from-coos-county-found-deceased/article_cc56a926-a1de-11ef-b0c2-2f9ba1cc3417.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coos County Sheriff’s Office Public Information Officer Sergeant Christopher Gill said Joshua McCoy had been missing since Saturday evening after leaving his residence on Stage Road in the Hauser area while his mother was asleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power outage impacting Elkton, Drain and Scottsburg Areas]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/08faecea-a1dd-11ef-9be7-5b007b302df0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/power-outage-impacting-elkton-drain-and-scottsburg-areas/article_08faecea-a1dd-11ef-9be7-5b007b302df0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T16:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An outage is impacting over 1,100 Douglas Electric Cooperative meters in the Elkton, Drain, and Scottsburg areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local author J.L. Davis to hold signing and reading event at While Away Books]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/02b3924c-9e0e-11ef-8ccd-dbd450d20efe</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local-author-j-l-davis-to-hold-signing-and-reading-event-at-while-away-books/article_02b3924c-9e0e-11ef-8ccd-dbd450d20efe.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those who've immersed themselves in the fantasy worlds of Middle-Earth, Narnia and Westeros can prepare to enter the world of Alnorda on Nov. 16. Oakland author J.L. Davis will take readers on a journey at While Away Books with a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barth presents on global warming]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/28d9faa8-a064-11ef-b983-cb6344a27945</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/barth-presents-on-global-warming/article_28d9faa8-a064-11ef-b983-cb6344a27945.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon State University Professor Jack Barth will give a presentation Wednesday, Nov. 13, on his research about how global warming is reducing the oxygen supply in coastal waters and how this affects marine life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library hosts 'Americans and the Holocaust' exhibition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/23445526-9fa5-11ef-a8a1-17bfd632b328</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-public-library-hosts-americans-and-the-holocaust-exhibition/article_23445526-9fa5-11ef-a8a1-17bfd632b328.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A traveling exhibition titled “Americans and the Holocaust” will be displayed through November and December at the Roseburg Public Library, educating the community on one of the darkest periods of modern history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POWER OUTAGE IMPACTING ELKTON, DRAIN AND SCOTTSBURG AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125996</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/power-outage-impacting-elkton-drain-and-scottsburg-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=power-outage-impacting-elkton-drain-and-scottsburg-areas"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T14:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 6:50 a.m.  An outage is impacting over 1,100 Douglas Electric Cooperative meters in the Elkton, Drain, and Scottsburg areas. An update from the utility said this is due to a loss of transmission to the Elkton and Scottsburg substations as of 3:15 a.m. Wednesday. At 6:00 a.m. crews coordinated with the Bonneville...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WET WEATHER PATTERN FOR THE UMPQUA VALLEY FOR A FEW DAYS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125991</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/wet-weather-pattern-for-the-umpqua-valley-for-a-few-days/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wet-weather-pattern-for-the-umpqua-valley-for-a-few-days"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T12:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 4:10 a.m.  A wet weather pattern is in place in the Umpqua Valley for the next few days. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the Roseburg area should see rain through at least Friday. Winds with gusts near 25 miles per hour are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COOS COUNTY MISSING 5-YEAR OLD FOUND DECEASED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125989</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/coos-county-missing-5-year-old-found-deceased/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=coos-county-missing-5-year-old-found-deceased"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T11:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 3:50 a.m. A missing 5-year-old boy from Coos County has been found deceased. Coos County Sheriff’s Office Public Information Officer Sergeant Christopher Gill said Joshua McCoy had been missing since Saturday evening after leaving his residence on Stage Road in the Hauser area while his mother was asleep. Gill said at approximately...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FUND FOR TEACHERS GRANT OPPORTUNITY IN DOUGLAS COUNTY FOR EIGHTH YEAR]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125987</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/fund-for-teachers-grant-opportunity-in-douglas-county-for-eighth-year/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fund-for-teachers-grant-opportunity-in-douglas-county-for-eighth-year"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T11:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 3:30 a.m.  The Ford Family Foundation is bringing the national Fund for Teachers grant program to Douglas County for an eighth year. A TFFF release said the program supports teacher-designed, summer learning experiences that impact their practice, students and school communities. Applications are open until January 23rd. Up to $50,000 total will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VINTAGE SINGERS PRESENT THEIR 47TH ANNUAL TWELFTH NIGHT CONCERT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125985</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/vintage-singers-present-their-47th-annual-twelfth-night-concert/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=vintage-singers-present-their-47th-annual-twelfth-night-concert"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T11:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 3:20 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Community College Performing and Visual Arts presents the Vintage Singers performing their 47th annual Twelfth Night concert on January 3rd at 7:00 p.m. and January 5th at 3:00 p.m. at First Presbyterian Church on Southeast Lane Avenue in downtown Roseburg. The music performance is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14TH ANNUAL ELKTON ART & WINE WEEKEND KICKS OFF HOLIDAY SEASON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125982</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/14th-annual-elkton-art-wine-weekend-kicks-off-holiday-season/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=14th-annual-elkton-art-wine-weekend-kicks-off-holiday-season"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T11:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 3:05 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The town of Elkton will host the 14th annual Elkton Art & Wine Weekend taking place Friday through Sunday, November 29th through December 1st. A release from Elkton Community Education Center said the event offers a unique opportunity to experience the community’s artistic and viticultural...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRAIN MAN JAILED FOLLOWING DUII/HIT AND RUN INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125980</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/drain-man-jailed-following-duii-hit-and-run-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=drain-man-jailed-following-duii-hit-and-run-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T11:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 13, 2024 2:50 a.m. A Drain man was jailed following a DUII/hit and run incident Monday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 7:25 p.m. deputies responded to a crash in the 100 block of B Avenue in Drain, where the driver allegedly got out of his pickup and ran from the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 11.12.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125977</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/13/true-wealth-11-12-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-11-12-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T01:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littlejohn Financial: David Littlejohn and Matt Dickson have our weekly local financial program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add a Little Spice to Your Reading Life]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f4537a86-a14c-11ef-b442-73dcb80f0465</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/add-a-little-spice-to-your-reading-life/article_f4537a86-a14c-11ef-b442-73dcb80f0465.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T23:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love is in the literary air in a big way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley for The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media Advisory:Lewis & Clark College and Tillamook forest center collaboration gives Oregonians an opportunity to voice their values (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176689</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176689"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T21:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rain Festival Offers Opportunity for Community Members to Engage and Share Input 
TILLAMOOK, OR, Nov. 8, 2024 – What common values, questions, and even misconceptions about state forests do Oregonians have?  On Nov.16, Lewis & Clark students will engage community members to help answer these questions as part of the Rain Festival being held at Tillamook Forest Center.
The Rain Festival is a free event providing the public with activities including a salmon release, guided walks, crafts, and displays that celebrate the Tillamook State Forest and its watersheds. For 19 students studying environmental engagement at Lewis & Clark, the Rain Festival will also be a pivotal opportunity for gathering public input about the perspectives, attitudes, and appreciation that define how Oregonians value our forests. Lewis & Clark Professor Alana Rader has developed the course in collaboration with Denise Berkshire of the Tillamook Forest Center, to deepen students’ engagement and communication skills in real-world settings. The Lewis & Clark students are preparing by designing and refining the public engagement activities for the Rain Festival. Afterwards, the students will analyze the data they gather and make a presentation to the state Board of Forestry to provide perspectives on people’s understanding of, and attitudes toward, Oregon’s state forests. 
Members of the media are invited to attend the Nov. 16 event, where Rader, Berkshire, and the Lewis & Clark students will be available for interviews about the process and goals of the collaboration. An RSVP to Tim Hoffman and Lori Friedman is requested, but day of coverage is also welcome.
###]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR DUII AFTER SECOND OFFENSE IN 90 MINUTES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125975</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-duii-after-second-offense-in-90-minutes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-duii-after-second-offense-in-90-minutes"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T21:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 1:50 p.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for DUII Monday after her second offense in just over 90 minutes. An RPD report said just after 2:20 a.m. an officer stopped the 30-year-old for traffic violations near the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and Northeast Garden Valley Boulevard. The officer observed signs of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 11.12.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125971</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/inside-douglas-county-11-12-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-11-12-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T21:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boys & Girls Club of the Umpqua Valley Chief Executive Officer Troy Johns talks about coming to Roseburg to lead the non-profit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE 10 PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125969</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/roseburg-police-cite-10-people-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-10-people-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T19:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited 10 people for prohibited camping between Friday morning and Sunday morning. An RPD report said contacts were made in the 1400 block of Southeast Micelli Street, in the 100 block of Southeast Templin Avenue, in the 2000 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive, at Gaddis Park in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR PREVIOUS THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125967</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-previous-theft-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-previous-theft-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T18:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 10:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a previous theft incident on Friday night. An RPD report said at 5:40 p.m. officers contacted 28-year-old Ryan Humphrey in the 2700 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive. Humphrey had been identified as a suspect in a previous theft case. He was taken into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR BUSINESS TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125965</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-business-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-business-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T18:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a business trespass incident on Saturday night. An RPD report said at 10:30 p.m. the 46-year-old was contacted after she returned to a store in the 1500 block of Southeast Stephens Street an hour after being advised of trespass. She was charged with second-degree...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAILED MAN FOR ALLEGED CRIMINAL TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125963</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/sutherlin-police-jailed-man-for-alleged-criminal-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jailed-man-for-alleged-criminal-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T18:18:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 10:10 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a man for an alleged criminal trespass incident early Sunday. An SPD report said just before 2;00 a.m. the 18-year-old was seen on video at a business which has No Trespassing signs in the 200 block of West Central Avenue. The man was reportedly looking in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOR BUSINESS TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125961</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-business-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-business-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T18:10:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a man for a business trespass incident early Sunday. An SPD report said just after 4:20 a.m. 21-year-old Bradly Carter was at a business in the 1300 block of West Central Avenue, despite being previously trespassed several times. Carter allegedly left garbage outside the business was reportedly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED DISORDERLY CONDUCT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125959</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-incident-7/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-incident-7"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged disorderly conduct incident on Monday. An RPD report said at 12:15 p.m. officers responded after a caller said that a man was laying in the road, impeding traffic near the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and Northeast Alameda Avenue. Officers responded and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125956</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-12/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-12"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged theft incident early Monday. An RPD report said at 3:00 a.m. 39-year-old Michael Hatton was allegedly found going through the victim’s van, which was parked in his driveway in the 1200 block of Northwest Keasey Street.  When contacted, Hatton was reportedly in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL A MAN FOR UNLAWFUL POSSESSION OF A FIREARM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125954</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/roseburg-police-jail-a-man-for-unlawful-possession-of-a-firearm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-a-man-for-unlawful-possession-of-a-firearm"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:42:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 930 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for unlawful possession of a firearm on Saturday. An RPD report said at 2:30 p.m. officers contacted the 57-year-old after an alleged disturbance at his residence in the 3100 block of West Shasta Avenue. The disturbance was unfounded, but the man admitted to having a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR INVASION OF PERSONAL PRIVACY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125952</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-invasion-of-personal-privacy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-invasion-of-personal-privacy"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man on the first-degree charge of invasion of personal property on Sunday. An RPD report said at 6:00 p.m. 26-year-old Dyllan Neiko of Myrtle Creek was contacted after he allegedly hid his cellphone in a trash can, pointed at a tanning bed, at a business in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 11.12.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125949</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/morning-conversation-11-12-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-11-12-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[County Commissioner Chris Boice and John Pierson talk about the volunteer help needed for Wreaths Across America, happening in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commissioners announce prestigious award for financial accounting]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a4ad4bc6-a104-11ef-8e9a-7b9cb2ae8eab</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/commissioners-announce-prestigious-award-for-financial-accounting/article_a4ad4bc6-a104-11ef-8e9a-7b9cb2ae8eab.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T14:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County received a Certificate of Achievement for Excellence in Financial Reporting by the Government Finance Office Association of the United States and Canada for their annual Comprehensive Financial Report for the year ending June 30, 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Historical Society sponsors presentation on Letitia Carson, first woman to prove homestead in Oregon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1b0cc9aa-a104-11ef-8114-37faed639504</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/historical-society-sponsors-presentation-on-letitia-carson-first-woman-to-prove-homestead-in-oregon/article_1b0cc9aa-a104-11ef-8114-37faed639504.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — The Douglas County Historical Society is sponsoring a presentation by Dr. Bob Zybach on his research into the life of Letitia Carson, a freed slave who accomplished unusual things for an African-American woman in the 1800s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY IN EFFECT UNTIL 10:00 A.M. TUESDAY ABOVE 5,000 FEET]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125940</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/winter-weather-advisory-in-effect-until-1000-a-m-tuesday-above-5000-feet/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-in-effect-until-1000-a-m-tuesday-above-5000-feet"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T12:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 4:00 a.m.  A Winter Weather Advisory is in effect until 10:00 a.m. Tuesday above 5,000 feet for mountain areas in southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said additional snow accumulations between 3 and 6 inches are forecast. Winds will gust as high as 35 miles per hour. The Advisory area...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADDITIONAL RESOURCES TO HELP WITH SEARCH FOR 5-YEAR-OLD BOY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125936</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/additional-resources-to-help-with-search-for-5-year-old-boy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=additional-resources-to-help-with-search-for-5-year-old-boy"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 3:50 a.m.  A Coos County 5-year-old remains missing with additional resources being added to the search effort. Coos County Sheriff’s Office Public Information Officer Christopher Gill said Joshua James McCoy was reported missing at 5:30 p.m. Saturday. Gill said the boy, who has autism, has not been seen since taking a nap...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATTORNEY GENERAL ELECT ANNOUNCES LEADERSHIP TEAM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125934</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/attorney-general-elect-announces-leadership-team/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=attorney-general-elect-announces-leadership-team"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 3:40 a.m.  Oregon Attorney General-Elect Dan Rayfield has announced the first two members of his executive team, Lisa Udland a deputy attorney general and Jenn Baker as chief of staff. Rayfield said, “I am excited to announce that we have already begun to assemble a strong team to help lead the Oregon...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY COMMISSIONERS MEETING WEDNESDAY MORNING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125932</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/county-commissioners-meeting-wednesday-morning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-commissioners-meeting-wednesday-morning"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 3:30 a.m.  Douglas County Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman, and Tom Kress will have their next weekly business meeting on Wednesday morning at 9:00 a.m. It will be held in room 216 of the courthouse on Southeast Douglas Avenue in downtown Roseburg. For additional information about the meeting, call 440-4201. The weekly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEADER PROGRAM AT DOUGLAS COUNTY MUSEUM SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125930</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/homesteader-program-at-douglas-county-museum-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homesteader-program-at-douglas-county-museum-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Douglas County Historical Society is hosting a program about Letitia Carson on Saturday afternoon at 2:00 p.m. at the Douglas County Museum. Information from The Ford Family Foundation said Carson is a formerly enslaved woman who came to Oregon in 1845 and was one of the first Black settlers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZONTA’S DIGNITY DRIVE CONTINUES THROUGH NOVEMBER 22ND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125928</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/zontas-dignity-drive-continues-through-november-22nd/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=zontas-dignity-drive-continues-through-november-22nd"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 22, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Zonta Club of Roseburg is continuing its Dignity Drive through November 22nd. The Dignity Drive collects women’s undergarments and sanitary products for victims of domestic violence. Abuse victims are often forced to flee their home with little more than the clothing they are wearing. Donated items provide dignity as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC UMPQUA SINGERS/BIG HORN JAZZ BAND “SWING INTO THE SEASON”]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125926</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/12/ucc-umpqua-singers-big-horn-jazz-band-swing-into-the-season/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-umpqua-singers-big-horn-jazz-band-swing-into-the-season"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 12, 2024 2:50 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Umpqua Community College Fine and Performing Arts Department presents the Umpqua Singers and the Big Horn Jazz Band in “Swing into the Season” on December 4th at 7:00 p.m. at Whipple Fine Arts Center on the main UCC campus. The Umpqua Singers, under the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>