<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-04-03T23:10:09.753Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STABBING INVESTIGATION CONTINUING, SUSPECT NOT LOCATED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117327</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/stabbing-investigation-continuing-suspect-not-located/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=stabbing-investigation-continuing-suspect-not-located"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T19:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 12:50 p.m.  A stabbing investigation in Roseburg is continuing, with the suspect still being sought. Sergeant Daniel Allen from the Roseburg Police said Wednesday morning at approximately 6:00 a.m. RPD officers responded to the 900 block of Northeast Willow Street regarding a reported stabbing. Allen said when officers arrived, they found that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stabbing Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news171249</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news171249"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T18:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 3, 2024 at approximately 6:00 AM, the Roseburg Police Department responded to the 900 block of NE Willow Street regarding a reported stabbing. When officers arrived, they found a 50 year old Roseburg man was injured due to a stab wound and immediately began life-saving efforts. The injured male was transported to Mercy Medical Center, then later transferred out of the area for additional treatment.
 A suspect in this case, a 20 year old Roseburg man, fled the scene and has not been located despite efforts from multiple assisting agencies and a DCSO K9 track; investigators found the victim and suspect are known to each other. Roseburg Police detectives, Douglas County Sheriff’s Office detectives, DCSO deputies and Oregon State Police responded to assist and will continue to investigate the matter with assistance from the Douglas County District Attorney’s Office. At this time, there is no known ongoing threat to the general public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Police Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CITED BY ROSEBURG POLICE FOLLOWING DUII INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117323</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-man-cited-by-roseburg-police-following-duii-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-cited-by-roseburg-police-following-duii-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 204 10:50 a.m. A Roseburg man was cited by Roseburg Police following a DUII incident early Wednesday. An RPD report said at 2:20 a.m. officers saw 41-year-old Robert Wilkerson leave the parking lot of an establishment in the 900 block of Southeast Stephens Street. An officer got behind his vehicle and saw it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CITED FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117321</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/three-cited-for-prohibited-camping-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=three-cited-for-prohibited-camping-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 10:30 a.m.   Three people were cited by Roseburg Police for prohibited camping on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 9:50 a.m. the group was contacted at their camp in the 500 block of Southeast Spruce Street after receiving numerous complaints about their camp. The two men and one woman, ranging in age...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR DRUGS/LITTERING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117319</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-drugs-littering-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-drugs-littering-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 10:15 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman following a littering incident on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 10:30 a.m. officers responded to the former Visitor’s Center building in the 400 block of Southeast Spruce Street after getting numerous reports of litter along the riverbank. The 57-year-old was contacted at her camp,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117317</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-9/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-9"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for drinking in public on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 2:10 p.m. officers contacted the 52- year-old at the intersection of Northeast Winchester Street and Northeast Shambrook Avenue where he was allegedly sitting and drinking an alcoholic beverage. The man was cited. and his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOLLOWING TRAFFIC STOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117315</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-police-cite-man-following-traffic-stop-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-following-traffic-stop-3"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man following a traffic stop on Tuesday. An RPD report said at approximately 10:50 a.m. officers stopped a pickup for a traffic violation near the intersection of Northeast Lincoln Street and Northeast Beulah Drive in Roseburg. The driver, 36-year-old Chad Woods returned with a suspended license...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Muchas Gracias set to open Roseburg location]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cebc9f62-f113-11ee-990f-3b06fe6c51d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/muchas-gracias-set-to-open-roseburg-location/article_cebc9f62-f113-11ee-990f-3b06fe6c51d5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Muchas Gracias is moving into the former Kentucky Fried Chicken/Long John Silver’s building on West Harvard Avenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSU Extension offers events for forest landowners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6dd8e768-f1c8-11ee-840a-33dee72f0acf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/osu-extension-offers-events-for-forest-landowners/article_6dd8e768-f1c8-11ee-840a-33dee72f0acf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The public is invited to attend the many forestry and natural resources programs offered by Oregon State University Extension in Douglas County this spring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Gem and Mineral show coming in May]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c6890966-f1c7-11ee-97d4-133faa4ea1db</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/umpqua-gem-and-mineral-show-coming-in-may/article_c6890966-f1c7-11ee-97d4-133faa4ea1db.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The annual event will take place May 4 and 5 in Douglas Hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forestry department invites public comment on state forest management activities&nbsp;]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171244</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171244"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore. -- The Oregon Department of Forestry is inviting public comment on planned projects, timber sales and other management activities in state-owned forests in fiscal year 2025.    
 From April 3 through 5 p.m. May 17, Oregonians can weigh in on draft Annual Operations Plans (AOPs) for state forests on the Astoria, Forest Grove, Klamath Falls, North Cascade, Tillamook, West Oregon, and Western Lane Districts. These plans lay out on-the-ground activities expected to take place in the coming fiscal year.  
 State forests by law must provide economic, environmental, and social benefits to Oregonians. To achieve that legal mandate, these lands are managed to create healthy productive forests, high-quality habitat for native fish and wildlife, clean water, timber, revenues to rural comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG TIES FOR HOTTEST DAY OF 2024, JUST MISSES RECORD HIGH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117310</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/roseburg-ties-for-hottest-day-of-2024-just-misses-record-high/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-ties-for-hottest-day-of-2024-just-misses-record-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T11:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 4:00 a.m. The high temperature in Roseburg Tuesday tied for the hottest day of the year, but just missed a record high for the date. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said the mercury reached 80 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport. That tied with the 80-degree mark set on March 18th....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CROSS COUNTRY SKIER RESCUED BY DCSO SEARCH & RESCUE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117304</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/cross-country-skier-rescued-by-dcso-search-rescue/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cross-country-skier-rescued-by-dcso-search-rescue"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 3:45 a.m.  A cross country skier was rescued after falling and injuring her ankle on Sunday afternoon. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at approximately 1:30 p.m. 911 dispatchers received a report of a 57-year-old woman who fell and injured her ankle while cross country skiing near Mt....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Family friendly employer summer this Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c6a6d85a-f114-11ee-8a7f-6318dbaddc41</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/family-friendly-employer-summer-this-thursday/article_c6a6d85a-f114-11ee-8a7f-6318dbaddc41.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Business Champions for KIDs will host the Family Friendly Employer Summit from 8:30 a.m. to 3 p.m. Thursday in the conference space of Aviva Health a the nonprofit's campus on Northeast Kenneth Ford Drive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODOT hosts open house]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f1bca3ba-f10c-11ee-8640-8b7e5dffc0db</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/odot-hosts-open-house/article_f1bca3ba-f10c-11ee-8640-8b7e5dffc0db.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Oregon Department of Transportation is hosting an open house from noon to 6 p.m. April 9 at the Roseburg headquarters on 3500 NW Stewart Parkway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONGRESSMAN BENTZ TO HOLD LISTENING SESSION ON WOLVES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117302</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/congressman-bentz-to-hold-listening-session-on-wolves/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=congressman-bentz-to-hold-listening-session-on-wolves"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 3:30 a.m. Congressman Cliff Bentz will hold a listening session on wolves with members of the ranching community and staff from the U.S. Department of Agriculture, U.S. Forest Service and Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife on Thursday in Pendleton. The event is open to the public and begins at 2:30 p.m....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSU EXTENSION OFFERS MANY FREE EVENTS FOR FOREST LANDOWNERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117300</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/osu-extension-offers-many-free-events-for-forest-landowners/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=osu-extension-offers-many-free-events-for-forest-landowners"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 3:20 a.m. The public is invited to attend the many forestry and natural resources programs offered by Oregon State University Extension in Douglas County this spring. An Extension release said the classes cover a variety of topics which are sure to be of interest to a wide range of landowners. Each of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SILENT DISCO EVENT IN MYRTLE CREEK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117297</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/silent-disco-event-in-myrtle-creek/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=silent-disco-event-in-myrtle-creek"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 3:05 a.m. Friends of the Myrtle Creek Library and the Myrtle Creeks Elks Lodge No. 1943 are presenting a Silent Disco event on Friday April 19th. Organizers said the unique experience will allow participants to get lost in the music with wireless headphones, from 6:00 p.m. to 11:00 p.m. at the Elks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA GEM AND MINERAL SHOW COMING IN MAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117294</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/03/umpqua-gem-and-mineral-show-coming-in-may/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-gem-and-mineral-show-coming-in-may"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 3, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Umpqua Gem and Mineral Show is coming in May. The annual event will take place on Saturday and Sunday May 4th and 5th in Douglas Hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds. Enjoy gem and mineral displays, vendor booths, demonstrations, prizes, rock hunts and more. Show hours are 9:00 a.m....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skier Rescued by Douglas County Search & Rescue on Easter (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news171239</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news171239"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T02:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND LAKE, Ore. - A cross country skier was rescued after falling and injuring her ankle Sunday afternoon.
On Sunday, March 31, 2024, at approximately 1:30 p.m. Douglas County 9-1-1 dispatchers received a report of a 57-year-old woman who fell and injured her ankle while cross country skiing near Mt. Thielsen with her companion. The victim was unable to bear weight on the injured leg and requested assistance.
Deputies activated the Douglas County Search & Rescue team who responded to the area along with volunteers from Diamond Lake Resort. Searchers used snowshoes to hike the four miles into the base of a tree line where they located the victim, Trina Reiter of Eugene and her companion just before 7:45 p.m. Searchers stabilized Reiter's injury, placed her in a litter and transported her back to the trailhead. They arrived at the trailhead shortly before 1:30 a.m., to a waiting ambulance. Reiter was evaluated by EMS at the scene and went to the hospital by private vehicle.
"This mission shows the dedication of our search and rescue deputies and volunteers who spent their Easter Sunday assisting someone in our community who was in need of their services," Lt. Brad O'Dell said. "This mission was very successful and Trina was extremely thankful for the care and compassion shown to her by Douglas County SAR and Diamond Lake Resort volunteers."
Douglas County SAR is a division of the Douglas County Sheriff's Office with approximately 90 active volunteers and two full-time Search and Rescue Deputies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON MAN JAILED FOLLOWING TRAFFIC STOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117287</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/winston-man-jailed-following-traffic-stop-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-man-jailed-following-traffic-stop-2"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T18:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 11:10 a.m.    A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 1:30 a.m. a deputy attempted to stop the sedan in the 2500 block of Happy Valley Road near Green. The vehicle turned up a private driveway and shut off the lights. The deputy made contact with the 29-year-old female driver and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED FOR HARASSMENT/WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117285</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/roseburg-man-jailed-for-harassment-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-for-harassment-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 204 10:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police Jailed a man for harassment and a warrant on Monday. An RPD report said at 8:30 a.m. officers responded after a caller said the suspect had shoved a victim in the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. Officers contacted the 29-year-old and discovered that he had a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRIVING UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF INTOXICANTS.]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117283</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-driving-under-the-influence-of-intoxicants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-driving-under-the-influence-of-intoxicants"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 10:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for driving while under the influence of intoxicants early Tuesday. An RPD report said just after 1:00 a.m. the 32-year-old was stopped for multiple traffic violations in the 900 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. During the traffic stop officers noticed signs of impairment. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Symphony Association hosts pianists for concert]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b760fd30-f114-11ee-833e-df2532de201f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/umpqua-symphony-association-hosts-pianists-for-concert/article_b760fd30-f114-11ee-833e-df2532de201f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Symphony Association will host internationally acclaimed classical pianist Dr. Alexander Tutunov in concert with Dr. Brian Hallo, featuring two pianos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR USING HIS CELLPHONE WHILE DRIVING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117281</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-using-his-cellphone-while-driving/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-using-his-cellphone-while-driving"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for using his cellphone while driving on Monday afternoon. An RPD report said shortly before 2:00 p.m. officers stopped the 54-year-old from Oakland in the 800 block of Southeast Stephens Street. During the stop it was determined that the man’s driver license was criminally suspended. He...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR USING HIS CELLOHONE WHILE DRIVING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117281</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-using-his-cellohone-while-driving/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-using-his-cellohone-while-driving"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for using his cellphone while driving on Monday afternoon. An RPD report said shortly before 2:00 p.m. officers stopped the 54-year-old from Oakland in the 800 block of Southeast Stephens Street. During the stop it was determined that the man’s driver license was criminally suspended. He...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED ROCK THROWING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117279</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-rock-throwing-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-rock-throwing-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 204 9:50 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged rock throwing incident on Monday. An RPD report said shortly before 10:00 p.m. officers responded to the west side of the Washington Street Bridge in the 500 block of Southeast Washington Avenue. A caller claimed that the suspect was throwing rocks at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117277</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-trespass-incident-5/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-trespass-incident-5"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a reported trespass incident on Monday. An RPD report said at 8:30 a.m. officers contacted the 41-year-old at a church in the 1100 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. The man admitted he had previously been trespassed from that location. He was charged with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED STRANGULATION INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117275</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-strangulation-incident-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-strangulation-incident-2"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged strangulation incident on Monday. An RPD report said at 8:30 p.m. officers were dispatched to the 2400 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard after a caller said there was a domestic incident, and a man was seen chocking a female. Dispatch advised...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reedsport prepares for increased train traffic]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/be51707e-f0a7-11ee-a138-439adad8d19c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/reedsport-prepares-for-increased-train-traffic/article_be51707e-f0a7-11ee-a138-439adad8d19c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REEDSPORT — Reedsport City Council approved a package — with alternate wording to include a pedestrian underpass — regarding the Reedsport Railroad Crossing Study at Monday night’s meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The home that love built' reaches completion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e9e457a2-ede5-11ee-ac55-e3236d25fb20</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/the-home-that-love-built-reaches-completion/article_e9e457a2-ede5-11ee-ac55-e3236d25fb20.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TRI CITY — After living in a trailer, Shelly Houghtlin, 69, is finally getting a place of her own.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aviva brings mobile medical unit to UCC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7950667a-f074-11ee-9b9e-83308bbdaed1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/aviva-brings-mobile-medical-unit-to-ucc/article_7950667a-f074-11ee-9b9e-83308bbdaed1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — Umpqua Community College students flocked to the Hawk Health Center, an Aviva Health mobile medical unit, on Monday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. David Brock Smith files cease and desist demand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d302ca02-f0fe-11ee-9c7b-736787bde26c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/sen-david-brock-smith-files-cease-and-desist-demand/article_d302ca02-f0fe-11ee-9c7b-736787bde26c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T14:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Senator David Brock Smith, R-Port Orford, claims he has been facing many months of “ridiculous campaign attacks from political individuals to assassinate his image.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg native nominated as American Heart Association's Woman of Impact]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2e82ae28-f04c-11ee-8c11-233b1d9ae8f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-native-nominated-as-american-heart-associations-woman-of-impact/article_2e82ae28-f04c-11ee-8c11-233b1d9ae8f9.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Born and raised in Roseburg, Brooke Xavier (locally known as Stacy Biethan), is making an impact. Xavier, who now resides in New York with her husband and two daughters, was nominated as the 2024 Woman of Impact by the American…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIGH JUST SHY OF RECORD, TEMPERATURES 15 DEGREES ABOVE NORMAL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117272</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/high-just-shy-of-record-temperatures-15-degrees-above-normal/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=high-just-shy-of-record-temperatures-15-degrees-above-normal"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T11:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 4:00 a.m. Roseburg’s high temperature Monday was a few degrees shy of the record for the date as the region enjoys two days of maximum temperatures that are 15 degrees above normal. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the mercury reached 74 degrees...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SENATOR BROCK SMITH FILES CEASE AND DESIST DEMAND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117270</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/senator-brock-smith-files-cease-and-desist-demand/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=senator-brock-smith-files-cease-and-desist-demand"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 3:30 a.m.   State Senator David Brock Smith of Port Orford claims he has been facing many months of “ridiculous campaign attacks from political individuals to assassinate his image”. A release said through false and misleading information, these individuals have sought to sow discord and hate to seemingly advance their own political goals....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REPUBLICAN LEADER HELFRICH WITH STATEMENT ON THE SIGNAGE OF HB 4002 INTO LAW]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117268</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/republican-leader-helfrich-with-statement-on-the-signage-of-hb-4002-into-law/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=republican-leader-helfrich-with-statement-on-the-signage-of-hb-4002-into-law"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 3:20 a.m.  On Monday, House Bill 4002 was signed into law, recriminalizing drugs and directing vital funding to frontline caregivers across the state. House Republican Leader Jeff Helfrich of Hood River said, “Republicans stood united and forced Democrats to do what Oregonians demanded: recriminalize drugs”. Helfrich said, “Make no mistake, this bill...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MUSIC FOR TWO PIANOS MAY 18TH AT UMPQUA COMMUNITY COLLEGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117265</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/music-for-two-pianos-may-18th-at-umpqua-community-college/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=music-for-two-pianos-may-18th-at-umpqua-community-college"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:21:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 3:05 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Symphony Association will host internationally acclaimed classical pianist Dr. Alexander Tutunov in concert with Dr. Brian Hallo, featuring two pianos. Dale Cranford has more: “Dale” Q: News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN It will be on Saturday May 18th at 3:00 p.m. on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FAMILY FRIENDLY EMPLOYER SUMMIT IS THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117263</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/02/family-friendly-employer-summit-is-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=family-friendly-employer-summit-is-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 2:50 a.m.  Business Champions for KIDs – a program of the Douglas Education Service District will have the Family Friendly Employer Summit on Thursday. It will be held in the conference space of Aviva Health on the non-profit campus on Northeast Kenneth Ford Drive, just north of Costco from 8:30 a.m. to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moon Over Buffalo opens Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/937b1908-ef09-11ee-9524-b3ff5e9ca5ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/moon-over-buffalo-opens-thursday/article_937b1908-ef09-11ee-9524-b3ff5e9ca5ae.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T02:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Umpqua Actors Community Theatre opens its production of Moon Over Buffalo on Thursday night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Arts Festival looks for young artists]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a6696914-ef06-11ee-9451-33ecc5a9f032</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/summer-arts-festival-looks-for-young-artists/article_a6696914-ef06-11ee-9451-33ecc5a9f032.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T02:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Umpqua Valley Arts is looking for artists between 8 and 18 to sell goods at the 55th Summer Arts Festival, scheduled for June 28-30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adaptive Management Program Committee meets April 8 - Correction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171198</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171198"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T22:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Correction: Independent Research and Science Team will not be joining the committee.
SALEM, Ore. — The Adaptive Management Program Committee and the Independent Research and Science Team will meet at 9 a.m. on Monday, April 8 in the Clatsop Room, Building C, at the Oregon Department of Forestry headquarters, located at 2600 State St. in Salem. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes three potential substantial decision items:

Initiating development of an Effectiveness Monitoring Plan
Address questions from the IRST regarding roads questions package
Process for initiating research questions

The meeting is open to the public to attend in person and online via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted near the start of the meeting. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours before the meeting by emailing adaptivemanagementprogram@odf.oregon.gov.
The 13-member committee The Adaptive Management Program Committee helps determine if forest practices are meeting their goals to protect natural resources through a science-based and transparent process. The committee sets the research agenda that the Independent Research and Science Team (IRST) implements. View more information on the AMPC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DUII EARLY SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117261</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-early-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-early-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T22:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 3:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for DUII early Saturday. An RPD report said at 12:20 a.m. the 54-year-old was contacted at a traffic stop at the intersection of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard and Northwest Mulholland Drive. He showed several signs of impairment before consenting to standard field sobriety tests. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117259</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-5/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-5"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T21:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 2:50 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping on Saturday. An RPD report said at 9:00 a.m. the 47-year-old had a camp set up near the Duck Pond in the 1000 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. That area is in a location where camping is prohibited. The man was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR MISUSE OF 911 ON SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117257</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-misuse-of-911-on-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-misuse-of-911-on-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T21:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 2:40 p.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for misuse of 911 on Saturday. An RPD report said at 11:30 a.m. the 23-year-old called 911 and hung up on dispatchers. Officers found the man at his apartment in the 2500 block of Northeast Stephens Street, and he admitted to calling 911. The suspect...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer art camp registration is open]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ad64c718-f064-11ee-9d7f-8f4104de406d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/summer-art-camp-registration-is-open/article_ad64c718-f064-11ee-9d7f-8f4104de406d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T20:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Arts opened registration for the 2024 Summer Camps offered for ages 3-18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public comment period on proposed rules for post-disturbance harvest rulemaking begins April 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171186</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171186"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T19:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore.— The Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) is holding a public comment period beginning April 1 for proposed rule changes related to post-disturbance timber harvest. Post-disturbance harvest refers to the removal of forest products after catastrophic events such as wildfire, wind, ice, insect or disease damage and is commonly referred to as salvage logging.
This rulemaking is required by Senate Bill 1501 (2022) that was part of the legislation that enacted the Private Forest Accord.
On Feb. 23, 2024, the Board of Forestry directed ODF to complete an analysis of the estimated economic impact of the draft rules and file a Notice of Proposed Rulemaking. The public comment period on the proposed rules will be open from April 1 to May 1 and a rules hearing will be held on April 22 at 1 p.m.  The Notice of Proposed Rulemaking includes important details including but not limited to the rule text, how to submit comments, and how to participate in the virtual rule hearing. The analysis of the estimated economic impact will be available on the ODF website before the close of the public comment period. 
More information on this rulemaking effort and ongoing updates can be found on the Proposed laws & rules page of the ODF website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117255</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-trespass/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-trespass"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 11:25 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged trespass incident on Saturday. An RPD report said at 5:15 p.m. officers responded to the Samaritan Inn in the 500 block of West Umpqua Street. The 43-year-old allegedly attacked staff and had climbed the fence at the facility. During contact with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CITED FOR THEFT FROM STORE ON FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117253</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-man-cited-for-theft-from-store-on-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-cited-for-theft-from-store-on-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 11:15 a.m. A Roseburg man was cited by Roseburg Police following a reported theft from a store on Friday. An RPD report said at 1:30 p.m. the 42-year-old was allegedly caught stealing over $287 worth of groceries and other items by loss prevention at the business in the 900 block of Northwest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117251</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-8/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-8"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 204 11:00 a.m.    Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged theft incident on Friday. An RPD report said at 2:30 p.m. the 35-year-old was detained by loss prevention at a store in the 2700 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway after he allegedly shoplifted alcohol and other assorted drinks. The man admitted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMART READING STILL SEEKING COMMUNITY VOLLUNTEERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117247</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/smart-reading-still-seeking-community-vollunteers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=smart-reading-still-seeking-community-vollunteers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Children’s literacy nonprofit SMART Reading is still seeking community volunteers. The organization is looking for volunteer readers who will be placed at an elementary school or pre-school to read with children on a weekly basis, providing reading practice time, one-on-one attention and fun, low-stress experiences with books. No prior experience...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GARDEN VOLUNTEERS NEEDED AT SHORE ACRES STATE PARK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117242</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/garden-volunteers-needed-at-shore-acres-state-park/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=garden-volunteers-needed-at-shore-acres-state-park"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 10:10 a.m.   Garden volunteers are needed at Shore Acres State Park near Coos Bay. An Oregon Parks and Recreation Department release said people can join rangers in caring for the gardens between 10:00 a.m. and 1:00 p.m. on the third Thursday of each month through September. Tasks vary depending on the season...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be a part of the conversation: Apply for the Smoke Management Advisory Committee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171167</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171167"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore.—The Oregon Department of Forestry is soliciting applications to join the Smoke Management Advisory Committee. The committee is currently seeking applications to fill one vacancy to represent the public.
Created in 1989, the Smoke Management Advisory Committee (SMAC) provides advice and assistance to the Oregon Department of Forestry Smoke Management Program. The membership of the committee consists of an industrial forestland owner representative, a non-industrial forestland owner representative, a public representative, a Forest Service representative, and a Bureau of Land Management representative. Each representative serves for two-year terms that are renewable after the two-year period.
“This is an opportunity for the public to get involved and make sure that their voice and concerns are heard when it comes to prescribed fire smoke management in Oregon.” Said Stacy McCarter, Mitigation Program Manager. 
Committee members gather for public meetings in Salem twice a year to discuss and provide advice to the Smoke Management Program regarding current prescribed burning and smoke intrusion trends, program fund balance, implementation plan items, and other current issues and projects of the program.
To apply, complete an online questionnaire at https://www.oregon.gov/odf/board/Documents/smac/smac-public-nomination-form-2024.pdf and submit to Stacy McCarter at ODF by email stacy.mccarter@odf.oregon.gov by May 1, 2024.
For specific questions about the committee, please contact Stacy McCarter at 503-701-0236 or stacy.mccarter@odf.oregon.gov. Additional SMAC background information can be found at https://www.oregon.gov/odf/board/Pages/smac.aspx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OOTFA 2024 SPRING CONVENTION STARTS THURSDAY IN WINSTON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117240</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/ootfa-2024-spring-convention-starts-thursday-in-winston/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ootfa-2024-spring-convention-starts-thursday-in-winston"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T16:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 9:30 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Oregon Old Time Fiddler’s Association 2024 Spring Convention is happening Thursday through Saturday. Musicians from around Oregon and beyond are expected. It is being held at Winston Assembly of God at 360 Darrell Avenue. Activities take place throughout the day, each day. Workshops, open...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local employees recognized as Banner Bank's Best]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/aa1d095e-f040-11ee-ba51-53d77d609cb2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/local-employees-recognized-as-banner-banks-best/article_aa1d095e-f040-11ee-ba51-53d77d609cb2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patti Curtis and Heather Coffie were selected to receive the Banner's Best award, which represents the highest level of recognition from the company, according to a press release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austin Page: helping people through their worst moments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d96b2088-d00b-11ee-8a18-e33b5df1c725</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/austin-page-helping-people-through-their-worst-moments/article_d96b2088-d00b-11ee-8a18-e33b5df1c725.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Austin Page, alongside his crew, has the responsibility of helping people through “the worst moments of their life.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 'unbelievable commitment' of Brennan Pettibone, other wildland firefighters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4c68d560-d013-11ee-882e-3bdc24a9c3ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/the-unbelievable-commitment-of-brennan-pettibone-other-wildland-firefighters/article_4c68d560-d013-11ee-882e-3bdc24a9c3ad.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things might be slow in the winter months for Douglas Forest Protective Association South Unit Protection Supervisor and Assistant Unit Forester Brennan Pettibone, but all that will change come fire season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAWSUITS REGARDING REPRESENTATIVE GOODWIN DROPPED FOR NOW]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117232</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/lawsuits-regarding-representative-goodwin-dropped-for-now/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lawsuits-regarding-representative-goodwin-dropped-for-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 3:40 a.m. A lawsuit filed against the Oregon Secretary of State’s Office, claiming that State Representative Christine Goodwin does not live within the boundary of Senate District 2 has been dismissed, at least until after the May primary election. Attorney for the plaintiffs Steven Joncus filed a voluntary dismissal late Friday, saying...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REPAIRS CONTINUE ON WINDY COVER CRAB AND FISHING DOCK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117230</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/repairs-continue-on-windy-cover-crab-and-fishing-dock/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=repairs-continue-on-windy-cover-crab-and-fishing-dock"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 3:30 a.m.   The Douglas County Parks Department has an update on the temporary closure of the Windy Cove Crab and Fishing Dock, located on Salmon Harbor Drive in Winchester Bay. A County release said the department had to temporarily close the facility on February 1st, due to structural damage that occurred during...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REEDSPORT RAILROAD CROSSING STUDY AT REEDSPORT COUNCIL MEETING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117227</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/reedsport-railroad-crossing-study-at-reedsport-council-meeting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=reedsport-railroad-crossing-study-at-reedsport-council-meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 3:05 a.m.   Covering coastal Douglas County: The City of Reedsport is preparing for potential future increases in train traffic, should the Port of Coos Bay container ship terminal be constructed on the North Spit in Coos Bay. Over the past year, the city, the Oregon Department of Transportation, the Port of Coos...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC VISUAL AND PERFORMING ARTS WIT HIGH DESERT TO HIGH TIDE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117224</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/ucc-visual-and-performing-arts-wit-high-desert-to-high-tide/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-visual-and-performing-arts-wit-high-desert-to-high-tide"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 2:50 a.m. n the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Community College Visual & Performing arts presents: High Desert to High Tide, an exhibition featuring fifteen watercolor and acrylic paintings by Oregon artist, Bets Cole. This series of paintings feature Oregon landscapes from the shore to the high desert, including depictions of valleys in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>