<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-10-04T13:19:43.601Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG SCHOOLS SEE GAINS IN ACHIEVEMENT DATA, HIGHER STANDARDS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124478</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/04/roseburg-schools-see-gains-in-achievement-data-higher-standards/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-schools-see-gains-in-achievement-data-higher-standards"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 4, 2024 3:40 a.m. Roseburg Public Schools is making progress in student achievement and has surpassed state averages in many areas, according to 2024 Oregon assessment results, released by the Oregon Department of Education on Thursday. An RPS release said the district maintains its focus on fostering even higher levels of growth to ensure...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AGENT ORANGE TOWN HALL ON SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124476</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/04/agent-orange-town-hall-on-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=agent-orange-town-hall-on-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T10:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 4, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Associate Vietnam Veterans of America Chapter 805 in Roseburg will hold an Agent Orange Town Hall on Saturday from 10:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. It will have held at Garden Valley Church on 3047 Garden Valley Road, just west of Roseburg. Several speakers will share information for veterans and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLOCKTOBER FEST IN DOWNTOWN ROSEBURG SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124472</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/04/blocktober-fest-in-downtown-roseburg-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=blocktober-fest-in-downtown-roseburg-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T10:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 4, 2024 3:20 a.m. Blocktober Fest is happening Saturday from 11:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m. in historic downtown Roseburg. The event is a celebration of what Roseburg has to offer in art, music, makers, food, drink and family fun. Blocktober Fest will take place on Southeast Jackson Street and Southeast Main Street, from Southeast...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA BREWFEST HAPPENING SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124470</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/04/umpqua-brewfest-happening-saturday-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-brewfest-happening-saturday-3"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T10:15:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 4, 2024 3:05 a.m.   Umpqua Brewfest is happening in downtown Roseburg on Saturday. An Umpqua Watersheds release said the 13th annual event will be held behind Old Soul Pizza on Southeast Main Street, during the Roseburg Blocktober Fest. Brew Fest is a community celebration of clean water, craft beer, and sustainable living in southern...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA SYMPHONY ASSOCIATION TO HOST YU & I IN CONCERT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124466</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/04/umpqua-symphony-association-to-host-yu-i-in-concert/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-symphony-association-to-host-yu-i-in-concert"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T10:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 4, 2024 2:50 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Umpqua Symphony Association kicks off its 2024-25 concert season this Sunday at 3:00 p.m. with YU & I, a violin and guitar duo. Acclaimed for what was termed, “individual virtuosity and seamless collaboration”, the YU & I duo captivates audiences with mesmerizing performances, according...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EUGENE MAN DIES IN SMALL PLANE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124459</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/eugene-man-dies-in-small-plane-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=eugene-man-dies-in-small-plane-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T23:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 5:00 p.m.  A Eugene man died in a small plane crash on Thursday on the edge of Roseburg. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said the accident happened while the pilot was attempting to land on the turf runway of George Felt Airport in the 400 block of Felt Street in Charter...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eugene Man Killed in Small Plane Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175777</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175777"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T23:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG, Ore. - The pilot and sole occupant of a single-engine plane was killed Thursday morning while attempting to land on the turf runway of George Felt Airport in the 400 block of Felt St in Roseburg.
At about 11:30 am on October 3, 2024, 9-1-1 dispatchers received calls from witnesses working at the private airfield known as Felt's Field. The witnesses advised the pilot was attempting to land the small, yellow, fixed-wing plane when the crash occurred.
After running out of runway on the first attempt, the pilot circled around and attempted the landing again, according to witnesses. The plane bounced off the ground, was launched back into the air and hit the top of a tree with the propeller before taking a nosedive to the ground. 
Deputies responded with firefighters and emergency medical providers from Central Douglas Fire and Rescue and Umpqua Valley Ambulance. 
The pilot, Steven H. Kretsinger, 65, of Eugene, was pronounced deceased on scene.
Investigators from the Federal Aviation Administration and National Transportation Safety Board were notified of the crash. Kretsinger's next of kin has been notified.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.4.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124454</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/inside-douglas-county-10-4-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-4-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T20:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Morgan Schmidt, executive director for the Central and Eastern Oregon chapter of the American Red Cross talks about hurricane disaster relief. Then Kasey Hovick of Umpqua Watersheds talks about Umpqua Brew Fes, happening on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO CHANGE IN SIZE ON HOMESTEAD/DIAMOND COMPLEX FIRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124452</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/no-change-in-size-on-homestead-diamond-complex-fires/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=no-change-in-size-on-homestead-diamond-complex-fires"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T18:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 11:10 a.m. There has been not change in size on the Homestead and Diamond Complex fires as of midday Thursday. An Umpqua National Forest update said 371 personnel are currently assigned to the fires. Although westerly winds brought slightly cooler and more humid conditions on Wednesday, fires continued to creep and back...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE JAILED, TWO CITED FOR DUII INCIDENTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124450</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/one-jailed-two-cited-for-duii-incidents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=one-jailed-two-cited-for-duii-incidents"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 10:50 a.m.  One person was jailed and two were cited, following DUII incident between late Wednesday night and early Thursday morning. A Roseburg Police report said at 11:50 p.m. officers stopped a 23-year-old Oakland woman after she allegedly committed several traffic violations on Interstate 5 northbound near the Edenbower Boulevard interchange. Officers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124448</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-driving-while-suspended-5/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-driving-while-suspended-5"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 204 10:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for driving while suspended early Thursday. An RPD report said at 1:00 a.m. the 41-year-old was pulled over for several traffic violations near the intersection of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard and Northwest Fairmount Street. He returned with a revoked license. The man was taken into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED TRESPASS ON CHURCH PROPERTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124446</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-trespass-on-church-property/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-trespass-on-church-property"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 10:20 a.m. Rosburg Police jailed a man for a reported trespass incident on a church property on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 9:30 p.m. officers responded to the 7th Day Adventist Church in the 1100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. The 59-year-old was arrested after being warned earlier in the day....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED CRIMINAL MISCHIEF WHILE ON SKATEBOARD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124444</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-criminal-mischief-while-on-skateboard/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-criminal-mischief-while-on-skateboard"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man following alleged criminal mischief in a school parking lot on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 1:15 p.m. officers contacted the 37-year-old after he allegedly broke two vehicle mirrors while riding south on Northeast Vine Street on a skateboard. This was in front of Joseph...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOG TRUCK DRIVER TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING HIGHWAY 42 CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124442</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/log-truck-driver-taken-to-hospital-following-highway-42-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=log-truck-driver-taken-to-hospital-following-highway-42-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 9:50 a.m.  A log truck driver was taken to the hospital following an accident on Highway 42 on Tuesday afternoon. An Oregon State Police report said at 12:20 p.m. the truck was towing a trailer with a full load of logs near the Douglas/Coos county line. The truck was eastbound when the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TEEN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING SINGLE VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124440</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/teen-taken-to-hospital-following-single-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=teen-taken-to-hospital-following-single-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 9:30 a.m. A teen was taken to the hospital following a single-vehicle crash on Wednesday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 3:00 p.m. the 18-year-old female from Roseburg was heading east on Dairy Loop Road when her vehicle approached a 90-degree turn. The teen thought she was taking the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STUDENT ARRESTED AFTER LOCKDOWN AT ELKTON HIGH SCHOOL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124437</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/student-arrested-after-lockdown-at-elkton-high-school/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=student-arrested-after-lockdown-at-elkton-high-school"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 9:20 a.m.  An Elkton High School student was arrested following a school-initiated lockdown on Wednesday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 1:40 p.m. dispatched received a call from the school’s principal who said they had taken the action because there was a student on campus with a firearm....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.3.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124433</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/morning-conversation-10-3-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-3-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Farm to School Executive Director Erin Maidlow talks about the organization and an upcoming fundraiser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regional Forest Practice Committee for eastern Oregon meets Oct. 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175755</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175755"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T15:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Regional Forest Practice Committee for eastern Oregon will meet at 9 a.m. on Thursday, Oct. 10 at the ODF Northeast Oregon District office, 611 20th Street, La Grande. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda. To provide public comment, please email forestresources.committees@odf.oregon.gov. 
The committee’s agenda includes:

Division updates
Operator of the Year discussion and voting
Forest Practice Technical Guidance (FPTG) development
E-Notification System (FERNS) changes
Forest resources training strategy
Compliance monitoring update

The public may attend in-person or online via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 72 hours before the meeting by emailing forestresources.committees@odf.oregon.gov.
Regional Forest Practices Committees are panels of citizens – mandated under Oregon law – that advise the Oregon Board of Forestry on current forestry issues and forest management approaches. In 1971, the legislature enacted Oregon’s Forest Practices Act which includes three Regional Forest Practices Committees, serving the Eastern, Northwest, and Southwest regions of the state. Under Oregon law, a majority of the committees’ members must be private forest landowners and logging or forest operations companies.
Oregon’s forests are among the state’s most valued resources, providing a balanced mix of environmental, economic, and social benefits. View more information on the RFPC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fourth grade students learn about the land with Ag Explorer Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9b9b639a-80ef-11ef-917a-efacfbc0b5e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/fourth-grade-students-learn-about-the-land-with-ag-explorer-days/article_9b9b639a-80ef-11ef-917a-efacfbc0b5e3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fourth graders from Yoncalla Elementary School wandered around tables in the barn at the Douglas County Fairgrounds on Wednesday, Oct. 2, as they spent their day exploring areas of agriculture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Student arrested for disorderly conduct in Elkton High School incident]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ff94974c-8197-11ef-89db-d762d7c7eb12</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/student-arrested-for-disorderly-conduct-in-elkton-high-school-incident/article_ff94974c-8197-11ef-89db-d762d7c7eb12.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ELKTON — A 17-year-old boy was arrested Wednesday afternoon after coming to Elkton High School with a firearm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Student Arrested for Disorderly Conduct in Elkton High School Incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175752</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175752"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ELKTON, Ore. - On Wednesday, October 2, 2024, at 1:38 pm, 9-1-1 dispatchers received a call from the Elkton High School reporting they were in a self-initiated lockdown. The principal reported the lockdown was the result of a student on campus with a firearm. At the time of the call, the student's whereabouts were unknown. 
Multiple deputies, along with Sutherlin Police Department and Oregon State Police responded to the scene. While responding, the school called back to indicate they believed the student was no longer on campus. Other area schools were placed in lockdown until the student could be located. 
Deputies eventually contacted the student in the area of Azalea Drive in Elkton. A backpack was recovered, and a Glock replica BB pistol was located inside. 
The student, a 17-year-old male, was taken into custody and lodged at the Douglas County Juvenile Detention Center on the following charges: 

Disorderly Conduct I
Menacing x2
Probation Violation

The Sheriff's Office is continuing its investigation working closely with school officials and agency partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winston area man dies in car accident]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f1aa5564-8196-11ef-af5e-67fcaaaaa94e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/winston-area-man-dies-in-car-accident/article_f1aa5564-8196-11ef-af5e-67fcaaaaa94e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMAS VALLEY — A Winston area man died in a single-vehicle accident in the Camas Valley area on Monday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County schools show varying results in school assessment data]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ac981d46-802c-11ef-9ca4-03f6db7b1d17</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/douglas-county-schools-show-varying-results-in-school-assessment-data/article_ac981d46-802c-11ef-9ca4-03f6db7b1d17.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Schools around Douglas County use information and data to keep improving student learning and opportunities as the world of education shifts and changes constantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN CITY HALL IS MOVING, CLOSED ON FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124428</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/sutherlin-city-hall-is-moving-closed-on-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-city-hall-is-moving-closed-on-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T10:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 4:00 a.m. Sutherlin City Hall is moving, and offices will be closed on Friday. City Recorder Melanie Masterfield said the new address will be 311 East Central Avenue. Masterfield said staff is hoping to be in the new building by Monday. The city is waiting on a certificate of occupancy and plans...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK WOMAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED PRIOR ASSAULT/ROBBERY/THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124426</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/myrtle-creek-woman-jailed-for-alleged-prior-assault-robbery-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-woman-jailed-for-alleged-prior-assault-robbery-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T10:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 3:50 a.m. A Myrtle Creek woman was jailed for an alleged prior assault, robbery and theft incident. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said on a prior date, a victim claimed he was at a park with his dog in the 400 block of South Canyon Street in Canyonville when a when...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENT JAILED FOR TRESPASSING TWICE WEST OF GREEN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124424</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/transient-jailed-for-trespassing-twice-west-of-green/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transient-jailed-for-trespassing-twice-west-of-green"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T10:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 3:40 a.m. A transient was jailed Tuesday for trespassing twice at a property west of Green. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said on Monday a resident in the 3000 block of Happy Valley Road called to say the woman was trespassing on her property. The 46-year-old was given a verbal warning....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HANNAH HERITAGE PLACE EXPLORING OPTIONS FOR FORMER ELMER’S BUILDING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124416</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/hannah-heritage-place-exploring-options-for-former-elmers-building/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hannah-heritage-place-exploring-options-for-former-elmers-building"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T10:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 3:30 a.m.  In the KQEN Business Spotlight: Hanna Heritage Place is exploring options for the former Elmer’s Restaurant building at the corner of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard and Northwest Mulholland Drive in Roseburg, according to property co-owner Bruce Hanna. Hanna told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the company is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG ELECTION VOTER’S INFORMATION AVAILABLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124414</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/roseburg-election-voters-information-available-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-election-voters-information-available-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T10:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 3:20 a.m. Residents can learn about candidates running for Roseburg Mayor and city council in a digital voters’ pamphlet that is now available. A city release said residents can find the November 5th, 2024, General Election pamphlet on the city’s website: www.cityofroseburg.org. Printed copies can also be picked up at Roseburg City...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STARTUP FINALISTS PREPARE FOR PITCH NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124412</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/startup-finalists-prepare-for-pitch-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=startup-finalists-prepare-for-pitch-night"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T10:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 3:05 a.m. Six local entrepreneurs will present their new business ideas to judges and a live audience in the next Pitch Night event, Wednesday October 16th at Backside Brewing in Roseburg. A release said Umpqua Growth Talk Pitch Nights are organized by the Umpqua Economic Development Partnership, with the goal of launching...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APPLICATIONS FOR SUMMER ARTS FESTIVAL NOW OPEN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124406</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/03/applications-for-summer-arts-festival-now-open/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=applications-for-summer-arts-festival-now-open"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T10:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 204 2:50 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Valley Arts has opened up applications for the Summer Arts Festival 2025! A UVA release said interested art vendors, food & beverage vendors, and entertainment groups can now apply to participate in the county’s most anticipated celebration of the arts. This three-day festival draws...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIKE WINTERS LAWN AND GARDEN SHOW 10.2.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124402</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-10-2-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-10-2-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T00:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County’s Commissioner of Dirt, Mike Winters, has our weekly local lawn and garden program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN JAILED FOLLOWING ALLEGED INCIDENT AT BUSINESS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124400</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/myrtle-creek-man-jailed-following-alleged-incident-at-business/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-jailed-following-alleged-incident-at-business"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T23:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 4:20 p.m.  A Myrtle Creek man was jailed following an alleged incident at a business on Tuesday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 1:00 p.m. the 45-year-old randomly attacked an employee while he was pumping gas at a station in the 200 block of Pruner Road.  The man then...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON MAN DIES IN CAMAS VALLEY AREA ACCIDENT ON MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124398</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/winston-man-dies-in-camas-valley-area-accident-on-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-man-dies-in-camas-valley-area-accident-on-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T22:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 4:00 p.m. A Winston man died in a single-vehicle accident in the Camas Valley area on Monday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 3:25 p.m. the wreck was reported in the 2000 block of Upper Camas Road. CPR was performed and the driver, 80-year-old John Parret, was pronounced deceased...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.2.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124390</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/inside-douglas-county-10-2-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-2-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T20:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brittany Arnold talks about Blocktoberfest happening Saturday in downtown Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA RIVER CLEANUP COMING SUNDAY OCTOBER 13TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124385</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/umpqua-river-cleanup-coming-sunday-october-13th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-river-cleanup-coming-sunday-october-13th"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T18:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 40th annual Umpqua River Cleanup is scheduled for Sunday October 13th. An Umpqua Watersheds release said the event offers volunteers an opportunity to help protect and preserve of one of Oregon’s most beautiful and vital waterways, from the headwaters to the sea. The event is organized by Umpqua Watersheds and supported by Thrive Umpqua,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compliance Monitoring Program Committee meets Oct. 10]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175732</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175732"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Compliance Monitoring Program Committee will hold a virtual meeting Thursday, Oct. 10, from 9 to 11 a.m. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes:

Reforestation final report
Roads & steep slopes rule selection

The meeting is open to the public to attend online via Zoom. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours before the meeting by emailing marta.l.friasbedolla@odf.oregon.gov.
The CMP Committee assists efforts to monitor compliance with Forest Practices Rules. The committee advises ODF regarding monitoring projects and procedures. View more information on the CMPC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INNOVATIVE RENAL CARE OPENING THIS FALL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124383</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/innovative-renal-care-opening-this-fall/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=innovative-renal-care-opening-this-fall"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 10:45 a.m.  In the KQEN Business Spotlight: Innovative Renal Care will soon welcome patients in Roseburg and the surrounding communities needing dialysis services. A company release said the business will be located at 171 Northwest Medical Loop, Suite 109. The facility will offer local dialysis services to those with kidney disease, including...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA WOOFSTOCK PRESENTS HOWL-O-WEEN CARNIVAL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124381</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/umpqua-woofstock-presents-howl-o-ween-carnival/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-woofstock-presents-howl-o-ween-carnival"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 10:40 a.m.  Umpqua Woofstock presents the 2024 Howl-O-Ween carnival and discount pet vaccine clinic on Saturday, October 12th. The event will be held at Central Park on East Central Avenue in Sutherlin. It includes games, vendors, storytelling, a photo booth, kids activity area and more. The carnival will run from 10:00 a.m....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSU EXTENSION OFFERS PRESSURE CANNING WORKSHOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124379</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/osu-extension-offers-pressure-canning-workshop/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=osu-extension-offers-pressure-canning-workshop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 10:30 a.m. The Oregon State University Extension Service and Master Food Preservers are offering a pressure canning workshop on Saturday, November 9th at the Elkton Community Education Center. An extension release said novice and expert food preservationists alike flounder when it comes time to use a pressure canner. Whether a fisherman looking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MINIMAL GROWTH ON HOMESTEAD COMPLEX/DIAMOND COMPLEX UNCHANGED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124377</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/minimal-growth-on-homestead-complex-diamond-complex-unchanged/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=minimal-growth-on-homestead-complex-diamond-complex-unchanged"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 10:20 a.m.  There has been minimal growth on the Homestead Complex, while the Diamond Complex remains unchanged as of midday Wednesday. An Umpqua National Forest update said the Homestead Complex is up to 10,248 acres with containment remaining at 35 percent. The Diamond Complex is listed at 11,141 acres and 90 percent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE TWO FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124375</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/roseburg-police-cite-two-for-drinking-in-public/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-two-for-drinking-in-public"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police cited two people for drinking in public on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 12:00 p.m. officers contacted the men, ages 42 and 48, on the property of a closed business at the intersection of Northeast Winchester Street and Northeast Wright Avenue. Both were reportedly drinking forty-ounce beers....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124373</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-9/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-9"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant after contacting him on Tuesday morning. An RPD report said at 10:20 a.m. officers contacted the 47-year-old in the 1400 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard after he was seen holding a beer can, which later turned out to be empty. During...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.2.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124370</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/morning-conversation-10-2-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-2-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joey Keeran talks with Feeding Umpqua Director Sarah McGregor about their annual Empty Bowls fundraiser, happening on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VA Pharmacy copayments have resumed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c116b9e4-80d1-11ef-a29c-4f2c68884b51</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/va-pharmacy-copayments-have-resumed/article_c116b9e4-80d1-11ef-a29c-4f2c68884b51.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NATION — The Veteran’s Administration has resumed charging copayments for outpatient pharmacy services this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vineyard Tour happens this weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6044c462-80d1-11ef-8cac-5b5dc716d1f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/vineyard-tour-happens-this-weekend/article_6044c462-80d1-11ef-8cac-5b5dc716d1f5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Vineyard Tour is happening this weekend, with cycling, wine and social events from Friday to Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New dialysis center opening this fall in Roseburg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/98097c2a-806e-11ef-9a56-6f960dd75563</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/health/new-dialysis-center-opening-this-fall-in-roseburg/article_98097c2a-806e-11ef-9a56-6f960dd75563.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovative Renal Care is opening a medical center this fall in Roseburg for people in need of dialysis services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrate fire safety during Fire Prevention Month]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f51515c2-806f-11ef-8f39-2b317dc6d9aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/celebrate-fire-safety-during-fire-prevention-month/article_f51515c2-806f-11ef-8f39-2b317dc6d9aa.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oregon State Fire Marshal is hosting a campaign “Celebrate Fire Safety” to celebrate October as Fire Prevention Month: a good time to focus on fire prevention and safety at home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg voters information now available online]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0dbc51de-8071-11ef-96cd-4bec1ced9a12</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/roseburg-voters-information-now-available-online/article_0dbc51de-8071-11ef-96cd-4bec1ced9a12.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A voters pamphlet is available for Roseburg residents who want to learn more about candidates running for mayor and City Council.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN ANNUAL TRUNK OR TREAT SATURDAY OCTOBER 24TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124364</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/sutherlin-annual-trunk-or-treat-saturday-october-24th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-annual-trunk-or-treat-saturday-october-24th"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T10:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 3, 2024 3:50 a.m. Sutherlin Downtown Development will present their annual Trunk or Treat event on Saturday October 26th from 4:00 p.m. to 6:00 p.m. This will turn Central Avenue into a gathering place for scarecrows, dancing witches and vendors will all things Halloween. Festivities will include the Roseburg Hexenbrut Dancing Witches, local businesses...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALVATION ARMY NOW ACCEPTING APPLICATIONS FOR ANGEL TREE PROGRAM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124362</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/salvation-army-now-accepting-applications-for-angel-tree-program/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=salvation-army-now-accepting-applications-for-angel-tree-program"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T10:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Salvation Army in Roseburg is now accepting applications for its Angel Tree Christmas toy program. Applications are being taken Tuesdays through Fridays from 9:00 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. and from 1:00 p.m. to 3:00 p.m. at the Salvation Army offices at 3130 Northeast Stephens Street. Those in need of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG CITY COUNCIL WORK STUDY SESSION ON URBAN CAMPGROUND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124360</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/roseburg-city-council-work-study-session-on-urban-campground/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-city-council-work-study-session-on-urban-campground"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T10:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 3:30 a.m.  The Roseburg City Council will have a Work Study Session Wednesday evening at 6:00 p.m. to discuss an Urban Campground Criteria. The meeting will be held in the city council chambers. It is open to the public, but no audience input will be taken. More information about what will be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VA PHARMACY COPAYMENTS HAVE RESUMED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124358</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/va-pharmacy-copayments-have-resumed/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=va-pharmacy-copayments-have-resumed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 3:20 a.m.  The Veteran’s Administration has resumed charging copayments for outpatient pharmacy services this month. A Roseburg VA release said copayment had been paused during the transition to the new Federal electronic health record system. On November statements, veterans will see required copayment charges for pharmacy medications dispensed on or after October...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VINEYARD TOUR HAPPENING THIS WEEKEND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124356</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/vineyard-tour-happening-this-weekend/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=vineyard-tour-happening-this-weekend"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T10:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Vineyard Tour is happening this weekend, with cycling, wine and social events between this Friday and next Monday. Presented by the Umpqua Velo Club, the events are designed to showcase the Umpqua Valley and attract cyclists from near and far. Activities include: *A Let’s Get It Started social Friday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WILDLIFE SAFARI ZOOBILEE EXPANDS TO THREE NIGHTS DUE TO DEMAND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124351</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/02/wildlife-safari-zoobilee-expands-to-three-nights-due-to-demand/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wildlife-safari-zoobilee-expands-to-three-nights-due-to-demand"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T10:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 2, 2024 2:50 a.m. Wildlife Safari has announced that due to overwhelming popularity, Zoobilee, the park’s annual family-friendly Halloween event, will be extended to three nights this year. A Safari release said Zoobilee will take place on October 25th, 26th and 27th from 5:00 p.m. to 8:00 p.m. For just $10 per person, Zoobilee...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 10.1.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124348</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/true-wealth-10-1-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-10-1-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T00:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littlejohn Financial, David Littlejohn and Justin Bruggeman have our weekly local financial program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.01.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124344</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/inside-douglas-county-10-01-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-01-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Representative Court Boice looks back at last week’s Legislative Days and covers a number of legislative issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public hearing scheduled for clarifying definitions related to emergency fire and emergency fire costs proposed rules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175706</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175706"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T18:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — A rulemaking hearing is scheduled for Tuesday, Oct. 22 at 10 a.m. to gather public input on administrative rules clarifying definitions related to emergency fire and emergency fire costs. Public comment can be made by joining the Zoom meeting link. See the notice of proposed rulemaking for draft rule language. 
The proposed revisions clarify existing language and include recommendations made to the Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) by Macias Gini & O'Connell LLP (MGO), an independent third-party contractor, that reviewed ODF’s financial practices. The proposed amended administrative rules ensure the true costs of wildland suppression costs are accurately accounted for, tracked, reported, and paid for at the statewide level.
Comments can also be sent to nancy.hirsch@odf.oregon.gov until 5 p.m. on Oct. 31. Please clarify which rule your comments pertain to in your email.
For additional information, please visit ODF’s proposed laws & rules website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR DRIVING WITH LICENSE REVOKED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124342</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/rosburg-police-jail-woman-for-driving-with-license-revoked/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rosburg-police-jail-woman-for-driving-with-license-revoked"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T18:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 11:10 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman early Tuesday for driving with a license that had been revoked. An RPD report said just after 12:15 a.m. officers stopped a vehicle in the 100 block of Northwest Dogwood Drive. After determining her status, she was taken into custody. She was also cited for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE ON HOMESTEAD/DIAMOND COMPLEX FIRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124340</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/update-on-homestead-diamond-complex-fires/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=update-on-homestead-diamond-complex-fires"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T17:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 10:50 a.m.  An Umpqua National Forest update said the Homestead Complex has grown by just over 100 acres to 10,159 acres as of midday Tuesday, with containment still at 35 percent. The Diamond Complex remains 90 percent contained at 11,141 acres. The Oregon Department of Transportation has temporarily lowered the speed limit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLCE JAIL MAN AFTER REPORTED FIGHT WITH OFFICERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124338</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/sutherlin-polce-jail-man-after-reported-fight-with-officers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-polce-jail-man-after-reported-fight-with-officers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T17:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 10:20 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a man after a reported fight with officers on Monday afternoon. An SPD report said at 1:30 p.m. 24-year-old Timothy Luzier was called in for driving while intoxicated in the 1400 block of West Central Avenue. Luzier was located as he backed his vehicle into another vehicle....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE FOUR PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124336</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/roseburg-police-cite-four-people-for-prohibited-camping-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-four-people-for-prohibited-camping-4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T17:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police cited four people for prohibited camping on Monday. An RPD report said at 9:15 a.m. officers contacted a 41-year-old man and a 35-year-old woman at their camp, which was located about one foot off the bike path near the bike jumps in Gaddis Park, in the 800 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL FUGITIVE FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124334</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-for-warrant-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-for-warrant-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant on Monday night. An RPD report said at 11:55 p.m. officers contacted the 43-year-old in the 3100 block of Northeast Stephens Street and attempted to detain him. The suspect was allegedly combative and hostile with officers. An officer pointed a taser at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING ALLEGED DISTURBANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124332</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-alleged-disturbance-10/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-alleged-disturbance-10"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man following an alleged disturbance late Monday night. A RPD report said at 10:30 p.m. officers responded to the incident in the 3000 block of West Harvard Avenue and developed probable cause to arrest the 37-year-old. He reportedly slapped a victim in the face while juveniles...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY INTO A MOTOR VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124330</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-unauthorized-entry-into-a-motor-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-unauthorized-entry-into-a-motor-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man Monday night for unauthorized entry into a motor vehicle. An RPD report said at 7:00 p.m. officers contacted 49-year-old Jason Roland because he was suspected of breaking into a vehicle and stealing a wallet. Roland was Mirandized and reportedly admitted to breaking in the SUV,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSP RESPONDS TO ROLLOVER CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124328</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/osp-responds-to-rollover-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=osp-responds-to-rollover-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:22:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 9:20 a.m. Troopers with Oregon State Police responded to a rollover crash on Monday night. An OSP reports said shortly after 6:30 p.m., a pickup was southbound near the Highway 42 exit at milepost 112. The vehicle was in the fast lane when the right rear tire popped, causing the pickup to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.1.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124325</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/morning-conversation-10-1-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-1-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Erik Schnautz of the Umpqua Velo Club talks about the Vineyard Tour events happening this weekend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari expands Halloween event to three nights]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7d91cb7e-8008-11ef-82da-afd57b84c62d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/wildlife-safari-expands-halloween-event-to-three-nights/article_7d91cb7e-8008-11ef-82da-afd57b84c62d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T15:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Wildlife Safari's annual family-friendly Halloween event, Zoobilee, will last three nights this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin seeks affordable housing funds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/903ea86c-7fab-11ef-9f03-3f4eab7ea84b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/sutherlin-seeks-affordable-housing-funds/article_903ea86c-7fab-11ef-9f03-3f4eab7ea84b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Sutherlin is seeking a $5.5 million federal grant to help pay for an affordable workforce housing project, known as Oak Street Commons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Bar Run’s golf course]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e38dcc10-7f82-11ef-b033-c359ccee9aaf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/managing-bar-run-s-golf-course/article_e38dcc10-7f82-11ef-b033-c359ccee9aaf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Barry Adams, superintendent for Bar Run’s golf course, was preparing the course for a Pacific Northwest Golf Association tournament, he noticed the greens were running faster than they typically do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSU hosts certified burn manager course]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b48f36b0-8004-11ef-b051-af1a6a1b7cf6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/osu-hosts-certified-burn-manager-course/article_b48f36b0-8004-11ef-b051-af1a6a1b7cf6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Oregon State University Extension Service is hosting a three day certified burn manager course from 8 a.m. to 5 p.m. Oct. 23-25 at its auditorium on 1134 SE Douglas Ave.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Important dates for the upcoming election]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/48662ae8-8004-11ef-8c9c-a71c2e29212b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/elections/important-dates-for-the-upcoming-election/article_48662ae8-8004-11ef-8c9c-a71c2e29212b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T14:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — The Nov. 5 General Election is approaching, and Douglas County Clerk Daniel Loomis has provided a list of important dates to be aware of:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Eichenbusch named school security coordinator]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fff65cf6-8003-11ef-9497-cfdb218e3bcf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/jeff-eichenbusch-named-school-security-coordinator/article_fff65cf6-8003-11ef-9497-cfdb218e3bcf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Roseburg Public Schools named Jeff Eichenbusch as the new security coordinator for the district.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNSEASONABLY HIGH TEMPERATURES CONTINUE THIS WEEK IN REGION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124319</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/unseasonably-high-temperatures-continue-this-week-in-region/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=unseasonably-high-temperatures-continue-this-week-in-region"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T10:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 3:50 a.m. Unseasonably high temperatures are expected to continue for most of this week in the Umpqua Valley. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said a flat ridge of high pressure will lead to afternoon high temperatures in the low to mid 80s with the exception of Wednesday when highs will cool...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANTS/WEAPONS VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124317</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-warrants-weapons-violation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-warrants-weapons-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T10:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 3:40 a.m. Sutherlin Police jailed for warrants and a weapons violation on Saturday afternoon. An SPD report said at 4:50 p.m. during a traffic stop in the 1200 block of West Central Avenue the 41-year-old was taken into custody. He is prohibited from possessing a firearm per a court order for a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GENERAL ELECTION APPROACHING – IMPORTANT DATES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124313</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/general-election-approaching-important-dates/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=general-election-approaching-important-dates"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T10:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 3:30 a.m. The November 5th General Election is approaching, and Douglas County Clerk Daniel Loomis has provided a list of important dates to be aware of: *October 8th: Local ballots for those who will be out of state go to the U.S. Postal Service *October 14th: Estimated delivery date by Oregon State...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY OF ROSEBURG PUBLIC WORKS PROJECTS STATUS UPDATE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124311</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/city-of-roseburg-public-works-projects-status-update/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-of-roseburg-public-works-projects-status-update"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T10:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 3:20 a.m. The City of Roseburg Public Works Department has an update on two projects impacting motorists. Paving work is underway on Northeast Stephens Street as roadway improvement and water main transmission line projects begin to wrap up The southbound lane of Northeast Stephens between Northeast Isabell Avenue and Northeast Newton Creek...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RPS NAMES JEFF EICHENBUSCH AS SECURITY COORDINATOR]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124308</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/rps-names-jeff-eichenbusch-as-security-coordinator/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rps-names-jeff-eichenbusch-as-security-coordinator"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T10:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 3:05 a.m. Roseburg Public Schools has named Jeff Eichenbusch as the new security coordinator for the district. Eichenbusch has lived in Douglas County since he was 3 years old. After graduating from Umpqua Valley Christian School in 1992, he pursued his education at Western Oregon University, earning a Bachelor of Science in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA BREWFEST HAPPENING SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124305</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/01/umpqua-brewfest-happening-saturday-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-brewfest-happening-saturday-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T10:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 1, 2024 2:50 a.m. Umpqua Watersheds is hosting the 13th annual Umpqua Brew Fest this Saturday. The event serves up great brews each fall and will be held from 11:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m. on Southeast Main Street in downtown Roseburg, behind Old Soul Pizza, during Roseburg Blocktober Fest. A UW release said it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>