<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-10-15T23:12:44.410Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Oregon District terminates regulated-use closure; fire season remains in effect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176037</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176037"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T21:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRINEVILLE, Ore. – Oregon Department of Forestry’s Central Oregon District will terminate regulated-use closure at 12:01 a.m., Wednesday, Oct. 16, 2024. Fire season remains in effect across the Central Oregon District.
“We caution the public to be mindful of activities which could start a fire as we continue to slowly ease into winter. Periods of dry windy weather are possible and can be a threat into November,” says Brandon Ferguson, Forest Resources Manager for the John Day Unit. “While fire danger has lessened with cooler nights and increased humidity, we can still have rapidly spreading fires during the heat of the day.”
Wildland fuels, including live vegetation and down wood material are extremely dry. Limited precipitation, combined with long-term drought conditions continue to elevate the risk of fire ignition and increase fire behavior in wildland fuels. Fire managers regularly evaluate conditions to determine current fire danger and necessary restrictions to limit impacts from wildfires.
During fire season backyard debris burning, including burn barrels is allowed by permit only. Many counties have burn bans in place prohibiting debris burning at this time. Check restrictions in your local area to help prevent wildfires.
With the termination of regulated-use closure, chainsaw use and mowing restrictions are lifted and small warming/recreational fires may be allowed on ODF-protected lands unless restricted locally.
Failure to follow fire season restrictions can result in citations, fines, and liability for costs associated with putting fires out. Wildfires impact public health, water quality, soil productivity, landowners, and local communities and businesses.
For additional information on ODF’s Central Oregon District, including regulated-use closure restrictions and contact information, please visit www.ODFcentraloregon.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DINT ARRESTS TWO FOLLOWING A MONTH-LONG INVESTIGATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124881</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/dint-arrests-two-following-a-month-long-investigation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dint-arrests-two-following-a-month-long-investigation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 1:50 p.m.  On Monday, detectives with the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team were assisted by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office in bringing to conclusion a month-long investigation into suspected drug trafficking. DINT Commander Lieutenant Rick McArthur said at approximately 8:30 p.m. a deputy initiated a traffic stop on a vehicle on Interstate 5...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.15.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124875</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/inside-douglas-county-10-15-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-15-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angela Wilhelms, president of Oregon Business and Industry talks about her group’s opposition to Ballot Measure 118.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DINT makes arrests in meth investigation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/efb8d82c-8b21-11ef-b45d-5755c2f38357</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/dint-makes-arrests-in-meth-investigation/article_efb8d82c-8b21-11ef-b45d-5755c2f38357.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team detectives brought a months-long investigation into suspected drug trafficking to a conclusion Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meth Arrest (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6255#news176024</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6255#news176024"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, October 14th, detectives with the Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT) were assisted by the Douglas County Sheriff's Office in bringing to conclusion a month long investigation into suspected drug trafficking.  
At approximately 8:30 PM, a Douglas County Sheriff's Deputy initiated a traffic stop on a vehicle on I-5 at milepost 161 near Curtin, at the request of DINT detectives.  Two persons were detained:  45 year old Jeffrey Bell, and 45 year old Annie Randles, both of Roseburg.
During a search of the vehicle, detectives found approximately 2 pounds of suspected methamphetamine.  Detectives followed up with a search of a residence in the 900 block of Shoestring Road in Riddle where they found more evidence of drug trafficking.  
Jeff Bell was lodged at the Douglas County Jail on charges of Possession, Manufacturing, and Delivery of Methamphetamine.  
Annie Randles was cited and released on charges on Unlawful Possession and Delivery of Methamphetamine.
 
The Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT) is a multi-jurisdictional narcotics task force that identifies, disrupts, and dismantles local, multi-state, and international drug trafficking organizations using an intelligence-driven, multi-agency prosecutor-supported approach.  DINT is supported by the Oregon-Idaho High-Intensity Drug Trafficking Area (HIDTA) and is composed of members from the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office, Roseburg Police Department, Oregon State Police, Douglas County District Attorney’s Office, and the Bureau of Land Management.
The Oregon-Idaho HIDTA program is an Office of National Drug Control Policy (ONDCP) sponsored counterdrug grant program that coordinates with and provides funding resources to multi-agency drug enforcement initiatives, including DINT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Interagency Narcotics Team (DINT)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPTD SELECTS TOP APPLICANT FOR INTERIM GM POSITION, BOARD MEMBER RESIGNS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124871</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/uptd-selects-top-applicant-for-interim-gm-position-board-member-resigns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uptd-selects-top-applicant-for-interim-gm-position-board-member-resigns"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 11:10 a.m. The Board of Directors of the Umpqua Public Transportation District has selected Ben Edtl as the top applicant for the position of interim general manager. Chair/Executive Director Position 2 Michaela Hammerson said the decision was reached by a vote of 4 in favor, 2 against and 1 abstention. Hammerson said...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Bruce Campus hosts trunk or treat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/592cd28c-8a54-11ef-b8e4-6f0bb1788c94</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/jerry-bruce-campus-hosts-trunk-or-treat/article_592cd28c-8a54-11ef-b8e4-6f0bb1788c94.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Jerry Bruce Community Campus partner organizations including the FISH Food Pantry and Aviva Health, are holding a trunk-or-treat for families Saturday, Oct. 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124869</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-17/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-17"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 10:40 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for drinking in public Monday evening. An RPD report said at 6:50 p.m. a 63-year-old man was contacted because he was sitting on the sidewalk in the 200 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard and was drinking a can of malt liquor. He was released...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE 5 PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124867</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-police-cite-5-people-for-prohibited-camping-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-5-people-for-prohibited-camping-4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited 5 people for prohibited camping between Monday morning and early Tuesday morning. An RPD report said contacts were made at camps in the corner of Northwest Stewart Parkway and Northwest Renann Street, in the 1400 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive, in the 200 block of Northwest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR CRIMINAL TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124865</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-criminal-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-criminal-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a criminal trespass incident on Monday. An RPD report said at 10:30 a.m. the 41-year-old was contacted in the 700 block of Southeast Jackson Street. Officers learned the man was a city expulsion violator on his third warning and that his parole officer wanted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN ARRESTED BY BOTH RPD AND DCSO FOLLOWING ELUDE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124863</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-man-arrested-by-both-rpd-and-dcso-following-elude/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-arrested-by-both-rpd-and-dcso-following-elude"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 10:00 a.m. A Roseburg man was arrested by both the Roseburg Police Department and the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office following an eluding incident on Monday night. Reports from both agencies indicate that 25-year-old Blake Van Norman was called in for driving recklessly in the area of West Godeck Avenue in Roseburg at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOTH DRIVERS CITED IN HUCREST TWO-VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124861</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/both-drivers-cited-in-hucrest-two-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=both-drivers-cited-in-hucrest-two-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 9:30 a.m. Both drivers were cited after a two-vehicle crash in the Hucrest neighborhood on Monday afternoon. A Roseburg Police report said at 5:30 p.m. officers responded to the accident at the intersection of Northwest Calkins Road and Northwest Troost Street. An 18-year-old driver said she did not stop at the stop...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.15.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124858</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/morning-conversation-10-15-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-15-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rebecca Marshall of the American Red Cross talks about the disaster relief work she has been doing in Tennessee, and the other places the non-profit is currently assisting around the nation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Halloween events throughout Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a24512fe-8211-11ef-9eb2-6b318c22e8d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/health/halloween-events-throughout-douglas-county/article_a24512fe-8211-11ef-9eb2-6b318c22e8d0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October brings with it fall weather and ghastly sights as Douglas County sets up for spooky times in the name of Halloween.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BEGINNING OF SIGNIFICANT CHANGE TO WEATHER IN THE UMPQUA VALLEY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124855</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/beginning-of-significant-change-to-weather-in-the-umpqua-valley/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=beginning-of-significant-change-to-weather-in-the-umpqua-valley"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T11:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 4:10 a.m. Tuesday will see the beginning of a significant change to the weather in the Umpqua Valley. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that Tuesday and Wednesday will see light showers with .10 inches of rain between the two days. Thursday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEAGUE OF WOMEN VOTERS TO HOST TOWN HALL FOR CITY COUNCIL CANDIDATES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124853</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/league-of-women-voters-to-host-town-hall-for-city-council-candidates/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=league-of-women-voters-to-host-town-hall-for-city-council-candidates"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 3:40 a.m. The League of Women Voters of the Umpqua Valley will host a town hall for Roseburg City Council candidates on Wednesday, October 23rd. For the first time in many years, there are two candidates running for all four council positions which are up a vote. Organizers say the event will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAST DAY TO REGISTER AS A NEW OREGON VOTER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124851</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/last-day-to-register-as-a-new-oregon-voter/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=last-day-to-register-as-a-new-oregon-voter"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 3:30 a.m. Tuesday is the last day to register as a new Oregon voter, ahead of the November General Election. Douglas County Clerk Daniel Loomis said current voters can make changes in their status up to election day. Loomis said to get registered, go to a link on the Oregon Secretary of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COMMUNITY HELP NEEDED FOR WREATHS ACROSS AMERICA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124848</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/community-help-needed-for-wreaths-across-america/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=community-help-needed-for-wreaths-across-america"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 3:20 a.m. Community help is needed for this year’s Wreaths Across America wreath laying ceremony on Saturday December 14th. Douglas County Commissioner Chris Boice has been working closely with location coordinator John Pierson. Pierson is battling terminal cancer, but his goal for many years has been to raise enough money to place...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTH DOUGLAS COUNTY LIBRARIES WITH FOOD DRIVE CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124846</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/south-douglas-county-libraries-with-food-drive-challenge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=south-douglas-county-libraries-with-food-drive-challenge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 3:05 a.m. The libraries in south Douglas County have launched a collaborative food drive challenge in support of the South Douglas Food Bank. The initiative aims to gather non-perishable food items to assist families in need within the community. The food drive challenge will run through December 15th. It also introduces a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN HOSPITALIZED/CITED FOLLOWING SINGLE VEHICLE ACCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124844</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/15/roseburg-man-hospitalized-cited-following-single-vehicle-accident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-hospitalized-cited-following-single-vehicle-accident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15, 2024 2:50 a.m. A Roseburg man was hospitalized and cited following a single-vehicle wreck early Monday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 1:20 a.m. the 21-year-old was driving west on Happy Valley Road in the Green area. He drifted out of his lane to the right and his vehicle struck...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari plans for African painted dogs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c237549c-8a8a-11ef-9d15-dfd122400431</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/wildlife-safari-plans-for-african-painted-dogs/article_c237549c-8a8a-11ef-9d15-dfd122400431.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T00:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Wildlife Safari's annual benefit dinner raised more than $200,000 to help fund the upcoming African painted dog exhibit, which will be located in the lion loop of the drive-through area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA CREWS DEAL WITH KENT CREEK FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124841</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/dfpa-crews-deal-with-kent-creek-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-crews-deal-with-kent-creek-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T22:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:00 p.m.  Crews with the Douglas Forest Protective Association dealt with the Kent Creek Fire on Sunday. Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said at approximately 3:20 p.m. DFPA, Central Douglas Fire & Rescue and Lookingglass Rural Fire District responded to a natural cover fire near the 200 block of Kent Creek Road...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.14.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124834</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/inside-douglas-county-10-14-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-14-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T20:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Commissioner Chris Boice talks about this year’s Wreaths Across America event at the Roseburg VA Cemetery and the community help that is needed to lay 7,000 wreaths.  Residents can sign up to help here:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE 14 PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124832</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/roseburg-police-cite-14-people-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-14-people-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T18:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 11:10 a.m. Roseburg Police cited 14 people for prohibited camping between Saturday afternoon and Sunday morning. An RPD report said the camps were located in the 1400 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive, at Deer Creek Park in the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street, at the corner of Southeast Cass Avenue...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE MAN JAILED FOR DISORDERLY CONDUCT/RESISTING ARREST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124830</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/riddle-man-jailed-for-disorderly-conduct-resisting-arrest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riddle-man-jailed-for-disorderly-conduct-resisting-arrest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 10:50 a.m.  A Riddle man was charged with second-degree disorderly conduct and resisting arrest following an incident Saturday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 11:00 p.m. deputies responded after a caller said there was a disturbance in the 300 block of East Fifth Avenue. When the first deputy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED FOR DUII WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124828</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/roseburg-man-jailed-for-duii-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-for-duii-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 10:20 a.m. A Roseburg man was jailed for a DUII wreck late Sunday morning. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 12:00 p.m. the 37-year-old wrecked his pickup in the 2000 block of South Deer Creek Road in Green. He was contacted by a nearby resident who believed that the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YONCALLA MAN JAILED FOR ALLEGED STRANGULATION INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124825</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/yoncalla-man-jailed-for-alleged-strangulation-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=yoncalla-man-jailed-for-alleged-strangulation-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 10:00 a.m.   A Yoncalla man was jailed for an alleged strangulation incident on Sunday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 8:00 p.m. a deputy responded to the 100 block of Birch Street. A victim had an injury to her neck area and legs. The victim stated that the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING HIGH-SPEED CHASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124823</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/winston-police-jail-man-following-high-speed-chase/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-police-jail-man-following-high-speed-chase"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2023 9:50 a.m.  Winston Police jailed a man following a high-speed chase that started late Sunday night. A WPD report said just before 12:00 a.m. Monday, officers attempted a stop on a motorcycle near the intersection of Brockway Road and Lookingglass Road for traffic violations.  The driver, later identified as 44-year-old Roy Abbot,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING REPORTED DISTURBANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124821</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/sutherlin-police-jail-man-following-reported-disturbance-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-following-reported-disturbance-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 9:30 a.m.    Sutherlin Police jailed a man following a reported disturbance on Friday night. An SPD report said just after 8:40 p.m. 25-year-old Corbin Christy and a victim were allegedly involved in the incident at a motel in the 1400 block of Hospitality Way. Neighbors reported loud yelling and physical fighting....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN ON DRUG AND WEAPON CHARGES SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124817</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/sutherlin-police-jail-man-on-drug-and-weapon-charges-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-on-drug-and-weapon-charges-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 9:20 a.m. Sutherlin Police jailed a man on drug and weapon charges on Saturday. An SPD report said just after 1:00 a.m. 36-year-old Miles Yohai allegedly agreed to see a half ounce of methamphetamine for $110. When Yohai arrived at Ford’s Pond at the agreed upon time, he was taken into custody...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.14.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124814</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/morning-conversation-10-14-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-14-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiffany Roddy of the Douglas County Chapter of the Oregon Women in Timber talks about the educational program OWIT offers for young people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Board of Forestry to meet on Oct. 16 and 17 in Pendleton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175999</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175999"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T15:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Oregon Board of Forestry will meet in Pendleton for their fall retreat on Oct. 16 and 17. The retreat’s two-day itinerary will include an executive session, field tour, and public social on Wednesday, Oct. 16, and an executive session and public meeting on Thursday, Oct. 17. Both executive sessions will be closed to the public, except for members of the press. The field tour and social event that will take place on Oct. 16 are open to the public for in-person participation, and recordings of highlights will be posted on the board’s meeting page afterward. The public meeting that will take place on Oct. 17 will be open for in-person observation and livestreamed on the department’s YouTube channel.
The board’s agenda for the retreat’s public meeting includes:

State of the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pink in Paradise show to honor breast cancer survivors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4fd632e8-88ea-11ef-b879-7b05756aebf4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/health/pink-in-paradise-show-to-honor-breast-cancer-survivors/article_4fd632e8-88ea-11ef-b879-7b05756aebf4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Vanessa Cummings visited her doctor for a routine mammogram in August 2022, they found a speck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ELDERLY MAN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING HEAD-ON CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124805</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/elderly-man-taken-to-hospital-following-head-on-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=elderly-man-taken-to-hospital-following-head-on-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 4:00 a.m. An elderly man was taken to the hospital following a head-on crash on Saturday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 1:50 p.m. a 22-year-old driver was traveling north in his sedan on old Highway 99 North near Del Rio Road when he failed to maintain his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WOMAN JAILED ON 28 CHARGES: THEFT IN UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124803</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/woman-jailed-on-28-charges-theft-in-umpqua-national-forest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=woman-jailed-on-28-charges-theft-in-umpqua-national-forest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:50 a.m. A Myrtle Creek woman was jailed on 28 charges for alleged theft incidents in the Umpqua National Forest on Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 5:45 p.m. a 45-year-old was stopped while driving a sedan on Highway 230 in the Tree Lakes Snow Park/Diamond Lake area. She...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLUMBUS DAY/INDIGENOUS PEOPLE’S DAY MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124801</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/columbus-day-indigenous-peoples-day-monday-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=columbus-day-indigenous-peoples-day-monday-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:40 a.m. Monday is Columbus Day, a federal holiday. However approximately 29 states and Washington D.C. do not celebrate it. In Oregon, Monday is Indigenous People’s Day and is a state holiday. With the two observances, federal and state offices will be closed. Regular mail will not be delivered. Banks and credit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY COUNCIL TO CONSIDER DOWNTOWN PARKING ENFORCEMENT OPTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124799</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/city-council-to-consider-downtown-parking-enforcement-options/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-council-to-consider-downtown-parking-enforcement-options"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Roseburg City Council will consider downtown parking enforcement options as part of its meeting Monday night. The city has had a contract with ACE Parking Enforcement since the start of 2022. However, ACE has failed to generate enough revenue to cover the cost of its contract. The council has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VETERAN’S HEALTH & AWARENESS FAIR ON TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124795</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/veterans-health-awareness-fair-on-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=veterans-health-awareness-fair-on-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3;20 a.m. The Roseburg VA Medical Center is presenting the 2024 Veteran’s Health & Awareness Fair on Tuesday. A VA release said the event is being held to help raise awareness as October is National Breast Cancer Awareness Month and National Domestic Violence Awareness Month. An Awareness Walk will begin at 11:00...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JERRY BRUCE CAMPUS NON-PROFIT PARTNERS TO HOLD TRUNK-OR-TREAT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124793</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/jerry-bruce-campus-non-profit-partners-to-hold-trunk-or-treat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=jerry-bruce-campus-non-profit-partners-to-hold-trunk-or-treat"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:05 a.m. Jerry Bruce Community Campus partner organizations Family Development Center, the FISH Food Pantry, Umpqua Homes, United Community Action Network and Aviva Health are holding a truck-or-treat for local families this Saturday October 19th. It will take place from 12:00 p.m. to 3:00 p.m. in the Aviva Health parking lot on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPOUSAL AND SURVIVORS BENEFITS EDUCATIONAL SEMINAR]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124790</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/spousal-and-survivors-benefits-educational-seminar-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spousal-and-survivors-benefits-educational-seminar-3"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024, 2:50 a.m.  Associates of Vietnam Veterans of America will have a Spousal and Survivor Benefits Educational Seminar coming soon. The event will be held on Saturday, November 2nd from 10:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. at Garden Valley Church, at 3047 Garden Valley Road, west of Roseburg. Those attending can learn about the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A paw-sitively good time at Howl-O-Ween in Sutherlin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c06ec9ac-88db-11ef-8dc2-278e151eb33f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/a-paw-sitively-good-time-at-howl-o-ween-in-sutherlin/article_c06ec9ac-88db-11ef-8dc2-278e151eb33f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Richard Atkinson brought his two heelers, 4-year-old Cricket and 5-year-old Bobo, to Sutherlin’s Central Park on Saturday to socialize at the 2024 Howl-O-Ween carnival.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hope for Helmets hands out headware to bikers, skaters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/47a9ae78-88dc-11ef-b20f-a768cab92343</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/court/hope-for-helmets-hands-out-headware-to-bikers-skaters/article_47a9ae78-88dc-11ef-b20f-a768cab92343.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noel Crownover organized Helmets for Hope to help prevent head injuries among skaters in Douglas County, as his community project for Douglas County H.O.P.E. Drug Court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN DIES IN VEHICLE VERSUS MOTORCYCLE ACCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124787</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/myrtle-creek-man-dies-in-vehicle-versus-motorcycle-accident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-dies-in-vehicle-versus-motorcycle-accident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 12, 2024 9:40 a.m. A Myrtle Creek man died in a vehicle versus motorcycle accident on Friday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said shortly after 10:30 p.m. dispatchers received a call regarding the wreck on Riddle Bypass Road near the intersection with E Street in Riddle. Deputies, along with fire and ambulance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN MAN JAILED FOR DUII/HIT AND RUN PROPERTY DAMAGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124785</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/sutherlin-man-jailed-for-duii-hit-and-run-property-damage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-man-jailed-for-duii-hit-and-run-property-damage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 9:20 a.m.   A Sutherlin man was jailed for a DUII and hit and run/property damage incident on Friday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 5:10 p.m. the 21-year-old was driving north in the 2000 block of Southside Road in the Sutherlin area when he failed to negotiate a turn...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deputies Investigate Fatal Vehicle vs. Motorcycle Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175986</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175986"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE, Ore. - A Myrtle Creek man died in a motorcycle vs. vehicle crash on Riddle Bypass Road Friday night. 
Shortly after 10:30 p.m. on Friday, October 11, 2024, 9-1-1 dispatchers received a report of a motorcycle vs. vehicle crash on Riddle Bypass Road near the intersection with E Street in Riddle. 
Deputies, along with fire and ambulance personnel, responded to the scene. Deputies learned that 81-year-old Warren Currier of Riddle was operating a 2007 Toyota Tacoma southbound on Riddle Bypass Road when he began a lefthand turn onto E Street. As Currier made the turn, a collision occurred with a northbound 2024 Ninja Kawasaki motorcycle operated by 20-year-old Gage Matthews of Myrtle Creek.
Matthews was pronounced deceased at the scene. Warren was transported by ambulance to Mercy Medical Center for treatment of his injuries. 
The roadway was closed for approximately five hours as deputies conducted the scene investigation. Anyone who witnessed the incident or may have information useful to the investigation is encouraged to contact the Douglas County Sheriff's Office at (541) 440-4471 or by email at dcso.pio@douglascountyor.gov. Reference Case #24-3959
The Douglas County Medical Examiner's Office, Riddle Fire District and Umpqua Valley Ambulance also responded to the scene.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO MAN JAILED FOR HAVING STOLEN VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124783</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/san-francisco-man-jailed-for-having-stolen-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=san-francisco-man-jailed-for-having-stolen-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 8:30 a.m. A San Francisco man was jailed for having a stolen vehicle on Wednesday night. An Oregon State Police report released late Friday said OSP had been notified that a recently stolen SUV from California was passing through the Grants Pass area. Just after 11:00 p.m. troopers located the vehicle in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BELLVUE, WASHINGTON MAN JAILED FOLLOWING HIT AND RUN CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124781</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/bellvue-washington-man-jailed-following-hit-and-run-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=bellvue-washington-man-jailed-following-hit-and-run-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 9:00 a.m.  A Bellevue, Washington man was jailed following a hit and run crash on Wednesday. An Oregon State Police report released late Friday said at 3:45 p.m. a witness said the crash had occurred on Interstate Five southbound about a mile south of the Rice Valley exit. The witness said the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION DISTRICT BOARD MEETING MONDAY AFTERNOON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124777</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/umpqua-public-transportation-district-board-meeting-monday-afternoon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-public-transportation-district-board-meeting-monday-afternoon"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 12, 2024 8:00 a.m. The Umpqua Public Transportation District Board of Directors will meet Monday afternoon. Board members will review applications for the interim general manager position and complete the final interview. An Executive Session, not open to the public, will be held to consider the employment of an officer, employee, staff member or...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>