<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.roseburgscanner.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2025-12-24T16:18:02.136Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.roseburgscanner.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.roseburgscanner.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December 24, 2025]]></title>
        <id>694bf4f22531890001330dab</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/december-24-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T14:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drive Sober or Get Pulled Over: DSCO participates in enhanced DUII patrols]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/be776e1d-e157-42f1-8456-34e597fdc06d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/drive-sober-or-get-pulled-over-dsco-participates-in-enhanced-duii-patrols/article_be776e1d-e157-42f1-8456-34e597fdc06d.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Sheriff's Office (DSCO) is partnering with the U.S. Department of Transportation’s National Highway Traffic Safety Administration and Oregon Impact to remind all drivers to Drive Sober or Get Pulled Over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIND ADVISORY IN EFFECT FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY, NEARBY AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141554</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/24/wind-advisory-in-effect-for-central-douglas-county-nearby-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wind-advisory-in-effect-for-central-douglas-county-nearby-areas"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T11:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 24, 2025 3:50 a.m.  A Wind Advisory remains in effect for central Douglas County, eastern Curry County and Josephine County. Southeast winds of 20 to 30 miles per hour with gusts up to 55 miles per hour are expected in some locations. The Advisory area includes the entire Interstate 5 corridor, especially over the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIGH WIND WARNING IN EFFECT FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141551</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/24/high-wind-warning-in-effect-for-mountain-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=high-wind-warning-in-effect-for-mountain-areas"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T11:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 24, 2025 3:40 a.m.  A High Wind Warning remains in effect through 1:00 p.m. Wednesday for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford said southeast winds of 35 to 50 miles per hour with gusts up to 75 miles per hour are expected. 1 to 4...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: Rep. Virgle Osborne]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0eb6820f-043f-42c3-9ba1-d32d261645e0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/q-a-rep-virgle-osborne/article_0eb6820f-043f-42c3-9ba1-d32d261645e0.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This interview has been edited for brevity and style. For the full interview go to kqennewsradio.com. Virgle Osborne is State Representative for Oregon’s House District 2. He first took office in November 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The News-Review Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY GOVERNMENT OFFICES CLOSED ON CHRISTMAS/NEW YEARS EVE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141549</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/24/douglas-county-government-offices-closed-on-christmas-new-years-eve/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-government-offices-closed-on-christmas-new-years-eve"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T11:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 24, 2025 3:30 a.m.  Douglas County government offices will be closed on Christmas Day and New Year’s Day. A county release said that includes offices at the courthouse, Justice Building, Courthouse Annex in Reedsport, transfer stations, fairgrounds, and all external government offices. As always, even when county government offices are closed, many officials and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FISH AND WILDLIFE SEEKING INFORMATION: BULL ELK LEFT TO WASTE IN DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141545</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/24/fish-and-wildlife-seeking-information-bull-elk-left-to-waste-in-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fish-and-wildlife-seeking-information-bull-elk-left-to-waste-in-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T11:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 24, 2025 3:20 a.m.  The Oregon State Police Fish and Wildlife Division is investigating a report of a bull elk that was shot and left to waste on November 22nd, the opening day of the Tioga Second Season. An OSP release said the bull elk was left in the area of the 8400 line...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COSA NAMES JON MARTZ 2026 OREGON HIGH SCHOOL PRINCIPAL OF THE YEAR]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141543</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/24/cosa-names-jon-martz-2026-oregon-high-school-principal-of-the-year/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cosa-names-jon-martz-2026-oregon-high-school-principal-of-the-year"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T11:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 24, 2025 3:05 a.m.   The Oregon Association of Secondary School Administrators, a subset of Coalition of Oregon School Administrators, has named Sutherlin High School Principal Jon Martz, as the 2026 Oregon High School Principal of the year. The announcement was made last week by COSA Executive Director Dr. Krista Parent. A COSA release said...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SNAP RECIPIENTS IN 19 OREGON COUNTIES HAVE TIME TO REPLACE FOOD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141541</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/24/snap-recipients-in-19-oregon-counties-have-time-to-replace-food/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=snap-recipients-in-19-oregon-counties-have-time-to-replace-food"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T11:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 24, 2025 2:50 a.m.  Residents of Douglas and 18 other Oregon counties who lost food bought with Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program benefits because of recent storms and power outages now have more time to ask for replacement benefits. A release said the Oregon Department of Human Services has extended the deadline to 30 days...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Disposal offers free Christmas tree recycling at multiple sites until January 12]]></title>
        <id>694b533bcbfd6b0001faabd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/roseburg-disposal-offers-free-christmas-tree-recycling-at-multiple-sites-until-january-12/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T02:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Disposal Co. will offer free Christmas tree recycling from December 29 through January 12, with drop off locations available throughout Roseburg and surrounding areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 12.23.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141538</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/true-wealth-12-23-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-12-23-25"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T00:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littlejohn Financial, David Littlejohn and Matt Dickson have their pre-Christmas  program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Man Jumps From Moving Car to Evade Police, Arrested]]></title>
        <id>694b276ccbfd6b0001faaba6</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/roseburg-man-jumps-from-moving-car-to-evade-police-arrested/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T23:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg police arrested a man wanted in a violent robbery after he jumped from a moving car in an attempt to escape officers. A police K-9 helped track him down. He now faces multiple felony charges in Douglas County.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regional Engineering Powerhouse Formed via Triple-Merger of Rogue Valley Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9141</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/regional-engineering-powerhouse-formed-via-triple-merger-of-rogue-valley-firms/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T23:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MEDFORD, OR – December 23, 2025 – In a move set to redefine the Southern Oregon development landscape, three of the Rogue Valley’s most prominent professional services firms have finalized a major merger. CSA Planning, CEC Engineering, and Marquez and Associates have officially joined forces with AKS Engineering and Forestry LLC, creating a regional titan…
The post Regional Engineering Powerhouse Formed via Triple-Merger of Rogue Valley Firms appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fish & Wildlife Investigating Bull Elk Shot and Left to Waste in Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>694b2419cbfd6b0001faab8a</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/fish-wildlife-investigating-bull-elk-shot-and-left-to-waste-in-douglas-county/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T23:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon State Police Fish and Wildlife Division is investigating a bull elk shot and left to waste on the opening day of Tioga Second Season near Hubbard Creek in Douglas County. Anyone with information is urged to contact the TIP line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Puck’s Donuts Owners Announce Retirement; 50-Year Legacy to Continue with Next Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9132</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/pucks-donuts-owners-announce-retirement-50-year-legacy-to-continue-with-next-generation/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T23:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASHLAND/PHOENIX, OR — Kimo and Mim, the longtime owners of the iconic Puck’s Donuts, have officially announced their retirement effective January 1, 2026. After nearly three decades of ownership, the couple will pass the torch to their daughter, Vilay, and her partner, Nicholas, ensuring the family-run business remains a staple of the Southern Oregon community.…
The post Puck’s Donuts Owners Announce Retirement; 50-Year Legacy to Continue with Next Generation appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIND AND WINTER STORMS EXPECTED TO IMPACT HOLIDAY TRAVEL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141535</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/wind-and-winter-storms-expected-to-impact-holiday-travel/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wind-and-winter-storms-expected-to-impact-holiday-travel"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T22:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 3:00 p.m.  Staff with the Oregon Department of Transportation is urging travelers to plan carefully around the timing of a strong windstorm expected to impact Oregon on Christmas Eve, a peak holiday travel period. Current forecasts call for strong winds from mid-morning through mid-day on Wednesday, when many people may be traveling...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Masterpiece Strategy: How The Websters Transformed Boutique Retail into a Global Destination]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9129</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/the-masterpiece-strategy-how-the-websters-transformed-boutique-retail-into-a-global-destination/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T22:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASHLAND, OR — In the shifting landscape of American retail, the “Experience Economy” has moved from a buzzword to a survival strategy. While many brick-and-mortar shops struggle against digital disruption, The Websters, a premier fiber arts destination in Ashland, is rewriting the script. Their model for the March 2026 Retreat provides a masterclass in how…
The post The Masterpiece Strategy: How The Websters Transformed Boutique Retail into a Global Destination appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed Order Would Require New Fish Passage at Winchester Dam by 2028]]></title>
        <id>694b111fcbfd6b0001faab49</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/proposed-order-would-require-new-fish-passage-at-winchester-dam-by-2028/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T22:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A proposed order would require the Winchester Water Control District to build new fish passage at Winchester Dam by 2028. The ruling follows a contested case over whether 2023 dam repairs triggered modern fish passage requirements under Oregon law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 12.23.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141532</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/inside-douglas-county-12-23-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-12-23-25"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T21:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An encore program today featuring a recent interview with new new Adapt Integrated Health Care CEO Steve Baron.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIND ADVISORY CALLS FOR HIGHER WINDS IN THE ROSEBURG AREA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141527</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/wind-advisory-calls-for-higher-winds-in-the-roseburg-area/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wind-advisory-calls-for-higher-winds-in-the-roseburg-area"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T19:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 11:10 a.m.  A Wind Advisory is in effect from 10:00 p.m. Tuesday through 1:00 p.m. Wednesday for central Douglas County, eastern Curry County and Josephine County. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford said southeast winds of 20 to 30 miles per hour with gusts up to 50 miles per hour...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watermain breaks on West Harvard Avenue on Saturday night]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e50a8a43-f84e-4775-800c-ee6865b4a74f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/watermain-breaks-on-west-harvard-avenue-on-saturday-night/article_e50a8a43-f84e-4775-800c-ee6865b4a74f.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T19:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A watermain break at the intersection of West Harvard Avenue and West Umpqua Street on Saturday night caused a mess and the city of Roseburg is working to fix the situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO-VEHICLE CRASH BLOCKS HIGHWAY 38, WEST OF SCOTTSBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141525</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/two-vehicle-crash-blocks-highway-38-west-of-scottsburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-vehicle-crash-blocks-highway-38-west-of-scottsburg"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T19:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 11:00 a.m.  Troopers with Oregon State Police responded to a two-vehicle crash on Highway 38, approximately three miles west of Scottsburg on Monday afternoon. An OSP report said just before 3:30 p.m. an eastbound vehicle attempted to pass multiple vehicles that were also heading eastbound. The driver did not see a vehicle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ELUDING, STOLEN VEHICLE, OTHER CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141523</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-eluding-stolen-vehicle-other-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-eluding-stolen-vehicle-other-charges"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T18:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23,  2025 10:45 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man after he eluded them in a stolen vehicle on Saturday evening. An RPD report said at 7:45 p.m. officers attempted to stop 34-year-old Riley Huskey who was driving a vehicle near the intersection of Northeast Nash Street and Northeast Winchester Street, after witnessing him commit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT, PROVIDING FALSE INFORMATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141521</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-providing-false-information/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-providing-false-information"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T18:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant and for providing false information to a peace officer, on Saturday night. An RPD report said at 8:15 p.m. the 47-year-old was contacted by officers outside a business in the 300 block of Northeast Stephens Street, during a search for a suspect...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg man jumps from moving car to escape, caught by police]]></title>
        <id>http://www.kezi.com/tncms/asset/editorial/90636d51-a660-4f2f-b9e5-89b27c1ecc0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.kezi.com/news/local/roseburg-man-jumps-from-moving-car-to-escape-caught-by-police/article_90636d51-a660-4f2f-b9e5-89b27c1ecc0d.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T18:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg police captured a man wanted for a violent robbery and assault after a dramatic escape attempt on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chelsea Deffenbacher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR REPORTED HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141519</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-reported-harassment-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-reported-harassment-2"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T18:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a reported harassment incident on Friday afternoon. An RPD report said at 3:00 p.m. employees at a business in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street said the 47-year-old suspect had walked through an open vehicle gate and was refusing to leave after being...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN ON MULTIPLE CHARGES FOLLOWING ALLEGED ASSAULT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141517</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/roseburg-police-jail-man-on-multiple-charges-following-alleged-assault-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-on-multiple-charges-following-alleged-assault-incident"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T18:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man on multiple charges following an alleged assault incident on Friday night. An RPD report said at 11:30 p.m. officers responded after a disturbance was called in at an establishment in the 900 block of Southeast Stephens Street. Officers learned that 52-year-old Nathan Robinson accused someone...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TROOPERS RESPOND TO TWO-VEHICLE CRASH ON HIGHWAY 138E ON MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141515</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/troopers-respond-to-two-vehicle-crash-on-highway-138e-on-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=troopers-respond-to-two-vehicle-crash-on-highway-138e-on-monday"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T17:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 9:40 a.m.  Troopers with Oregon State Police responded to a two-vehicle crash on Highway 138E on Monday morning An OSP report said at 8:30 a.m. a vehicle was traveling eastbound in a construction zone approximately three miles east of Glide. One lane was closed and coned off, due to work taking place....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CHARGE MAN WITH SEXUAL HARASSMENT, DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141513</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/roseburg-police-charge-man-with-sexual-harassment-disorderly-conduct/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-charge-man-with-sexual-harassment-disorderly-conduct"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T17:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police charged a man with sexual harassment and second-degree disorderly conduct following an incident Friday afternoon. An RPD report said at 3:00 p.m. the 63-year entered a business in the 1300 of Northeast Stephens Street and allegedly became aggressive with staff after he was unable to withdrew money from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT, DRUGS ALLEGEDLY LOCATED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141511</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-warrant-drugs-allegedly-located/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-warrant-drugs-allegedly-located"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T17:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 9:20 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a man for a warrant and allegedly located drugs on his person when he was contacted on Monday night. An SPD report said at 10:00 p.m. the 31-year was contacted in the 900 block of West Central Avenue. Dispatch confirmed the warrant and the man was taken...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 12.23.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141507</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/morning-conversation-12-23-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-12-23-25"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T17:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Captain Edith-Dye Mabie of the Salvation Army Roseburg Corps talks about the needs they are seeing this holiday season and how the community can help out before Christmas Day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Birders flock to the outdoors for 126th annual Audubon Christmas Bird Count]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2a3471be-c367-4a29-8ff3-f4366f78c56b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/birders-flock-to-the-outdoors-for-126th-annual-audubon-christmas-bird-count/article_2a3471be-c367-4a29-8ff3-f4366f78c56b.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a wet, freezing cold morning at Stewart Park. A group makes their way through grassy fields, boots squelching through mud and icy-numb fingers clutching hand warmers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Absolute Motosport to Close Roseburg and Grants Pass Locations After December 31]]></title>
        <id>694ab020cbfd6b0001faab31</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/absolute-motosport-to-close-roseburg-and-grants-pass-locations-after-december-31/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T15:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Absolute Motosport has announced it will close its Roseburg and Grants Pass locations after December 31. A liquidation sale is underway with unmarked pricing and deep discounts on all in-stock inventory. The Roseburg store is open Monday through Wednesday, 8 a.m. to 5 p.m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025]]></title>
        <id>694aa2cdcbfd6b0001faa9da</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/december-23-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T14:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIND ADVISORY FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY AND ITS EASTERN FOOTHILLS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141501</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/wind-advisory-for-central-douglas-county-and-its-eastern-foothills/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wind-advisory-for-central-douglas-county-and-its-eastern-foothills"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T11:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 4;00 a.m.  A Wind Advisory remains in effect from 10:00 p.m. Tuesday through 10:00 am. Wednesday for central Douglas County and its eastern foothills, plus other adjacent areas in the region. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that a surface low pressure...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141498</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/winter-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas-18/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas-18"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T11:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 3:50 a.m.  A Winter Weather Advisory remains in effect from 10:00 a.m. Tuesday through 10:00 a.m. Wednesday for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said the Advisory is for elevations above 5,500 feet in the Cascade Mountains and includes Crater Lake. Winds are expected to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WATERMAIN BREAK ON WEST HARVARD AVENUE SATURDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141491</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/watermain-break-on-west-harvard-avenue-saturday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=watermain-break-on-west-harvard-avenue-saturday-night"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T11:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 3:40 a.m.  A watermain break at the intersection of West Harvard Avenue and West Umpqua Street on Saturday night caused a mess and the City of Roseburg is working to fix the situation. Public Works Director Ryan Herinckx told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that a leak began just after...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO CITIES ANNOUNCE ADDITIONAL CLOSURES FOR THE HOLIDAYS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141489</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/two-cities-announce-additional-closures-for-the-holidays/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-cities-announce-additional-closures-for-the-holidays"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 3:30 a.m. Two cities in Douglas County have announced additional holiday closures. City Recorder Cindy Sarti said the City of Winston will be closed on Wednesday, Thursday and Friday and again on January first. City Recorder Joanna Bilbrey said the City of Myrtle Creek will close at 12:00 p.m. on Wednesday, in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ELECTRICAL FIRE CONTAINED IN ONE FROOM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141487</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/electrical-fire-contained-in-one-froom/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=electrical-fire-contained-in-one-froom"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T11:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 3:20 a.m.  An electrical fire was contained in one room of a residential structure on Sunday. Information from the City of Roseburg Fire Department said just after 9:30 a.m. firefighters responded to the fire at a home on Northeast Russell Avenue. Cow Creek Tribal Police arrived on the scene before fire units...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHERIFF’S OFFICE TO PARTICIPATE IN ENHANCED DUII PATROLS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141485</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/sheriffs-office-to-participate-in-enhanced-duii-patrols/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sheriffs-office-to-participate-in-enhanced-duii-patrols"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T11:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 3:05 a.m.   During the holiday season, the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office is partnering with the U.S. Department of Transportation’s National Highway Traffic Safety Administration and Oregon Impact to share the message about the dangers of drunk driving. Undersheriff Brad O’Dell said the agencies want all drivers to remember a lifesaving message: Drive...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG SCHOOLS INVITES COMMUNITY MEMBERS TO JON NEW COMMUNITY FACILITIES ADVISORY COMMITTEE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141483</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/23/roseburg-schools-invites-community-members-to-jon-new-community-facilities-advisory-committee/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-schools-invites-community-members-to-jon-new-community-facilities-advisory-committee"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T11:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 2:50 a.m.  Roseburg Schools is inviting community members to join a new Community Facilities Advisory Committee. A district release said committee members will take a close look at needs such as aging infrastructure, safety and security, student privacy and accessibility, improved quality and building systems that support student wellness, and learning space...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cash Stolen After ATM Damaged at Rogue Credit Union in Roseburg]]></title>
        <id>6949e98dcbfd6b0001faa9b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/cash-stolen-after-atm-damaged-at-rogue-credit-union-in-roseburg/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T01:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Police are investigating an early-morning ATM theft at Rogue Credit Union on NW Garden Valley Blvd. Officers found a damaged ATM and a stolen pickup left running at the scene. Two suspects fled in a white SUV. The investigation is ongoing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL BUSINESS CLOSURE – COLORCRAFT PAINT]]></title>
        <id>6949e6bdcbfd6b0001faa9a6</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/local-business-closure-colorcraft-paint/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T00:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colorcraft Paint, located next to the former Waldron’s Outdoor Sports on Garden Valley Blvd, has closed after serving the Roseburg community for 70 years. The longtime local business thanked the community as it marked the end of an era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE INVESTIGATE THEFT FROM ATM, WHICH WAS DAMAGED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141479</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/roseburg-police-investigate-theft-from-atm-which-was-damaged/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-investigate-theft-from-atm-which-was-damaged"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T00:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 23, 2025 4:50 p.m.  Roseburg Police are investigating the theft of money from an automatic teller machine which was damaged at a credit union early Friday morning. An RPD report said at 4:10 a.m. officers responded to a panic/ATM alarm at Rogue Credit Union in the 1300 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. Upon...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHERIFF’S OFFICE TO PARTICIPATE IN ENHANCED DUII PATROLS THIS HOLIDAY SEASON]]></title>
        <id>6949ba89cbfd6b0001faa990</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/sheriffs-office-to-participate-in-enhanced-duii-patrols-this-holiday-season/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T21:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office will conduct enhanced DUII patrols from December 10 through January 1 as part of the Drive Sober or Get Pulled Over campaign, focusing on removing impaired drivers from local roadways during the holiday season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 12.22.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141475</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/inside-douglas-county-12-22-25-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-12-22-25-2"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T21:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Representative Virgle Osbourne talks about the gas tax repeal ballot measure,  the upcoming short session of the legislature and other topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WILDLIFE SAFARI’S WILD LIGHTS BRINGS HOLIDAY MAGIC TO WINSTON]]></title>
        <id>6949adf8cbfd6b0001faa974</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/wildlife-safaris-wild-lights-brings-holiday-magic-to-winston/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T21:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari’s Wild Lights brings holiday magic to Winston with illuminated paths, animal encounters, hot cocoa, Santa visits, and the popular Candy Cane Caboose. With one weekend left, families still have time to enjoy this seasonal tradition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED EARLY FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141472</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-driving-while-suspended-early-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-driving-while-suspended-early-friday"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T19:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2205 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a misdemeanor count of driving while suspended early Friday morning. An RPD report said at 2:00 a.m. officers stopped the vehicle in the 2600 block of Northwest Edenbower Boulevard. They recognized the driver as a 58-year-old Myrtle Creek woman whose license was revoked in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR UNLAWFUL ENTRY TO MOTOR VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141470</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-unlawful-entry-to-motor-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-unlawful-entry-to-motor-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T18:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 10:45 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man on the charge of unlawful entry into a motor vehicle on Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 7:50 a.m. officers contacted 38-year-old Keith Weatherford in the 100 block of Sunshine Road regarding a previous case involving several vehicle break ins. During the incident, Weatherford...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE VEHICLE ROLLS, ONE HITS GO-CART ON INTERSTATE 5]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141468</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/one-vehicle-rolls-one-hits-go-cart-on-interstate-5/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=one-vehicle-rolls-one-hits-go-cart-on-interstate-5"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T18:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 10:30 a.m.  One vehicle rolled after swerving to miss a go-cart while a second vehicle hit the go-cart in a lane of travel on Interstate 5 southbound on Saturday night. An Oregon State Police report said shortly after 9:00 p.m. the crash was called in, in the southbound lane of travel near...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Schools calls on community for facilities committee input]]></title>
        <id>http://www.kezi.com/tncms/asset/editorial/40afa9cb-f11b-4cbe-bc4d-9db03bed9fcf</id>
        <link href="https://www.kezi.com/news/local/roseburg-schools-calls-on-community-for-facilities-committee-input/article_40afa9cb-f11b-4cbe-bc4d-9db03bed9fcf.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T18:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Schools is inviting community members to join a new Community Facilities Advisory Committee. This group will help assess the condition of aging school buildings and explore long-term facility needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRIVER LOSES CONTROL OF VEHICLE DUE TO WET WEATHER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141466</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/driver-loses-control-of-vehicle-due-to-wet-weather/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=driver-loses-control-of-vehicle-due-to-wet-weather"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T18:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 10:00 a.m.  A driver lost control of her vehicle, due to wet weather on Sunday afternoon. An Oregon State Police report said just before 2:45 p.m. troopers were dispatched to the single-vehicle wreck on Interstate 5 northbound, about two miles south of the Canyon Creek exit. The driver stated that she was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR CRIMINAL TRESPASS, MISCHIEF COUNTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141464</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-criminal-trespass-mischief-counts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-criminal-trespass-mischief-counts"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T17:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 9:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for second-degree criminal trespass, and third-degree criminal mischief on Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 8:15 a.m. the 59-year-old was contacted in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street after a caller said that he was sleeping in front of a business. Before leaving...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR OFFENSIVE LITTERING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141462</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-offensive-littering/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-offensive-littering"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T17:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for offensive littering early Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 12:40 a.m. the 39-year-old was contacted at Eagles Park in the 700 block of Southeast Jackson Street. She was camping in a prohibited area and was surrounded by refuse. The woman was charged for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT, CITE FOR CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141460</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-cite-for-camping-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-cite-for-camping-3"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T17:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 9:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant and cited him for camping early Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 5:40 a.m. the 47-year-old was contacted at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. He was taken into custody due to the warrant. He was camping...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WISH UPON A STAR 12.22.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141457</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/wish-upon-a-star-12-22-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wish-upon-a-star-12-22-25"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T17:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wish #10: From Brooke Communications and Rogue Credit Union, we wrap up Wish Upon a Star with assistance for Michelle, who is moving out of the shelter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025]]></title>
        <id>6948e0b0cbfd6b0001faa785</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/december-22-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T16:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFP Dillard plywood layoffs settlements come to a close]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8e6b8042-4272-4ada-8a39-34f4d8dcb750</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/rfp-dillard-plywood-layoffs-settlements-come-to-a-close/article_8e6b8042-4272-4ada-8a39-34f4d8dcb750.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sept. 25, Roseburg Forest Products (RFP) announced it had discontinued operations at its hardwood plywood facility in Dillard, leading to layoffs for more than 100 employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODOT lays out upcoming projects to continue into new year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/27db85cf-e427-47ac-bfa5-b3a6a17bce8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/odot-lays-out-upcoming-projects-to-continue-into-new-year/article_27db85cf-e427-47ac-bfa5-b3a6a17bce8c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the year comes to a close, the Oregon Department of Transportation (ODOT) is looking forward to a year of new and ongoing projects intended to make roads safer for motorists and pedestrians alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Timber Town Toy Land Electric Light Parade returns for 33rd year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/291699e4-91fd-4dd5-a9bf-c5b10052e3c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/sutherlin-timber-town-toy-land-electric-light-parade-returns-for-33rd-year/article_291699e4-91fd-4dd5-a9bf-c5b10052e3c9.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — As Cody Salberg handed out hot drinks and snacks to a crowd of smiling faces, it occurred to her that this kind of happiness and togetherness is what Sutherlin is all about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon anglers get a bigger lingcod limit in 2026 per ODFW Commission]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b065dd15-7c4d-401d-8cb3-d8892a92fd40</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/oregon-anglers-get-a-bigger-lingcod-limit-in-2026-per-odfw-commission/article_b065dd15-7c4d-401d-8cb3-d8892a92fd40.html"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coastal anglers will be able to keep more lingcod in 2026, while Oregon’s general marine bag limit for rockfish and other nearshore species will remain at four fish per day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONTINUED SHOWERS EXPECTED THIS WEEK IN THE UMPQUA VALLEY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141453</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/continued-showers-expected-this-week-in-the-umpqua-valley/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=continued-showers-expected-this-week-in-the-umpqua-valley"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T11:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 3:50 a.m.  A couple more weather systems moving through the region are expected to bring continued showers in the Umpqua Valley leading up to Christmas Day. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the heaviest rain will likely be Tuesday evening heading...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFTH WHEEL DAMAGED IN FRIDAY NIGHT FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141451</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/fifth-wheel-damaged-in-friday-night-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fifth-wheel-damaged-in-friday-night-fire"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T11:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 205 3:40 a.m.  A fifth wheel was damaged in a fire on Friday night in the Drain area. A report from North Douglas County Fire and EMS said the fire was reported just before 11:30 p.m. in the 7500 block of Laurel Hill Drive. The front end of the vehicle received heavy fire...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY OF ROSEBURG BUILDINGS TO CLOSE FOR CHRISTMAS, NEW YEARS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141449</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/city-of-roseburg-buildings-to-close-for-christmas-new-years/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-of-roseburg-buildings-to-close-for-christmas-new-years"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T11:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 3:30 a.m.  City of Roseburg buildings will be closed this Thursday and Friday for the Christmas holiday and Thursday, January 1st, for the New Year holiday. A city release said that means that Roseburg City Hall and the Roseburg Public Safety Center, both on Southeast Douglas Avenue, and Roseburg Public Library on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LUNCHBOX EXPRESS DELIVERING FREE MEALS OVER WINTER BREAK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141446</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/lunchbox-express-delivering-free-meals-over-winter-break-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lunchbox-express-delivering-free-meals-over-winter-break-2"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T11:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 3:20 a.m.  Roseburg Schools has the Lunchbox Express Van delivering free meals over the Winter Break. A district release said the service helps to ensure that children have access to healthy food and steady support while school is out. Meals are available Monday and Tuesday of this week and again next Monday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WILD SPRING CHINOOK HARVEST PROHIBITED ON MAINSTEM UMPQUA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141443</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/wild-spring-chinook-harvest-prohibited-on-mainstem-umpqua/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wild-spring-chinook-harvest-prohibited-on-mainstem-umpqua"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 3:05 a.m.  On Friday, the Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife announced a temporary rule prohibiting wild spring Chinook salmon harvest on the mainstem Umpqua River and keeping the North Umpqua bag limit the same as 2025. An ODFW release said from February 1st through June 30th: *Mainstem Umpqua River: only hatchery...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERKLEY: NOW IS THE TIME FOR COMMONSENSE CANNABIS REFORMS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=141441</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/12/22/merkley-now-is-the-time-for-commonsense-cannabis-reforms/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=merkley-now-is-the-time-for-commonsense-cannabis-reforms"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T11:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 22, 2025 2:50 a.m.  Last week, Oregon’s U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley – the lead sponsor of the bipartisan SAFER Banking Act – issued a statement in response to President Trump’s announcement that he has signed an Executive Order directing the U.S. Department of Justice to complete the process of moving cannabis from Schedule I...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Timber Town Toy Land Electric Light Parade Raises $7,000, Honors 2025 Winners]]></title>
        <id>694871a9cbfd6b0001faa75d</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/sutherlin-timber-town-toy-land-electric-light-parade-raises-7-000-honors-2025-winners/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-21T22:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin’s Timber Town Toy Land Electric Light Parade featured 79 vehicles, raised $7,000 in sponsorships, and paid out all prize money across multiple categories while reflecting on nearly two decades of community tradition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>