<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-07-25T02:31:15.942Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIKE WINTERS LAWN AND GARDEN SHOW7.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121554</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show7-24-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show7-24-24"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T00:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County’s Commissioner of Dirt, Mike Winters, has our weekly local lawn and garden program:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MEDIA ALERT: Oregon Department of Forestry Begins Daily Situation Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174036</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174036"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T22:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Correction/Clarification: Media can post/publish/share the daily ODF situation reports. The ask to not share or publish was meant to be about the media alert itself. We apologize for the confusion. 
 
 
With the Regional Preparedness Level and ODF Fire Activity Level at 5, the Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) will begin to send out Daily Situation Reports via GovDelivery in the afternoon. The reports will include information on ODF incident management teams, what fires the agency is prioritizing, district highlights, and other pertinent information. 
These reports will be published daily on ODFfire.com and on ODF’s Statewide Facebook page if you would like to guide people to it.  The public can also sign up through GovDelivery to receive these reports. 
If you have follow-up or clarifying questions, please reach out to jessica.neujahr@odf.oregon.gov.  
Details: Click to subscribe through GovDelivery to receive these reports daily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX AT 3,800 ACRES WITH 20 FIRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121552</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/diamond-complex-at-3800-acres-with-20-fires/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-at-3800-acres-with-20-fires"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T20:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 1:50 p.m.  The Diamond Complex burning in the Umpqua National Forest is comprised of 20 fires totaling 3,811 acres, as of mid-day Wednesday. A UNF update said while some fires are now out, 8 new fires totaling an estimated 62 acres have been identified and added to the complex, since mid-day on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 7.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121548</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/inside-douglas-county-7-24-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-7-24-24"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T20:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[City of Roseburg Community Development Director Stuart Cowie talks about the land swap proposal and eventual potential development in Charter Oaks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEVEN FIRES ON HOMESTEAD COMPLEX NOW AT 910 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121545</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/seven-fires-on-homestead-complex-now-at-910-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=seven-fires-on-homestead-complex-now-at-910-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T18:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 11:10 a.m. The Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, has seven fires totaling a combined 910 acres as of mid-day Wednesday. A Forest Service update said about 230 people are assigned to the complex with more scheduled to arrive. The Horse Heaven Creek Fire, at 258 acres, was the most...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great Basin Complex Incident Management Team 6 takes command of the Microwave Tower Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174028</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174028"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T18:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE DALLES, Ore. – The Great Basin Complex Incident Management Team 6, led by Incident Commander Mack McFarland, assumed command of the Microwave Tower Fire at 6:00 a.m. this morning, Wednesday, July 24, 2024. The Complex Incident Management Team brings additional resources and management capabilities to implement a full suppression strategy for the Microwave Tower Fire. 
The fire has seen moderate activity with intermittent single tree torching, some flanking and smoldering creating a moderate amount of smoke. The fire also saw growth backing down the north slope. With the expected increased winds today, crews are ready to address increased fire behavior. There is a potential for increased smoke in the area.
More accurate mapping has sized the fire at 704 acres and 0% containment. The fire is located 5 miles west, southwest of Mosier, OR. Currently there are approximately 72 personnel assigned to the fire. They are building a combination of dozer and hand line on the southern edge to contain the fire. Additionally, crews are working to improve roads, trails and previously constructed contingency lines around the remainder of the fire.
The Microwave Tower Fire was first detected on July 22, 2024 and the cause is currently under investigation.
Evacuations
The Mosier Senior Center at 500 E. 2nd Ave., is being used as a cooling center for the public where they can also charge their devices. For up-to-date information on evacuations in the area, please visit https://www.facebook.com/WascoCountySheriff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[39TH ANNUAL MYRTLE CREEK SUMMER FESTIVAL STARTS THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121543</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/39th-annual-myrtle-creek-summer-festival-starts-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=39th-annual-myrtle-creek-summer-festival-starts-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T17:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 10:45 a.m.  The 39th annual Myrtle Creek Summer Festival runs Thursday through Sunday at Millsite Park in Myrtle Creek. It is sponsored by the Myrtle Creek Lions Club. The event includes live music, a children’s play area, a sand volleyball tournament, chili pepper eating contest, car show, a fear factor eating contest,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121541</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-14/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-14"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T17:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2042 10:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for drinking in public on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 10:30 a.m. an officer observed the 42-year-old man drinking a beer at the corner of Northeast Stephens Street and Northeast Rowe Street. A citation was issued and the man was released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON MAN CITED FOR PRIOR THEFT BY ROSEBURG POLICE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121536</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/winston-man-cited-for-prior-theft-by-roseburg-police/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-man-cited-for-prior-theft-by-roseburg-police"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T17:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 20240 10:10 a.m. A Winston man was cited for second-degree theft by Roseburg Police on Tuesday. An RPD report said the 36-year-old year old was identified as the suspect who stole a package off a porch in the 1300 block of Northwest Domenico Drive on July 9th. The package contained cookware valued at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121534</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-harassment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-harassment"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T16:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a woman for harassment following an incident Tuesday. An RPD report said at 2:00 p.m. officers contacted a juvenile after learning the suspect had struck him in the face with her hand. The incident allegedly occurred in the 800 block of Northeast Huntley Avenue. Officers could see...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR GIVING FALSE INFORMATION/WARRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121532</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-giving-false-information-warrants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-giving-false-information-warrants"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T16:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for giving false information and for warrants on Tuesday morning. An RPD report said at 8:50 a.m. 34-year-old Krystine Lynn was contacted during a camp cleanup at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. Lynn initially gave the officer a false name,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX/HOMESTEAD COMPLEX COMMUNITY MEETING WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121530</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/diamond-complex-homestead-complex-community-meeting-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-homestead-complex-community-meeting-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T16:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 9:20 a.m. Fire officials will hold a community meeting for area residents and landowners impacted by fires in the Diamond Complex and the Homestead Complex, on Wednesday evening. Forest Service, Northwest Incident Management Team 7 and Great Basin National Incident Management Team 5 staff will provide information to attendees and will also...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 7.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121526</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/morning-conversation-7-24-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-7-24-24"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T16:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Molly Allen joins us from the Diamond Complex Fire on the Umpqua National Forest for an update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summertime and feeling feeling fine with the Healthy Kids Outreach Programs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/26ab0a1c-490f-11ef-a84a-67962de4622b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/summertime-and-feeling-feeling-fine-with-the-healthy-kids-outreach-programs/article_26ab0a1c-490f-11ef-a84a-67962de4622b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mercy Foundation’s Healthy Kids Outreach Program (HKOP) serves Douglas County youth by providing oral health care and education, resource nurses and connection to care, and health and nutrition education throughout the school year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LISA PLATT For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua National Forest issues closure due to new fire activity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/202425e2-491a-11ef-9269-83661cb349ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/umpqua-national-forest-issues-closure-due-to-new-fire-activity/article_202425e2-491a-11ef-9269-83661cb349ab.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Umpqua National Forest closed portions of the Umpqua National Forest on Tuesday due to fire activity to protect public and wildland firefighter safety on the Rocky Ridge Fire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community BBQ fundraiser Thursday for Alzheimer's]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8cb606a0-485f-11ef-a9a9-8b9d343b459b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/community-bbq-fundraiser-thursday-for-alzheimers/article_8cb606a0-485f-11ef-a9a9-8b9d343b459b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The community is invited to enjoy some classic, finger-licking barbecue in a fundraising effort for the Walk to End Alzheimer’s. The Rodeo Days BBQ Dinner will be held at 5 p.m. Thursday at The Landing in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bar Run opens Lazy River]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2c0f3d36-45e8-11ef-a5a2-73cc8177af37</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/bar-run-opens-lazy-river/article_2c0f3d36-45e8-11ef-a5a2-73cc8177af37.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tucked in with the Callahan Mountains overlooking Bar Run Golf and RV Resort, the lazy river pool provides a peaceful, easy feeling for RV campers and resort members.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oakland Creek Vineyards coming to Oakland]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ffb66178-43a4-11ef-9591-1b917c56d684</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/oakland-creek-vineyards-coming-to-oakland/article_ffb66178-43a4-11ef-9591-1b917c56d684.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — The former E.G. Young bank building in Oakland is now the home of the new Oakland Creek Vineyards Tasting Room, where the new owners are embracing the community and its history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIR QUALITY ALERT REMAINS FOR MUCH OF SOUTHERN OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121522</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/air-quality-alert-remains-for-much-of-southern-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=air-quality-alert-remains-for-much-of-southern-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T11:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 4:10 a.m.  An Air Quality Alert remains in effect until 5:00 p.m. Wednesday for much of southern Oregon. The Oregon Department of Environmental Quality has issued an Air Pollution Advisory for Douglas, Jackson, Josephine, and Klamath counties Wildfires burning in the region combined with forecast conditions will cause air quality levels to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXPECT CONTINUED INTERSTATE AND HIGHWAY CLOSURES IN EASTERN OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121519</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/expect-continued-interstate-and-highway-closures-in-eastern-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=expect-continued-interstate-and-highway-closures-in-eastern-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2042 3:50 a.m. Those who plan to travel across Oregon in the coming days should make sure to carefully plan their route. An update from the Oregon Department of Transportation said Interstate 84 and many other highways may be closed or unreliable due to wildfires. With a long hot summer ahead, other fires...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNF ISSUES CLOSURE ORDER – ROCKY RIDGE FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121516</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/unf-issues-closure-order-rocky-ridge-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=unf-issues-closure-order-rocky-ridge-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 3:40 a.m. A forest closure order has gone into effect for portions of the Umpqua National Forest in response to fire activity to protect public and wildland firefighter safety on the Rocky Ridge Fire. A UNF release said this closure, which is in addition to an earlier closure on the North Zone...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY EMPLOYERS ADD 90 JOBS IN JUNE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121514</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/douglas-county-employers-add-90-jobs-in-june/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-employers-add-90-jobs-in-june"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024  3;30 a.m. Douglas County’s payroll employment gained 90 jobs in June after a gain of 10 in May and a loss of 190 in April. A State of Oregon Employment Department release said in the not seasonally adjusted private-sector industries in June, there were seasonal gains of 130 jobs in leisure and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UACT SUMMER MUSICAL OPENS THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121510</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/uact-summer-musical-opens-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uact-summer-musical-opens-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 2024 3:20 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Actors Community Theatre opens its summer musical, “Charlie and the Chocolate Factory” on Thursday night. In the production, the world-famous Willy Wonka is opening the gates to his mysterious factory, but only to a few. Young Charlie Bucket and four other golden ticket winners...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CAMPFIRES TEMPORARILY BANNED AT MOST OREGON STATE PARKS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121507</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/campfires-temporarily-banned-at-most-oregon-state-parks/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=campfires-temporarily-banned-at-most-oregon-state-parks"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 3:05 a.m. The Oregon Parks and Recreation Department has temporarily banned campfires at most Oregon State Parks, due to dry conditions and the strain on firefighting resources from wildfires burning across the state. An OPRD release said campfires and open flames are banned at all parks east of the Cascades due to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WYDEN, MERKLEY, HOYLE ANNOUNCE $16.6 MILLION TO OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121505</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/24/wyden-merkley-hoyle-announce-16-6-million-to-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wyden-merkley-hoyle-announce-16-6-million-to-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 24, 204 2:50 a.m. On Tuesday, U.S. Senators Ron Wyden and Jeff Merkley and Representative Val Hoyle announced $16.6 million in federal funds for Oregon habitat restoration and coastal resilience projects have been made available through the Bipartisan Infrastructure Law and Inflation Reduction Act. Wyden said, “Salmon, fishing and our beautiful outdoors are all...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefighters on Microwave Tower Fire take advantage of more favorable weather]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174025</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174025"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T04:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dalles, Ore. – Moderate fire behavior allowed for further progress on the Microwave Tower Fire today as crews worked to secure more of the fire’s east end with hand line, dozer line, and water drops from helicopters and other air resources. The fire continued to back down on a north facing ridge along I-84 just west of Mosier and will likely do so through tomorrow. Smoke can be observed along the highway.
More accurate mapping has sized the fire at 704 acres. Tonight, crews will work towards hooking in line with hand crews and dozers along the eastern and southern edges of the fire footprint while structural firefighters will continue to assess and further secure homes.
Tomorrow, the Type 1 Great Basin Team 6 will assume command at 6 a.m. The incident command post will be at the Hood River High School. Public information officers with the team will receive inquiries about both the nearby Whiskey Creek and Microwave Tower fires. 
Evacuation levels remain in place. There is an estimate of 100 homes that are under Level 3 evacuations and 500 residences threatened in the Mosier area. The gymnasium at the Hood River Middle School is a designated Red Cross Shelter for those evacuated.
LEVEL 3 - GO NOW! Evacuate immediately from Hwy 30 south the Proctor Rd., east to Huskey Rd and the border of the City of Mosier and west to the Hood River County line.
LEVEL 2 - GET SET from the City of Mosier and Huskey Rd., south to Wilson Rd., and east to Mosier Creek Rd.
LEVEL 1 - GET READY from Mosier Creek Rd., east to Dry Creek Rd., north to the City of Mosier border and south to Osborn Cutoff Rd.
For the most up-to-date evacuation information, please visit the Wasco County Sheriff’s Facebook page at https://www.facebook.com/WascoCountySheriff/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 7.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121501</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/true-wealth-7-23-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-7-23-24"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T00:08:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littlejohn Financial, David Littlejohn and Matt Dickson have our weekly local financial program:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 NEW FIRES IDENTIFIED ON THE DIAMOND COMPLEX]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121497</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/11-new-fires-identified-on-the-diamond-complex/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=11-new-fires-identified-on-the-diamond-complex"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T21:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 2:00 p.m. Since midday Monday another 11 fires totaling an estimated 55 acres have been identified and added to the Diamond Complex, on the Diamond Lake Ranger District of the Umpqua National Forest. A UNF update said there are now 23 fires totaling an estimated 3,318 acres in the complex, with 243...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress made overnight on the Microwave Tower Fire (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174015</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174015"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T20:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE DALLES, Ore. – Crews worked through the night on the Microwave Tower fire near Mosier, taking advantage of the cooler temperatures and higher humidity. Much of the progress was along the southern portion of the fire, while the northern portion continues to present challenges due to limited access and steep slopes. Air resources played a critical role in helping slow the fire’s spread in difficult terrain.
The fire is currently being mapped, but early indications show that it is roughly 591 acres. Currently, the fire is backing down north facing slopes just west of Mosier, and smoke is visible from I-84.
Today, winds are predicted to be calmer than yesterday, allowing firefighters a good opportunity to continue the progress from last night. The Type 1 Great Basin National Team currently managing the Whiskey Creek Fire in Hood River County will assume command from Oregon Department of Forestry Central Oregon District tomorrow morning at 6 a.m. The incident command post will be at the Hood River High School.
Evacuation levels have not changed since the last Wasco County Sheriff’s update at 10 p.m. yesterday. The gymnasium at the Hood River Middle School is a designated Red Cross Shelter for those evacuating.
LEVEL 3 - GO NOW! Evacuate immediately from Hwy 30 south the Proctor Rd., east to Huskey Rd and the border of the City of Mosier and west to the Hood River County line.
LEVEL 2 - GET SET from the City of Mosier and Huskey Rd., south to Wilson Rd., and east to Mosier Creek Rd.
LEVEL 1 - GET READY from Mosier Creek Rd., east to Dry Creek Rd., north to the City of Mosier border and south to Osborn Cutoff Rd.
For the most up-to-date evacuation information, please visit the Wasco County Sheriff’s Facebook page at https://www.facebook.com/WascoCountySheriff/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 7.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121490</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/inside-douglas-county-7-23-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-7-23-24"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T20:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circuit Court Judge the Honorable Robert B. Johnson and Program Coordinator Crystina Dunehew talk about Drug Court and the 106th graduation ceremony Tuesday night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observatory hosts stargazing party Friday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1f7b21b0-4922-11ef-8651-936b1299046d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/observatory-hosts-stargazing-party-friday/article_1f7b21b0-4922-11ef-8651-936b1299046d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T18:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — The Paul Morgan observatory will host a stargazing party from 9:30-10:30 p.m. Friday. Local astronomers will journey across he Milky Way Galaxy and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX NEARS 800 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121487</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/homestead-complex-nears-800-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-nears-800-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T17:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 10:50 a.m.   The Homestead Complex, burning in the Umpqua National Forest, is nearing a total size of 800 acres as of midday Tuesday. A UNF update said more than 200 people are assigned to the complex. The No Man Fire, north of Chilcoot Mountain near No Man Creek saw moderate fire activity...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121485</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-15/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-15"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T17:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping early Tuesday. An RPD report said 2:35 a.m. officers contacted the 39-year-old at his camp at Riverside Park in the 500 block of Southeast Spruce Street. The man’s camp consisted of hung-up tarps and blankets from the trees in a prohibited zone....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR THEFT OF SHOPPING CART]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121483</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-theft-of-shopping-cart/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-theft-of-shopping-cart"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T16:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a woman for the theft of a shopping cart on Monday. An RPD report said at 2:30 p.m. officers contacted the 39-year-old at the duck pond in the 1000 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. The woman was reportedly in possession of a shopping cart belonging to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE PAIR FOR HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121481</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/roseburg-police-cite-pair-for-harassment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-pair-for-harassment"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T16:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 9:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited two people for harassment following a reported disturbance Monday afternoon. An RPD report said at 2:15 p.m. officers responded to a residence in the 2000 block of Northeast Stephens Street. A 30-year-old man and a 28-year-old woman admitted to pushing and poking the other person and were...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121479</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T16:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a reported theft on Monday. An RPD report said at 10:00 p.m. officers responded to a business in the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway after a caller said a man was shoplifting from the store. The 28-year-old left the business and was stopped...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED MENACING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121477</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-menacing-incident-7/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-menacing-incident-7"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T16:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged menacing incident on Monday. An RPD report said just after 8:20 p.m. the 29-year-old was contacted after he allegedly threatened several people with a knife at Stewart Park in the 2000 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive. After he was taken into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 7.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121474</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/morning-conversation-7-23-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-7-23-24"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T16:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kelly Leonard and Marcy Williams were live in Stewart Park to talk about tonight’s Music on the Half Shell concert with Ian Moore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIR QUALITY ALERT FOR MUCH OF SOUTHERN OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121464</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/air-quality-alert-for-much-of-southern-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=air-quality-alert-for-much-of-southern-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T11:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 4:20 a.m. An Air Quality Alert is in effect until 5:00 p.m. Wednesday for much of southern Oregon. The Oregon Department of Environmental Quality has issued an Air Pollution Advisory for eastern Douglas County, Jackson, Josephine, and Klamath counties, due to numerous wildfires burning in the region. Wildfire smoke combined with forecast...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIRE EVACUATION LEVEL BOUNDARY LINE UPDATES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121461</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/fire-evacuation-level-boundary-line-updates/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fire-evacuation-level-boundary-line-updates"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T11:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 4:00 a.m. The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office has made modifications to the evacuation level boundaries for the Lemolo Fire, which is part of the Diamond Complex. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell said largely the boundaries remain the same. O’Dell said however, the Pool Creek Campground and the Lemolo KOA have been downgraded to a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA WITH ONE FIRE IN MOP-UP STATUS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121457</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/dfpa-with-one-fire-in-mop-up-status/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-with-one-fire-in-mop-up-status"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T11:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 3:50 a.m. Following lightning storms which swept across the Douglas District late Saturday night into Sunday morning, bringing several registered air-to-ground strikes, crews with the Douglas Forest Protective Association immediately initiated lightning reconnaissance. DFPA Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said as of mid-day Monday, staff has responded to 36 smoke investigations. Six...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX AT 2,816 ACRES AS OF MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121455</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/diamond-complex-at-2816-acres-as-of-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-at-2816-acres-as-of-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 3:30 a.m. Twelve fires known as the Diamond Complex in the Umpqua National Forest are now at an estimated 2,816 acres, as of Monday. A UNF release said 236 personnel are assigned to the fires. The largest fires in the complex are: *Pine Bench: 1.107 acres and zero percent contained. It is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAN MOORE AT HALF SHELL TUESDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121452</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/ian-moore-at-half-shell-tuesday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ian-moore-at-half-shell-tuesday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 3:20 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Music on the Half Shell features rock singer songwriter Ian Moore on Tuesday night. It’s the sixth concert in the popular summertime series held at the Nichols Bandshell in Roseburg’s Stewart Park. Attendees can bring dinner from home, along with wine and beer, or purchase...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG LIBRARY HOSTS FOURTH ANNUAL HARRY POTTER DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121448</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/roseburg-library-hosts-fourth-annual-harry-potter-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-library-hosts-fourth-annual-harry-potter-day"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2024 3:05 a.m.  Roseburg Public Library will have its fourth annual Harry Potter Day this Saturday from 10:00 a.m. to 1:30 p.m. A city release said it will be a celebration of Hogwarts, magic and the power of imagination. The community is invited to dress up and join staff for activities, trivia, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODEO DAYS BBQ DINNER FUNDRAISER ON THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121445</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/23/rodeo-days-bbq-dinner-fundraiser-on-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rodeo-days-bbq-dinner-fundraiser-on-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 23, 2023 2:50 a.m. A Rodeo Days BBQ dinner fundraiser will be held at The Landing – A Senior Living Community in Roseburg. The event begins at 5:00 p.m. at 2490 Northwest Edenbower Boulevard. It includes a barbecue dinner, live music and more. Tickets are $10 per place with all proceeds going to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fire Evacuation Level Boundary Line Updates (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news173997</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news173997"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T03:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas County Sheriff's Office has made modifications to the evacuation level boundaries for the Lemolo Fire, which is part of the Diamond Complex. 
Largely the the boundaries remain the same. However, the Pool Creek Campground and the Lemolo KOA have been downgraded to a Level 2 - BE SET notice. This change is to reflect the current public safety needs of the incident.
For the most current interactive evacuation map, please visit our website at www.dcso.com/evacuations. 
The Sheriff's Office encourages the community to follow official sources and news outlets for the most current information related to this incident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aircraft and ground firefighters battle Microwave Tower Fire west of Mosier (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173994</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173994"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T01:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE DALLES, Ore. – Residents west of the Columbia Gorge town of Mosier are being told to evacuate as the fast-moving Microwave Tower Fire burns eastward, driven by strong westerly winds of 30 to 35 miles per hour. 
LEVEL 3 - GO NOW! Evacuate immediately from Hwy 30 south the Proctor Rd., east to Huskey Rd and the border of the City of Mosier and west to the Hood River County line.
LEVEL 2 - GET SET to evacuate from the city of Mosier and from Huskey Rd. east to Mosier Creek Rd., and south to Jasper Lane.
A Red Cross shelter for evacuees has been set up at the Hood River Middle School, 1602 May Street, Hood River, OR 97031
Firefighters from ODF’s Unit Office in The Dalles are being aided by Columbia River Gorge National Scenic Area U.S. Forest Service and local fire departments in battling the blaze that started west of Rattler Ridge just west of Mosier in the Columbia Gorge. A very large airtanker has been ordered to help on the fire, which was reported at 4 p.m. this afternoon. A task force of fire engines and a dozer from the Larch Creek Fire in south Wasco County are being diverted to assist on the fire. The I-84 freeway currently remains open. 
The fire is burning in grass and timber, pushed eastwards by strong westerly winds of 30 to 35 miles per hour. Earlier this afternoon it was estimated at 100 to 150 acres. Cause is not known at this time. 
Evacuation levels may change quickly given the spread rate of the fire, with new areas being moved into evacuation status. For the most up-to-date evacuation information, please visit the Wasco County Sheriff’s Facebook page at https://www.facebook.com/WascoCountySheriff/
                                                              # # #]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AIR QUALITY ALERT FOR EASTERN DOUGLAS/KLAMATH COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121442</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/air-quality-alert-for-eastern-douglas-klamath-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=air-quality-alert-for-eastern-douglas-klamath-county"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T23:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 4:20 p.m.  An Air Quality Alert is in effect until 5:00 p.m. Wednesday for parts of southern Oregon. The Oregon Department of Environmental Quality has issued an Air Pollution Advisory for eastern Douglas County and Klamath County due to numerous wildfires burning in the region. DEQ also expects intermittent smoke in Jackson,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intoxicated woman searches for scared child]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fade4f5c-486e-11ef-a272-5b237a78587b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/intoxicated-woman-searches-for-scared-child/article_fade4f5c-486e-11ef-a272-5b237a78587b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A woman was arrested for driving under the influence of intoxicants at 9:15 p.m. Sunday in the 2700 block of West Langenberg Avenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Rotary to hold annual golf tourney]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0a8156ee-486e-11ef-99f1-3f62545495f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/sutherlin-rotary-to-hold-annual-golf-tourney/article_0a8156ee-486e-11ef-99f1-3f62545495f8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — The Sutherlin Rotary Club will host its 25th annual golf tournament on Friday, Aug. 16, at Oak Hills Golf Club.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man threatens to kill woman with hammer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d53e97da-486d-11ef-81a0-e34cd474bfcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/man-threatens-to-kill-woman-with-hammer/article_d53e97da-486d-11ef-81a0-e34cd474bfcb.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T21:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A man allegedly threatened to kill a woman with a hammer just after 10 a.m. Sunday in the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man driving his SUV on the bike path]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b5e7857e-486b-11ef-889d-33cd70d8c16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/man-driving-his-suv-on-the-bike-path/article_b5e7857e-486b-11ef-889d-33cd70d8c16d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T20:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A 30-year-old man was reported to be driving a red GMC on the bike path around 1:30 a.m. Sunday at the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Woman smears dog feces on self]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/5bb71746-486a-11ef-b122-b3bf2d34b8bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/woman-smears-dog-feces-on-self/article_5bb71746-486a-11ef-b122-b3bf2d34b8bf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T20:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A 32-year-old Roseburg woman was arrested for disorderly conduct Friday in an incident that reportedly started with her yelling at Walmart customers and ended with her smearing dog feces on herself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 7.22.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121437</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/inside-douglas-county-7-22-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-7-22-24"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T20:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg VA Medical Center Director Patrick Hull talks about his first 15 months leading the facility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightning across Oregon reminds everyone to be informed and prepared]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173983</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173983"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T19:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore – Starting this past Wednesday, July 17, and into Sunday, July 21, Oregon experienced two separate lightning events that resulted in over 2,000 strikes across the state, which primarily affected Southern, Central and Eastern Oregon. With multiple crews engaged in initial attack on new fire starts and all of Oregon’s available incident management teams on assignment, now is the time for Oregonians to be prepared for wildfires and help prevent future ignitions. 
Oregonians are urged to actively practice wildfire prevention, prepare their home and a go-bag for evacuation and know where to sign up for alerts. 
How can people help prevent wildfires?
The Oregon Department of Forestry is urging the public to actively practice wildfire prevention as the state works to control over 20 la…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend storms bring more fires to Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2696f584-4853-11ef-81e5-c7d1ac76d9cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/weekend-storms-bring-more-fires-to-douglas-county/article_2696f584-4853-11ef-81e5-c7d1ac76d9cb.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The predicted thunderstorms struck Douglas County and much of Oregon during Saturday night with lightning and light rain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR LITTERING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121435</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-littering-incident-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-littering-incident-3"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T17:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 10:45 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for a littering incident on Sunday. An RPD report said at 9:30 a.m. the 52-year-old was contacted at his camp in the 2000 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. The camp was surrounded by trash approximately thirty yards from the bank of the South Umpqua River....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE FIVE PEOPLE FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121432</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/roseburg-police-cite-five-people-for-drinking-in-public/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-five-people-for-drinking-in-public"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T17:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 10:30 a.m.   Roseburg Police cited five people for drinking in public during three incidents on Saturday. An RPD report said at 11:25 a.m. a 64-year-old woman was observed consuming alcohol from a can at the corner of Northeast Winchester Street and Northeast Rowe Street. A citation was issued. Just after 2:30 p.m....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR FELONY WAARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121430</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-felony-waarrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-felony-waarrant"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T17:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 10:10 a.m.    Roseburg Police jailed a man for a felony warrant on Friday. An RPD report said at 7:30 a.m. officers contacted the 55-year-old in the 3000 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway and learned he had the warrant on an original charge of possession of dangerous drugs and unlawful possession of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR REPORTED DISORDERLY CONDUCT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121427</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T17:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 9:50 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a reported disorderly conduct incident on Friday. An RPD report said at 7:30 p.m.32-year-old Ashley Basgall was contacted after she was at Walmart in the 2100 block of Northeast Stephens Street. Basgall was allegedly yelling at customers and flashing her breasts to the employees...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR BIKE PATH DUII]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121425</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-bike-path-duii/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-bike-path-duii"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T16:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a DUII incident on the bike path early Sunday. An RPD report said just after 1:30 a.m. 30-year-old Easton Bartley was contacted as he was driving a large SUV on the path in the area of Deer Creek Park in the 200 block of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED MENACING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121423</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-menacing-incident-6/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-menacing-incident-6"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T16:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged menacing incident on Sunday. An RPD report said just after 10:00 a.m. officers contacted the 37-year-old after he allegedly threatened a victim with a hammer in the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. The man’s belongings were blocking the sidewalk and the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 7.22.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121420</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/morning-conversation-7-22-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-7-22-24"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T16:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Senator David Brock Smith talks about his trip to the Republican National Convention, and President Biden’s exit from the race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg VA hosts class about patient portal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b08b500a-483a-11ef-80b5-1b57235f625c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/roseburg-va-hosts-class-about-patient-portal/article_b08b500a-483a-11ef-80b5-1b57235f625c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T14:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patients of the Roseburg VA Medical Center can learn how to navigate its patient portal during a class, held at 10:30 a.m. July 31 in the Health Resource Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAWMAKERS RESPOND TO PRESIDENT BIDEN’S EXIT FROM 2024 RACE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121415</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/lawmakers-respond-to-president-bidens-exit-from-2024-race/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lawmakers-respond-to-president-bidens-exit-from-2024-race"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T10:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 3:40 a.m.  On Sunday, Oregon lawmakers responded to President Joe Biden’s exit from the 2024 presidential race. In statements to News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN: Senator Ron Wyden said, “I’ve been proud to work with President Biden on a record of Democratic successes these past 3 1/2 years that includes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG CITY COUNCIL TO HOLD PUBLIC HEARING ON PROPOSED LAND SWAP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121413</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/roseburg-city-council-to-hold-public-hearing-on-proposed-land-swap/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-city-council-to-hold-public-hearing-on-proposed-land-swap"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T10:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 3:30 a.m. Roseburg City Council will hold a public hearing on a proposed land swap at its meeting Monday night. The city has initiated an amendment to its Urban Growth Boundary. If approved, the process will include removing two large parcels of land from the UGB that have significant development constraints, while...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[H.O.P.E. DRUG COURT ANNOUNCES 106TH GRADUATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121411</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/h-o-p-e-drug-court-announces-106th-graduation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=h-o-p-e-drug-court-announces-106th-graduation"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T10:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Douglas County H.O.P.E. Drug Court will hold its 106th graduation on Tuesday at 5:15 p.m. It will take place at 5:15 p.m. in the Community Conference Hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds. Professor Mark T. Harris J.D., Director of Pre-Law Studies at the University of California and managing attorney...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS TIMBER OPERATORS MEETING THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121409</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/douglas-timber-operators-meeting-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-timber-operators-meeting-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T10:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Douglas Timber Operators will meet on Thursday morning. DTO Executive Director Matt Hill will have a presentation titled, “Update on State and Federal Forest Management Policies Affecting Douglas County”. The meeting will be held at 8:00 a.m. at The Loft at Del Ray Café on Northeast Stephens Street in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN ROTARY CLUB TO HOLD 25TH ANNUAL GOLF TOURNEY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121407</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/22/sutherlin-rotary-club-to-hold-25th-annual-golf-tourney/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-rotary-club-to-hold-25th-annual-golf-tourney"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T10:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 2:50 a.m.  The Sutherlin Rotary Club will have its 25th annual golf tourney on Friday August 16th at Oak Hills Golf Club. The tournament is a four-person scramble. Registration is at 8:30 a.m. with tee time at 9:30 a.m. The cost is $500 per team, which includes golf, a cart, and snacks....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWELVE FIRES TOTALING 2,385 ACRES IN UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121404</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/21/twelve-fires-totaling-2385-acres-in-umpqua-national-forest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=twelve-fires-totaling-2385-acres-in-umpqua-national-forest"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T21:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 21. 2024 2:00 p.m.   There are twelve fires totaling 2,385 acres in the Diamond Complex on the Umpqua National Forest, under a strategy of full suppression. An Umpqua National Forest release said the fires are: *Pine Bend: 917 acres, north of Highway 138 near Dry Creek *Trail: 808 acres, east of Highway 138 on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA DEALS WITH FIVE LIGHTNING CAUSED FIRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=121401</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/07/21/dfpa-deals-with-five-lightning-caused-fires/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-deals-with-five-lightning-caused-fires"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T20:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 22, 2024 1:40 p.m.  Saturday night at approximately 11:00 p.m. the first predicted thunderstorm swept across the Douglas District, bringing with it several registered strikes. Douglas Forest Protective Association Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said that immediately initiated the first found of lightning reconnaissance. Pope said at 2:00 a.m. Sunday a more considerable thunderstorm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jensen Mast graduates from Millikin University]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/152cbfb0-42d4-11ef-b2e8-bf7d7c535db8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/jensen-mast-graduates-from-millikin-university/article_152cbfb0-42d4-11ef-b2e8-bf7d7c535db8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DECATUR, ILL — Jensen Mast, of Reedsport, graduated summa cum laude from Millikin University with a bachelor's of science in biology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mud flies at Camas Valley Fun Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/20c68326-46ab-11ef-a75e-cf07e1707f0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/mud-flies-at-camas-valley-fun-days/article_20c68326-46ab-11ef-a75e-cf07e1707f0e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMAS VALLEY — Mud flew as the crowd applauded vehicles that braved the muddy pits that lay ahead of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARIAH JOHNSTON The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glide Sasquatch Festival sees all things Bigfoot on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/83b90d02-46ef-11ef-bb72-7f8c5b784dd8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/glide-sasquatch-festival-sees-all-things-bigfoot-on-saturday/article_83b90d02-46ef-11ef-bb72-7f8c5b784dd8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — Cars lined up and down North Umpqua Highway, waiting to turn into the parking lot of the Glide Sasquatch Festival as the festival opened at noon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer is the perfect season for outdoor service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/116be0c6-4537-11ef-acc3-bfcf5dd25c18</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/summer-is-the-perfect-season-for-outdoor-service/article_116be0c6-4537-11ef-acc3-bfcf5dd25c18.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sunny skies and longer days make this the perfect season for outdoor service projects. From a downtown Roseburg clean up activity to a massive bed building event, you can make a positive impact in our community while enjoying the summer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JENNIFER D. COALWELL For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motorcyclist dies in accident]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c71da0f4-46bc-11ef-92d8-cb9ace8ecc6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/motorcyclist-dies-in-accident/article_c71da0f4-46bc-11ef-92d8-cb9ace8ecc6c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A man from Umpqua died in an SUV versus motorcycle accident Wednesday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>