<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-02-27T02:14:49.031Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR CHILD NEGLECT IN THE SECOND-DEGREE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116105</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/27/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-child-neglect-in-the-second-degree/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-child-neglect-in-the-second-degree"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T01:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Police cited a man for child neglect in the second-degree Sunday afternoon. An RPD report said just before 5:30 p.m. officers responded to the 2200 block of Northeast Vine Street after a caller said a 3-year-old in a t-shirt and a diaper was running unsupervised in the middle of the street. Officers located the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG WOMAN CHARGED FOR ALLEGEDLY ATTEMPTING TO ELUDE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116103</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/roseburg-woman-charged-for-allegedly-attempting-to-elude/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-woman-charged-for-allegedly-attempting-to-elude"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T00:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 5:00 p.m.   A Roseburg woman was charged by Roseburg for allegedly attempting to elude on Saturday night. An RPD report said at 8:50 p.m. an officer attempted to conduct a traffic stop on a sedan near Southeast Fowler Street and Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard after a traffic violation was observed. The vehicle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR SECOND-DEGREE CRIMINAL TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116101</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-second-degree-criminal-trespass/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-second-degree-criminal-trespass"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T00:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2023 4:50 p.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for second-degree criminal trespass on Friday. An RPD report said just after 1:10 p.m. the 39-year-old was spotted near the intersection of Southeast Jackson Street and Southeast Court Street. An officer knew the suspect was a City Expulsion Violator on his third warning and was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FUGITIVE ARRESTED BY ROSEBURG POLICE ON FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116099</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/fugitive-arrested-by-roseburg-police-on-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fugitive-arrested-by-roseburg-police-on-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T00:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 4:40 p.m.  A fugitive was arrested by Roseburg Police on Friday. An RPD report said at 12:40 p.m. officers contacted the 46-year-old in the 400 block of Northeast Oakland Avenue after a caller said the man was acting strange. He was taken into custody for a Coos Bay Police Department warrant. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WATCH STARTING WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON ABOVE 2,500 FEET]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116095</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/winter-storm-watch-starting-wednesday-afternoon-above-2500-feet/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-watch-starting-wednesday-afternoon-above-2500-feet"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T23:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 3:20 p.m.   A Winter Storm Watch is in effect for central Douglas County, eastern Curry Country and Josephine and Jackson counties from Wednesday afternoon through Thursday evening above 2,500 feet. An Urgent Weather Message from the National Weather Service said heavy snow is possible above that elevation, with up to 11 inches...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREAT AT UCC DEEMED NOT CREDIBLE, ORIGINATED OUTSIDE THE US.]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116092</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/threat-at-ucc-deemed-not-credible-originated-outside-the-us/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=threat-at-ucc-deemed-not-credible-originated-outside-the-us"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T23:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 3:10 p.m.   Monday’s threat at Umpqua Community College has been determined to not be credible and originated outside the United States. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell said on Monday the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office was notified by UCC staff of a security threat to the campus. O’Dell said in an effort to prioritize the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat at UCC Determined Not Credible, Originated Outside of United States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170289</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170289"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T22:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG, Ore. On Monday, February 26, 2024, the Sheriff's Office was notified by Umpqua Community College staff of a security threat to the campus. In an effort to prioritize the safety of students, staff and faculty, the College elected to cancel all classes, events, and activities until further notice. 
The Sheriff's Office is working in partnership with the College regarding the threat. There is an increased law enforcement presence on the campus today. 
“The Sheriff's Office takes seriously any threat directed toward the safety of our schools, whether kindergarten or higher education institutions," Sheriff Hanlin said. “The Sheriff’s Office, with assistance from the FBI, has determined the source of the email originated from outside the country. At this time the threatening email is not considered credible, and there is no immediate threat to the college.”
The specifics of the security threat will not be released by the Sheriff's Office in order to protect the integrity of the investigation. 
"We are committed to taking all necessary precautions to ensure safe learning and working environments for everyone. We understand that this closure may cause inconvenience to the academic and personal lives of our community, and we appreciate your cooperation and understanding," said UCC President, Dr. Rachel Pokrandt.
Anyone with information may contact the Douglas County Sheriff's Office at 541-440-4471.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED BURGLARY/DUII]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116085</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-alleged-burglary-duii/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-alleged-burglary-duii"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 10:45 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a man for an alleged burglary and DUII incident on Saturday night. An SPD report said 9:10 p.m. officers responded to a residence in the 400 block of Southeast First Street in Oakland. 42-year-old Cord Daves had allegedly broken into a victim’s home when she was gone....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOUSE REPUBLICAN LEADER HELFRICH STATEMENT ON HB4002 AMENDMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116083</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/house-republican-leader-helfrich-statement-on-hb4002-amendment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=house-republican-leader-helfrich-statement-on-hb4002-amendment"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 10:20 a.m.  In response to the recently proposed amendment to HB4002, House Republican Leader Jeff Helfrich of Hood River offered the following statement: “House Republicans stand today where we’ve always stood: On the side of Oregonians who want to end Measure 110. As of today, the proposal before the legislature is far...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLY-IN PIG SET FOR MAY AT MYRTLE CREEK AIRPORT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116080</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/fly-in-pig-set-for-may-at-myrtle-creek-airport/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fly-in-pig-set-for-may-at-myrtle-creek-airport"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T18:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 10:00 a.m. The Fly-in Pig barbecue competition is set for May 18th and 19th at the Myrtle Creek Municipal Airport. Sponsored by the City of Myrtle Creek and a number of businesses, the event is a fully sanctioned barbecue competition, fully sanctioned by the Pacific Northwest BBQ Association. The event runs on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BENTZ HOLDS LISTENING SESSION ON GROWING POPULATION OF WOLVES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116078</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/bentz-holds-listening-session-on-growing-population-of-wolves/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=bentz-holds-listening-session-on-growing-population-of-wolves"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 9:40 a.m. On Thursday, Congressman Cliff Bentz held a roundtable listening session in Prineville on the increasing population of wolves and its impact on the community. A release from the Congressman’s office said the session included local ranchers and stakeholders and was aimed at fostering dialogue and identifying solutions in preparing for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC CLOSES CAMPUSES IN RESPONSE TO SECURITY THREAT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116076</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/ucc-closes-campuses-in-response-to-security-threat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-closes-campuses-in-response-to-security-threat"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua College College has closed its campus as of Monday morning in response to a security threat in order to prioritize the safety of its students, staff, faculty and community. A release issued shortly after 9:00 a.m. said all classes, events and activities are canceled until further notice. Additional updates and instructions will be communicated...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A flipping good time at Riverside Classic 2024 gymnastics competition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/27927e8a-d360-11ee-ba89-bf30185767fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/a-flipping-good-time-at-riverside-classic-2024-gymnastics-competition/article_27927e8a-d360-11ee-ba89-bf30185767fa.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legs fluttered, arms twirled and bodies flipped around for the annual Riverside Classic 2024 gymnastics competition Saturday at the Douglas County Fairgrounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG SEES SUNNY CONDITIONS, ABOVE NORMAL TEMPERATURES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116070</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/roseburg-sees-sunny-conditions-above-normal-temperatures/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-sees-sunny-conditions-above-normal-temperatures"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T11:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 4;00 a.m.  Roseburg saw sunny conditions and above normal temperatures between Friday and Sunday, just ahead of a big change in the weather. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the mercury reached 65 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport on Friday....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING THROUGH 1:00 A.M. MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116067</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/winter-storm-warning-through-100-a-m-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-through-100-a-m-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T11:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 3:40 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect through 1:00 a.m. Tuesday for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected. Total snow accumulations of 8 to 22 inches are expected. Winds will gust as high as 40 miles per hour....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COASTAL CAUCUS URGES BOEM TO ADDRESS CONCERNS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116065</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/coastal-caucus-urges-boem-to-address-concerns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=coastal-caucus-urges-boem-to-address-concerns"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T11:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 3:20 a.m. On Friday, the Oregon Legislative Coastal Caucus issued a call for the federal Bureau of Ocean Energy Management to address significant concerns before advancing offshore wind projects off the coast of Oregon. In a letter to BOEM Director Heidi Klein, the group expressed extreme disappointment with BOEM’s decision to finalize...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG CITY COUNCIL WITH VARIED AGENDA MONDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116063</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/roseburg-city-council-with-varied-agenda-monday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-city-council-with-varied-agenda-monday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T11:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024  3:05 a.m. The Roseburg City Council has a varied agenda for its Monday night meeting. Mayor Larry Rich will report on awards the city has received for excellence and outstanding achievement in financial reporting. The annual comprehensive financial report will be given by auditor Jeff Cooley of Neuner Davidson & Co. Councilors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STATE PARKS RECRUITING FOR SEASON STAFF]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116059</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/26/state-parks-recruiting-for-season-staff/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=state-parks-recruiting-for-season-staff"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T11:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 26, 2024 2:50 a.m. Oregon Parks and Recreation is recruiting 250 seasonal park rangers and assistants for positions across the station that range anywhere from four to nine months. An OPRD release said the peak season is from April to September, but some positions start as early as March and run as late as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zonta Club to celebrate Dignity Drive on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/933a0820-d350-11ee-8276-9f1d02169cd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/zonta-club-to-celebrate-dignity-drive-on-wednesday/article_933a0820-d350-11ee-8276-9f1d02169cd4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Zonta Club of Roseburg will celebrate a successful Dignity Drive at noon Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merkley announces in-person town hall for Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/27c5e4ce-d350-11ee-ad99-0371dc17857c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/merkley-announces-in-person-town-hall-for-douglas-county/article_27c5e4ce-d350-11ee-ad99-0371dc17857c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-25T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley has announced that there will be an in-person town hall in Douglas County on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Storm Watch Sunday evening thru Monday evening]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c3071f1c-d34f-11ee-a3e6-4b895ea515f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/winter-storm-watch-sunday-evening-thru-monday-evening/article_c3071f1c-d34f-11ee-a3e6-4b895ea515f8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — A Winter Storm Watch is in effect from Sunday evening through Monday evening for higher elevations in parts of southern Oregon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING SUNDAY NIGHT THROUGH TUESDAY MORNING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116056</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/25/winter-storm-warning-sunday-night-through-tuesday-morning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-sunday-night-through-tuesday-morning"/>
        <updated>2024-02-25T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 25, 2024 5:50 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect from 10:00 p.m. Sunday through 1:00 a.m. Tuesday for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected. Total snow accumulations of 10 to 21 inches are expected with winds gusting as high as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Watershed hosts presentation on wilderness]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8c79e81e-d2da-11ee-be7c-476e91dafd02</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/umpqua-watershed-hosts-presentation-on-wilderness/article_8c79e81e-d2da-11ee-be7c-476e91dafd02.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A flute song, photos of the bodies of water and wildlife in the forests around Douglas County and maps of the Umpqua National Forest greeted those who entered the Roseburg library Ford Room on Friday night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SENATORS ANNOUNCE $27 MILLION TO SUPPORT PACIFIC SALMON RECOVERY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116054</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/24/senators-announce-27-million-to-support-pacific-salmon-recovery/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=senators-announce-27-million-to-support-pacific-salmon-recovery"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T18:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 24, 2024 10:45 a.m. On Thursday, Oregon Senators Ron Wyden and Jeff Merkley announced an investment of $27 million from the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration to help support recovery efforts for Pacific salmon populations. A joint release said the federal funds are available due to the passage of the Inflation Reduction Act. This...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE DEAL WITH 3 DUII INCIDENTS IN 3 HOURS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116052</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/24/roseburg-police-deal-with-3-duii-incidents-in-3-hours/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-deal-with-3-duii-incidents-in-3-hours"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T17:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 24, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police dealt with 3 DUII incidents in 3 hours between late Thursday night and early Friday morning. An RPD report said just after 10:20 p.m. a 27-year-old woman was pulled over for running a stop sign at the intersection of Southeast Lane Avenue and Southeast Pine Street. During the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European capitals of culture]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/15ef5dbc-cf4e-11ee-a628-57124d84dd7b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/european-capitals-of-culture/article_15ef5dbc-cf4e-11ee-a628-57124d84dd7b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T17:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re thinking about a trip to Europe this year but you want an experience that’s out of the ordinary, consider visiting one of the three communities being celebrated as a European Capital of Culture for 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Travel Leaders/Fly Away Travel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respect for Law banquet honors Douglas County law enforcement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/62988944-d36e-11ee-917e-9767de427ecd</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/respect-for-law-banquet-honors-douglas-county-law-enforcement/article_62988944-d36e-11ee-917e-9767de427ecd.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A positive example. Approachable and encouraging. A dedicated team player. An ability to handle calls with grace. Selfless service. These are some of the qualities recognized Friday when Roseburg Optimist Club hosted the Respectful for Law Banquet, honoring law enforcement…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR REPORTED TRESPASS/IMPROPER 911]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116050</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/24/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-reported-trespass-improper-911/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-reported-trespass-improper-911"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T17:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 24, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman following at incident at CHI Mercy Medical Center on Northwest Stewart Parkway on Thursday night. An RPD report said officers responded just after 10:00 p.m. when the 34-year-old allegedly began calling 911 and yelling at dispatchers, while refusing to leave the hospital. She was taken...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club News: Explore Brice Creek Trail on March 2]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/26f54db0-d1a6-11ee-88cf-fb0e13ba5eb0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/club-news-explore-brice-creek-trail-on-march-2/article_26f54db0-d1a6-11ee-88cf-fb0e13ba5eb0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next Friends of the Umpqua Hiking Club hike is scheduled for March 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg library asks for community feedback]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/636e81e2-d270-11ee-8d60-9b10a14c98b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/roseburg-library-asks-for-community-feedback/article_636e81e2-d270-11ee-8d60-9b10a14c98b5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the current RARE AmeriCorps member serving as the outreach services lead for Roseburg Public Library, I am leading this spring’s library use assessment survey project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Sala Library News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg announces streamline to parking ticket appeals process]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f3b249ce-d283-11ee-8502-cb6bc57120f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/roseburg-announces-streamline-to-parking-ticket-appeals-process/article_f3b249ce-d283-11ee-8502-cb6bc57120f3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After months of questions surrounding parking tickets in the downtown and Laurelwood neighborhood, the city of Roseburg has announced a simplification to the parking ticket appeals process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forest bug: Wheaton receives Douglas Small Woodlands Association scholarship]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/35b3b928-d21d-11ee-b5a7-8bbe4629921e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/forest-bug-wheaton-receives-douglas-small-woodlands-association-scholarship/article_35b3b928-d21d-11ee-b5a7-8bbe4629921e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After working on wildland fires over the past three summers, Maggie Wheaton couldn’t give up the forestry bug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMART Reading issues call for community volunteers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fb4bb5be-d114-11ee-a82b-73dc7f19b2ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/smart-reading-issues-call-for-community-volunteers/article_fb4bb5be-d114-11ee-a82b-73dc7f19b2ad.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Children’s literacy nonprofit SMART Reading is issuing an invitation for the community to give one hour a week to a make a meaningful difference for kids learning to read.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FireBug Tools: geared up for blowing glass]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f80444fc-d00b-11ee-8385-373dc2df255c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/firebug-tools-geared-up-for-blowing-glass/article_f80444fc-d00b-11ee-8385-373dc2df255c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Walker came in hot to the glassblowing business, not as someone who “plays with lava all day long,” but as the provider of the tools needed to craft the delicate creations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know Douglas ESD: Future foundations for students]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/12f3a13e-d1a8-11ee-9267-07b69c6bc594</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/get-to-know-douglas-esd-future-foundations-for-students/article_12f3a13e-d1a8-11ee-9267-07b69c6bc594.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students build websites, some crochet and others work on computer-aided design while a 3D printer hums in the background. Students innovate in Elkton High School’s Maker Space classroom. This type of learning is part of Career and Technical Education (CTE).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HEATHER VILLA For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marriages: Feb. 12-16]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c826d90e-d01d-11ee-a94a-17cd9abb228a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/marriages-feb-12-16/article_c826d90e-d01d-11ee-a94a-17cd9abb228a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas County Clerk’s Office issued these licenses Feb. 12-16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Public Universities visit Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/75ba8930-d276-11ee-aeb6-8b09b7b44659</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/oregon-public-universities-visit-douglas-county/article_75ba8930-d276-11ee-aeb6-8b09b7b44659.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Public Universities will have representatives available to meet with prospective students and parents at 6 p.m. Thursday in the foyer of Roseburg High School's Main building.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explore UCC event coming March 7]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e5c54ce2-d276-11ee-a8cd-0b7d65645e8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/explore-ucc-event-coming-march-7/article_e5c54ce2-d276-11ee-a8cd-0b7d65645e8b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 14th annual Explore UCC event is taking place from 4:30-6:30 p.m. March 7 at the gymnasium at Umpqua Community College, 1140 Umpqua College Road, Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WATCH SUNDAY EVENING THROUGH MONDAY EVENING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116044</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/24/winter-storm-watch-sunday-evening-through-monday-evening/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-watch-sunday-evening-through-monday-evening"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T14:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 24, 2024 6:00 a.m.  A Winter Storm Watch remains in effect from Sunday evening through Monday evening for higher elevations in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is possible with total snow accumulations of 6 to 14 inches expected. Winds could gust as high as 45 miles...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geneva Academy to hold informational meeting Monday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9434acc8-d27c-11ee-81e2-bb04cc048443</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/geneva-academy-to-hold-informational-meeting-monday/article_9434acc8-d27c-11ee-81e2-bb04cc048443.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geneva Academy will host an informational meeting called "What is Classical Christian Education, and is it Right for Our Family?" at 6 p.m. Monday at the NewChurch Roseburg sanctuary, 2075 Witherspoon Ave., Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Committee for Emergency Fire Cost meets March 5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170260</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170260"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T00:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Emergency Fire Cost Committee will meet in the Tillamook Room, Building C, Oregon Department of Forestry, 2600 State Street in Salem on Tuesday, March 5, 2024, at 10 a.m. A virtual option will be available via Zoom video conference, which can be found on the agenda. To provide public comment, please contact Lorna Hobbs at 503-881-8292.
The committee’s agenda includes:

Financial status of the Oregon Forest Land Protection Fund
Weather update
Update on status of large fire cost collection efforts
Determine Unencumbered Balance of the OFLPF as of Feb. 16
Administrative Branch/Fire Protection Division/Administrator reports

The meeting is open to the public to attend in-person or virtually via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted near the end of the meeting. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 72 hours before the meeting by contacting Lorna Hobbs at 503-881-8292.
The Emergency Fire Cost Committee (EFCC) oversees the Oregon Forest Land Protection Fund (OFLPF), established by the Oregon Legislature as a fund with the purpose of equalizing emergency fire suppression costs among the various Oregon Department of Forestry protection districts and forest protective associations. All districts/associations contribute to the fund so that money will be available to any individual district/association to pay fire suppression costs on eligible emergency fires. View more information on the EFCC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Board of Forestry to meet on March 6 and 7, Forestry Program for Oregon Subcommittee meets March 6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170253</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170253"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T23:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Oregon Board of Forestrywill meet for hybrid public meetings on Wednesday, March 6 at 1:30 p.m. and Thursday, March 7 at 8 a.m. The meetings will be held in the Tillamook Room, Building C, at the Oregon Department of Forestry headquarters, located at 2600 State St. in Salem. The meetings will also be livestreamed on the department’s YouTube channel.
The Forestry Program for Oregon Subcommittee meets March 6 at 10 a.m. in the Tillamook room and available by Zoom link included with the agenda. View the subcommittee’s full agenda.
The board’s business agenda for March 6 includes:

Financial Dashboard Report – January and February 2024
Approval of agency director financial transactions, Fiscal Year 2023
Rangeland Protection Association formation: Expansion of Field-Andrews RP…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED UNLAWFUL ENTRY INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116042</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-unlawful-entry-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-unlawful-entry-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T22:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 2:40 p.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged unlawful entry and theft incident on Thursday. An RPD report said a 35-year-old suspect allegedly stole a purse and cellphone out of a victim’s vehicle then demanded money from the victim over the phone if she wanted to get the purse back....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED ON 8 CHARGES THURSDAY MORNING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116039</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/roseburg-man-jailed-on-8-charges-thursday-morning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-on-8-charges-thursday-morning"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T22:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 2:30 p.m.  A Roseburg man was jailed on 8 charges by Roseburg Police Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 8:20 a.m. officers responded to the 2000 block of Southeast Douglas Avenue after a caller said there had been a theft from a vehicle. 29-year-old Nicholas Artherholt was located and taken into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED PRIOR BURGLARY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116037</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-prior-burglary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-prior-burglary"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T22:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 2:15 p.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man on Thursday for an alleged prior burglary. An RPD report said on or about February 14th, a victim returned to his home in the 1800 block of West Harvard Avenue and found that it had been broken into with numerous items moved around. 37-year-old Patrick...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE DETAIN WOMAN ON 13 CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116035</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/roseburg-police-detain-woman-on-13-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-detain-woman-on-13-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T22:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 2:00 p.m.  Roseburg Police detained a woman on 13 charges after contacting her on Thursday. An RPD report said at 5:00 p.m. 37-year-old Tamara Owsley was spotted in the 600 block of West Madrone Street after being developed as a suspect in a case. During the months of November and December, Owsley...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG SCHOOL BOARD APPROVES CONTRACT EXTENSION FOR SUPERINTENDENT CORDON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116029</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/roseburg-school-board-approves-contract-extension-for-superintendent-cordon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-school-board-approves-contract-extension-for-superintendent-cordon"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T19:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 11:10 a.m. On Wednesday, the Roseburg School Board approved a contract extension for Superintendent Jared Cordon. A release said the board noted his “…exceptional leadership and numerous accomplishments in serving and supporting students in the Roseburg School District over the past five years”. Following its annual superintendent evaluation, school board members unanimously...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOYLE/ACTING SECRETARY OF LABOR TOUR WORKFORCE TRAINING CENTER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116027</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/hoyle-acting-secretary-of-labor-tour-workforce-training-center/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hoyle-acting-secretary-of-labor-tour-workforce-training-center"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 10:40 a.m.  On Thursday, Congresswoman Val Hoyle and Acting U.S. Secretary of Labor Julie Su toured the UA Local 290 Training Facility and the Spark at Booth Kelly youth program, which offer apprenticeships and hands-on training. A release from Hoyle said programs like this are key to the Biden Administration’s push for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERKLEY ANNOUNCES IN-PERSON TOWN HALL IN DOUGLAS COUNTY MARCH 2ND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116025</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/merkley-announces-in-person-town-hall-in-douglas-county-march-2nd/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=merkley-announces-in-person-town-hall-in-douglas-county-march-2nd"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 10:20 a.m.   U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley has announced that there will be an in-person Town Hall in Douglas County on Saturday March 2nd. This will kick off Merkley’s Town Hall Tour of Oregon, where he will hold community conservations for each of the state’s 36 counties. Merkley said, “I hold a town...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG HIGH TO HOST PUBLIC UNIVERSITIES VISIT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116023</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/roseburg-high-to-host-public-universities-visit/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-high-to-host-public-universities-visit"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T18:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg High School will host a visit from representatives of Oregon Public Universities on Thursday, February 29th at 6:00 p.m. The event will be in the Main building foyer. Students and parents can meet with them. Those who are prospective 4-year college bound students are encouraged to attend. Representatives will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZONTA CLUB OF ROSEBURG TO CELEBRATE DIGNITY DRIVE SUCCESS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116019</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/23/zonta-club-of-roseburg-to-celebrate-dignity-drive-success/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=zonta-club-of-roseburg-to-celebrate-dignity-drive-success"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 23, 2024 9:30 a.m.  The Zonta Club of Roseburg will celebrate a successful Dignity Drive on Wednesday, February 28th at 12:00 p.m. Last October through November, the YMCA of Douglas County, Red Robin Gourmet Burgers and Brews, Sherm’s Thunderbird Market and the City of Roseburg Public Library, helped collect undergarments and sanitary products for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respect for Law banquet honors Douglas County law enforcement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a897aa26-d024-11ee-a6c3-8f45ad299f04</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/respect-for-law-banquet-honors-douglas-county-law-enforcement/article_a897aa26-d024-11ee-a6c3-8f45ad299f04.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A positive example. Approachable and encouraging. A dedicated team player. An ability to handle calls with grace. Selfless service. These are some of the qualities recognized Friday when Roseburg Optimist Club hosted the Respectful for Law Banquet, honoring law enforcement…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg High School Foundation announces finalists for Future First Citizen award]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2f3744c8-d1e8-11ee-8112-7baccd9e0216</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/roseburg-high-school-foundation-announces-finalists-for-future-first-citizen-award/article_2f3744c8-d1e8-11ee-8112-7baccd9e0216.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christina Chi, Elias Malak, Kate Dammann, Malia Reichel Martin Narciso and Massimo Falleni are the finalist for the 2024 Future First Citizen award.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Starting vegetables from seeds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b30de6c0-cf50-11ee-85bb-8715c2613f0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/ask-a-master-gardener-starting-vegetables-from-seeds/article_b30de6c0-cf50-11ee-85bb-8715c2613f0b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I’d like to try starting my own vegetables from seeds this year. Can you give me some tips on ways to do that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MACKENZI HALL For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hops for K9 Cops happening March 10]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/132eefb6-d115-11ee-ac5c-8f81e86071d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/hops-for-k9-cops-happening-march-10/article_132eefb6-d115-11ee-ac5c-8f81e86071d2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Friends of Umpqua Valley Police K9 Programs is holding Hops for K9 Cops at 2 p.m. March 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Children take home free books, make crafts at Roseburg Library event]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3c16872a-d1f8-11ee-9ed8-f3edb1d42665</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/children-take-home-free-books-make-crafts-at-roseburg-library-event/article_3c16872a-d1f8-11ee-9ed8-f3edb1d42665.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of Altrusa International of Roseburg's annual Celebration of Literacy event, Roseburg Public Library hosted an arts and crafts event and allowed children to take a book home along with their crafts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WILL GESCHKE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>