<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-11-08T23:11:30.812Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon’s Hazelnut Harvest]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8537</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/oregons-hazelnut-harvest/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T23:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Pat O’Connor Oregon Regional Economist Orchards are not very difficult to find in Oregon. In the Columbia Gorge, one can hardly miss the cherry, pear, and apple orchards. In southern Oregon, pear orchards fill Jackson County’s countryside. The Willamette Valley has a variety of fruit and nut orchards, but more acres in the valley are planted in hazelnuts than any…
The post Oregon’s Hazelnut Harvest appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSP SEIZES ALMOST 10 POUNDS OF FENTANYL POWDER IN DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125863</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/osp-seizes-almost-10-pounds-of-fentanyl-powder-in-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=osp-seizes-almost-10-pounds-of-fentanyl-powder-in-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T22:19:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 2:20 p.m.  On Wednesday, troopers with the Oregon State Police seized almost 10 pounds of illegal drugs during a traffic stop. An OSP report said at about 11:00 a.m. a trooper stopped a vehicle on Interstate 5 northbound in Douglas County for traffic violations. During the stop, the trooper observed signs of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacific Northwest semiconductor and mass timber industries each receive $500,000 awards from White House]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8520</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/pacific-northwest-semiconductor-and-mass-timber-industries-each-receive-500000-awards-from-white-house/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T22:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CORVALLIS, Ore. – Oregon State University-led efforts focused on microfluidic technology for semiconductors and mass timber design and manufacturing each have received $500,000 awards from the White House. In Oct. 2023, the White House, through the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Economic Development Administration, announced the designation of 31 Tech Hubs(Link is external), including the two led by…
The post Pacific Northwest semiconductor and mass timber industries each receive $500,000 awards from White House appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon State University receives $5.5 million to help grow market for hemp-based products]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8517</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/oregon-state-university-receives-5-5-million-to-help-grow-market-for-hemp-based-products/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T22:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CORVALLIS, Ore. – Oregon State University’s Global Hemp Innovation Center will receive $5.5 million during the next five years to research new food, beverage and biobased industrial product uses of industrial hemp. With the funding, researchers from Oregon State and the U.S. Department of Agriculture’s Agricultural Research Service will develop customized hemp genetics that meet the…
The post Oregon State University receives $5.5 million to help grow market for hemp-based products appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOU computer scientist receives Sloan grant for “tacit knowledge” research]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8514</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/sou-computer-scientist-receives-sloan-grant-for-tacit-knowledge-research/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T21:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Ashland, Ore.) — Bernadette Boscoe, an assistant professor in the Computer Science Department at Southern Oregon University, recognizes a shared need in fields as dissimilar as astronomy, environmental science and violin acoustics, and a new grant will pay for research that may benefit those and other academic disciplines. Boscoe has received a $250,000 grant from…
The post SOU computer scientist receives Sloan grant for “tacit knowledge” research appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainability conference at SOU builds regional collaboration]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8511</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/sustainability-conference-at-sou-builds-regional-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T21:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Ashland, Ore.) — The initial conference of Southern Oregon University’s Institute for Applied Sustainability attracted about 85 sustainability professionals from southern Oregon and northern California this month for two days of hands-on learning, actionable insights and connection-building in Ashland and nearby venues. The invitation-only conference on Oct. 3 and 4 was open to those in…
The post Sustainability conference at SOU builds regional collaboration appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOU alumni receive awards for their work and service]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8508</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/sou-alumni-receive-awards-for-their-work-and-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T21:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Ashland, Ore.) — A Colorado State University professor who is helping develop the Periodic Table of Food; the founder and executive director of a nonprofit that protects Siskiyou backcountry trails; a former La Clinica CFO and current equity policy strategist with the Oregon Health Authority; and the CEO of a Beaverton-based computer software company and…
The post SOU alumni receive awards for their work and service appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon’s Measure 118: A business tax proposal that failed]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8502</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/oregons-measure-118-a-business-tax-proposal-that-failed/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T21:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon’s Measure 118, also known as the “Oregon Rebate,” was a highly debated proposal that aimed to increase corporate taxes and distribute the proceeds to all Oregon residents. The measure proposed a 3% tax on businesses with annual sales over $25 million, with the revenue being divided among residents, regardless of age or situation. The…
The post Oregon’s Measure 118: A business tax proposal that failed appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 11.8.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125854</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/inside-douglas-county-11-8-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-11-8-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T21:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans Roger Boucock and Lonnie Shields talk about their time in the military in this special interview ahead of Veterans Day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EVENTS TO HONOR VETERANS IN DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125852</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/events-to-honor-veterans-in-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=events-to-honor-veterans-in-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 11:00 a.m.  There are several events to honor veterans in Douglas County happening on Sunday and Monday. *Sunday at 3:00 p.m. the Umpqua Community College Concert Band and the Roseburg Concert Chorale will present a Veterans Day concert. It will include an afternoon of rousing patriotic favorites and exciting traditional selections. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE TWO – TIME, PLACE AND MANNER ENFORCEMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125850</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/roseburg-police-cite-two-time-place-and-manner-enforcement/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-two-time-place-and-manner-enforcement"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 10:40 a.m. Roseburg Police cited two people as officers conducted time, place and manner enforcement on Thursday. An RPD report said just after 11:15 a.m. a 41-year-old man was contacted while sleeping in a camp at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. At 4:45 p.m. officers contacted a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR OFFENSIVE LITTERING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125848</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-offensive-littering-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-offensive-littering-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for an offensive littering incident on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 10:25 p.m. officers contacted 42-year-old Ryan Flock drinking a beer next to a warming fire in the 400 block of Northeast Stephens Street. Flock was also found to be sitting in a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR PROBATION VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125846</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-probation-violation-6/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-probation-violation-6"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 10:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for a probation violation on Thursday. An RPD report said at 1:15 p.m. officers contacted the 50-year-old after he was called in for causing a disturbance near a business in the 900 block of West Harvard Avenue. Officers learned that the man was on parole...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR LITTERING, BURNING AND CAMPING CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125844</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-littering-burning-and-camping-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-littering-burning-and-camping-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for littering, burning, and camping charged on Thursday. An RPD report said at 10:30 a.m. 44-year-old Johnathon Shell was contacted at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. Shell reportedly had a bed and cardboard shelter set up in the pavilion next...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR UNLAWFUL POSSESSION OF METH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125842</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-unlawful-possession-of-meth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-unlawful-possession-of-meth"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for unlawful possession of methamphetamine on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 8:25 p.m. officers contacted the 64-year-old in the 1000 block of West Pilger Street after a caller said the man was causing a disturbance. The man agreed to go to the Sobering...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL FUGITIVE ON MULTIPLE CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125840</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/sutherlin-police-jail-fugitive-on-multiple-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-fugitive-on-multiple-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 9:40 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a fugitive on multiple charges Thursday night. An SPD report said at 9:00 p.m. 37-year-old Joshua Breeding was contacted during a traffic stop near the intersection of South Calapooia Street and Hastings Avenue. Breeding had multiple warrants for his arrest. There was also a no contact release...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YONCALLA MAN JAILED FOR DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125838</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/yoncalla-man-jailed-for-driving-while-suspended-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=yoncalla-man-jailed-for-driving-while-suspended-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 9;20 a.m. A Yoncalla man was jailed for driving while suspended Thursday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 8:30 p.m. a deputy observed a pickup heading northbound on Interstate 5 with a license plate that was almost unreadable. After running the plate, the deputy noticed that it was registered...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 11.8.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125835</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/local-real-estate-today-11-8-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-11-8-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group of Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our local real estate update live from the National Association of Realtor Conference in Boston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.8.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125828</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/morning-conversation-10-8-24-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-8-24-2"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ashley Cluver with an update on classes and other educational opportunities for adults and kids happening at Umpqua Valley Arts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forest Trust Land Advisory Committee meets virtually on Nov. 15]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176617</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176617"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Forest Trust Land Advisory Committee will meet virtually on Friday, Nov. 15 at 10 a.m. To join, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes:

Review of proposed forest modeling scenarios for draft Forest Management Plan

Public comment is scheduled at the beginning of the meeting. To submit written comment, email ftlac.comment@odf.oregon.gov. Written comments sent at least 48 hours before the meeting will give the FTLAC time to review and consider information. Comments submitted after that window of time will be sent to the FTLAC after the meeting, entered into the record and posted online. Comments are not accepted after the meeting concludes.
Accommodations for people with disabilities, and special materials, services, or assistance can be arranged by calling at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting at 503-945-7200 or by email at forestryinformation@odf.oregon.gov.
The Forest Trust Land Advisory Committee is comprised of seven county commissioners representing 15 Oregon counties where state forestlands are located. The FTLAC is a statutorily established committee that advises the Board of Forestry on matters related to forestland managed by ODF. View more information on the FTLAC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffenberry Middle School 2024 first quarter honor roll]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b108eb82-97c2-11ef-a9de-6377098e17a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/coffenberry-middle-school-2024-first-quarter-honor-roll/article_b108eb82-97c2-11ef-a9de-6377098e17a2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — Coffenberry Middle School released its honor roll for the first quarter of the 2024-25 year. Students named to the president's list had a 4.0 GPA, while high honors students had a GPA between 3.86-3.5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Constructing and caring for a terrarium]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bee09b18-9afd-11ef-a825-6bda5cc280f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/ask-a-master-gardener-constructing-and-caring-for-a-terrarium/article_bee09b18-9afd-11ef-a825-6bda5cc280f8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: Can you give me some tips for constructing a DIY terrarium? I would like to make one as a gift.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Rusch for The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library can help with alternative book forms; Reading is for everyone]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ef25446c-9b03-11ef-ab83-4fd9699708ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-public-library-can-help-with-alternative-book-forms-reading-is-for-everyone/article_ef25446c-9b03-11ef-ab83-4fd9699708ba.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library is here to support readers searching for alternative book formats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear John: Creating a lasting impact on people, community]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cea9950a-9c78-11ef-a88f-bba5b765d72f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/dear-john-creating-a-lasting-impact-on-people-community/article_cea9950a-9c78-11ef-a88f-bba5b765d72f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three years ago, this cowboy sauntered into my office and said he liked my pictures. And then he came back. Said he really liked my pictures. A lot. And then he came back. Said he liked my pictures and perhaps,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kellie Trenkle For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY HOMELESS YOUTH SOLUTIONS INITIATIVE FUNDRAISER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125826</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/douglas-county-homeless-youth-solutions-initiative-fundraiser/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-homeless-youth-solutions-initiative-fundraiser"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T15:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 7:30 a.m. Douglas County Homeless Youth Solutions Initiative plans to open a youth homelessness campus early next year. The campus, located on Northeast Douglas Avenue, will consist of three homes with three youth supporting organizations each using one of the homes to provide services. The groups are Peace at Home Advocacy Center,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DENSE FOG ADVISORY THROUGH 9:00 A.M. FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125822</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/dense-fog-advisory-through-900-a-m-friday-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dense-fog-advisory-through-900-a-m-friday-2"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T13:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 5:50 a.m. A Dense Fog Advisory is in effect through 9:00 a.m. Friday for central Douglas County. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford said visibility of one quarter of a mile or less is expected in dense fog. It applies across the Umpqua Valley. Forecasters said low visibility could make...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOUSE REPUBLICAN LEADER STATEMENT ON 2024 ELECTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125818</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/house-republican-leader-statement-on-2024-elections/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=house-republican-leader-statement-on-2024-elections"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8. 2024 3:50 a.m.  Oregon House Republican Leader Jeff Helfrich issued a statement Thursday night, following the 2024 election. Helfrich said, “The elections results send a clear message: voters want lawmakers who can work across the aisle while standing firm on fiscal issues. We look forward to partnering with our colleagues on both sides...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serving those who served]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a3b0b5e4-9bd9-11ef-b93f-a74d3a3f1282</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/serving-those-who-served/article_a3b0b5e4-9bd9-11ef-b93f-a74d3a3f1282.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Veterans Day our thoughts turn to those who served or continue to serve in our nation’s military. How we honor and care for these men and women says much about us as a society and as individuals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Coalwell for The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[College-level courses at Roseburg High School build paths to success]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c74a980a-9bdc-11ef-b0ad-0336e789892d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/college-level-courses-at-roseburg-high-school-build-paths-to-success/article_c74a980a-9bdc-11ef-b0ad-0336e789892d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg High School students understand the value of hard work. In the case of free, dual credit courses, students not only complete college-level work, they save money while preparing for high-wage, high-demand jobs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heather Villa For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PROPERTY TAXES DUE NOVEMBER 15TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125816</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/property-taxes-due-november-15th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=property-taxes-due-november-15th"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 3:40 a.m. Property Taxes in Douglas County are due next Friday, November 15th. A county release said property tax statements were mailed in late October. Property owners can receive a 3 percent discount and avoid interest and penalties by making payment in full by the due date. Second trimester taxes are due...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WREATH MAKING WORKSHOP HAPPENING NOVEMBER 21ST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125814</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/wreath-making-workshop-happening-november-21st/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wreath-making-workshop-happening-november-21st"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 3:30 a.m. Oregon State University Extension Service and the Women Owning Woodlands Network of Douglas County are inviting women woodland owners to a workshop where they can learn to make wreaths using greenery from local woodlands. An extension release said the Wreath Making with Non-Timber Forest Products workshop will be held on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE ARE INVESTIGATING A TWO-VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125812</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/roseburg-police-are-investigating-a-two-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-are-investigating-a-two-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 3:05 a.m. Roseburg Police are investigating a two-vehicle crash which took place Wednesday morning. An RPD report said at approximately 10:40 a.m. officers responded to the accident near the intersection of Southeast Pine Street and Southeast Mosher Avenue. Upon arrival, officers learned that a 66-year-old Sutherlin man was driving south on Pine...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125810</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/08/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-31/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-31"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 2:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged trespass incident on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 7:30 a.m. officers contacted the 40-year-old while he was walking on the railroad tracks near the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street. The man reportedly refused to get off the track after being...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125808</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-17/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-17"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T22:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 2024 2:30 p.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping on Wednesday night. An RPD report said at 10:30 p.m. officers contacted the 52-year-old who was camping next to the sidewalk in the 1700 block of Northeast Airport Road. The man’s tent was less than 80 feet from the sidewalk and was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE ARREST A WOMAN FOR DUII EARLY THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125806</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/roseburg-police-arrest-a-woman-for-duii-early-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-arrest-a-woman-for-duii-early-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T22:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 8, 20-24 2:20 p.m.  Roseburg Police arrested a woman for DUII early Thursday. An RPD report said at 3:30 a.m. officers observed a sedan being driven with no headlights and stopped the driver near the intersection of Northeast Vine Street and Northeast Oakland Avenue. Officers allegedly observed several indicators of impairment. The 21-year-old driver...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 11.7.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125797</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/inside-douglas-county-11-7-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-11-7-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Bailey and Joey Keeran were live at Aviva Health, for the Vets and Their Pets event:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLM looking for hosts in six park locations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1b6c058e-9d42-11ef-acc8-7bc06d66c8bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/life/blm-looking-for-hosts-in-six-park-locations/article_1b6c058e-9d42-11ef-acc8-7bc06d66c8bc.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bureau of Land Management recreation managers are looking for volunteers to fill host positions for the 2025 summer recreation season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FESTIVAL OF LIGHTS PREPARES FOR 32ND SEASON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125795</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/festival-of-lights-prepares-for-32nd-season/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=festival-of-lights-prepares-for-32nd-season"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 11:20 a.m.  The 32nd annual Umpqua Valley Festival of Lights, organized by the Roseburg Rotary Club, will launch on November 24th, showcasing over 500,000 lights and 90 displays at River Forks Park. Event Chair Tabitha Layman said visitors will be excited by the return of the Dutch Bros Holliday Village to River...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PIANIST THOMAS OTTEN PERFORMS WITH UCC MUSIC GROUPS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125793</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/pianist-thomas-otten-performs-with-ucc-music-groups/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pianist-thomas-otten-performs-with-ucc-music-groups"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 11:00 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Umpqua Community College Fine and Performing Arts Department presents the Umpqua Chamber Orchestra and UCC Chamber Choir under the direction of Dr. Jason Heald, in concert on November 12th at 7:00 p.m. at the Whipple Fine Arts Center on the UCC campus. The concert...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESIDENTIAL LEAF PICKUPS CONTINUE IN ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125791</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/residential-leaf-pickups-continue-in-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=residential-leaf-pickups-continue-in-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 10:40 a.m.  Roseburg Public Works is offering leaf collection service to homeowners through January 3rd. Public Works crews follow a cyclical, systematic route to help residents with leaf disposal and to ensure leaf collection is provided in an effective cost-controlled program that helps keep leaves out of storm drains, creeks and rivers....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FISHERY ENHANCEMENT DERBY AND DTO ANNOUNCE 33RD ANNUAL EVENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125789</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/fishery-enhancement-derby-and-dto-announce-33rd-annual-event/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fishery-enhancement-derby-and-dto-announce-33rd-annual-event"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 10:20 a.m.   The Umpqua Fishery Enhancement Derby and the Douglas Timber Operators have announced that the 33rd annual event is set for January 29th through February 1st, 2025. A release said the Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Tribe of Indians will be the presenting sponsor. Derby events include: *Wednesday, January 29th is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONGRESSMAN BENTZ RESPONDS TO BEING RE-ELECTED TO A THIRD TERM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125787</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/congressman-bentz-responds-to-being-re-elected-to-a-third-term/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=congressman-bentz-responds-to-being-re-elected-to-a-third-term"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 10:05 a.m.  On Election Day, Congressman Cliff Bentz won his third term in Congress. A campaign release said Bentz was victorious in the race for the 2nd District seat, defeating Democrat candidate Dan Ruby. :Bentz said, “Having the opportunity again to represent the people of Oregon’s Second Congressional District is one of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MONIQUE DESPAIN RESPONDS TO DISTRICT 4 ELECTION RETURNS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125785</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/monique-despain-responds-to-district-4-election-returns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=monique-despain-responds-to-district-4-election-returns"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 9:40 a.m.  Oregon Fourth Congressional District Republican candidate Monique DeSpain has commented on the election returns for her race. DeSpain said, “Every vote counts, but not all District 4 votes have been received or counted. DeSpain said, “The turnout numbers so far show that out of the roughly 520,000 eligible registered voters,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLM SEEKS VOLUNTEER HOSTS FOR 2025 NW OREGON RECREATION SEAASON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125783</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/blm-seeks-volunteer-hosts-for-2025-nw-oregon-recreation-seaason/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=blm-seeks-volunteer-hosts-for-2025-nw-oregon-recreation-seaason"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 9;20 a.m.  Bureau of Land Management recreation managers are looking for enthusiastic volunteers to fill host positions at six unique locations for the 2025 summer recreation season. A BLM release said volunteer hosts play a critical role at BLM recreation sites. They are the primary, daily connection between public land users and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 11.7.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125777</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/morning-conversation-11-7-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-11-7-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library Director Kris Wiley talks about the exhibition on the Holocaust which opens Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin football coach continues coaching, despite DUII]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/55a507fe-9cb7-11ef-ab3e-2b91064595ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/sutherlin-football-coach-continues-coaching-despite-duii/article_55a507fe-9cb7-11ef-ab3e-2b91064595ac.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — A formal complaint has been filed with the Sutherlin School District regarding the behavior of Bret Prock, Sutherlin High School dean of students and varsity football head coach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMART reading needs volunteers across Douglas County]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/07be7642-9afa-11ef-8592-1349aea9e8c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/smart-reading-needs-volunteers-across-douglas-county/article_07be7642-9afa-11ef-8592-1349aea9e8c6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SMART Reading is a nonprofit organization that aims to help Oregon children reach benchmarks through reading with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Courthouse illuminates green for Project Greenlight]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/5cf0d34c-9962-11ef-b7a0-8b4b5c4b3b80</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/douglas-county-courthouse-illuminates-green-for-project-greenlight/article_5cf0d34c-9962-11ef-b7a0-8b4b5c4b3b80.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas County Courthouse will be illuminated with green light throughout the month of November in solidarity of veterans and their families after Douglas County Commissioners issued a proclamation encouraging county residents to honor those who served.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DENSE FOG ADVISORY THROUGH 8:00 A.M. THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125771</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/dense-fog-advisory-through-800-a-m-thursday-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dense-fog-advisory-through-800-a-m-thursday-2"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T12:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 4:10 a.m. A Dense Fog Advisory is in effect for central Douglas County through 8:00 a.m. Thursday morning. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford said visibility of one quarter mile or less is expected in dense fog across the Umpqua Valley. Low visibility could make driving conditions hazardous. Drivers should...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STATE POLICE RESPOND TO TWO FATAL CRASHES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125769</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/state-police-respond-to-two-fatal-crashes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=state-police-respond-to-two-fatal-crashes"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 3:50 a.m.  Troopers with Oregon State Police dealt with two fatal accidents which took place earlier this week in Douglas County. An OSP report said Monday at approximately 10:40 a.m. troopers responded to a single vehicle crash on Highway 38, about two miles west of Drain. A preliminary investigation indicated that an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY GOVERNMENT MONDAY CLOSURE ANNOUNCEMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125766</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/county-government-monday-closure-announcement/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-government-monday-closure-announcement"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 3:40 a.m.  The Douglas County Board of Commissioners would like to remind residents that most county offices will be closed on Monday for Veterans Day. A county release said that includes offices at the courthouse, Justice Building, fairgrounds, landfill and transfer sites and all external county government offices. The Douglas County Museum of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[41ST ANNUAL DOUGLAS COUNTY TREE LIGHTING CEREMONY DECEMBER 1ST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125762</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/41st-annual-douglas-county-tree-lighting-ceremony-december-1st/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=41st-annual-douglas-county-tree-lighting-ceremony-december-1st"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 3:20 a.m. Douglas County Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman and Tom Kress are excited to officially kick off the Christmas Season with the lighting of the 41st annual Douglas County Christmas Tree on Sunday, December 1st at 6:00 p.m. on the front lawn of the courthouse. A county release on that evening,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHRISTMAS TREE PERMITS AVAILABLE BEGINNING NOVEMBER 12TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125760</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/christmas-tree-permits-available-beginning-november-12th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=christmas-tree-permits-available-beginning-november-12th"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 3:05 a.m. Christmas Tree permits for cutting trees from Bureau of Land Management-administered lands will be available from the BLM’S Roseburg District beginning November 12th at this link: https://forestproducts.blm.gov/customer/permitselect/OR Public Affairs Specialist Greg Deimel said in addition, those interested in getting a Christmas tree permit in person can purchase a permit starting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TICKETS GOING FAST FOR ALEXANDER STRING QUARTET CONCERT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125755</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/tickets-going-fast-for-alexander-string-quartet-concert/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tickets-going-fast-for-alexander-string-quartet-concert"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 7, 2024 2:50 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Tickets are going fast for the Alexander String Quartet in concert Sunday November 17th at 3:00 p.m. at The Chapel, located at 2837 West Harvard Avenue in Roseburg. Presented by the Umpqua Symphony Association, the quartet will perform their arrangement of music from Mozart, Beethoven...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIKE WINTERS LAWN AND GARDEN SHOW 11.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125752</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/07/mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-11-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-11-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T01:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County’s Commissioner of Dirt, Mike Winters, has our weekly local lawn and garden program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zonta Dignity Drive continues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cc78e5ae-9c93-11ef-b86d-2bc19d217e9b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/zonta-dignity-drive-continues/article_cc78e5ae-9c93-11ef-b86d-2bc19d217e9b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T23:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Zonta Club of Roseburg is continuing its ninth annual Dignity Drive through Nov. 22.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 11.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125746</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/inside-douglas-county-11-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-11-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T21:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Urban Sanitary Authority General Manager Jim Baird talks about its work to implement a transformative energy program, through grants and loans it has received.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC hosts Nov. 16 performance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/62f9a7f8-9c7a-11ef-9b23-db5b09c86249</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/ucc-hosts-nov-16-performance/article_62f9a7f8-9c7a-11ef-9b23-db5b09c86249.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Umpqua Community College fine and performing arts department presents the Umpqua Singers and Kirby Shaw Singers at 7 p.m. Nov. 16 at the Whipple Fine Arts Center on the UCC campus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RHS performs play in December]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f3fcfb94-9c78-11ef-a3e6-3f096b834d0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/rhs-performs-play-in-december/article_f3fcfb94-9c78-11ef-a3e6-3f096b834d0d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Roseburg High School Theater Department presents “Something Like a Christmas Carol” on stage in December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON CITY COUNCIL DECLARES VACANCY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125744</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/winston-city-council-declares-vacancy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-city-council-declares-vacancy"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 11:05 a.m.  On Monday at their regular meeting, the Winston City Council declared a vacancy for a Ward II seat on the council. City Manager Thomas McIntosh said the seat was formerly occupied by Alesha Anderson, who will be moving out of the area. Her term expires at the end of 2026....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZONTA DIGNITY DRIVE CONTINUES THROUGH NOVEMBER 22ND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125742</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/zonta-dignity-drive-continues-through-november-22nd/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=zonta-dignity-drive-continues-through-november-22nd"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2022 10:50 a.m.  The Zonta Club of Roseburg is continuing its 9th annual Dignity Drive through November 22nd. The organization collects undergarments and sanitary products for victims of abuse. A Zonta Club release said abuse victims are often forced to flee their home with little more than the clothing they are wearing. Residents...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LIBRARY HOSTING “AMERICANS AND THE HOLOCAUST EXHIBITION STARTING THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125738</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/library-hosting-americans-and-the-holocaus-exhibiton-starting-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=library-hosting-americans-and-the-holocaus-exhibiton-starting-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Public Library is hosting the “Americans and the Holocaust: A Traveling Exhibition for Libraries” beginning Thursday. A city release said the exhibition is from the United States Holocaust Memorial Museum and the American Library Association. It presents stories of individual Americans, some of whom took actions that went against...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR FELONY FAILURE TO APPEAR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125736</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-felony-failure-to-appear-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-felony-failure-to-appear-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a felony failure to appear warrant on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 5:50 p.m. officers contacted the 38-year-old in the 2100 block of Northeast Stephens Street, knowing he had the warrant. The man was taken into custody without incident. Bail was set at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR FELONY WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125729</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-felony-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-felony-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a felony warrant on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 3:30 p.m. officers responded to the 1800 block of Northeast Klamath Avenue after an anonymous person called to say that the 32-year-old was at that location. Officers contacted the woman and took her into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING REPORTED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125725</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-trespass-incident-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-trespass-incident-3"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man following a reported trespass incident on Tuesday night. An RPD report said at 11:25 p.m. the 31-year-old allegedly attempted to get into several vehicles in the driveway of a residence in the 200 block of Southeast Rifle Range Street. The suspect was detained by an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRIVER APPARENTLY FALLS ASLEEP, LEADING TO A VEHICLE STRIKING POWER POLE TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125721</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/driver-apparently-falls-asleep-leading-to-a-vehicle-striking-power-pole-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=driver-apparently-falls-asleep-leading-to-a-vehicle-striking-power-pole-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 9:20 a.m. A driver apparently fell asleep, leading to his pickup striking a power pole on Tuesday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 1:00 p.m. the 50-year-old from Roseburg was traveling westbound on Garden Valley Road near Fisher Road when the accident took place. The vehicle drifted off the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 11.6.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125716</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/morning-conversation-11-6-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-11-6-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aviva Health’s Shawn Hopher talks about their Vets and Their Pets event happening on Thursday on the non-profit campus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City, county offices closed Monday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/303600a2-9c5a-11ef-9e5e-0391d8290b6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/city-county-offices-closed-monday/article_303600a2-9c5a-11ef-9e5e-0391d8290b6d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — City and county offices will be closed Monday, Nov. 11, in observance of Veterans Day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tourism grant cycle opens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b6acdcec-9c59-11ef-ae5b-fbb01ce7f6ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/tourism-grant-cycle-opens/article_b6acdcec-9c59-11ef-ae5b-fbb01ce7f6ed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Roseburg Community Development Department is accepting applications for fall 2024 tourism grants until Dec. 31.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY RACES AND MEASURES: RESULTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125710</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/douglas-county-races-and-measures-results/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-races-and-measures-results"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T12:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 4: 20 a.m.  While many races were uncontested locally, there is still plenty to report. In Unofficial General Election Results from the Douglas County Clerk’s Office as of 3:45 a.m. Wednesday: Douglas County Clerk Daniel Loomis beat challenger Samantha Frost 63 percent to 37 percent. In Roseburg, Ward 1 Position 2 city...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGONIANS SAY NO TO 3 OF 5 STATEWIDE BALLOT MEASURES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125708</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/oregonians-say-no-to-3-of-5-statewide-ballot-measures/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregonians-say-no-to-3-of-5-statewide-ballot-measures"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T11:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2025 3:55 a.m.  Oregon voters said no to 3 of 5 statewide ballot measures on Tuesday. In Unofficial General Election Results from the Oregon Secretary of State’s Office as of 3:00 a.m. Wednesday: Voters passed Measure 115 which amends the state constitution to authorize impeachment of statewide elected officials by the Oregon Legislature...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEMOCRATS RETAIN HOLD ON STATEWIDE OFFICES IN OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125706</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/democrats-retain-hold-on-statewide-offices-in-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=democrats-retain-hold-on-statewide-offices-in-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T11:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 3:45 a.m.  Democrats retained their hold on statewide offices in Oregon, according to results from the Oregon Secretary of State’s Office as of 3:00 a.m. Wednesday: Tobias Read was elected Oregon Secretary of State, beating Dennis Linthicum 54 percent to 43 percent. Linthicum won in Douglas County, getting 67 percent of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY RACES FOR STATE SENATE, STATE HOUSE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125704</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/county-races-for-state-senate-state-house/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-races-for-state-senate-state-house"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T11:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 3:30 a.m.  Looking at races for seats in the Oregon State Legislature, according to results from the Oregon Secretary of State’s Office as of 3:00 a.m. Wednesday: State Senator David Brock Smith was re-elected to his District 1 seat, beating Democratic challenger Lupe Preciado-McAlister 70 percent to 30 percent. In Douglas County,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOYLE, BENTZ RETAIN THEIR CONGRESSIONAL SEATS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125702</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/hoyle-bentz-retain-their-congressional-seats/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hoyle-bentz-retain-their-congressional-seats"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T11:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 3:15 a.m.  Oregon’s two members of Congress that represent parts of Douglas County have retained their seats. Unofficial General Election results from the Oregon Secretary of State’s Office as of 3:00 a.m. Wednesday show 4th District Congresswoman Val Hoyle beating Republican Monique DeSpain 53 percent to 44 percent. In Douglas County voting,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INDUSTRIAL SLASH BURNING MAY INCREASE IN DOUGLAS DISTRICT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125700</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/industrial-slash-burning-may-increase-in-douglas-district/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=industrial-slash-burning-may-increase-in-douglas-district"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T11:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 3:05 a.m. A persistent weather pattern of cooler temperatures and consistent rain has prompted a decrease in restrictions for industrial slash-burning on lands protected by the Douglas Forest Protective Association, effective on Monday. As a result, industrial slash burning may increase through the Douglas District. A DFPA release said these restrictions are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY OF ROSEBURG TO CLOSE OFFICES MONDAY FOR VETERANS DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125698</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/city-of-roseburg-to-close-offices-monday-for-veterans-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-of-roseburg-to-close-offices-monday-for-veterans-day"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 6, 2024 2:50 a.m. City of Roseburg Buildings will be closed on Monday, November 11th, in observance of Veterans Day. A city release said that means that Roseburg City Hall, the Public Safety Center, Roseburg Public Library and other city buildings will be closed to the public. The city council meeting that would normally...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voters overwhelmingly approve Tenmile tax levy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a66010e4-9bbd-11ef-9a49-4b6ac206f62a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/voters-overwhelmingly-approve-tenmile-tax-levy/article_a66010e4-9bbd-11ef-9a49-4b6ac206f62a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TENMILE — A tax levy assessed to Tenmile homeowners paying the salary of the local fire chief and other costs will extend another five years, following Tuesday’s election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin residents continue psilocybin ban]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/87b39282-9bbe-11ef-a539-0ffe1a9f1864</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/sutherlin-residents-continue-psilocybin-ban/article_87b39282-9bbe-11ef-a539-0ffe1a9f1864.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Psilocybin will continue to be banned in Sutherlin following a vote in Tuesday’s election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canyonville library offers STEAM Hub]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3ad6b8e8-9be8-11ef-b152-7338590cf7eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/canyonville-library-offers-steam-hub/article_3ad6b8e8-9be8-11ef-b152-7338590cf7eb.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T02:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE — The Canyonville Community Library received state-of-the-art robotics and coding equipment from the Umpqua Valley STEAM Hub.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canyonville library offers STEAM Hub robotic enhancement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3ad6b8e8-9be8-11ef-b152-7338590cf7eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/canyonville-library-offers-steam-hub-robotic-enhancement/article_3ad6b8e8-9be8-11ef-b152-7338590cf7eb.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T02:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE — The Canyonville Community Library announced an new enhancement to its educational programming, made possible by an Umpqua Valley STEAM Hub donation. The donation includes state-of-the-art robotics and coding equipment providing learning experiences for children and families in our…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GENERAL ELECTION COVERAGE 11.5.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125695</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/general-election-coverage-11-5-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=general-election-coverage-11-5-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T01:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 5:30 p.m. Listen to national coverage until 10:00 p.m. on News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN.  Check for local information after 8:00 p.m. on our site listed above.  Complete information on The Morning Report Wednesday, starting at 7:00 a.m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 11.5.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125692</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/06/true-wealth-11-5-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-11-5-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T01:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littlejohn Financial, David Littlejohn and Matt Dickson have our weekly local financial program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FALL TOURISM GRANT CYCLE OPENS IN ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125689</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/fall-tourism-grant-cycle-opens-in-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fall-tourism-grant-cycle-opens-in-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T23:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 3:10 p.m.  The Roseburg Community Development Department is accepting applications for fall 2024 tourism grants until December 31st A city release said successful applicants may win grants of up to $7,500 or even more, to help draw visitors to Roseburg and the surrounding areas. Last April, the city council authorized the Economic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVIVA HEALTH VETS AND THEIR PETS EVENT IS THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125687</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/aviva-health-vets-and-their-pets-event-is-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=aviva-health-vets-and-their-pets-event-is-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T23:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 3:00 p.m.   Aviva Health is hosting its third annual Vets and Their Pets Veteran’s Day celebration will be Thursday from 11:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. on the non-profit campus on Northeast Kenneth Ford Drive, just north of Roseburg. The event honors U.S. Armed Forces veterans with a complimentary lunch prepared by Aviva...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 11.5.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125684</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/inside-douglas-county-11-5-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-11-5-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas Forest Protective Association Public Information Officer Rachel Pope talks about Fire Season data and current information residents should be aware of.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leading With Your Best Efforts]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8486</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/leading-with-your-best-efforts/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T20:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a divergence from what an individual business might need or an area to develop, rather it focuses on us – who we are, where we may be going, and why we should consider going there. From an economic development perspective, countless people in all kinds of different climates, economic conditions and resource…
The post Leading With Your Best Efforts appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE TWO PEOPLE FOR OVERNIGHT DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125682</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/roseburg-police-cite-two-people-for-overnight-drinking-in-public/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-two-people-for-overnight-drinking-in-public"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T18:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5. 2024 10:30 a.m. Roseburg Police cited two people for overnight drinking in public incidents early Tuesday. An RPD report said at 2:50 a.m. officers contacted a 70-year-old man in the 900 block of Northeast Rowe Avenue after officers saw multiple empty beer cans and whiskey bottles around him. The man was allegedly highly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR CAMPING IN BUSINESS ENTRYWAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125680</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-camping-in-business-entryway/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-camping-in-business-entryway"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T18:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 10:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping early Tuesday. An RPD report said shortly after 2:30 a.m. the 56-year-old was contacted in the 800 block of Northeast Winchester Street. His camp was set up in the entryway of a closed business and was in violation of time, place and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING AT DUCK POND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125678</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-at-duck-pond/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-at-duck-pond"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T18:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping on Monday afternoon. An RPD report said at 3;00 p.m. the 43-year-old was contacted at his camp at the duck pond in the 1000 block of Northeast Garden Valley Boulevard. The camp consisted of a tarp/tent structure in the brush at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE TWO WOMEN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125676</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/roseburg-police-cite-two-women-for-prohibited-camping-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-two-women-for-prohibited-camping-2"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited two women for prohibited camping Monday morning. An RPD report said at 8:20 a.m. officers contacted a 45-year-old at her camp near the riverbank in the 100 block of Southeast Templin Avenue. Her camp consisted of a small tent and a large wagon filled with various personal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO VEHICLE ACCIDENT DURING AFTERNOON RUSH HOUR MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125674</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/two-vehicle-accident-during-afternoon-rush-hour-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-vehicle-accident-during-afternoon-rush-hour-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 9:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police dealt with a two-vehicle crash during the afternoon rush hour on Monday. An RPD report said at 5:20 p.m. officers responded to the accident at the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and Northwest Edenbower Boulevard. Officers learned that a 50-year-old woman drove her vehicle into the back of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PRIOR SEXUAL HARASSMENT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125672</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prior-sexual-harassment-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prior-sexual-harassment-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man Monday for a prior sexual harassment incident. An RPD report said on October 19th, the 50-year-old allegedly harassed a female by placing his mouth on an intimate part of her body at a public event, without her consent. Monday at 1:00 p.m. the man turned...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOLLOWING ALLEGED CRIMINAL TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125670</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/roseburg-police-jail-woman-following-alleged-criminal-trespass-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-following-alleged-criminal-trespass-2"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman following an alleged criminal trespass incident on Monday. An RPD report said at 1:40 p.m. officers contacted the 51-year-old in the 100 block of Northeast Northpark Avenue, after she refused to leave the residence. During the contact, the woman reportedly walked out of the home...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 11.5.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125664</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/morning-conversation-11-5-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-11-5-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:18:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Clerk Daniel Loomis talks about the process of counting ballots, and has reminders for last minute voters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OVER 58 PERCENT OF COUNTY BALLOTS HAVE BEEN RECEIVED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125658</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/over-58-percent-of-county-ballots-have-been-received/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=over-58-percent-of-county-ballots-have-been-received"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T11:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 4:00 a.m. Over 58 percent of county ballots have been received for the 2024 Douglas County November Presidential General Election, as of Monday evening. County Clerk Daniel Loomis said 52,499 ballots have been turned in. Loomis said that lags 13.09 percent behind the participation rate for the same point in the previous...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RHS TAKES 10TH PLACE IN BAND COMPETITION AT AUTZEN STADIUM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125656</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/rhs-takes-10th-place-in-band-competition-at-autzen-stadium/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rhs-takes-10th-place-in-band-competition-at-autzen-stadium"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T11:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 3;50 a.m. The Roseburg High School Marching Ensemble competed in the annual Festival of Bands at Autzen Stadium in Eugene on Saturday, taking 10th place overall. A release from the band program said the site served as one of two marching band championship sites for the region. Split across two stadiums, RHS...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAFE HAVEN MATERNITY HOME RECEIVES DONATION FROM UMPQUA DAIRY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125645</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/05/safe-haven-maternity-home-receives-donation-from-umpqua-dairy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=safe-haven-maternity-home-receives-donation-from-umpqua-dairy"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T11:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 5, 2024 3:40 a.m.  Safe Haven Maternity Home has announced that it has received a generous donation from Umpqua Dairy. A Safe Haven release said the donation will significantly support the mission of the non-profit to provide a safe home environment and aftercare services to pregnant women and mothers of young children in crisis....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>