<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.roseburgscanner.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T19:10:00.341Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.roseburgscanner.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.roseburgscanner.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southern Oregon Regional Economic Development, Inc. (SOREDI) Names Blair Sundell as New Executive Director]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9018</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/southern-oregon-regional-economic-development-inc-soredi-names-blair-sundell-as-new-executive-director/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T02:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Medford, Oregon – August 28, 2025 – The Board of Directors for Southern Oregon Regional Economic Development, Inc. (SOREDI) is pleased to announce the appointment of Blair Sundell as its new Executive Director. Sundell will assume the role on September 1, 2025, and brings with him a wealth of experience in economic development, strategic planning,…
The post Southern Oregon Regional Economic Development, Inc. (SOREDI) Names Blair Sundell as New Executive Director appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rogue Valley Travel Impacts 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9010</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/rogue-valley-travel-impacts-2024/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T01:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preliminary data for 2024 from a Dean Runyan Associates study for the Oregon Tourism Commission shows that total direct travel spending in Oregon rose 1.1% in 2024 compared with the 2023 total. Travel spending rose from $14.15 billion in 2023 to $14.3 billion in 2024, an inflation-adjusted increase of 1.0%. Adjusted for inflation, Oregon’s total…
The post Rogue Valley Travel Impacts 2024 appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Building Permits Drop in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9005</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/douglas-county-building-permits-drop-in-2024-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T01:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building permit data from the U.S. Census Bureau shows that new housing construction in Douglas County as measured by permits for living units dropped to 190 units in 2024 from 246 in 2023. It was the lowest level since 2015 when there were 172 building permits for living units. Building permits in Douglas County peaked…
The post Douglas County Building Permits Drop in 2024 appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Snapshot of Oregon Firms by Size Class, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8996</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/a-snapshot-of-oregon-firms-by-size-class-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T01:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first quarter of 2025, Oregon had just over 155,000 private firms that were subject to paying unemployment insurance taxes. Over 108,000 of these firms had at least one payroll employee in March.  More than 19 out of 20 firms (96%) with workers on their payrolls had less than 50 employees. While that left…
The post A Snapshot of Oregon Firms by Size Class, 2025 appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Business Oregon and Oregon InC Award $3.7 Million to Support Oregon Innovators]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8981</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/business-oregon-and-oregon-inc-award-3-7-million-to-support-oregon-innovators/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T01:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grant funding was awarded to eight Regional Innovation Hubs to support Oregon’s innovation-based entrepreneurs. AUGUST 12, 2025 Business Oregon and the Oregon Innovation Council (Oregon InC) are pleased to announce the intent to award 2025-2027 Regional Innovation Hub grants. Regional Innovation Hubs provide technical assistance, access to capital, networking, mentorship and talent development to innovation-based…
The post Business Oregon and Oregon InC Award $3.7 Million to Support Oregon Innovators appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Business Oregon Funds Unique Solution to Oregon’s Wine Bottle Shortage]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8978</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/business-oregon-funds-unique-solution-to-oregons-wine-bottle-shortage/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T01:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AUGUST 29, 2025 Revino Inc.’s new bottle-washing facility in the Portland metro area will bring washable, reusable, American-made glass wine bottles to the market.  Oregon’s wine industry generates $8 billion worth of economic activity in the state, employing more than 40,000 people, and it is increasingly constrained by an unreliable supply chain for glass bottles.…
The post Business Oregon Funds Unique Solution to Oregon’s Wine Bottle Shortage appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creative Industries project gains legislative funding]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8975</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/creative-industries-project-gains-legislative-funding/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T01:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southern Oregon University is celebrating a piece of its future by acknowledging the Oregon Legislature’s recent approval of $40 million in capital construction bonds to update and consolidate SOU’s facilities for creative industries – music, media and film. The cross-disciplinary project will transform the university’s programs and help secure Oregon’s future as a national leader…
The post Creative Industries project gains legislative funding appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Concise Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8966</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/a-concise-communication/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T01:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One very important area of business success to highlight is communication. Great communication is avalue-driver and a success measure. It follows that having an efficient and concise communication abilityis fundamental to the success of any business. We are bombarded with messaging from multiple sources on a constant basis, so our filters aredeveloped to screen out…
The post A Concise Communication appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defining Your Operating Horizon]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8964</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/defining-your-operating-horizon/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T01:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being in business for yourself is one of the most important and difficult endeavors a person cantake on, especially in rural areas. It is with the utmost respect we have for the individuals whotake on the challenge of being in business that the talented people who work at the SOU SmallBusiness Development Center provide our…
The post Defining Your Operating Horizon appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENT JAILED FOR ONGOING DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137493</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/30/transient-jailed-for-ongoing-disorderly-conduct/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transient-jailed-for-ongoing-disorderly-conduct"/>
        <updated>2025-08-30T20:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2025 1:00 p.m.  Covering coastal Douglas County: A Coos County area transient was jailed by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office on Friday. A DCSO report said for several days 30-year-old Jordan Edwards had been acting disorderly throughout the Reedsport and Winchester Bay areas. Thursday night he showed up again at a residence in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE MAN JAILED FOR REPORTED ASSAULT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137491</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/30/riddle-man-jailed-for-reported-assault-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riddle-man-jailed-for-reported-assault-incident"/>
        <updated>2025-08-30T18:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2025 11:10 a.m.   A Riddle man was jailed for a reported assault incident on Friday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 4:00 p.m. a victim claimed that an unknown man followed him home and then punched him in the face, causing physical injury and substantial pain. This allegedly took...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES JAIL MAN FOR STRANGULATION/ASSAULT CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137489</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/30/deputies-jail-man-for-strangulation-assault-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-jail-man-for-strangulation-assault-charges"/>
        <updated>2025-08-30T17:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2025 11:00 a.m. Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a man following an overnight disturbance early Saturday. A DCSO report said at 3:45 a.m. a victim messaged a friend requesting assistance in the 1000 block of Byron Creek Road in the Olalla area. The friend then notified dispatch of the information...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUGAR LOAF FIRE HOLDING AT 53 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137487</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/30/sugar-loaf-fire-holding-at-53-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sugar-loaf-fire-holding-at-53-acres"/>
        <updated>2025-08-30T17:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2025 10:30 a.m.  The Sugar Loaf Fire in the Cottage Grove Ranger District of the Umpqua National Forest is holding at 53 acres as of midday Saturday. An update from Northwest Incident Management Team 13 said crews have completed 100 percent of hand and dozer line. Firefighters are now installing plumbing, which consists...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHERIFF HANLIN JOINS 33 OTHER OREGON SHERIFF’S SEEKING CLARIFICATION ON ICE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137483</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/30/sheriff-hanlin-joins-33-other-oregon-sheriffs-seeking-clarification-on-ice/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sheriff-hanlin-joins-33-other-oregon-sheriffs-seeking-clarification-on-ice"/>
        <updated>2025-08-30T14:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 30, 2025 7:30 a.m.  Douglas County Sheriff John Hanlin has joined 33 other Oregon Sheriff’s in signing a letter asking for legal clarity on U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement immigration subpoenas. Wednesday’s letter went to Marion County’s legal counsel, Oregon Attorney General Dan Rayfield and United States Attorney General Pam Bondi. A release from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPTD ANNOUNCES TEMPORARY SERVICE REDUCTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137477</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/30/uptd-announces-temporary-service-reductions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uptd-announces-temporary-service-reductions"/>
        <updated>2025-08-30T14:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(photo credit: Patrick Moore) August 30, 2025 7:00 a.m.  On Friday, the Umpqua Public Transportation District announced that it will be reducing services beginning September 15th, following significant delays in both federal and state funding allocations. UPTD Chief Operations Officer George Carrillo said, “These reductions were not a choice but a necessity”. Carrillo said, “This...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOU Digital Cinema named to national Top 30]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=8971</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/sou-digital-cinema-named-to-national-top-30/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-30T01:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Ashland, Ore.) — Southern Oregon University’s Digital Cinema program has been ranked among the nation’s Top 30 film schools by MovieMaker Magazine for the second consecutive year – a recognition of SOU’s role in preparing Oregon’s next generation of creative professionals. MovieMaker cited SOU Digital Cinema’s distinctive blend of hands-on training, industry partnerships and cross-disciplinary collaboration. The program emphasizes…
The post SOU Digital Cinema named to national Top 30 appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Public Transportation District announces temporary service reductions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/055c89d1-40c6-4d73-8e97-1b400d8ee40a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/umpqua-public-transportation-district-announces-temporary-service-reductions/article_055c89d1-40c6-4d73-8e97-1b400d8ee40a.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T21:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — According to a press release from Umpqua Public Transportation District (UPTD), transportation service reductions will start Sept. 15 across five bus lines. The UPTD Board of Directors voted to implement the changes on Aug. 27.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sugar Loaf Fire has slight growth]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0136516f-dd3b-4b69-ada6-ceb77ebc2b7b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/sugar-loaf-fire-has-slight-growth/article_0136516f-dd3b-4b69-ada6-ceb77ebc2b7b.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T20:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST — The Sugar Loaf Fire in the Cottage Grove Ranger District of the Umpqua National Forest has grown slightly to 53 acres, as of midday Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 8.29.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137472</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/inside-douglas-county-8-29-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-8-29-25"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T20:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ali Shaver talks about events happening and Wildlife Safari, and John Dimof of Thrive Umpqua covers summer and fall activities they have going on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUGAR LOAF FIRE HAS SLIGHT GROWTH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137469</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/sugar-loaf-fire-has-slight-growth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sugar-loaf-fire-has-slight-growth"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T18:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 11:00 a.m.  The Sugar Loaf Fire in the Cottage Grove Ranger District of the Umpqua National Forest has grown slightly to 53 acres, as of midday on Friday. An update from Northwest Incident Management Team 13 said the growth is taking place primarily on the north and south corners of the fire....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137467</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-driving-while-suspended-19/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-driving-while-suspended-19"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T17:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 10:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for driving while suspended on Thursday. An RPD report said at 7:15 p.m. officers stopped the 62-year-old in his vehicle near the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and Northeast Housely Avenue, knowing his license was revoked. Dispatch confirmed his status, and he was cited in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR OFFENSIVE LITTERING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137464</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-offensive-littering-6/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-offensive-littering-6"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T17:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a woman for offensive littering on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 7:00 p.m. officers contacted the 49-year-old in front of city hall in the 900 block of Southeast Douglas Avenue. She had allegedly thrown a large amount of trash all over the sidewalk. The woman...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL TWO PEOPLE FOR WARRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137462</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/roseburg-police-jail-two-people-for-warrants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-two-people-for-warrants"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T17:23:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 10:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed two people for warrants early Friday. An RPD report said at 1:05 a.m. the 41-year-old woman and 53-year-old man at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. Both were found to have warrants for their arrest and were taken into custody without incident. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR WARRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137460</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-warrants-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-warrants-4"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T17:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for warrants early Friday. An RPD report said at 1:00 a.m. officers contacted the 34-year-old at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. She was found to have the warrant with multiple charges and was taken into custody without incident. Bail was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR RESTRAINING ORDER VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137458</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-restraining-order-violation-16/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-restraining-order-violation-16"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T17:05:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a restraining order violation on Thursday. An RPD report said at 5:10 p.m. a victim called and claimed the 68-year-old was at her house in the 1700 block of Southeast Starmer Street, in violation of a restraining order. Dispatch confirmed a valid restraining order,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT, UNLAWFUL POSSESSION OF METHAMPHETAMINE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137456</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-unlawful-possession-of-methamphetamine-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-unlawful-possession-of-methamphetamine-2"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant, and unlawful possession of drugs, on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report said at 4:40 p.m. officers contacted the 46-year-old in the parking lot of a business in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street. He was found to have a valid felony...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observatory closed, staff still available for programs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fba9a678-e812-41e4-b197-cd2838a5ab27</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/life/observatory-closed-staff-still-available-for-programs/article_fba9a678-e812-41e4-b197-cd2838a5ab27.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mars slips into the evening twilight as Saturn and Neptune rise. Mars makes a slow steady descent and disappears into the tree tops by Sept. 21.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PAUL MORGAN For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Library focuses on children’s books]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/55c357ae-96b0-47b0-bc71-4cecaf12221a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/library-focuses-on-children-s-books/article_55c357ae-96b0-47b0-bc71-4cecaf12221a.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library patrons love their children’s books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOLLOWING REPORTED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137454</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/roseburg-police-jail-woman-following-reported-trespass-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-following-reported-trespass-incident"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 9:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman following a reported trespass incident on Thursday. An RPD report said at 6:00 p.m. officers contacted the 54-year-old after she returned to Fred Meyer in the 900 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. The woman had been trespassed by officers less than an hour prior....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A native treasure to add to your garden]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1c712e4f-b823-4c2a-b24d-254639a4db50</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/life/a-native-treasure-to-add-to-your-garden/article_1c712e4f-b823-4c2a-b24d-254639a4db50.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: As this gardening season winds down, I am thinking about next year. Is there one native plant I could add to my garden that attracts a wide variety of pollinators?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Burchstead Master Gardner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 8.29.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137450</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/local-real-estate-today-8-29-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-8-29-25"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group at Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our weekly look at local real estate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hanlin joins other Oregon sheriffs seeking clarification on ICE subpoenas]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/02f59d89-1b2d-41bf-a46d-b925a21ad184</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/hanlin-joins-other-oregon-sheriffs-seeking-clarification-on-ice-subpoenas/article_02f59d89-1b2d-41bf-a46d-b925a21ad184.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Sheriff John Hanlin has joined 33 other sheriffs across the state in signing a letter to Marion County’s legal counsel, Oregon Attorney General Dan Rayfield and United States Attorney General Pam Bondi, seeking legal clarify on U.S. Immigration…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Reynolds The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 8.29.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137447</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/morning-conversation-8-29-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-8-29-25"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elkton Community Education Center Co-Executive Director Deborah Gritton talks about Fort Umpqua Days, which is happening Saturday and Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diamond Lake Blvd. improvement project to increase safety and convenience]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/927b72a4-2f19-4c41-ab21-412703f386a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/diamond-lake-blvd-improvement-project-to-increase-safety-and-convenience/article_927b72a4-2f19-4c41-ab21-412703f386a2.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A total of 201 crashes on the Diamond Lake Boulevard stretch of Highway 138 occurred between Jan. 1, 2015, and Dec. 31, 2024, according to data from the Oregon Department of Transportation (ODOT) state highway crash reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amelia Winkelman The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard work, hardships and humility through it all: The life of veteran Ernie Reed.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2ee2ad70-cd74-488e-8e3c-546f61913092</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/hard-work-hardships-and-humility-through-it-all-the-life-of-veteran-ernie-reed/article_2ee2ad70-cd74-488e-8e3c-546f61913092.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a century of life on Earth — 102 years — experiencing all the love and violence that has occurred between then and now. World War II veteran Ernie Reed is no stranger to that love and violence. Struggling to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pack a satisfying school lunch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fcf86432-0d2a-4d55-be19-8996637d996f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/pack-a-satisfying-school-lunch/article_fcf86432-0d2a-4d55-be19-8996637d996f.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, school’s back in session! That means meeting new teachers, reuniting with old friends, and getting back into familiar routines. If packing a school lunch is one of them, here are some tips to keep your kids’ lunches simple, healthy,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Bates For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Road resurfacing to take place in southeast Roseburg next week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/11e9e994-8851-444c-931f-0eab74188324</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/road-resurfacing-to-take-place-in-southeast-roseburg-next-week/article_11e9e994-8851-444c-931f-0eab74188324.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting Sept. 3, the city of Roseburg is scheduled to begin days of road resurfacing work in Southeast Roseburg, maintaining and restoring the surface of 2.6 miles of road following weather delays that postponed the work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Korean War veteran to take part in Honor Flight to Washington DC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/dbe19f8e-9d4d-41c4-be67-09ebe711307c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-korean-war-veteran-to-take-part-in-honor-flight-to-washington-dc/article_dbe19f8e-9d4d-41c4-be67-09ebe711307c.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During his time in the Korean War, Navy veteran Vincent Escriva traveled to many places, but never to Washington, D.C. Now, at 93 years old, he will finally have the opportunity as he has been selected for Honor Flight this…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[County government offices to close Monday for Labor Day]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/356fc16f-91b8-49e2-b6dc-3cee0ef1a231</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/county-government-offices-to-close-monday-for-labor-day/article_356fc16f-91b8-49e2-b6dc-3cee0ef1a231.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — Douglas County Commissioners Tim Freeman, Tom Kress and Chris Boice are reminding residents that county government offices at the courthouse, Justice Building, County Annex in Reedsport, fairgrounds office, landfill and transfer sites and all external government offices…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library to host geologist Larry Broeker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ee725af0-7a13-4ce1-9f75-d5aeba7ce4ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/roseburg-public-library-to-host-geologist-larry-broeker/article_ee725af0-7a13-4ce1-9f75-d5aeba7ce4ec.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T14:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Roseburg Public Library invites the public to a presentation on Oregon’s Table Rocks presented by geologist Larry Broeker at 6:30 p.m. Thursday, Sept. 11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Pitch Night to be held Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/be4613f2-8067-486d-8e4d-d7f8545cb1bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/next-pitch-night-to-be-held-thursday/article_be4613f2-8067-486d-8e4d-d7f8545cb1bf.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T14:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Six entrepreneurs have been selected for the next Pitch Night event, scheduled for Thursday, Sept. 4 at Backside Brewing in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[School safety Q&A with DSCO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/22c7ed21-23be-4c3f-915b-d6dd7c2fe5bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/school-safety-q-a-with-dsco/article_22c7ed21-23be-4c3f-915b-d6dd7c2fe5bd.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — As summer shifts to a close, schools begin to open back up and safety is one topic that seems to be at the forefront of discussion. The News-Review had the opportunity to sit down with Douglas County…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025]]></title>
        <id>68b1a58bcbfd6b0001fa245a</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/august-29-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T13:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FAIRLY STABLE HIGH PRESSURE THROUGH HOLIDAY WEEKEND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137442</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/fairly-stable-high-pressure-through-holiday-weekend/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fairly-stable-high-pressure-through-holiday-weekend"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T10:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 3:50 a.m.  Fairly stable high pressure will remain in the Umpqua Valley throughout the holiday weekend. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that Roseburg should see a high in the low 90’s Friday, before dropping slightly to the upper 80s Saturday through...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORT UMPQUA DAYS AT ECEC ON SATURDAY AND SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137440</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/fort-umpqua-days-at-ecec-on-saturday-and-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fort-umpqua-days-at-ecec-on-saturday-and-sunday"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T10:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 3:40 a.m.  The Elkton Community Education Center is presenting Fort Umpqua Days on Saturday and Sunday. An ECEC release said the Labor Day Weekend tradition brings together history, family, fun, food and community spirit at one of Elkton’s most unique educational and historical sites. Visitors can enjoy living history demonstrations at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UVHBA SHOWCASE OF HOMES HAPPENING SEPTEMBER 13TH/14TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137437</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/uvhba-showcase-of-homes-happening-september-13th-14th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uvhba-showcase-of-homes-happening-september-13th-14th"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T10:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 3:30 a.m.  The Umpqua Valley Homebuilders Association has announced the return of the 2025 Showcase of Homes, on Saturday and Sunday, September 13th and 14th. An UVHBA release said this year’s event will feature a diverse lineup of builders, contractors, and unique locations, offering inspiration and ideas for visitors of all interests....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADAPT WITH ANNUAL CLOSURE NOTICE FOR LABOR DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137435</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/adapt-with-annual-closure-notice-for-labor-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=adapt-with-annual-closure-notice-for-labor-day"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T10:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 3:20 a.m. Adapt Integrated Health Care will be closed for services for all non-crisis, non-residential services and sites in Douglas County on Monday, for Labor Day. This will be a full-day closure with services resuming on Tuesday, September 2nd. 24/7 Crisis Support Services will continue operations as normal and may be reached...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WILDLIFE SAFARI TO HAVE “A NIGHT UNDER THE STARS”]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137432</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/wildlife-safari-to-have-a-night-under-the-stars/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wildlife-safari-to-have-a-night-under-the-stars"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T10:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 3:05 a.m. Wildlife Safari will have “A Night Under the Stars” happening next week. The annual benefit dinner for the game park will take place on Friday, September 5th, beginning at 6:00 p.m. The evening includes a catered dinner, complimentary wine, beer, soda and water, plus silent and oral auctions. A number...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEXT PITCH NIGHT IS HAPPENING SEPTEMBER 4TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137430</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/29/next-pitch-night-is-happening-september-4th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=next-pitch-night-is-happening-september-4th"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T10:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 2:50 a.m. Six entrepreneurs have been selected for the next Pitch Night event. On Thursday, September 4th at Backside Brewing in Roseburg. The participants will compete for their share of a $2,000 prize fund and the final two spots in the first ever Pitch Night Grand Finale on October 23rd. Pitch Night...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FREEWAY CRASH CLOSES INTERSTATE 5 NORTHBOUND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137428</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/freeway-crash-closes-interstate-5-northbound/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=freeway-crash-closes-interstate-5-northbound"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T22:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 29, 2025 3:40 p.m.  A freeway crash early on Wednesday morning closed Interstate 5 northbound and one southbound lane of the freeway for a time, in the Curtin area. Information from the Oregon State Police said the wreck happened just before 6:30 a.m. near milepost 163. A log truck traveling northbound, operated by a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 8.28.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137424</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/inside-douglas-county-8-28-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-8-28-25"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T20:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Moist Forest proposal from Forest Bridges is unveiled by Denis Barrett and Rick Sohn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUGAR LOAF FIRE REMAINS AT 46 ACRES: COTTAGE GROVE RANGER DISTRICT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137421</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/sugar-loaf-fire-remains-at-46-acres-cottage-grove-ranger-district/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sugar-loaf-fire-remains-at-46-acres-cottage-grove-ranger-district"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T18:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 11:00 a.m.   The Sugar Loaf Fire remains at 46 acres in the Cottage Grove Ranger District of the Umpqua National Forest. An update from NW Incident Management Team 13 said three Interagency Hotshot crews and three Type 2 crews with specialized training are directly attacking the fire to minimize the number of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG  POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137419</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-28/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-28"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T17:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 10:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for drinking in public early Thursday morning. An RPD report said just before 2:30 a.m. the 65-year-old was contacted in front of a business in the 200 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. The man was allegedly in possession of an open beer container, with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR STATEWIDE FELONY PAROLE WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137417</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-statewide-felony-parole-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-statewide-felony-parole-warrant"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T17:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 10:30 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed man for a statewide felony parole violation warrant on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 8:00 p.m. the 31-year-old was contacted near a business in the 1200 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard, during a trespass complaint. The warrant was confirmed, and he was taken into custody....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR FAILURE TO APPEAR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137415</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-failure-to-appear-warrant-7/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-failure-to-appear-warrant-7"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T17:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 10:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for a failure to appear warrant on Wednesday. An RPD report said just after 9:30 a.m. the 68-year-old was contacted for drinking in public in the 2600 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. During the contact, the officer learned the man had an active warrant for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137413</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-17/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-incident-17"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T17:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 10:10 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man on Wednesday for an alleged prior theft incident. An RPD report said at 5:00 p.m. officers contacted 25-year-old Rad Osburn in the 100 block of Northeast Garden Valley Boulevard. Osburn was a person of interest in a past theft case where a chainsaw was taken...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN ON FELONY ASSAULT CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137411</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/sutherlin-police-jail-man-on-felony-assault-charge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-on-felony-assault-charge"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T17:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 9:50 a.m.   Sutherlin Police jailed a man on the charge of 4th-degree felony assault on Wednesday, for an alleged prior incident. An SPD report said on August 19th at 10:30 p.m. a victim flagged an officer down in the 100 block of West Central Avenue and claimed she had been assaulted about...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GLENDALE AREA TRANSIENT JAILED FOR FAILURE TO APPEAR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137409</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/glendale-area-transient-jailed-for-failure-to-appear-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=glendale-area-transient-jailed-for-failure-to-appear-warrant"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T16:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 9:30 a.m.   A Glendale area transient was jailed for a failure to appear warrant on Tuesday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 5:40 p.m. a deputy was driving on Pacific Avenue in Glendale and noticed the 29-year-old walking towards the railroad tracks. When the suspect saw the deputy, he took...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENT JAILED FOR PAROLE VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137407</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/transient-jailed-for-parole-violation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transient-jailed-for-parole-violation"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T16:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 9:20 a.m.   A transient was jailed for a parole violation by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office on Wednesday night. A DCSO report said at 9:30 p.m. a deputy learned the woman was in the 400 block of Curtin Road in the Curtin area and was wanted by her parole officer. The deputy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 8.28.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137403</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/morning-conversation-8-28-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-8-28-25"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T16:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Actors Community Theatre’s Ashley Chitwood is the director for their production of, “Picasso at the Lapin Agile”, which open on September 4th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two historic figures bring big laughs to UACT]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f8003a1b-d671-4e33-82a0-21d08dd4ae02</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/two-historic-figures-bring-big-laughs-to-uact/article_f8003a1b-d671-4e33-82a0-21d08dd4ae02.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What would happen if two massively influential historical figures — Pablo Picasso and Albert Einstein — met in a bar just before putting out their greatest achievements? What would have resulted from their conversation?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camel ride spurs lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f3689e40-e78b-490c-bd18-429e6560b232</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/camel-ride-spurs-lawsuit/article_f3689e40-e78b-490c-bd18-429e6560b232.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Quantivia Lopez said that almost as soon as she and her 2-year-old daughter got on Leo the camel, she noticed something was wrong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rediscover downtown Roseburg during Fifth Friday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ee734680-b4ba-4ba1-a627-bfe50102e8f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/rediscover-downtown-roseburg-during-fifth-friday/article_ee734680-b4ba-4ba1-a627-bfe50102e8f5.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Re)Discover Downtown Roseburg’s Fifth Friday event returns from from 4:30-7:30 p.m. Friday. It includes an author book signing at Yours Truly Bookshop, Central Art Supply store opening, a kitten adoption pop-up and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amelia Winkelman The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025]]></title>
        <id>68b05962cbfd6b0001fa22e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/august-28-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T13:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDGE OF HIGH PRESSURCE STAYS IN PLACE BUT COOLING EXPECTED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137398</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/ridge-of-high-pressurce-stays-in-place-but-cooling-expected/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ridge-of-high-pressurce-stays-in-place-but-cooling-expected"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T11:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 4:10 a.m.  A ridge of high pressure is staying in place in the Umpqua Valley, but some cooling is expected for the next two days. Forecasters at the National Weather Service in Medford told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that highs should be right at or slightly above 90 degrees...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOVERNOR ORDERS FLAGS LOWERED AT HALF-STAFF: MINNEAPOLIS SHOOTING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137396</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/governor-orders-flags-lowered-at-half-staff-minneapolis-shooting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=governor-orders-flags-lowered-at-half-staff-minneapolis-shooting"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T11:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 3:50 a.m.   On Wednesday, Governor Tina Kotek ordered flags at Oregon public institutions to be flown at half-staff until sunset on August 31st, pursuant to a Presidential Proclamation in honor of the victims and survivors of the shooting that occurred at Annunciation Catholic School in Minneapolis, Minnesota. Governor Kotek said, “Children and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY GOVERNMENT OFFICES TO CLOSE ON MONDAY- LABOR DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137394</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/county-government-offices-to-close-on-monday-labor-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-government-offices-to-close-on-monday-labor-day"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T10:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 3:40 a.m,   Douglas County Commissioners Tim Freeman, Tom Kress, and Chris Boice are reminding residents that county government offices at the courthouse, Justice Building, County Annex in Reedsport, fairgrounds office, landfill and transfer sites, and all external government offices will be closed to the public on Monday, September 1st in observance of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG ROAD RESURFACING TO BEGIN SOON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137392</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/roseburg-road-resurfacing-to-begin-soon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-road-resurfacing-to-begin-soon"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T10:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 3:30 a.m. Maintenance to extend the life of over 2.5 miles of southeastern Roseburg streets is set to begin next Wednesday, September 3rd, weather permitting. A city release said the Roseburg Public Works Department asks vehicle owners to be sure to remove their vehicles from street sections scheduled and posted for maintenance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG PUBLIC LIBRARY TO HOST GEOLOGIST LARRY BROEKER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137389</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/roseburg-public-library-to-host-geologist-larry-broeker/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-public-library-to-host-geologist-larry-broeker"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T10:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 3:20 a.m. Roseburg Public Library invites the public to a presentation on Oregon’s Table Rocks presented by geologist Larry Broeker at 6:30 p.m. on Thursday, September 11th. A city release said Broeker retired from the Umpqua National Forest and speaks regularly about the iconic landforms of southern Oregon and northern California. Broeker...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY OF MYRTLE CREEK PUBLIC MEETINTGS CALENDAR FOR SEPTEMBER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137387</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/city-of-myrtle-creek-public-meetintgs-calendar-for-september/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-of-myrtle-creek-public-meetintgs-calendar-for-september"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T10:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 3:05 a.m.  The City of Myrtle Creek has released its public meetings calendar for September. *The city council will meet on Tuesday, September 2nd and Monday, September 15th at 5:30 p.m. *The mural committee will meet on Tuesday, September 30th at 2:00 p.m. The park commission and planning commission meetings have been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MUSIC IN THE PARK WRAPS UP ITS 38TH SEASON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=137385</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/08/28/music-in-the-park-wraps-up-its-38th-season/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=music-in-the-park-wraps-up-its-38th-season"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T10:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 28, 2025 2:50 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Music in the Park in Myrtle Creek is concluding its 38th year of free concerts on Thursday night. Pendleton Highway, a country dance band from Eugene, will be on stage at Millsite Park. The concert will be from 6:00 p.m. to 8:30 p.m. Attendees should...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>