<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-10-08T23:12:07.431Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.8.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124619</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/inside-douglas-county-10-8-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-8-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T20:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican candidate of Oregon Attorney General Will Lathrop talks about the work of the AG’s office and what he would do if elected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FUELS CONTINUE TO DRY OUT ON HOMESTEAD COMPLEX]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124616</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/fuels-continue-to-dry-out-on-homestead-complex/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fuels-continue-to-dry-out-on-homestead-complex"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T18:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 11:10 a.m. Fuels continue to dry out and become more available to burn in the Homestead Complex. An Umpqua National Forest update said the fire areas saw the highest temperatures of the recent warming and drying trend, with a corresponding increase in fire behavior. Conditions are now beginning to cool, and humidity...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REEDSPORT DEALING WITH SEWAGE SPILL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124614</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/reedsport-dealing-with-sewage-spill/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=reedsport-dealing-with-sewage-spill"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 10:40 a.m.  Covering coastal Douglas County: On Tuesday, staff with the City of Reedsport was contacted regarding a sewage spill from a manhole near the 1800 block of Decker Point. City Manager Deanna Schafer said wastewater staff investigated and determined that a spill of approximately 40,000 gallons of raw sewage had been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE ISSUE CITY ORDINANCE VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124612</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/roseburg-police-issue-city-ordinance-violation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-issue-city-ordinance-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 10:40 a.m.   Roseburg Police issued a city ordinance violation on Monday night. An RPD report said at 8:00 p.m. officers contacted the 44-year-old near the corner of Southeast Jackson Street and Southeast Cass Avenue. The man had an open alcoholic beverage with him. He was cited for drinking in public and issued...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE 5 PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124610</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/roseburg-police-cite-5-people-for-prohibited-camping-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-5-people-for-prohibited-camping-3"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 10:30 a.m. Roseburg Police cited 5 people for prohibited camping on Monday. An RPD report said citations were given in Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street, at the duck pond in the 1000 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard, and at Charles Gardiner Park in the 2600 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANTS, UNLAWFUL POSSESSION OF SCHEDULE II DRUG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124608</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrants-unlawful-possession-of-schedule-ii-drug/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrants-unlawful-possession-of-schedule-ii-drug"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for warrants and for unlawful possession of a Schedule II controlled substance early Tuesday. An RPD report said at 12:15 a.m. officers found 35-year-old William June in a parking lot in the 3000 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. June was found to have two valid...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK WOMAN JAILED ON 13 CHARGES FROM 3 DCSO CASES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124606</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/myrtle-creek-woman-jailed-on-13-charges-from-3-dcso-cases/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-woman-jailed-on-13-charges-from-3-dcso-cases"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 10:00 a.m. A Myrtle Creek woman was jailed Monday on 13 charges stemming from 3 Douglas County Sheriff’s Office cases. A DCSO report said just before 2:00 p.m. a search warrant was served at a residence in the 700 block of Lees Creek Road. 45-year-old Alecia Garrick was taken into custody in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOTORCYCLIST TAKEN TO HOSPITAL AFTER TWO-VEHICLE ACCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124601</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/motorcyclist-taken-to-hospital-after-two-vehicle-accident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=motorcyclist-taken-to-hospital-after-two-vehicle-accident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 9:40 a.m.  A motorcyclist was taken to the hospital after a two-vehicle accident Monday afternoon. A Roseburg Police report said at 4:45 p.m. officers responded to the crash at the intersection of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard and Northeast Fowler Street. A juvenile driver was stopped on Fowler Street waiting to make a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO CRIMINAL CHARGES FILED AFTER HIT AND RUN INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124599</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/no-criminal-charges-filed-after-hit-and-run-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=no-criminal-charges-filed-after-hit-and-run-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 9:20 a.m. No criminal charges were filed following a hit and run incident on Monday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 12:00 p.m. a victim reported that an unknown sedan had side swiped his vehicle on Old Highway 99 South near Tipton Road, just south of Roseburg.  A deputy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.8.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124594</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/morning-conversation-10-8-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-8-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drug Court participant Noel Crownover talks about his experiences, what he has learned in the court process, and his Helmets for HOPE distribution happening on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOVERNOR CALLS FOR AUDIT, PAUSE IN AUTOMATIC VOTER REGISTRATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124591</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/governor-calls-for-audit-pause-in-automatic-voter-registration/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=governor-calls-for-audit-pause-in-automatic-voter-registration"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T11:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 4:00 a.m. On Monday, Governor Tina Kotek announced a set of actions following an Oregon Driver and Motor Vehicles Services “after-action” report detailing errors within the Oregon Moter Voter Program. A release said the report was among an initial set of actions the governor directed the Oregon DMV to undertake two weeks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG JUST MISSES TYING RECORD HIGH FOR THE DATE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124588</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/roseburg-just-misses-tying-record-high-for-the-date/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-just-misses-tying-record-high-for-the-date"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T10:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 3:40 a.m.  It was an unseasonably hot afternoon in the Umpqua Valley on Monday, but just missed tying a record high temperature for the date. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the mercury reached 90 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport. The record...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY CLERK’S OFFICE BEGINNING TO GET BALLOTS OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124586</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/county-clerks-office-beginning-to-get-ballots-out/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-clerks-office-beginning-to-get-ballots-out"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T10:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Douglas County Clerk’s Office is beginning to get the ballots out for the November General Election. *Tuesday ballots for those who are currently out-of-state are going to the U.S. Postal Service Other election cycle dates include: *October 14th is the estimated delivery date for the Voters Pamphlet from the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY SET TO FACE REVENUE SHORTFALL TO MAINTAIN COUNTY ROADS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124583</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/douglas-county-set-to-face-revenue-shortfall-to-maintain-county-roads/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-set-to-face-revenue-shortfall-to-maintain-county-roads"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T10:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Association of Oregon Counties recently presented its 2024 County Road Needs Study to the Oregon to the Oregon Legislative Joint Committee on Transportation, forecasting a statewide annual revenue shortfall of 59 percent over the next five years, resulting in an additional $834 million per year needed to maintain and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SECTION OF EDENBOWER BOULEVARD TO CLOSE TUESDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124580</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/section-of-edenbower-boulevard-to-close-tuesday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section-of-edenbower-boulevard-to-close-tuesday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T10:10:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 3:05 a.m. A section of Northwest Edenbower Boulevard from Northwest Aviation Drive to Northeast Stephens Street in Roseburg will be closed to all traffic Tuesday night to complete pavement restoration work after installation of a 24-inch water transmission pipe. A city release said that section of Edenbower Boulevard will close from 7:00...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG VA CONTINUES WITH FLU/COVID-19 VACCINE CLINIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124578</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/08/roseburg-va-continues-with-flu-covid-19-vaccine-clinic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-va-continues-with-flu-covid-19-vaccine-clinic"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T10:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 8, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Roseburg VA Medical Center is continuing its flu and COVID-19 vaccine clinics through November 2nd. Enrolled veterans may access vaccines during scheduled VA primary care visits or at the clinics, where no appointment is needed. Clinics are drive-through and are held under the canopy of Building 1 on the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.7.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124569</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/inside-douglas-county-10-7-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-7-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T21:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiffany Roddy, forester for Roseburg Forest Products, talks about the Douglas County Chapter of Oregon Women in Timber.  October is National Forest Products Month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE 4 PEOPLE FOR DUII EARLY SATURDAY TO EARLY MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124566</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/roseburg-police-cite-4-people-for-duii-early-saturday-to-early-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-4-people-for-duii-early-saturday-to-early-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T18:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 11:10 a.m.   Roseburg Police cited 4 people for DUII between early Saturday morning and early Monday morning. An RPD report said the incidents occurred in the 2000 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard, near the intersection of Southeast Douglas Avenue and Southeast Eastwood Street, near the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIX STORAGE UNITS SUFFER FIRE AND SMOKE DAMAGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124563</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/six-storage-units-suffer-fire-and-smoke-damage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=six-storage-units-suffer-fire-and-smoke-damage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T17:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 10:50 a.m.  Six storage units suffered fire and smoke damage while numerous others suffered smoke damage in a commercial structure fire Sunday night. A Roseburg Fire Department report said at 8:30 p.m. firefighters responded to the fire at Gecko RV and Boat Storage in the 300 block of Northeast Pomona Street, just...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commercial Structure Fire - 350 NE Pomona Street - 10-6-24 (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news175836</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5568#news175836"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T17:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 8:29 p.m. on October 6, 2024, Roseburg Fire Department personnel responded to a commercial structure fire, located at 350 NE Pomona Street.  Several concerned citizens contacted the Douglas County Emergency Dispatch Center after both fire and smoke were showing from the commercial structure known as Gecko RV and Boat Storage.  Firefighters arrived on scene to find fire and heavy smoke showing from approximately fourteen storage units located within the storage unit complex.  
Firefighters conducted a search for potential occupants and quickly extinguished the fire. Firefighters used rotary saws to gain access through garage doors of individual storage units to check for fire and to confirm the fire was not spreading to additional units through the common attic space.  Six units suffered fire and smoke damage while numerous other units suffered smoke damage.  Firefighters were on scene for approximately four hours completing extensive overhaul of the damaged storage units. 
Throughout the day, fire investigators will be on scene processing several of the storage units.  The cause of the fire is undetermined at this time and is not criminal in nature.  There were no reported firefighter or civilian injuries.  Twenty-one firefighters assisted with firefighting operations.  Other agencies assisting with the fire included Central Douglas Fire & Rescue, Umpqua Valley Ambulance, Roseburg Police Department, Avista Utilities, and Pacific Power.
The Roseburg Fire Department would like to thank the citizens who quickly reported the fire to the Douglas County Emergency Dispatch Center.  Their quick action assisted in limiting the damage to additional storage units.
For the latest information regarding the City of Roseburg Fire Department, please visit our website at www.cityofroseburg.org or like us on Facebook at www.facebook.com/roseburgfire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Fire Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIRES ACTIVE IN HOMESTEAD COMPLEX, DIAMOND COMPLEX UNCHANGED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124561</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/fires-active-in-homestead-complex-diamond-complex-unchanged/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fires-active-in-homestead-complex-diamond-complex-unchanged"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T17:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 10:30 a.m.   Fires were active in the Homestead Complex on Sunday, where winds and slope aligned. An Umpqua National Forest update said conditions are expected to remain similar with the potential for cooler temperatures and higher humidity later in the week, which will moderate fire behavior. On the Horse Heaven Fire, crews...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWNIG HIT AND RUN INCIDENT FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124559</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/sutherlin-police-jail-man-follownig-hit-and-run-incident-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-follownig-hit-and-run-incident-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T17:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 10:15 a.m.   Sutherlin Police jailed a man following a hit and run incident on Friday afternoon. An SPD report said at 2:20 p.m. the victim was traveling east on Hastings Avenue, on his motorcycle, when he realized a sports car was following him and he knew who it belonged to. The report...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED STORE THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124557</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-store-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-store-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T16:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 9:50 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged theft at a store on Sunday night. An RPD report said at 7:00 p.m. officers contacted the 28-year-old after she was detained by loss prevention employees for allegedly shoplifting at Goodwill in the 2400 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway.  An investigation revealed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL PAIR FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124553</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/roseburg-police-jail-pair-for-alleged-theft-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-pair-for-alleged-theft-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T16:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed two people for an alleged theft incident on Friday night. An RPD report said at 6:30 p.m. officers contacted the 36-year-old man and 28-year-old woman after they allegedly both stole from Harbor Freight in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street and then fled the scene. They...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124551</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-trespass-incident-9/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-trespass-incident-9"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T16:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 9:30 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man following a reported trespass incident on Friday. An RPD report said at approximately 9:10 a.m. officers contacted the 29-year-old at the Roseburg Seventh Day Adventist Church Better Living Center, in the 1100 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. The suspect had refused to leave after...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ELUDING INCIDENT ON FREEWAY THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124549</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-eluding-incident-on-freeway-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-for-eluding-incident-on-freeway-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T16:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 9:20 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a man for an eluding incident on Interstate 5 on Thursday afternoon. An SPD report released on Monday said at 5:45 p.m. an officer attempted to stop a commercial motor vehicle for speeding at 77 miles per hour while heading southbound on the freeway south of Sutherlin....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.7.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124545</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/morning-conversation-10-7-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-7-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T16:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Laurel Hallock-Koppelman is an Oregon Health and Science University Assistant Professor of Medicine and a family nurse practitioner. She talked about last month’s recovery month observance and the issues of overdose deaths and opioid use disorder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tour hydropower project with Pacificorp Oct. 16]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0bdebf7c-8211-11ef-a487-5bd53290dfa0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/tour-hydropower-project-with-pacificorp-oct-16/article_0bdebf7c-8211-11ef-a487-5bd53290dfa0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those who have wondered about hydropower and how it works in the Umpqua River, there will be a tour Wednesday, Oct. 16, of the Pacificorp hydroelectric project at Soda Springs Dam on the North Umpqua River.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER SHERIFF’S DEPUTY SENTENCED TO PRISON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124539</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/former-sheriffs-deputy-sentenced-to-prison/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=former-sheriffs-deputy-sentenced-to-prison"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T12:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 5:20 a.m. The News Review is reporting: Former Douglas County Sheriff’s Office deputy Peter Collins was sentenced Friday to two years in prison for embezzling more than $20,000 from the Douglas County Law Enforcement Association. Collins was found guilty on two counts of first-degree aggravated theft for stealing more than $10,000 from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEAR RECORD HIGH TEMPERATURE FOR THE DATE EXPECTED ON MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124535</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/near-record-high-temperature-for-the-date-expected-on-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=near-record-high-temperature-for-the-date-expected-on-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T10:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 3:50 a.m.  The Umpqua Valley continues to have above normal high temperatures for this part of October, with the potential to reach near a record high for the date on Monday. Forecasters at the National Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the mercury is expected to reach near...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCSO JAILS MAN FOR WARRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124533</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/dcso-jails-man-for-warrants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dcso-jails-man-for-warrants"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T10:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 3:40 a.m.  Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a man for warrants late Saturday morning. A DCSO report deputies knew that the 41-year-old had warrants and attempted to contact him in the 800 block of North Old Pacific Highway near Myrtle Creek just before 12:00 p.m. Deputies spoke with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAYNE STINSON EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT CENTER OPEN HOUSE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124530</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/wayne-stinson-emergency-management-center-open-house/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wayne-stinson-emergency-management-center-open-house"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T10:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 3:30 a.m. Douglas County Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman and Tom Kress are inviting the public to attend the open house and dedication ceremony for the Wayne Stinson Emergency Management Center on Tuesday, October 22nd, from 6:00 p.m. to 7:00 p.m. A county release said the newly remodeled building will be home...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY COMMISSIONERS NOT HOLDING BUSINESS MEETING WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124528</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/county-commissioners-not-holding-business-meeting-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-commissioners-not-holding-business-meeting-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T10:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 3:20 a.m. Douglas County Commissioners will not be holding their weekly business meeting this week. Their next meeting will be Wednesday October 16th at 9:00 a.m. in room 216 of the courthouse. Meeting agendas for board meetings are posted at least 24 hours in advance at: https://douglascountyor.gov/ Call the commissioner’s office at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST VOLUNTEER OPPORTUNITIES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124526</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/umpqua-national-forest-volunteer-opportunities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-national-forest-volunteer-opportunities"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T10:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Umpqua National Forest has a number of volunteer opportunities throughout the year. A UNF release said while formal volunteer events slow down during the winter months, the work still continues. Upcoming volunteer opportunities include: *Dorena Genetic Resource Center is seeking volunteers this Wednesday and the second Wednesday of every...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WALK & ROLL TO SCHOOL DAY WITH LOCAL EVENTS THIS WEEK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124524</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/07/walk-roll-to-school-day-with-local-events-this-week/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=walk-roll-to-school-day-with-local-events-this-week"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T10:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 2:50 a.m. The 28th annual National Walk & Roll to School Day is Wednesday and some schools in Douglas County have events planned for this week or later in the month. Janelle James of Safe Routes to School and Thrive Umpqua said the local events include: Tuesday, Tri City Elementary is hosting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INCREASED FIRE ACTIVITY ON HOMESTEAD, NO GROWTH ON DIAMOND COMPLEX]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124522</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/06/increased-fire-activity-on-homestead-no-growth-on-diamond-complex/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=increased-fire-activity-on-homestead-no-growth-on-diamond-complex"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T16:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 6, 2024 9:20 a.m. Another day of warm dry activity contributed to an increase in fire activity as well as minor fire growth on a portion of the Homestead Complex on Saturday. An Umpqua National Forest update said fire managers took a reconnaissance helicopter flight to evaluate fire activity across the fires that remain...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONLY SLIGHT GROWTH ON HOMESTEAD COMPLEX/DIAMOND COMPLEX UNCHANGED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124520</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/05/only-slight-growth-on-homestead-complex-diamond-complex-unchanged/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=only-slight-growth-on-homestead-complex-diamond-complex-unchanged"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T17:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 5, 2024 10:00 a.m. There has only been slight growth on the Homestead Complex with the Diamond Complex remaining unchanged. An Umpqua National Forest update said anticipated precipitation failed to materialize across the fire area Friday. Cooler temperatures and moisture helped to subdue fire behavior through midday. In the afternoon, fire activity picked up...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRIVER LOSES CONTROL OF VEHICLE, CRASHES INTO A FENCE AND TRANSFORMER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124518</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/05/driver-loses-control-of-vehicle-crashes-into-a-fence-and-transformer/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=driver-loses-control-of-vehicle-crashes-into-a-fence-and-transformer"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T16:09:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 9:10 a.m. A driver lost control of his vehicle, which then went over a curb, crashed into a fence in front of a home and hit a transformer box in Green on Friday morning. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 10:00 a.m. the 77-year-old was turning onto the 100 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN MAN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING SINGLE-VEHICLE WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124516</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/05/sutherlin-man-taken-to-hospital-following-single-vehicle-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-man-taken-to-hospital-following-single-vehicle-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T15:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 8:50 a.m. A Sutherlin man was taken to the hospital following a single vehicle wreck on Friday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 3:00 p.m. the 60-year-old was driving east on Hayhurst Road in the Yoncalla area when his vehicle went over the white line, and hit the gravel,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENT JAILED FOR TRESPASSING A SECOND TIME]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124514</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/05/transient-jailed-for-trespassing-a-second-time/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transient-jailed-for-trespassing-a-second-time"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T15:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 7, 2024 8:30 a.m.  A transient was jailed for trespassing by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office on Thursday afternoon. A DCSO report said at 12:50 p.m. the woman was contacted at a property in the 3800 block of Happy Valley Road in Green. She had returned to the residence after being released from corrections...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prescribed burn in Glide slated to benefit school]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/14b0af08-81fc-11ef-a6fa-8bf7af557386</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/prescribed-burn-in-glide-slated-to-benefit-school/article_14b0af08-81fc-11ef-a6fa-8bf7af557386.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — In mid-September, the Glide High School fire science class and Wolf Creek Job Corps forestry students cleared an area in the Glide Elementary School nature area, behind the school.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>