<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-04-02T02:19:55.059Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adaptive Management Program Committee meets April 8 - Correction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171198</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171198"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T22:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Correction: Independent Research and Science Team will not be joining the committee.
SALEM, Ore. — The Adaptive Management Program Committee and the Independent Research and Science Team will meet at 9 a.m. on Monday, April 8 in the Clatsop Room, Building C, at the Oregon Department of Forestry headquarters, located at 2600 State St. in Salem. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes three potential substantial decision items:

Initiating development of an Effectiveness Monitoring Plan
Address questions from the IRST regarding roads questions package
Process for initiating research questions

The meeting is open to the public to attend in person and online via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted near the start of the meeting. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours before the meeting by emailing adaptivemanagementprogram@odf.oregon.gov.
The 13-member committee The Adaptive Management Program Committee helps determine if forest practices are meeting their goals to protect natural resources through a science-based and transparent process. The committee sets the research agenda that the Independent Research and Science Team (IRST) implements. View more information on the AMPC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DUII EARLY SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117261</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-early-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-early-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T22:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 2, 2024 3:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for DUII early Saturday. An RPD report said at 12:20 a.m. the 54-year-old was contacted at a traffic stop at the intersection of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard and Northwest Mulholland Drive. He showed several signs of impairment before consenting to standard field sobriety tests. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117259</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-5/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-5"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T21:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 2:50 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping on Saturday. An RPD report said at 9:00 a.m. the 47-year-old had a camp set up near the Duck Pond in the 1000 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. That area is in a location where camping is prohibited. The man was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR MISUSE OF 911 ON SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117257</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-misuse-of-911-on-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-misuse-of-911-on-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T21:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 2:40 p.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for misuse of 911 on Saturday. An RPD report said at 11:30 a.m. the 23-year-old called 911 and hung up on dispatchers. Officers found the man at his apartment in the 2500 block of Northeast Stephens Street, and he admitted to calling 911. The suspect...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public comment period on proposed rules for post-disturbance harvest rulemaking begins April 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171186</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171186"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T19:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore.— The Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) is holding a public comment period beginning April 1 for proposed rule changes related to post-disturbance timber harvest. Post-disturbance harvest refers to the removal of forest products after catastrophic events such as wildfire, wind, ice, insect or disease damage and is commonly referred to as salvage logging.
This rulemaking is required by Senate Bill 1501 (2022) that was part of the legislation that enacted the Private Forest Accord.
On Feb. 23, 2024, the Board of Forestry directed ODF to complete an analysis of the estimated economic impact of the draft rules and file a Notice of Proposed Rulemaking. The public comment period on the proposed rules will be open from April 1 to May 1 and a rules hearing will be held on April 22 at 1 p.m.  The Notice of Proposed Rulemaking includes important details including but not limited to the rule text, how to submit comments, and how to participate in the virtual rule hearing. The analysis of the estimated economic impact will be available on the ODF website before the close of the public comment period. 
More information on this rulemaking effort and ongoing updates can be found on the Proposed laws & rules page of the ODF website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117255</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-trespass/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-trespass"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 11:25 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged trespass incident on Saturday. An RPD report said at 5:15 p.m. officers responded to the Samaritan Inn in the 500 block of West Umpqua Street. The 43-year-old allegedly attacked staff and had climbed the fence at the facility. During contact with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CITED FOR THEFT FROM STORE ON FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117253</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-man-cited-for-theft-from-store-on-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-cited-for-theft-from-store-on-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 11:15 a.m. A Roseburg man was cited by Roseburg Police following a reported theft from a store on Friday. An RPD report said at 1:30 p.m. the 42-year-old was allegedly caught stealing over $287 worth of groceries and other items by loss prevention at the business in the 900 block of Northwest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117251</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-8/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-8"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 204 11:00 a.m.    Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged theft incident on Friday. An RPD report said at 2:30 p.m. the 35-year-old was detained by loss prevention at a store in the 2700 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway after he allegedly shoplifted alcohol and other assorted drinks. The man admitted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMART READING STILL SEEKING COMMUNITY VOLLUNTEERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117247</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/smart-reading-still-seeking-community-vollunteers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=smart-reading-still-seeking-community-vollunteers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Children’s literacy nonprofit SMART Reading is still seeking community volunteers. The organization is looking for volunteer readers who will be placed at an elementary school or pre-school to read with children on a weekly basis, providing reading practice time, one-on-one attention and fun, low-stress experiences with books. No prior experience...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GARDEN VOLUNTEERS NEEDED AT SHORE ACRES STATE PARK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117242</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/garden-volunteers-needed-at-shore-acres-state-park/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=garden-volunteers-needed-at-shore-acres-state-park"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 10:10 a.m.   Garden volunteers are needed at Shore Acres State Park near Coos Bay. An Oregon Parks and Recreation Department release said people can join rangers in caring for the gardens between 10:00 a.m. and 1:00 p.m. on the third Thursday of each month through September. Tasks vary depending on the season...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be a part of the conversation: Apply for the Smoke Management Advisory Committee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171167</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news171167"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore.—The Oregon Department of Forestry is soliciting applications to join the Smoke Management Advisory Committee. The committee is currently seeking applications to fill one vacancy to represent the public.
Created in 1989, the Smoke Management Advisory Committee (SMAC) provides advice and assistance to the Oregon Department of Forestry Smoke Management Program. The membership of the committee consists of an industrial forestland owner representative, a non-industrial forestland owner representative, a public representative, a Forest Service representative, and a Bureau of Land Management representative. Each representative serves for two-year terms that are renewable after the two-year period.
“This is an opportunity for the public to get involved and make sure that their voice and concerns are heard when it comes to prescribed fire smoke management in Oregon.” Said Stacy McCarter, Mitigation Program Manager. 
Committee members gather for public meetings in Salem twice a year to discuss and provide advice to the Smoke Management Program regarding current prescribed burning and smoke intrusion trends, program fund balance, implementation plan items, and other current issues and projects of the program.
To apply, complete an online questionnaire at https://www.oregon.gov/odf/board/Documents/smac/smac-public-nomination-form-2024.pdf and submit to Stacy McCarter at ODF by email stacy.mccarter@odf.oregon.gov by May 1, 2024.
For specific questions about the committee, please contact Stacy McCarter at 503-701-0236 or stacy.mccarter@odf.oregon.gov. Additional SMAC background information can be found at https://www.oregon.gov/odf/board/Pages/smac.aspx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OOTFA 2024 SPRING CONVENTION STARTS THURSDAY IN WINSTON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117240</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/ootfa-2024-spring-convention-starts-thursday-in-winston/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ootfa-2024-spring-convention-starts-thursday-in-winston"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T16:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 9:30 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Oregon Old Time Fiddler’s Association 2024 Spring Convention is happening Thursday through Saturday. Musicians from around Oregon and beyond are expected. It is being held at Winston Assembly of God at 360 Darrell Avenue. Activities take place throughout the day, each day. Workshops, open...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local employees recognized as Banner Bank's Best]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/aa1d095e-f040-11ee-ba51-53d77d609cb2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/local-employees-recognized-as-banner-banks-best/article_aa1d095e-f040-11ee-ba51-53d77d609cb2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patti Curtis and Heather Coffie were selected to receive the Banner's Best award, which represents the highest level of recognition from the company, according to a press release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austin Page: helping people through their worst moments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d96b2088-d00b-11ee-8a18-e33b5df1c725</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/austin-page-helping-people-through-their-worst-moments/article_d96b2088-d00b-11ee-8a18-e33b5df1c725.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Austin Page, alongside his crew, has the responsibility of helping people through “the worst moments of their life.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 'unbelievable commitment' of Brennan Pettibone, other wildland firefighters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4c68d560-d013-11ee-882e-3bdc24a9c3ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/the-unbelievable-commitment-of-brennan-pettibone-other-wildland-firefighters/article_4c68d560-d013-11ee-882e-3bdc24a9c3ad.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things might be slow in the winter months for Douglas Forest Protective Association South Unit Protection Supervisor and Assistant Unit Forester Brennan Pettibone, but all that will change come fire season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAWSUITS REGARDING REPRESENTATIVE GOODWIN DROPPED FOR NOW]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117232</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/lawsuits-regarding-representative-goodwin-dropped-for-now/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lawsuits-regarding-representative-goodwin-dropped-for-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 3:40 a.m. A lawsuit filed against the Oregon Secretary of State’s Office, claiming that State Representative Christine Goodwin does not live within the boundary of Senate District 2 has been dismissed, at least until after the May primary election. Attorney for the plaintiffs Steven Joncus filed a voluntary dismissal late Friday, saying...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REPAIRS CONTINUE ON WINDY COVER CRAB AND FISHING DOCK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117230</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/repairs-continue-on-windy-cover-crab-and-fishing-dock/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=repairs-continue-on-windy-cover-crab-and-fishing-dock"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 3:30 a.m.   The Douglas County Parks Department has an update on the temporary closure of the Windy Cove Crab and Fishing Dock, located on Salmon Harbor Drive in Winchester Bay. A County release said the department had to temporarily close the facility on February 1st, due to structural damage that occurred during...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REEDSPORT RAILROAD CROSSING STUDY AT REEDSPORT COUNCIL MEETING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117227</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/reedsport-railroad-crossing-study-at-reedsport-council-meeting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=reedsport-railroad-crossing-study-at-reedsport-council-meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 3:05 a.m.   Covering coastal Douglas County: The City of Reedsport is preparing for potential future increases in train traffic, should the Port of Coos Bay container ship terminal be constructed on the North Spit in Coos Bay. Over the past year, the city, the Oregon Department of Transportation, the Port of Coos...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC VISUAL AND PERFORMING ARTS WIT HIGH DESERT TO HIGH TIDE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117224</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/04/01/ucc-visual-and-performing-arts-wit-high-desert-to-high-tide/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-visual-and-performing-arts-wit-high-desert-to-high-tide"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 1, 2024 2:50 a.m. n the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Community College Visual & Performing arts presents: High Desert to High Tide, an exhibition featuring fifteen watercolor and acrylic paintings by Oregon artist, Bets Cole. This series of paintings feature Oregon landscapes from the shore to the high desert, including depictions of valleys in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg enters urban growth boundary swap process]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0c51a9b0-ed56-11ee-9b43-a36400746d69</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-enters-urban-growth-boundary-swap-process/article_0c51a9b0-ed56-11ee-9b43-a36400746d69.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg is entering a key phase in a proposed urban growth boundary swap process — public input.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solar eclipse watch party at UCC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2ab3fcf2-e53e-11ee-bc30-ab32ad030075</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/solar-eclipse-watch-party-at-ucc/article_2ab3fcf2-e53e-11ee-bc30-ab32ad030075.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — The Paul Morgan Observatory at Umpqua Community College will host a public watch party of the solar eclipse April 8.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extension Spotlight: New project areas in 4-H]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/52e582fc-eabd-11ee-bfaa-47c532f9a6e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/agriculture/extension-spotlight-new-project-areas-in-4-h/article_52e582fc-eabd-11ee-bfaa-47c532f9a6e5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4-H is all about trying new things, stepping outside of our comfort zones, and finding our spark! Have you ever thought of trying something new? This year Douglas County 4-H has 3 new project areas: market meat goats, livestock evaluation…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATIE BAXTER For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg library considers electronic magazine subscription]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9ee1c628-ed3a-11ee-9d8b-6753f5685043</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/roseburg-library-considers-electronic-magazine-subscription/article_9ee1c628-ed3a-11ee-9d8b-6753f5685043.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you like to read popular magazines, help us decide whether to add electronic magazines to Roseburg Public Library’s collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KRIS WILEY For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Star Gazer: Jupiter and its moons on display in April]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7cbc3372-ebb8-11ee-950c-2f76a76b81f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/umpqua-star-gazer-jupiter-and-its-moons-on-display-in-april/article_7cbc3372-ebb8-11ee-950c-2f76a76b81f4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April is the last month to watch bright Jupiter in the semi-dark evening sky. Each night, Jupiter will sink a bit closer to the sunset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Morgan For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WOLF CREEK MAN ARRESTED FOR ALLEGED KIDNAPPING/STOLEN VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117221</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/30/wolf-creek-man-arrested-for-alleged-kidnapping-stolen-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wolf-creek-man-arrested-for-alleged-kidnapping-stolen-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T12:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 30, 2024 5:45 a.m. A Wolf Creek man was arrested Thursday for an alleged kidnapping and stolen vehicle incident. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said shortly after 1:00 p.m. dispatchers received a call from a man who said his mother had been taken against her will. The victim was able to send information...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolf Creek Man Arrested for Kidnapping, Stolen Vehicle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news171148</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news171148"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T23:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLENDALE, Ore. - A Wolf Creek man has been arrested and lodged in the Douglas County Jail on a number of charges to include kidnapping.
On Thursday, March 28, 2024, shortly after 1:00 pm, 9-1-1 dispatchers received a call from a male who said his mother had been taken against her will. The victim was able to send information to her son, which he relayed to deputies.
Deputies learned the male suspect, 35-year-old Richard Goodin of Wolf Creek, OR, was in a 2006 Chevy Silverado pickup which had been reported stolen earlier in the day.
During the investigation, the victim was able to get away and called 9-1-1 allowing deputies to get an approximate location. Deputies converged on the area, locating Goodin and took him into custody without further incident. The victim was located and taken to safety.
Goodin was lodged in the Douglas County Jail on the following charges:
Kidnap in the Second Degree
Possession of a Stolen Vehicle
Unlawful Use of a Motor Vehicle
Unlawful Possession of Methamphetamine - Violation Level]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES JAIL ROSEBURG MAN ON MULTIPLE CHARGES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117219</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/deputies-jail-roseburg-man-on-multiple-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-jail-roseburg-man-on-multiple-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T20:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 2024 2:00 p.m. Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a Roseburg man on a series of charges following incidents Thursday night. Dale Cranford has the story: “Dale” Q: News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN A DCSO report said at 9:50 p.m. units responded to a residence in the 4100 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITED MAN FOR DUII AFTER OVERNIGHT TRAFFIC STOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117216</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/roseburg-police-cited-man-for-duii-after-overnight-traffic-stop/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cited-man-for-duii-after-overnight-traffic-stop"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 2024 11:00 a.m.  An RPD report said just after 12:00 a.m. the 37-year-old was pulled over in the 500 block of West Umpqua Street for a traffic violation. The man consented to standard field sobriety tests and reportedly performed poorly. He was taken into custody and transported to corrections where he provided a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN CITED FOR DUII-ALCOHOL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117214</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/myrtle-creek-man-cited-for-duii-alcohol/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-cited-for-duii-alcohol"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 2024 10:50 a.m. A Myrtle Creek man was cited for DUII-alcohol by Roseburg Police on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 11:20 p.m. officers stopped a pickup near the intersection of West Harvard Avenue and West Madrone Street for multiple traffic violations. During the stop, the officer identified the 37-year-old driver and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR STORE THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117212</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-store-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-store-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 2024 10:40 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a woman for a theft at a store on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 9:00 p.m. the 55-year-old was cited for second-degree theft after she allegedly walked out of the business in the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway with $232 in items. The woman...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR ALLEGED MENACING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117210</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-alleged-menacing-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-alleged-menacing-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a woman for alleged menacing on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 6:30 p.m. two women were involved in a disturbance at the suspect’s house in the 900 block of Northeast Parkview Court. During the incident, the 69-year-old allegedly slapped the victim, pulled her hair, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117208</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-10/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-10"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 2024 10:25 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for alleged disorderly conduct following an incident Thursday morning. An RPD report said just after 7:30 a.m. officers observed the 30-year-old unlawfully walk across the street in front of traffic in the 700 block of Northeast Stephens Street. The pedestrian allegedly continued to obstruct traffic,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOLLOWING ALLEGED CRIMINAL TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117206</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/roseburg-police-jail-woman-following-alleged-criminal-trespass/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-following-alleged-criminal-trespass"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 204 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman following an alleged criminal trespass incident on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 6:00 p.m. the 59-year-old from Camas Valley was contacted at an establishment in the 900 block of Southeast Stephens Street. She was allegedly trying to fight patrons and would not leave....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG PUBLIC LIBRARY TO HOST UMPQUA VALLEY WINE PROGRAM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117202</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/roseburg-public-library-to-host-umpqua-valley-wine-program/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-public-library-to-host-umpqua-valley-wine-program"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T16:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Public Library will host a presentation on wine making, viticulture and the history of wine in the Umpqua Valley on Thursday April 11th at 6:30 p.m. The presenter will be Joel Goodwillie, winery manager for the Southern Oregon Wine Institute at Umpqua Community College. Goodwillie has thirty years of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOON OVER BUFFALO OPENS THURSDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=117199</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/29/moon-over-buffalo-opens-thursday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=moon-over-buffalo-opens-thursday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T16:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 29, 2024 9:20 a.m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Arts hosts spring break art camp]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fdbde68a-ec91-11ee-9d5d-0b26584f3158</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/umpqua-valley-arts-hosts-spring-break-art-camp/article_fdbde68a-ec91-11ee-9d5d-0b26584f3158.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chloe Brake, 9, doesn't like people telling her what to draw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WILL GESCHKE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg to issue burn permits April through May]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c851e090-ed28-11ee-bd8a-ef6990f162db</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/roseburg-to-issue-burn-permits-april-through-may/article_c851e090-ed28-11ee-bd8a-ef6990f162db.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Roseburg Fire Department will be issuing burn permits from April 15 to May 15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Police get a taste of their town]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/100cd338-ebd8-11ee-a72b-f73f0f307434</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/sutherlin-police-get-a-taste-of-their-town/article_100cd338-ebd8-11ee-a72b-f73f0f307434.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — There’s a hungry person underneath the uniform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>