<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-08-19T23:11:56.042Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADDITIONAL DOWNGRADES TO EVACUATION NOTICES ON DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122672</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/additional-downgrades-to-evacuation-notices-on-dixon-fire-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=additional-downgrades-to-evacuation-notices-on-dixon-fire-2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T22:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 202 3:50 p.m.  The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office has implemented additional evacuation downgrades for the Dixon Fire due to suppression efforts. As of 2:00 p.m. Monday there are no Level 3 “GO” or Level 2 “BE SET” evacuation notices for this incident. Level 1, “BE READY: *All residences on Crume Ranch Lane *All...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STATE POLICE JAIL WOMAN CHARGED WITH 4TH DEGREE ASSAULT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122670</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/state-police-jail-woman-charged-with-4th-degree-assault/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=state-police-jail-woman-charged-with-4th-degree-assault"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T22:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 20, 2024 3:30 p.m.  Oregon State Police jailed a woman on the charge of 4th degree felony assault on Sunday. An OSP report said at 11:40 a.m. witnesses reported someone kicking another person in the rear seat of a vehicle along the right shoulder of Interstate 5 northbound at Rice Hill. When a trooper...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident management personnel from Hawaii join Dixon Fire (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174656</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174656"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T22:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAYS CREEK, Ore. — Hawaii, the most recent state to join the Northwest Compact, hit the ground running by sending personnel to Oregon on their first fire assignments under the compact. 
This past April, Hawaii became the eleventh member of the Northwest Wildland Fire Protection Agreement (NW Compact). The purpose of the NW Compact is to promote effective prevention, suppression, and control of forest fires in the Northwest wildland region of the United States and Western areas of Canada. It provides an efficient way for member states, provinces, and territories to cope with wildland fires that might be beyond the capabilities of a single member agency, through information sharing, technology and resource distribution.
NW compact members include the U.S states of Oregon, Washington, Idaho, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 8.19.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122662</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/inside-douglas-county-8-19-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-8-19-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T20:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kent Romney at the Dixon Fire has an update on that incident. Then Congresswoman Val Hoyle joined us to talk about her efforts to secure federal funds for an emergency communications upgrade for Douglas County government.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Winston police chief Scott Gugel dies after cancer battle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f37593aa-5e63-11ef-bf14-2be73c7e51d6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/former-winston-police-chief-scott-gugel-dies-after-cancer-battle/article_f37593aa-5e63-11ef-bf14-2be73c7e51d6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T19:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Former Winston Police Department Chief Scott Gugel died Friday, after battling cancer for more than a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winston VFW to host open house]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c42922f6-5b3e-11ef-b6f1-570442ad7f4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/winston-vfw-to-host-open-house/article_c42922f6-5b3e-11ef-b6f1-570442ad7f4a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T19:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — The Winston VFW Amos R. Osborne Post 9745 is celebrating its reopening with an open house from 12:30-3 p.m. Sept. 29, at 570 W. Douglas Blvd. in Winston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW MANAGEMENT TAKES OVER HOMESTEAD COMPLEX MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122660</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/new-management-takes-over-homestead-complex-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=new-management-takes-over-homestead-complex-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T18:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 11:20 a.m. Northern Rockies Team 6 took over management of the Homestead Complex Monday morning. A Type 1 helicopter is expected to arrive to assist with operations across all fires. The rain event on Saturday helped to moderate fire growth and behavior. No active starts from the lightning that came through were...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man arrested for assaulting woman, children]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/98fdfad2-5e56-11ef-afb5-c320ee3ec89d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/man-arrested-for-assaulting-woman-children/article_98fdfad2-5e56-11ef-afb5-c320ee3ec89d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T18:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Nathan Joao Ramirez was arrested just before 1 a.m. Sunday for allegedly assaulting a woman and two children in the 500 block of West Agee Street in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX AT 10,984 ACRES, 38 PERCENT CONTAINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122658</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/diamond-complex-at-10984-acres-38-percent-contained/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-at-10984-acres-38-percent-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T18:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 11:00 a.m. The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, consists of 28 lightning caused fires totaling approximately 10,984 acres and 38 percent contained. A UNF update said 20 of the original 28 fires are now 100 percent contained. On Saturday, there were two initial attack responses – the Luke Fire...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Woman steals more than $20K while working for bank]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cd2eae9c-5e55-11ef-8354-6f6512b47c9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/woman-steals-more-than-20k-while-working-for-bank/article_cd2eae9c-5e55-11ef-8354-6f6512b47c9a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T18:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Jamie Marie Springstead, of Winston, turned herself into Roseburg police around 3:30 p.m. Saturday for allegedly stealing more than $20,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED EMBEZZLEMENT/THEFT CASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122656</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-embezzlement-theft-case/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-embezzlement-theft-case"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T17:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 10:45 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a Winston woman in an alleged embezzlement and theft case on Friday. An RPD report said while employed as a teller at Oregon Pacific Bank, in the 2500 block of Northwest Edenbower Boulevard, 46-year-old Jamie Springstead allegedly stole $20,000 from a customer, withdrawing small amounts at a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR SECOND-DEGREE CRIMINAL TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122654</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-second-degree-criminal-trespass-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-second-degree-criminal-trespass-3"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T17:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for second-degree criminal trespass on Saturday night. An RPD report said just after 9:10 p.m. officers contacted the 34-year-old after staff at CHI Mercy Medical Center said he refused to leave the property after being trespassed. Officers spoke to the man who ultimately refused to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING REPORTED DISTURBANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122652</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-disturbance-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-disturbance-3"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T17:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 10:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man following a reported disturbance on Sunday. An RPD report said just after 12:50 a.m. officers responded to the incident in the 500 block of West Agee Street. After an investigation it was determined that 41-year-old Nathan Ramirez had shoved a juvenile into a television set...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN ON SECOND-DEGREE BURGLARY CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122650</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/roseburg-police-jail-man-on-second-degree-burglary-charge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-on-second-degree-burglary-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T17:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man on the charge of second burglary on Sunday. An RPD report said at 3:30 a.m. three male juveniles broke into a store in the 1900 block of Northeast Stephens Street and stole several vapes and alcoholic beverages. They left about two minutes later but returned...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED STORE ROBBERY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122648</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-store-robbery/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-store-robbery"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T17:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged store robbery on Saturday night. An RPD report said just after 8:10 p.m. 24-year-old Elizabeth Weist allegedly stole numerous items from Fred Meyer in the 900 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. As she was attempting to leave, an employee tried to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerald ash borer discovered in more counties in Oregon (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174642</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174642"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T16:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. – The invasive emerald ash borer (EAB) pest has been discovered in three new Oregon counties this summer, according to the Oregon Dept. of Agriculture (ODA) and Oregon Dept. of Forestry (ODF). The U.S. Dept. of Agriculture (USDA) Animal Plant Health Inspection Service (APHIS) laboratory in Maryland has officially confirmed the insect in Marion and Yamhill counties. A third site on the border of Clackamas and Marion is believed to harbor EAB, Still, state officials first need to confirm with the federal lab the identity of the insects found there.
Yamhill County
One adult beetle was found in a trap in the Gaston area - one of 197 traps distributed by ODF and USDA APHIS in the Willamette Valley. The federal lab officially confirmed the find as EAB on Aug. 12. The trap was located…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CREWS SHIFTING TO SUPPRESSION REPAIR ON DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122644</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/crews-shifting-to-suppression-repair-on-dixon-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=crews-shifting-to-suppression-repair-on-dixon-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T16:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 9:20 a.m. Crews are shifting to suppression repair on the Dixon Fire, burning in the Days Creek and Tiller area. While no fire growth has occurred for several days, crews continue to find and douse hot spots to further secure the fire perimeter. An update said in the northeast section of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 8.19.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122640</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/morning-conversation-8-19-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-8-19-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T16:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Dimof of Thrive Umpqua talks about “The Longest Table: event which is happening on Saturday.  Volunteers are still needed to help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More frequent power outage to prevent wildfires frustrate customers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c29c17aa-5c19-11ef-b61d-833b32cfbced</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/more-frequent-power-outage-to-prevent-wildfires-frustrate-customers/article_c29c17aa-5c19-11ef-b61d-833b32cfbced.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Douglas Electric Cooperative and Pacific Power have set their systems to “enhanced safety settings” during fire season, frustrating some Douglas County residents who are experiencing frequent power outages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KIMBERLI HOLMQUIST The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forest Trust Land Advisory Committee meets Aug. 23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174640</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news174640"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T15:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Forest Trust Land Advisory Committee meets Aug. 23 at 10 a.m. at ODF headquarters in Salem, with a virtual option.
The public meeting will be held in the Tillamook Room, Building C, at the Oregon Department of Forestry’s Salem headquarters, 2600 State St., Salem, OR 97310. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes:

Prepare for discussion with the Board of Forestry regarding FMP modeling scenarios at the September Board of Forestry meeting

Public comment is scheduled at the beginning of the meeting. To submit written comment, email ftlac.comment@odf.oregon.gov. Written comments sent at least 48 hours before the meeting will give the FTLAC time to review and consider information. Comments submitted after that window of time will be sent to the FTLAC after the meeting, entered into the record and posted online. Comments are not accepted after the meeting concludes.
The Forest Trust Land Advisory Committee is comprised of seven county commissioners representing 15 Oregon counties where state forestlands are located. The FTLAC is a statutorily established committee that advises the Board of Forestry on matters related to forestland managed by ODF. View more information on the FTLAC webpage.
Questions about accessibility or special accommodations can be directed to the Oregon Department of Forestry at least 24 hours prior to the meeting at 503-945-7200.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA VALLEY SEES FIRST MEASURABLE RAIN SINCE MID-JUNE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122632</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/umpqua-valley-sees-first-measurable-rain-since-mid-june/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-valley-sees-first-measurable-rain-since-mid-june"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 3:50 a.m. The Umpqua Valley saw the first measurable rain since mid-June on Saturday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that the rain gauge at the Roseburg Regional Airport recorded .23 inches of rain. That is much lower than many residents have reported on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPOKANE MAN JAILED FOR DUII/RECKLESS DRIVING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122630</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/spokane-man-jailed-for-duii-reckless-driving/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spokane-man-jailed-for-duii-reckless-driving"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 3:40 a.m. A Spokane, Washington man was charged with driving under the influence of intoxicants and reckless driving on Saturday afternoon. An Oregon State Police report said at approximately 3:50 p.m. a sedan was southbound on Interstate 5 about two miles north of Winchester traveling at 111 miles per hour in heavy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTHEAST DOUGLAS AVENUE ROAD MAINTENANCE UNDERWAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122627</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/southeast-douglas-avenue-road-maintenance-underway/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=southeast-douglas-avenue-road-maintenance-underway"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 3:30 a.m. Drivers should use caution and expect delays as road maintenance is underway on Southeast Douglas Avenue in Roseburg. A City of Roseburg release said the Roseburg Public Works Department has hired a contractor to replace six curb ramps on Douglas Avenue at Southeast Rose, Jackson and Main streets. Curb ramp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA HEALTH NEWTON CREEK CLINIC BACK TO SCHOOL DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122625</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/umpqua-health-newton-creek-clinic-back-to-school-day/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-health-newton-creek-clinic-back-to-school-day"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:11:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 3:20 a.m. Umpqua Health has its Back-to-School Day Monday. The event runs from 10:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m. and offers a wide range of services to make sure children are ready and healthy for school. That includes: *Free immunizations for students from preschool through college *Free sports physicals which are required for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCD 2ND ANNUAL ABUNDANCY CONCEPT EVENT IN SEPTEMBER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122623</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/ccd-2nd-annual-abundancy-concept-event-in-september/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ccd-2nd-annual-abundancy-concept-event-in-september"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 3:05 a.m. CCD Business Development Corporation is bringing its second annual Abundancy Concept Event to Roseburg on Tuesday, September 17th. The small business workshop is dedicated to owners and organizations who want to connect and network with their community. Attendees will hear presentations from subject matter experts designed to inspire, inform and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LONGEST TABLE, COMMUNITY DINNER AND CELEBRATION SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122621</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/19/longest-table-community-dinner-and-celebration-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=longest-table-community-dinner-and-celebration-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 19, 2024 2:50 a.m. Thrive Umpqua’s “The Longest Table, Community Dinner and Celebration” event is this Saturday. A release said residents are invited to gather for a farm-to-table style dinner, crafted by local chefs, at the Stewart Park green bridge, on Northwest Parks Drive between Fir Grove School and the soccer fields in Roseburg....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FISH AND WILDLIFE SEEKING INFORMATION ABOUT COW ELK KILLING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122618</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/18/fish-and-wildlife-seeking-information-about-cow-elk-killing/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fish-and-wildlife-seeking-information-about-cow-elk-killing"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T21:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 18, 2024 2:30 p.m.  The Oregon State Police Fish & Wildlife Division is seeking the public’s help in identifying the person or persons responsible for the killing and waste of a cow elk in Douglas County. An OSP report said the preliminary investigation indicated the animal was shot and left to waste in a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADDITIONAL DOWNGRADES TO EVACUATION NOTICES ON DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122616</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/18/additional-downgrades-to-evacuation-notices-on-dixon-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=additional-downgrades-to-evacuation-notices-on-dixon-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T21:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 18, 2024 2:20 p.m.  The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office has implemented additional evacuation downgrades for the Dixon Fire, due to suppression efforts. No Level 3 evacuation notices exist for this incident. The previous Level 3 evacuation notices have been downgraded. Four evacuation notices have been canceled. Get the latest information by viewing an interactive...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX 5,832 ACRES, 31 PERCENT CONTAINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122612</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/18/homestead-complex-5832-acres-31-percent-contained/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-5832-acres-31-percent-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T21:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 18, 2024 2:10 p.m.    The Homestead Complex on the Umpqua National Forest includes 7 fires totaling 5,832 acres with an overall containment of 31 percent. A UNF update said there are 771 personnel currently assigned to the complex. Northern Rockies Team 6 Is taking over management of the complex as of Monday morning....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX AT 10,843 ACRES, 833 PERSONNEL ASSIGINED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122609</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/18/diamond-complex-at-10843-acres-833-personnel-assigined/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-at-10843-acres-833-personnel-assigined"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T20:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 18, 2024 1:40 p.m. The Diamond Complex on the Umpqua National Forest consists of 28 lightning caused fires totaling approximately 10,843 acres, with 833 personnel assigned. A UNF update said 19 of the 28 fires in the Diamond Complex are now 100 percent contained. The Middle Fork in the northwest corner of Crater Lake...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEARCH UNDERWAY FOR MAN PRESUMED DROWNED AT DIAMOND LAKE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122607</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/18/search-underway-for-man-presumed-drowned-at-diamond-lake/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=search-underway-for-man-presumed-drowned-at-diamond-lake"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T20:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 18, 2024 1:20 p.m.  The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office is continuing a search for a man who is presumed to have drowned at Diamond Lake Saturday evening. Saturday just before 5:40 p.m. 911 dispatchers received a report of a man who had been on a pontoon boat with friends at Diamond Lake when he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man presumed drowned at Diamond Lake, search underway]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2637006a-5d94-11ef-9284-f7bbc7321347</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/man-presumed-drowned-at-diamond-lake-search-underway/article_2637006a-5d94-11ef-9284-f7bbc7321347.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND LAKE — A man presumably drowned Saturday evening at Diamond Lake and first responders are continuing the search for his body Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search Underway for Man Presumed Drowned at Diamond Lake (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174631</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174631"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T17:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND LAKE, Ore. - The Douglas County Sheriff's Office is continuing a search for a man who drowned at Diamond Lake Saturday evening. 
On Saturday, August 17, 2024, at approximately 5:38 pm, 9-1-1 dispatchers received a report of a man who had been on a pontoon boat with friends at Diamond Lake when he jumped into the water to swim. Shortly after entering the water the victim went under and never resurfaced. 
Marine Deputies, along with a rescue crew from Central Douglas Fire & Rescue and an ambulance from Umpqua Valley responded to the scene. Along with volunteers from the Diamond Lake Resort, crews searched unsuccessfully until dark. The 37-year-old, whose name is being withheld pending next of kin notification, is presumed drowned.
Today, searchers have returned to Diamond Lake to resume recovery efforts. Resources from Douglas County Marine Patrol, Douglas County Dive Team, Douglas County Search and Rescue, Klamath County Sheriff's Office Search and Rescue, and Oregon State Police are on scene.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DECREASE IN FIRE DANGER LEVELS CAUSES A DECREASE IN RESTRICTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122604</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/18/decrease-in-fire-danger-levels-causes-a-decrease-in-restrictions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=decrease-in-fire-danger-levels-causes-a-decrease-in-restrictions"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T12:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 18, 2024 5:20 a.m.  Industrial Fire Precaution Levels have decreased to IFPL LEVEL 2 on all lands protected by the Douglas Forest Protective Association. Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said that includes lands managed by the Bureau of Land Management. Pope said Public Use Restrictions have decreased to moderate for all private, county, state,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life in a fire camp: Strong plans keep the ducks in a row]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e751bd60-5ce2-11ef-9403-77fdc2b97cbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/life-in-a-fire-camp-strong-plans-keep-the-ducks-in-a-row/article_e751bd60-5ce2-11ef-9403-77fdc2b97cbe.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editor’s Note:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plein air painting favorites]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7bac60e6-5cd4-11ef-a403-13844eb84ce8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/plein-air-painting-favorites/article_7bac60e6-5cd4-11ef-a403-13844eb84ce8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T04:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Plein Air just around the corner, here’s a list of notable locations to paint. For serious artists or budding beginners, this list is for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MERCEDES ORR For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing people of all ages together at Sutherlin Blackberry Festival]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d5f5a174-5cd5-11ef-b78a-6764beea8066</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/bringing-people-of-all-ages-together-at-sutherlin-blackberry-festival/article_d5f5a174-5cd5-11ef-b78a-6764beea8066.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Those in need of a good time and a busy weekend flocked to the Sutherlin Blackberry Festival to look at cars, play mud volleyball and participate in BMX bike racing among other festival activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARIAH JOHNSTON The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed intervenors denied in Winchester Dam lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ab6e6bb8-5cdd-11ef-bae0-3f65e8d9e824</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/proposed-intervenors-denied-in-winchester-dam-lawsuit/article_ab6e6bb8-5cdd-11ef-bae0-3f65e8d9e824.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Circuit Court Pro Tem Judge Jason Thomas denied the motion to intervene in the State of Oregon vs. Winchester Water Control District and Co. lawsuit at a status check hearing Friday morning in the Douglas County Circuit Court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cow Creek Umpqua tribal timber used in airport remodel]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e6eedf68-5c12-11ef-97cb-3ffa892ae6c5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/cow-creek-umpqua-tribal-timber-used-in-airport-remodel/article_e6eedf68-5c12-11ef-97cb-3ffa892ae6c5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PORTLAND — Leaders of the Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Tribe of Indians celebrated the remodel of Portland International Airport, which incorporated local timber, on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEVERE THUNDERSTORM WATCH THROUGH 9:00 P.M. SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122600</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/17/severe-thunderstorm-watch-through-900-p-m-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=severe-thunderstorm-watch-through-900-p-m-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T21:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 17, 2024 2:00 p.m.  The National Weather Service has issued a Severe Thunderstorm Watch for much of southern Oregon through 9:00 p.m. Saturday. Forecasters said a strong thunderstorm will impact portions of south-central Douglas, northwest Jackson and northeastern Josephine counties Just after 1:30 p.m. Doppler radar was tracking a strong thunderstorm near Interstate 5...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintenance starts Monday on Douglas Ave.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9fa2cd78-5c0c-11ef-a402-9bd544e0c56a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/maintenance-starts-monday-on-douglas-ave/article_9fa2cd78-5c0c-11ef-a402-9bd544e0c56a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T20:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Roseburg Public Works Department hired a contractor to replace six curb ramps on Southeast Douglas Avenue, starting Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Additional Downgrades to Evacuation Notices on Dixon Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174626</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174626"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T18:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADDITIONAL DOWNGRADES TO EVACUATION NOTICES
TILLER, Ore. - Additional evacuation downgrades have been implemented for the Dixon Fire due to fire suppression efforts. The following is a summary of the current evacuation levels as of Saturday, August 17, 2024, as of 12:00 pm. An interactive map reflecting these evacuation levels can be found online at www.dcso.com/evacuations. 

LEVEL 3 "GO!":
No Level 3 evacuation notices exist for this incident. The previous Level 3 evacuation notices for this incident have been downgraded. 
 

LEVEL 2 "BE SET":
All residences on Crume Ranch Lane
All residences on Devil's Knob Road, also known as USFS Road #1610
All residences on the north side of Tiller Trail Highway from the intersection of Devil's Knob (USFS 1610) south to milepost 32.5 on Tiller Trail …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD COMPLEX AT 5,698 ACRES, CONTAINMENT AT 27 PERCENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122598</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/17/homestead-complex-at-5698-acres-containment-at-27-percent/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-complex-at-5698-acres-containment-at-27-percent"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T17:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 17, 2024 10:05 a.m. The Homestead Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest includes 7 fires burning in 5,698 acres, with an overall containment of 27 percent. A UNF update said 774 personnel are currently assigned to the complex. The largest fires are: *Horse Heaven Creek Fire: 2,240 acres *No Man Fire: 1,899 acres...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX RISES TO 10,843 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122596</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/17/diamond-complex-rises-to-10843-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-rises-to-10843-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T16:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 17, 2024 9:55 a.m. The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, consists of 28 lightning caused fires totaling approximately 10,843 acres, with 823 people assigned. A UNF update said the Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 59 people assigned. The park remains open. The North...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONTAINMENT MORE THAN DOUBLES ON DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122594</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/17/containment-more-than-doubles-on-dixon-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=containment-more-than-doubles-on-dixon-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T16:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 17, 2024 9:45 a.m. Containment on the Dixon Fire increased from 11 percent to 23 percent on Friday night. An update said this was possible due to around-the-clock efforts of fire responders. Operations Section Chief Adam Sinkey said, “Having a 24/7 operation has been absolutely crucial to our success in catching this fire and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRAIN MAN JAILED ON WARRANT/DRUG CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122592</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/17/drain-man-jailed-on-warrant-drug-charge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=drain-man-jailed-on-warrant-drug-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T14:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 17, 2024 8:00 a.m. A Drain man was jailed for a warrant and on a drug charge by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office Friday night. A DCSO report said just before 6:30 p.m. a deputy made a traffic stop on a vehicle near the intersection of Cedar Street and West B Street in Drain....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangkok West owners to retire at the end of the month]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bb907958-5b8b-11ef-9ee6-f7fc55999112</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/bangkok-west-owners-to-retire-at-the-end-of-the-month/article_bb907958-5b8b-11ef-9ee6-f7fc55999112.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The family-owned Bangkok West Thai restaurant will close Aug. 30 and owners of 18 years, Samart and Jitpasson Khaehit Phet, will enjoy the retired life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Erika Bare ready to unlock potential at South Umpqua School District]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d6e89664-5b8f-11ef-a456-8b612461819f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/erika-bare-ready-to-unlock-potential-at-south-umpqua-school-district/article_d6e89664-5b8f-11ef-a456-8b612461819f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — New superintendent, Erika Bare, said the South Umpqua School District motto contributed to her decision to join the district.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RED FLAG WARNING FOR REGION FOR SATURDAY AFTERNOON/EVENING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122589</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/17/red-flag-warning-for-region-for-saturday-afternoon-evening/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=red-flag-warning-for-region-for-saturday-afternoon-evening"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T13:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 17, 2024 6:40 a.m. The National Weather Service has issued a Red Flag Warning in effect from 1:00 p.m. to 9:00 p.m. on Saturday for abundant lightning on dry fuels in much of the region. The Warning area includes the Umpqua National Forest, Umpqua Basin, Southern Oregon Cascades and Siskiyou Mountains, eastern Rogue Valley...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Little’s Kids Back to School Shopping Spree sees success]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e124e6e4-5b37-11ef-841f-3bb5f33cb5c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/john-little-s-kids-back-to-school-shopping-spree-sees-success/article_e124e6e4-5b37-11ef-841f-3bb5f33cb5c6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Little’s Kids Back to School Shopping Spree returned for the 21st time on Aug. 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DORIS KOBERNIK For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extension Spotlight: Tree school Umpqua — a great place to learn and grow]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d02a7138-59bb-11ef-a986-0fbfe7ca6b56</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/extension-spotlight-tree-school-umpqua-a-great-place-to-learn-and-grow/article_d02a7138-59bb-11ef-a986-0fbfe7ca6b56.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you own or manage a small woodlot in Southern Oregon? Are you thinking about acquiring property? Are you a land manager, logger, arborist, certified pesticide applicator, or simply a natural resource enthusiast? If you answered “yes” to any of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alicia Christiansen For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer reading program wraps up]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a27b162a-5beb-11ef-a3d1-47c94d51a1b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/summer-reading-program-wraps-up/article_a27b162a-5beb-11ef-a3d1-47c94d51a1b8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library’s Summer Reading Program is drawing to a close.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley for The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon's nonfarm payroll employment rises in July]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3c9346e8-5b3c-11ef-a95a-c7dc6fa34e4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/oregons-nonfarm-payroll-employment-rises-in-july/article_3c9346e8-5b3c-11ef-a95a-c7dc6fa34e4a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July, Oregon’s seasonally adjusted nonfarm payroll employment rose by 8,500 jobs, following a revised decline of 700 jobs in June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODF TEAM 2 GAINS UPPER HAND ON DIXON FIRE AHEAD OF RED FLAG WARNING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122587</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/17/odf-team-2-gains-upper-hand-on-dixon-fire-ahead-of-red-flag-warning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=odf-team-2-gains-upper-hand-on-dixon-fire-ahead-of-red-flag-warning"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T13:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 17, 2024 6:20 a.m.  The Oregon Department of Forestry Team 2 has gained the upper hand on the Dixon Fire, ahead of Red Flag conditions. A fire update said there has been no new fire growth for a third consecutive day. It remains at 1,997 acres and is 23 percent contained as of Friday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALL BUT 1 EVACUATION ZONE CANCELED ON DIAMOND COMPLEX]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122585</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/17/all-but-1-evacuation-zone-canceled-on-diamond-complex/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=all-but-1-evacuation-zone-canceled-on-diamond-complex"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T13:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 17, 2024 6:00 a.m. In coordination with fire managers, the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office has canceled all but one evacuation zone in the Diamond Complex. A Level 1 Be Ready notice remains in place for one residence on the east side of the Potter Fire. An interactive map reflecting current evacuation areas can be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All But One Level 1 Evacuation Zone Cancelled on Diamond Complex]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174620</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news174620"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T03:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND LAKE, Ore. - In coordination with fire managers, the Douglas County Sheriff's Office has cancelled most evacuation levels in the Diamond Complex. 
CANCELLED EVACUATION LEVELS: 

All homes in the Slide Creek area downstream to the Soda Springs area
Lemolo Lake area, including the KOA and all USFS Campgrounds around the lake
Diamond Lake Horse Corrals
Diamond Lake Campground (east side of the lake) - ALL 238 sites, all loops A-M.
Diamond Lake RV Park - All 110 sites.
Pacific Crest Trail from the Intersection of Highway 138E at the North Crater Trailhead to the intersection of Maidu Lake Trail #1446 near Miller Lake. 
USFS North Crater Trail #1410
USFS Mt. Thielsen Trail #1456
USFS Summit Rock / Crater Trail #1457
USFS Spruce Ridge Trail #1458
USFS Howlock Mountain Trail #1448
USFS Thielsen Creek Trail #1449

LEVEL 1 EVACUATION LEVEL
A Level 1 - Be Ready Notice remains in place for one residence on the east side of the Potter Fire. 
A LEVEL 1 - BE READY EVACUATION NOTICE means you should be aware of the danger that exists in the area, monitor emergency services websites and local media outlets for information. This is the time for preparation and precautionary movement of persons with special needs, mobile property and (under certain circumstances) pets and livestock. If conditions worsen, emergency services personnel may contact you via an emergency notification system.
An interactive evacuation map reflecting current evacuation areas can be found on our website at https://www.dcso.com/evacuations.
UNITED STATES FOREST SERVICE FOREST CLOSURE REMAINS IN PLACE
Although evacuation level have been cancelled in these areas, it is important to know that there is a significant forest closure which may include the above USFS roads, campgrounds and trails. This forest closure is independent of the Sheriff's Office evacuation notice process. For current information on the status of the campgrounds and associated forest closure, please contact the United States Forest Service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RED FLAG WARNING FOR MUCH OF REGION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122582</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/red-flag-warning-for-much-of-region/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=red-flag-warning-for-much-of-region"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T21:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 2:00 p.m.  The National Weather Service has issued a Red Flag Warning in effect from 1:00 p.m. to 9:00 p.m. Saturday for abundant lightning on dry fuels in much of the region. The Warning area includes the Umpqua Basin, Umpqua National Forest, Southern Oregon Cascades and Siskiyou Mountains, and Western Rogue Basin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 8.16.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122577</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/inside-douglas-county-8-16-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-8-16-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T20:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates on the Diamond Complex and Homestead Complex fires with fire information staffers Jeni Garcin and Jim Cahill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police seek information about elk killing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6eee2f2a-5c0b-11ef-9312-4b9f431f7685</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/police-seek-information-about-elk-killing/article_6eee2f2a-5c0b-11ef-9312-4b9f431f7685.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T20:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — Oregon State Police Fish and Wildlife Division is seeking information connected to the killing and waste of a cow elk in Douglas County.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norris Blueberry fruitstand reopens]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d0bad2fe-5b3d-11ef-bae7-4bdfe8778de1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/norris-blueberry-fruitstand-reopens/article_d0bad2fe-5b3d-11ef-bae7-4bdfe8778de1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T19:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Norris Blueberry Farms reopened its fruit stand Friday at 13900 Garden Valley Road in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOMESTEAD FIRE GROWS TO 5,597 ACRES, CONTAINMENT AT 26 PERCENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122575</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/homestead-fire-grows-to-5597-acres-containment-at-26-percent/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=homestead-fire-grows-to-5597-acres-containment-at-26-percent"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T18:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 11:10 a.m.  The Homestead Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest includes 7 fires that have grown to 5,597 acres with an overall containment of 26 percent. A UNF update said 646 personnel are currently working on the fire. The largest of the fires are: *Horse Heaven Creek Fire: 2,240 acres *No...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIAMOND COMPLEX AT 10,455 ACRES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122573</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/diamond-complex-at-10455-acres/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=diamond-complex-at-10455-acres"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T17:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 10:50 a.m. The Diamond Complex, burning on the Umpqua National Forest, consists of 28 lightning caused fires totaling approximately 10,455 acres, with 832 people assigned. A UNF update said a new start was discovered recently. The Middle Fork Fire in the northwest corner of Crater Lake National Park has 38 people assigned....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STATE FIRE MARSHAL THANKED FOR PARTNERSHIP-DIXON FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122571</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/state-fire-marshal-thanked-for-partnership-dixon-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=state-fire-marshal-thanked-for-partnership-dixon-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T17:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 10:30 a.m. After several days of structure preparation and protection, Oregon State Fire Marshal crews demobilized from the Dixon Fire Friday morning. Oregon Department of Forestry Incident Commander Matt Howard said, “Thanks in part to OSFM’s efforts, this fire is on a very positive trajectory”. Howard said, “OSFM provides strong service to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN AFTER TRAFFIC STOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122569</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/roseburg-police-cite-man-after-traffic-stop/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-after-traffic-stop"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T17:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 10:10 a.m.   Roseburg Police cited a man after a traffic stop on Thursday. An RPD report said at approximately 9:15 p.m. officers stopped a vehicle for a traffic violation in the 2000 block of Northeast Diamond Lae Boulevard. They observed drug paraphernalia in plain view. The driver, a 33-year-old Myrtle Creek man,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PAST THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122567</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-past-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-past-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T17:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for a past theft case on Thursday. An RPD report said at 7:30 p.m. the 27-year-old was contacted in the 900 block of Northeast Klamath Street. He was cited for second-degree theft and was cited in lieu of custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANTS/DRUG CRIME]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122565</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrants-drug-crime/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrants-drug-crime"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for warrants and drug crimes on Thursday. An RPD report said just after 8:00 p.m.34-year-old Earl Cary was seen walking through the parking lot of a business in the 1500 block of Northeast Stephens Street. The man was known to have outstanding warrants. Dispatch confirmed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL FUGITIVE THURSDAY EVENING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122563</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-thursday-evening/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-thursday-evening"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 9;30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a fugitive on Thursday evening. An RPD report said at 7:10 p.m. an officer was driving through the parking lot of a business in the 1500 block of Northeast Stephens Street and saw the 25-year-old woman sitting in a parked vehicle. The officer believed she had a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR PREVIOUS THEFT CASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122561</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-previous-theft-case/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-previous-theft-case"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 16, 2024 9;20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman Thursday for a previous theft. An RPD report said at 9:30 a.m. the 35-year-old was contacted in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street. She was taken into custody and charged with second-degree theft. The woman was detained without bail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geneva hosts informational meeting]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0b11fd60-5bed-11ef-9807-3798657b7125</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/geneva-hosts-informational-meeting/article_0b11fd60-5bed-11ef-9807-3798657b7125.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geneva Academy is hosting an information meeting from 6:30-7:30 p.m. Thursday at its 2245 NW Kline Street Campus in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 8.16.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122558</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/local-real-estate-today-8-16-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-8-16-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert from the Mary Gilbert Group powered by Place at Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our local real estate update for this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 8.16.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=122554</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/08/16/morning-conversation-8-16-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-8-16-24"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Tribe of Indians Communications and Marketing Director Lindsay Campman talks about Tribal timber being used as part of a remodel at the Portland International Airport.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structures burned in Dixon Fire held memories for owners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/615b0e98-5b73-11ef-ad61-2b7257d93f94</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/structures-burned-in-dixon-fire-held-memories-for-owners/article_615b0e98-5b73-11ef-ad61-2b7257d93f94.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAYS CREEK — The Dixon Fire was estimated 1,997 acres with 11% containment Thursday evening, and the Oregon State Fire Marshal will demobilize from the fire to return home Friday morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trades camp students construct shelters for Hastings Village]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/71325d98-5b65-11ef-a432-bf6760c81c65</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/trades-camp-students-construct-shelters-for-hastings-village/article_71325d98-5b65-11ef-a432-bf6760c81c65.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Thor McCoy spent most of Thursday at the Sutherlin City Maintenance Shop working with power tools and wood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Four o'clock rock!]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f25bb974-58d0-11ef-a31c-e7fd09ed7b5b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/ask-a-master-gardener-four-oclock-rock/article_f25bb974-58d0-11ef-a31c-e7fd09ed7b5b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: While digging around with a friend in her new garden bed in late spring, we happened to spy an unusual green plant shooting up with paddle-shaped leaves. Curious, we dug it up, hoping to repot it and see what…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BONNIE COURTER Master Gardener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>