<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-10-14T16:13:45.085Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.14.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124814</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/morning-conversation-10-14-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-14-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiffany Roddy of the Douglas County Chapter of the Oregon Women in Timber talks about the educational program OWIT offers for young people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Board of Forestry to meet on Oct. 16 and 17 in Pendleton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175999</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news175999"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T15:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Oregon Board of Forestry will meet in Pendleton for their fall retreat on Oct. 16 and 17. The retreat’s two-day itinerary will include an executive session, field tour, and public social on Wednesday, Oct. 16, and an executive session and public meeting on Thursday, Oct. 17. Both executive sessions will be closed to the public, except for members of the press. The field tour and social event that will take place on Oct. 16 are open to the public for in-person participation, and recordings of highlights will be posted on the board’s meeting page afterward. The public meeting that will take place on Oct. 17 will be open for in-person observation and livestreamed on the department’s YouTube channel.
The board’s agenda for the retreat’s public meeting includes:

State of the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ELDERLY MAN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING HEAD-ON CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124805</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/elderly-man-taken-to-hospital-following-head-on-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=elderly-man-taken-to-hospital-following-head-on-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 4:00 a.m. An elderly man was taken to the hospital following a head-on crash on Saturday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 1:50 p.m. a 22-year-old driver was traveling north in his sedan on old Highway 99 North near Del Rio Road when he failed to maintain his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WOMAN JAILED ON 28 CHARGES: THEFT IN UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124803</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/woman-jailed-on-28-charges-theft-in-umpqua-national-forest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=woman-jailed-on-28-charges-theft-in-umpqua-national-forest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:50 a.m. A Myrtle Creek woman was jailed on 28 charges for alleged theft incidents in the Umpqua National Forest on Saturday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 5:45 p.m. a 45-year-old was stopped while driving a sedan on Highway 230 in the Tree Lakes Snow Park/Diamond Lake area. She...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLUMBUS DAY/INDIGENOUS PEOPLE’S DAY MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124801</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/columbus-day-indigenous-peoples-day-monday-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=columbus-day-indigenous-peoples-day-monday-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:40 a.m. Monday is Columbus Day, a federal holiday. However approximately 29 states and Washington D.C. do not celebrate it. In Oregon, Monday is Indigenous People’s Day and is a state holiday. With the two observances, federal and state offices will be closed. Regular mail will not be delivered. Banks and credit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY COUNCIL TO CONSIDER DOWNTOWN PARKING ENFORCEMENT OPTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124799</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/city-council-to-consider-downtown-parking-enforcement-options/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-council-to-consider-downtown-parking-enforcement-options"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Roseburg City Council will consider downtown parking enforcement options as part of its meeting Monday night. The city has had a contract with ACE Parking Enforcement since the start of 2022. However, ACE has failed to generate enough revenue to cover the cost of its contract. The council has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VETERAN’S HEALTH & AWARENESS FAIR ON TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124795</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/veterans-health-awareness-fair-on-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=veterans-health-awareness-fair-on-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3;20 a.m. The Roseburg VA Medical Center is presenting the 2024 Veteran’s Health & Awareness Fair on Tuesday. A VA release said the event is being held to help raise awareness as October is National Breast Cancer Awareness Month and National Domestic Violence Awareness Month. An Awareness Walk will begin at 11:00...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JERRY BRUCE CAMPUS NON-PROFIT PARTNERS TO HOLD TRUNK-OR-TREAT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124793</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/jerry-bruce-campus-non-profit-partners-to-hold-trunk-or-treat/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=jerry-bruce-campus-non-profit-partners-to-hold-trunk-or-treat"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 3:05 a.m. Jerry Bruce Community Campus partner organizations Family Development Center, the FISH Food Pantry, Umpqua Homes, United Community Action Network and Aviva Health are holding a truck-or-treat for local families this Saturday October 19th. It will take place from 12:00 p.m. to 3:00 p.m. in the Aviva Health parking lot on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPOUSAL AND SURVIVORS BENEFITS EDUCATIONAL SEMINAR]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124790</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/14/spousal-and-survivors-benefits-educational-seminar-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spousal-and-survivors-benefits-educational-seminar-3"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024, 2:50 a.m.  Associates of Vietnam Veterans of America will have a Spousal and Survivor Benefits Educational Seminar coming soon. The event will be held on Saturday, November 2nd from 10:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. at Garden Valley Church, at 3047 Garden Valley Road, west of Roseburg. Those attending can learn about the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN DIES IN VEHICLE VERSUS MOTORCYCLE ACCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124787</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/myrtle-creek-man-dies-in-vehicle-versus-motorcycle-accident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-dies-in-vehicle-versus-motorcycle-accident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 12, 2024 9:40 a.m. A Myrtle Creek man died in a vehicle versus motorcycle accident on Friday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said shortly after 10:30 p.m. dispatchers received a call regarding the wreck on Riddle Bypass Road near the intersection with E Street in Riddle. Deputies, along with fire and ambulance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN MAN JAILED FOR DUII/HIT AND RUN PROPERTY DAMAGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124785</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/sutherlin-man-jailed-for-duii-hit-and-run-property-damage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-man-jailed-for-duii-hit-and-run-property-damage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 9:20 a.m.   A Sutherlin man was jailed for a DUII and hit and run/property damage incident on Friday afternoon. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 5:10 p.m. the 21-year-old was driving north in the 2000 block of Southside Road in the Sutherlin area when he failed to negotiate a turn...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deputies Investigate Fatal Vehicle vs. Motorcycle Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175986</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news175986"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE, Ore. - A Myrtle Creek man died in a motorcycle vs. vehicle crash on Riddle Bypass Road Friday night. 
Shortly after 10:30 p.m. on Friday, October 11, 2024, 9-1-1 dispatchers received a report of a motorcycle vs. vehicle crash on Riddle Bypass Road near the intersection with E Street in Riddle. 
Deputies, along with fire and ambulance personnel, responded to the scene. Deputies learned that 81-year-old Warren Currier of Riddle was operating a 2007 Toyota Tacoma southbound on Riddle Bypass Road when he began a lefthand turn onto E Street. As Currier made the turn, a collision occurred with a northbound 2024 Ninja Kawasaki motorcycle operated by 20-year-old Gage Matthews of Myrtle Creek.
Matthews was pronounced deceased at the scene. Warren was transported by ambulance to Mercy Medical Center for treatment of his injuries. 
The roadway was closed for approximately five hours as deputies conducted the scene investigation. Anyone who witnessed the incident or may have information useful to the investigation is encouraged to contact the Douglas County Sheriff's Office at (541) 440-4471 or by email at dcso.pio@douglascountyor.gov. Reference Case #24-3959
The Douglas County Medical Examiner's Office, Riddle Fire District and Umpqua Valley Ambulance also responded to the scene.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO MAN JAILED FOR HAVING STOLEN VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124783</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/san-francisco-man-jailed-for-having-stolen-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=san-francisco-man-jailed-for-having-stolen-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 8:30 a.m. A San Francisco man was jailed for having a stolen vehicle on Wednesday night. An Oregon State Police report released late Friday said OSP had been notified that a recently stolen SUV from California was passing through the Grants Pass area. Just after 11:00 p.m. troopers located the vehicle in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BELLVUE, WASHINGTON MAN JAILED FOLLOWING HIT AND RUN CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124781</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/bellvue-washington-man-jailed-following-hit-and-run-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=bellvue-washington-man-jailed-following-hit-and-run-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 14, 2024 9:00 a.m.  A Bellevue, Washington man was jailed following a hit and run crash on Wednesday. An Oregon State Police report released late Friday said at 3:45 p.m. a witness said the crash had occurred on Interstate Five southbound about a mile south of the Rice Valley exit. The witness said the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION DISTRICT BOARD MEETING MONDAY AFTERNOON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124777</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/12/umpqua-public-transportation-district-board-meeting-monday-afternoon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-public-transportation-district-board-meeting-monday-afternoon"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 12, 2024 8:00 a.m. The Umpqua Public Transportation District Board of Directors will meet Monday afternoon. Board members will review applications for the interim general manager position and complete the final interview. An Executive Session, not open to the public, will be held to consider the employment of an officer, employee, staff member or...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.11.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124772</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/inside-douglas-county-10-11-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-11-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Dimof and Jeff Twibell of Thrive Umpqua talk about upcoming fall events that the organization is involved in and how to get involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA NATIONAL FOREST RESCINDS DIAMOND COMPLEX CLOSURE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124770</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/umpqua-national-forest-rescinds-diamond-complex-closure/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-national-forest-rescinds-diamond-complex-closure"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 10:50 a.m.  On Friday, the Umpqua National Forest rescinded the Diamond Complex Emergency Fire Closure Order. A UNF release said the closure impacted a small portion of the Diamond Lake Ranger District, just east of the Boulder Creek Wilderness. The Homestead Emergency Fire Closure Order still remains in effect on portions of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBGURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR OVERNIGHT DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124768</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/rosebgurg-police-cite-man-for-overnight-drinking-in-public/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rosebgurg-police-cite-man-for-overnight-drinking-in-public"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 10:40 a.m.   Roseburg Police cited a man for drinking in public early Friday. An RPD report said at 3:30 a.m. the 28-year-old was stopped for walking in the middle of the road in the 900 block of Northwest Highland Street. The man allegedly had an open alcoholic beverage in his hand. He...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE TEEN FOR PREVIOUS STORE THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124766</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/roseburg-police-cite-teen-for-previous-store-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-teen-for-previous-store-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 10:30 a.m.   Roseburg Police cited a teen for a previous store theft on Thursday. An RPD report said officers identified the 16-year-old male as the suspect in the incident at Fred Meyer, in the 900 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. He was called on the phone and admitted to theft from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR UNLAWFUL COASTING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124764</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-unlawful-coasting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-unlawful-coasting"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 10:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a 48-year-old woman for unlawful coasting following an early morning accident on Friday. An RPD report said at 5:30 a.m. the woman’s van, which is 52-years old, did not run. She was coasting in it west on Northwest Edenbower Boulevard and turned left onto Northwest Aviation Drive...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE THREE PEOPLE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124762</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/roseburg-police-cite-three-people-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-three-people-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police cited three people for prohibited camping on Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 10:45 a.m. officers contacted the men, ranging in age from 49 to 54, at their camp in Deer Creek Park in the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street. The camps were in violation of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR FAILURE TO APPEAR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124760</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-failure-to-appear-warrant-3/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-failure-to-appear-warrant-3"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man Thursday for a failure to appear warrant. An RPD report said at 4:00 p.m. the 56-year-old was contacted under the Stewart Park Pavilion on Stewart Park Drive. An officer learned that he had an active warrant for his arrest. He was taken into custody without...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YONCALLA MAN JAILED FOR PAROLE VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124758</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/yoncalla-man-jailed-for-parole-violation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=yoncalla-man-jailed-for-parole-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 9:50 a.m.  A Yoncalla man was jailed for a parole violation by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office Thursday night. A DCSO report said at 6:00 p.m. a deputy contacted the 40-year-old in the 5200 block of Elkhead Road near Yoncalla. The deputy learned that the man was wanted by his parole officer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND MAN JAILED FOR FELONY COUNT OF DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124756</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/oakland-man-jailed-for-felony-count-of-driving-while-suspended/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oakland-man-jailed-for-felony-count-of-driving-while-suspended"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 9:40 a.m.   An Oakland man was jailed for a felony count of driving while suspended on Thursday evening. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 7:30 p.m. a deputy stopped a pickup for failing to maintain a lane of travel in the 5900 block of Elkhead Road, north of Oakland. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAYS CREEK MAN TAKEN TO HOSPITAL FOLLOWING SINGLE-VEHICLE CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124754</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/days-creek-man-taken-to-hospital-following-single-vehicle-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=days-creek-man-taken-to-hospital-following-single-vehicle-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 9:20 a.m. A Days Creek man was taken to the hospital following a single-vehicle crash on Thursday morning. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 8:25 a.m. the 20-year-old was driving a westbound SUV in the 8700 block of Tiller Trail Highway in the Canyonville area when he began to have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 10.11.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124752</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/local-real-estate-today-10-11-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-10-11-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group of Keller Williams Southern Oregon has Local Real Estate Today – a look at the local market and information you should know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What a year for this reader]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bfa0f91c-85b3-11ef-b20d-d77ddc73f4ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/what-a-year-for-this-reader/article_bfa0f91c-85b3-11ef-b20d-d77ddc73f4ac.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am in the final push to reach my reading goal of 200 books this year, and with a couple of well-timed days off from work, I think I’ll make it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KRIS WILEY For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a master gardener: Growing eucalyptus]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/27c2d178-84fb-11ef-9bf5-b3832df8fb1f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/ask-a-master-gardener-growing-eucalyptus/article_27c2d178-84fb-11ef-9bf5-b3832df8fb1f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I want to grow some eucalyptus to use for decorating and in flower arrangements. Is that possible in our climate?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JANET BITTER Master Gardener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planning for the future: Creating ties to the land]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4ce34aec-8667-11ef-9b02-b73e29861563</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/planning-for-the-future-creating-ties-to-the-land/article_4ce34aec-8667-11ef-9b02-b73e29861563.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you own a forest, farm, or rangeland, you probably are concerned about leaving those lands in good shape for future generations. If you have seen a crop through to harvest, whether it is timber, corn or cattle, you have…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alicia Christiansen For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public School grads return as teachers to serve the community]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/82db6ad0-84fa-11ef-a43e-933b33f01a4d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/roseburg-public-school-grads-return-as-teachers-to-serve-the-community/article_82db6ad0-84fa-11ef-a43e-933b33f01a4d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the heart of Roseburg High School, a unique bond has formed between past and present, as former students have returned to their roots to teach. Around a third of the school’s teachers are Roseburg High School graduates. These educators…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heather Villa For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making a Difference One Project at a Time]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b6fca136-85b2-11ef-9fa0-3fac7609d01e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/making-a-difference-one-project-at-a-time/article_b6fca136-85b2-11ef-9fa0-3fac7609d01e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come one, come all — it’s time to Make a Difference! The third annual Make a Difference Day — Douglas County will take place on Saturday, Oct. 26 from 9 a.m. to noon at sites in Roseburg, Glide and Winchester.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JENNIFER D. COALWELL For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeking: hats, scarves and afghans for children]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a2239b12-85b6-11ef-9223-0b771b0c6500</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/seeking-hats-scarves-and-afghans-for-children/article_a2239b12-85b6-11ef-9223-0b771b0c6500.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seeking: hats, scarves and afghans for children]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TEAMSTERS EXTEND PICKET LINES TO EVERY BIGFOOT LOCATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124742</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/teamsters-extend-picket-lines-to-every-bigfoot-location/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=teamsters-extend-picket-lines-to-every-bigfoot-location"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T10:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 3:50 a.m.  Teamsters have extended picket lines to every Bigfoot Beverages location including its distribution facility in Bend. A release from Teamsters Joint Council 37 calls the move part of an unfair labor practice strike led by more than 240 members of Teamsters locals 206 and 324. Secretary-Treasurer of Local 324 Chris...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FARMERS MARKET TO MOVE TO DOWNTOWN ROSEBURG IN NOVEMBER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124739</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/farmers-market-to-move-to-downtown-roseburg-in-november/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=farmers-market-to-move-to-downtown-roseburg-in-november"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T10:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 3:40 a.m.  After months of planning with the City of Roseburg, and meeting with downtown businesses and vendors, the Umpqua Valley Farmers’ Market has announced that it will move to the 500 block of Southeast Jackson Street downtown beginning on November 2nd. Market Manager Erin Maidlow said the longest running farmers’ market...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIMBER OPERATORS HOLD FINAL BREAKFAST MEETING OF 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124737</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/timber-operators-hold-final-breakfast-meeting-of-2024/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=timber-operators-hold-final-breakfast-meeting-of-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T10:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 3:30 a.m. Douglas Timber Operators will have their final breakfast meeting of the year on Thursday, October 24th. It will be held at 8:00 a.m. in The Loft at the Del Rey Café’ on Northeast Stephens Street in Winchester. The no host event will feature Douglas County Clerk Daniel Loomis. His presentation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG’S NEEWOLLAH PARADE PROMISES FRIGHTFUL FUN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124733</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/roseburgs-neewollah-parade-promises-frightful-fun/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburgs-neewollah-parade-promises-frightful-fun"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T10:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 3:20 a.m. Roseburg’s Neewollah Parade promises an evening of frightful fun in downtown on Halloween evening, October 31st, at 5:00 p.m. A city release said hundreds of costumed tricksters will prowl the pavement, Captain Jack Sparrow will return with his Black Pearl pirate ship and dancing witches will shake their broomsticks. A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA WOOFSTOCK PRESENTS HOWL-O-WEEN SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124731</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/umpqua-woofstock-presents-howl-o-ween-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-woofstock-presents-howl-o-ween-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T10:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 3:05 a.m. Umpqua Woofstock presents the 2024 Howl-O-Ween carnival and discount pet vaccine clinic on Saturday. It will take place at Central Park on East Central Avenue in Sutherlin. The carnival runs from 10:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. with the vaccine clinic beginning at 11:00 a.m. The event includes games, vendors, storytelling,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC WITH FINAL PUBLIC STARGAZING EVENT OF 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=124729</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/11/ucc-with-final-public-stargazing-event-of-2023/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-with-final-public-stargazing-event-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T10:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 11, 2024 2:50 a.m. Umpqua Community College has their final public stargazing event of the year next Friday night, October 18th. It will be held at the Paul Morgan observatory from 6:30 p.m. to 8:00 p.m. The public can join UCC astronomers to see a new comet and more. Attendees should bring folding chairs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indoor Market enters into second year in Myrtle Creek Grange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bae7c942-86b1-11ef-a47b-df0e9fc733d3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/indoor-market-enters-into-second-year-in-myrtle-creek-grange/article_bae7c942-86b1-11ef-a47b-df0e9fc733d3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — Ethan Perkins owns a dahlia farm with his family in Myrtle Creek. He and his wife also find time for other projects to work on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International pianist Andreev crescendos into Oakland]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d6f7e4f6-86b0-11ef-8f6b-5fdbd30ce8ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/international-pianist-andreev-crescendos-into-oakland/article_d6f7e4f6-86b0-11ef-8f6b-5fdbd30ce8ab.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — In the next stage of his life, Andrei Andreev is hoping to make a performance career for himself in the United States. He plans to start his concerts by playing at The Secret Wine Society in Oakland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans health, awareness fair on Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c27a2af2-8660-11ef-93f1-2b33af59daee</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/veterans-health-awareness-fair-on-tuesday/article_c27a2af2-8660-11ef-93f1-2b33af59daee.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Community partners are hosting a veteran's health and awareness fair from 11 a.m. to 3 p.m. Tuesday, Oct. 15 at the Roseburg VA Medical Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mercy sued following alleged patient assault]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d526ea2e-868c-11ef-86a0-abce1b59ac3e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/mercy-sued-following-alleged-patient-assault/article_d526ea2e-868c-11ef-86a0-abce1b59ac3e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A woman who says she was wrongly placed in the psychiatric ward at CHI Mercy Health is suing the hospital, claiming a mentally ill patient in the ward, who was left unsupervised, entered her room and assaulted her.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remain fire prepared during Fire Prevention Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/856fe9c0-85e4-11ef-b8cd-2b1242577d78</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/remain-fire-prepared-during-fire-prevention-week/article_856fe9c0-85e4-11ef-b8cd-2b1242577d78.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Fire Protection Association named October 6-12 as Fire Prevention Week, according to its website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Woofstock hosts animal halloween party in Sutherlin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e276d1f0-8211-11ef-88bb-d3f2ec894f5a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/umpqua-woofstock-hosts-animal-halloween-party-in-sutherlin/article_e276d1f0-8211-11ef-88bb-d3f2ec894f5a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Umpqua Woofstock’s Howl-O-Ween will bring fun, games, prizes and many treats for animals and people alike to Central Park in Sutherlin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Howl-O-Ween bounds into Sutherlin on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e276d1f0-8211-11ef-88bb-d3f2ec894f5a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/howl-o-ween-bounds-into-sutherlin-on-saturday/article_e276d1f0-8211-11ef-88bb-d3f2ec894f5a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Umpqua Woofstock's Howl-O-Ween will bring fun, games, prizes and many treats for animals and people alike to Central Park in Sutherlin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>