<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-06-21T23:10:06.749Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA PUBLIC USE RESTRICTION LEVEL CHANGE: TO MODERATE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120267</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/dfpa-public-use-restriction-level-change-to-moderate/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-public-use-restriction-level-change-to-moderate"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T20:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 1:30 p.m. Effective Saturday, the Douglas Forest Protective Association is changing the Public Use Restriction Level to Moderate for all private, county, state and Bureau of Indian Affairs lands within the Douglas District. Public Information Office Rachel Pope said this imposes certain fire restrictions on the public to help prevent wildfires. Pope...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 6.21.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120257</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/inside-douglas-county-6-21-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-6-21-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T20:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Commissioner Tom Kress talks about the FEMA grant the county has received to help in the up-grade of the 30-year old outdated communications radio system:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STATE FIRE MARSHAL MOBILIZES TWO TASK FORCES TO UPPER APPLEGATE FIRE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120254</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/state-fire-marshal-mobilizes-two-task-forces-to-upper-applegate-fire/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=state-fire-marshal-mobilizes-two-task-forces-to-upper-applegate-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T17:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 10:50 a.m.   Friday morning, the Oregon State Fire Marshal mobilized two structural task forces to the Upper Applegate Fire in Jackson County. An OSFM release said the task forces are from Lane and Polk counties and were mobilized through Immediate Response, a tool the state fire marshal uses to send firefighting resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Committee for Family Forestlands meets on June 26]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173207</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173207"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T17:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Committee for Family Forestlands will meet virtually on Wednesday, June 26 from 9 a.m. to 2:30 p.m. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda. 
The committee’s agenda includes:

Forest Resources Division update
Small Forestland Investment in Stream Habitat Program (SFISH) tax guidance
Stream crossing presentation
Oregon Forest Resources Institute (OFRI) guide overview
Board of Forestry update
CFF annual report

The meeting is open to the public to attend online via Zoom. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 24 hours before the meeting by emailing committee.of.family.forestlands@odf.oregon.gov.
The 13-member committee researches policies that affect family forests, natural resources and forestry benefits. Based on its findings, the committee recommends actions to the Oregon Board of Forestry and the State Forester. View more information on the CFF webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR CAMPING AFTER DISTURBANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120252</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-camping-after-disturbance/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-camping-after-disturbance"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T17:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 10:40 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for camping after a disturbance late Thursday night. An RPD report said shortly before 11:00 p.m. the 18-year-old was contacted at his camp following the incident in the 500 block of Southeast Stephens Street. He was found to be camping between the bike path and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120250</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-10/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-10"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T17:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 10:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping on Thursday. An RPD report said just before 11:00 a.m. the 43-year-old had his camp set up along the water’s edge at Stewart Park in the 2000 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive. This was near the Roseburg Parks Department Shops. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR REPORTED PRIOR THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120248</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-reported-prior-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-reported-prior-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T17:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 20204 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man Friday for a reported prior theft incident. An RPD report said the 42-year-old was developed as a suspect for an incident on Wednesday where he allegedly stole $100 worth of tools for a business in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens. At 1:00 a.m. Friday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODF sends 19 firefighters to New Mexico (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173194</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173194"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. – This week the Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) filled an order to send 19 firefighters to New Mexico to assist in fighting numerous, out of control wildfires. Many of the firefighters arrived in the state today and the rest will arrive within the next day. The two-week rotation with our New Mexico partners will allow our firefighters to brush up on their skills before Oregon’s fire season hits its peak later this summer. 
The firefighters went to New Mexico under mutual assistance agreements between the states. When wildfire activity is low in Oregon, firefighters can be spared to help in places experiencing high levels of wildfire. So far in 2024, Oregon has deployed:

48 firefighters to Texas
14 firefighters to Alaska
Five firefighters to California
Two firefighters to T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120246</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-7/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-7"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T16:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 9:55 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report said just after 4:00 p.m. the 36-year-old was contacted near the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and Northeast Neuner Street. He was found to have a warrant for his arrest. The man was also reportedly found...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAILED MAN FOR OVERNIGHT DUII]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120244</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/roseburg-police-jailed-man-for-overnight-duii/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jailed-man-for-overnight-duii"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T16:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 9:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an overnight DUII incident early Friday. An RDP report said at 12:50 a.m. the 38-year-old was stopped for an un-signaled turn near the corner of Northwest Board Street and Northwest Navajo Avenue. During the contact, officers observed signs of impairment. The driver agreed to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER ALLEGED HARASSMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120242</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/roseburg-police-jail-man-after-alleged-harassment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-after-alleged-harassment"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T16:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 9:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man after an alleged harassment incident on Thursday. An RPD report said at 7:10 a.m. the 62-year-old was contacted in the 500 block of Southeast Woodward Avenue. An investigation revealed that the suspect reportedly kicked a victim’s leg, leaving several red scratch marks. The man was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 6.21.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120238</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/local-real-estate-today-6-21-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-6-21-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T16:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group, Powered by Place of Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our weekly Local Real Estate Today feature:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 6.21.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120234</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/morning-conversation-6-21-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-6-21-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T16:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The News Review Editor Sanne Godrey and Special Sections Editor/Photographer Will Geschke talk about the Fairs, Festivals and Fun special section coming to Sunday’s edition of the paper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running the tables: Michael Murphy’s tear through the 2024 World Series of Poker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e2875e90-2f40-11ef-89d0-7b8f7c1124a6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/running-the-tables-michael-murphy-s-tear-through-the-2024-world-series-of-poker/article_e2875e90-2f40-11ef-89d0-7b8f7c1124a6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On day three of the World Series of Poker in Las Vegas, Roseburg resident Michael Murphy was at the top of the leaderboards with a total chip count of $7.7 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feeding the community for 20 years, and counting]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2fc9dd3e-2f34-11ef-bb11-57ed064a4f43</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/health/feeding-the-community-for-20-years-and-counting/article_2fc9dd3e-2f34-11ef-bb11-57ed064a4f43.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With full stomachs and a safe place, St. Joseph and St. Francis Xavier Catholic Church celebrate 20 years of serving the people of Douglas County in the community kitchen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARIAH JOHNSTON For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon lawmakers urge VA to build Roseburg veterans home]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/26fb3042-2fd7-11ef-95ee-cbe5b61dce00</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/oregon-lawmakers-urge-va-to-build-roseburg-veterans-home/article_26fb3042-2fd7-11ef-95ee-cbe5b61dce00.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T14:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon’s U.S. Sens. Jeff Merkley and Ron Wyden, alongside U.S. Rep. Val Hoyle, have urged the Department of Veterans Affairs to urgently prioritize the application and funding for the Oregon Department of Veterans Affairs Roseburg Veterans’ Home project in fiscal…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Weed or welcome addition?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d0d34f6a-2cc5-11ef-8ebd-973df6ac90a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/ask-a-master-gardener-weed-or-welcome-addition/article_d0d34f6a-2cc5-11ef-8ebd-973df6ac90a7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I have these plants with heart-shaped leaves growing in my garden. I would like to identify this plant before I spend any more time pulling it up. I have included a few photos. They are attractive but they grow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LINDA ESTEP Master Gardener</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERKLEY/WYDEN/HOYLE URGE VA TO BUILD ROSEBURG VETERANS’ HOME]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120230</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/merkley-wyden-hoyle-urge-va-to-build-roseburg-veterans-home/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=merkley-wyden-hoyle-urge-va-to-build-roseburg-veterans-home"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T11:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 4:10 a.m. Oregon’s U.S. Senators Jeff Merkley and Ron Wyden, alongside U.S. Representative Val Hoyle have urged the Department of Veterans Affairs to urgently prioritize the application and funding for the Oregon Department of Veterans Affairs Roseburg Veterans’ Home project in Fiscal Year 2025. A joint release said currently ODVA operates two...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO MORE DAYS AT OR NEAR 90 DEGREES FOR THE UMPQUA VALLEY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120228</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/two-more-days-at-or-near-90-degrees-for-the-umpqua-valley/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-more-days-at-or-near-90-degrees-for-the-umpqua-valley"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 3:50 a.m.  The Umpqua Valley will see two more days with high temperatures at or near 90 degrees before cooling for most of the next week. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said the mercury reached 88 degrees at the Roseburg Regional Airport on Thursday. The record for the date was 93...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 POSITIONS ELIMINATED IN RESTRUCTURING AT CHI MERCY MEDICAL CENTER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120226</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/18-positions-eliminated-in-restructuring-at-chi-mercy-medical-center/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=18-positions-eliminated-in-restructuring-at-chi-mercy-medical-center"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 3:30 a.m.  Restructuring is leading to the elimination of 18 positions at CHI Mercy Medical Center and Centennial Medical Group, according to Mercy Health CEO and President Russell Woolley. In an email, Wooley said, “Like health systems across the country, we continue to face financial pressures and workforce challenges. Our top priority...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY MANAGER EVALUATION GROUP WILL MEET JUNE 26TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120224</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/city-manager-evaluation-group-will-meet-june-26th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-manager-evaluation-group-will-meet-june-26th"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 3:20 a.m. Members of the Roseburg City Council and staff will meet next again week to talk about the city manager evaluation process. A city release said the group will gather on Wednesday, June 26th at 3:00 p.m. in the third-floor conference room at city hall. This group will meet on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOVIES IN THE PARK WITH THIRD FRIDAY NIGHT OF ENTERTAINMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120222</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/movies-in-the-park-with-third-friday-night-of-entertainment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=movies-in-the-park-with-third-friday-night-of-entertainment"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 3:05 a.m. Movies in the Park has its third evening of entertainment Friday night at the Nichols Band Shell in Roseburg’s Stewart Park. A city release said the series is cosponsored by Roseburg Parks and Recreation and Rogue Credit Union. Each week, pre-movie entertainment begins at 7:30 p.m. That’s followed by the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WYDEN INTRODUCES BILL TO EMPOWER FIRST RESPONDERS-TRAINING FOR EV CRASHES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120220</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/21/wyden-introduces-bill-to-empower-first-responders-training-for-ev-crashes/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wyden-introduces-bill-to-empower-first-responders-training-for-ev-crashes"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 21, 2024 2:50 a.m. On Thursday, Senator Ron Wyden introduced legislation that would require federal agencies to provide electric vehicle safety information, testing standards, and training materials for local first responders across the nation. A release said electric vehicles pose a unique challenge to first responders used to dealing with traditional vehicles. Batteries are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most popular library books so far this year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/474466ec-2f56-11ef-a001-c395a8410b51</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/most-popular-library-books-so-far-this-year/article_474466ec-2f56-11ef-a001-c395a8410b51.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library patrons continue to be wild about national bestsellers, manga and digital materials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley for The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vineyard tour moves to October]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d3916312-2f55-11ef-baa8-1f5fc983ba5e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/vineyard-tour-moves-to-october/article_d3916312-2f55-11ef-baa8-1f5fc983ba5e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA VALLEY — The Umpqua Velo Club is getting ready for this year’s Vineyard Tour and has made some big changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 soil and water conservation board positions on November ballot]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cffb6e5a-2f50-11ef-8d34-4b5dba9088b0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/elections/4-soil-and-water-conservation-board-positions-on-november-ballot/article_cffb6e5a-2f50-11ef-8d34-4b5dba9088b0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — There will be four positions on the Nov. 5 ballot for the Douglas Soil & Water Conservation District Board: Zone 1, Zone 2, Zone 3 and an at-large position.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 6.20.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120216</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/inside-douglas-county-6-20-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-6-20-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cow Creek Umpqua Indian Foundation Executive Director Carma Mornarich talks about their work and grants given out this week to non-profit organizations in several counties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALTRUSA STUFF THE EVENT IS SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120212</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/altrusa-stuff-the-event-is-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=altrusa-stuff-the-event-is-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 11:20 a.m.  The Altrusa Club of Roseburg will hold another Stuff the Bus with Children’s Books” event on Saturday. It will be held from 10:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m. in the parking lot of Sherm’s Thunderbird Market on Northwest Stewart Parkway. The organization is seeking help in getting new or gently used...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODFW HOSTS JUNE 27TH MEETING TO DISCUSS HATCHERY RESILIENCY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120210</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/odfw-hosts-june-27th-meeting-to-discuss-hatchery-resiliency/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=odfw-hosts-june-27th-meeting-to-discuss-hatchery-resiliency"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 11:00 a.m.  A release from the Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife said the agency is looking ahead to chart a sustainable future for Oregon’s hatcheries. The public is invited to a June 27th meeting to learn more about the process ODFW is using to thoroughly review the state’s hatcheries and plan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGON’S NONFARM PAYROLL EMPLOYMENT RISES BY 4,000 IN MAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120206</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/oregons-nonfarm-payroll-employment-rises-by-4000-in-may/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregons-nonfarm-payroll-employment-rises-by-4000-in-may"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 2020, 2024 10:40 a.m.   In May, Oregon’s seasonally adjusted nonfarm payroll employment rose by 4,000 jobs, following a revised gain of 2,400 jobs in April. A release from the Oregon Employment Department said health care and social assistance gained 1,900 jobs in May, while leisure and hospitality added 1,000. Monthly declines were largest in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONGRESSMAN BENTZ HONORS CLASS OF 2028 U.S. SERVICE ACADEMY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120204</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/congressman-bentz-honors-class-of-2028-u-s-service-academy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=congressman-bentz-honors-class-of-2028-u-s-service-academy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 10:15 a.m.  Second District Congressman Cliff Bentz has released the names of 7 individuals he nominated to be considered for attendance at the nation’s service academies. The full list of students who received then accepted offers of appointment are: *Sean Donohue of Phoenix High School to the United States Naval Academy *Konnor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120202</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-alleged-theft-5/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-alleged-theft-5"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 950 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for an alleged theft on Wednesday night. An RPD report said just after 10:30 p.m. an employee of a business in the 3000 block of Northwest Aviation Drive said the 24-year-old was trying to cash a lottery receipt which had been stolen from inside the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED HARASSMENT AT A STORE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120200</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-at-a-store/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-harassment-at-a-store"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 9:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged harassment incident at a store on Wednesday night. An RPD report said at 10:00 p.m. officers responded to Fred Meyer in the 900 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard after employees said a man physically assaulted an employee after refusing to leave....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL FUGITIVE WEDNESDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120198</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-wednesday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-wednesday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a fugitive Wednesday night. An RPD report said shortly after 7:00 p.m. officers contacted the 32-year-old woman in the 100 block of Southeast Stephens Street and found that she had a warrant for her arrest for a probation violation. The warrant was confirmed, and the woman was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 6.20.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120195</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/morning-conversation-6-20-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-6-20-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley joins us live from Washington D.C. to talk about funding for the Douglas County emergency radio upgrade, an ask of VA officials to provide money for the proposed Roseburg Veteran’s Home, forest management and other topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moon Tree to be planted near library]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/062a00de-2e86-11ef-9414-ef53a2897daa</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/moon-tree-to-be-planted-near-library/article_062a00de-2e86-11ef-9414-ef53a2897daa.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — Friends of the Myrtle Creek Library is inviting the public to the planting of the library's moon tree Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jungle Things Oregon moves into bigger space, hold grand opening]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3902b164-2e85-11ef-9b8a-6b4e6dce6d03</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/jungle-things-oregon-moves-into-bigger-space-hold-grand-opening/article_3902b164-2e85-11ef-9b8a-6b4e6dce6d03.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After stacking cages and creating fake walls to create more space where there really wasn’t room, Roseburg-based reptile rescue Jungle Things Oregon slithered over to a bigger space about two weeks ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back to the basics with Anime Your Way class]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3fe1d2c4-2e6e-11ef-b5b4-b7d65602ff13</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/back-to-the-basics-with-anime-your-way-class/article_3fe1d2c4-2e6e-11ef-b5b4-b7d65602ff13.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime Your Way, a drawing class hosted by the Roseburg Public Library, brought dozens of children to learn skills for improving their drawing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LEO GIMBEL The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Arts highlights LGBTQ+ artists across Oregon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3f4db712-2dd1-11ef-a78f-df118714c3b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/umpqua-valley-arts-highlights-lgbtq-artists-across-oregon/article_3f4db712-2dd1-11ef-a78f-df118714c3b3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Arts’ new exhibit, “I Want You to See Me,” brings together painting, sculpture, multimedia formats and more to showcase LGBTQ+ artists based in Oregon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WILL GESCHKE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adolfo Paqueno: Going above and beyond expectations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b43907b2-2e6b-11ef-96c9-3fd1b0aabcd5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/south_county/riddle/adolfo-paqueno-going-above-and-beyond-expectations/article_b43907b2-2e6b-11ef-96c9-3fd1b0aabcd5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE — Adolfo Paqueno, 16, never hesitated before running toward danger when he heard an explosion mere yards away from where he was sitting with family friend Aaron Christensen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA VALLEY HEATING UP THROUGH SATURDAY AS SUMMER BEGINS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120187</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/umpqua-valley-heating-up-through-saturday-as-summer-begins/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-valley-heating-up-through-saturday-as-summer-begins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T11:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 4:00 a.m. As summer begins, the Umpqua Valley is heating up through Saturday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said upper-level ridging in the area means no clouds, less wind, and more exposure to the sun, causing warmer temperatures. Highs in Roseburg are forecast to be at or near 90 degrees for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCSO SEEKING INFORMATION FROM PUBLIC ON WHISTLERS BEND DISC GOLF COURSE DAMAGE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120179</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/dcso-seeking-information-from-public-on-whistlers-bend-disc-golf-course-damage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dcso-seeking-information-from-public-on-whistlers-bend-disc-golf-course-damage"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 3:40 a.m. The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office is seeking information regarding damage to the disc golf baskets at Whistler’s Bend County Park. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell said on Friday, DCSO was advised of criminal damage to three new disc golf baskets at the park. O’Dell said the damages are estimated to be just...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY PRESENTS “THE GRAND LUNCH” SERIES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120176</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/douglas-county-presents-the-grand-lunch-series/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-presents-the-grand-lunch-series"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 3:30 a.m.  Douglas County Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman and Tom Kress, along with the county’s Senior Services Director Jeanne Wright and her staff are excited to present “The Grand Lunch”. A county release said it will an intergenerational lunch series offered for the summer at the Bistro Sixty Senior Dining Site...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COASTAL GIVING AWAY 300 FREE LIFE JACKETS PER STORE ON SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120174</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/coastal-giving-away-300-free-life-jackets-per-store-on-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=coastal-giving-away-300-free-life-jackets-per-store-on-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 3:20 a.m. In the KQEN Business Spotlight: With temperatures getting warmer, families are heading to local lakes, streams and pools, and every Coastal store will give away 300 life jackets for kids up to age 12 this Saturday. A Coastal release said life jackets are absolutely free for all families, while supplies...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHEETAH CUB FROM WILDLIFE SAFARI TO BE FOSTERED AT CINCINNATI ZOO]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120168</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/cheetah-cub-from-wildlife-safari-to-be-fostered-at-cincinnati-zoo/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cheetah-cub-from-wildlife-safari-to-be-fostered-at-cincinnati-zoo"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 20, 2024 3:05 a.m. Wildlife Safari has announced the successful transfer of a cheetah cub, born on June 7th this year, to the Cincinnati Zoo and Botanical Garden for fostering. Public Relations Manager Taylor Holeman said the male cub, which weighed 460 grams at birth, was born to mom Zuri, the #1 genetically valued...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VINEYARD TOUR MOVING TO OCTOBER 6TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120165</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/20/vineyard-tour-moving-to-october-6th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=vineyard-tour-moving-to-october-6th"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Umpqua Velo Club is getting ready for this year’s Vineyard Tour and has made some big changes. After struggling with the reality of wildfire smoke every Labor Day, the organization is going to try holding the event the first weekend of October. The ride will happen on Sunday October 6th and will be the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEATH INVESTIGATION UNDERWAY BY ROSEBURG POLICE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120159</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/death-investigation-underway-by-roseburg-police/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=death-investigation-underway-by-roseburg-police"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T00:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 5:15 p.m. The Roseburg Police Department is conducting a death investigation. Public Information Officer Sergeant Daniel Allen said Wednesday at 11:30 a.m. RPD responded to an address in the 1100 block of Southeast Pine Street to conduct a welfare check on 77-year-old Samuel Steven Smeth. Allen said Smeth was found deceased inside...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Death Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news173162</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5489#news173162"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T00:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 19, 2024, at approximately 11:30 AM, the Roseburg Police Department responded to an address in the 1100 block of SE Pine to conduct a welfare check on 77 year old Samuel Steven Smeth.  Smeth was found deceased in his residence.  Next of kin has been notified.  
Roseburg Police detectives, Douglas County Sheriff’s Office detectives, and Oregon State Police responded to assist and will continue to investigate the matter with assistance from the Douglas County District Attorney’s Office. At this time, there is no known ongoing threat to the general public]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roseburg Police Dept.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg school district settles lawsuit with family of girl who was allegedly raped]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/5a33507e-2e7a-11ef-b10e-c31764259568</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/roseburg-school-district-settles-lawsuit-with-family-of-girl-who-was-allegedly-raped/article_5a33507e-2e7a-11ef-b10e-c31764259568.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Schools agreed to pay $475,000 to settle a lawsuit filed on behalf of a former Joseph Lane Middle School student who was sent home with an adult acquaintance — not approved by the girl’s family — who authorities…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disc golf baskets damaged, police seek answers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3ed92a7e-2e8e-11ef-870a-b76a6d486ff0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/disc-golf-baskets-damaged-police-seek-answers/article_3ed92a7e-2e8e-11ef-870a-b76a6d486ff0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — The Douglas County Sheriff's Office is seeking information about damages to the disc golf baskets at Whistlers Bend County Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reward offered for tips leading to arrest]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3ed92a7e-2e8e-11ef-870a-b76a6d486ff0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/reward-offered-for-tips-leading-to-arrest/article_3ed92a7e-2e8e-11ef-870a-b76a6d486ff0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — The Douglas County Sheriff's Office is seeking information about damages to the disc golf baskets at Whistlers Bend County Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coastal to hand out life jackets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/91a2cd76-2dc3-11ef-861d-cfc67a8ba8d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/coastal-to-hand-out-life-jackets/article_91a2cd76-2dc3-11ef-861d-cfc67a8ba8d1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Coastal Farm & Ranch will hand out 250 lifejackets at 11 a.m. Saturday at its Roseburg store at 782 NE Garden Valley Blvd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reward Offered for Tip Leading to Arrest of Individual(s) Responsible for Damage of Whistlers Bend Disc Golf Course Baskets (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news173159</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news173159"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG, Ore. - The Douglas County Sheriff's Office is seeking information regarding damage to the disc golf baskets at Whistlers Bend County Park. 
On Friday, June 14, 2024, the Sheriff's Office was advised of criminal damage to three new disc golf baskets at Whistlers Bend Park. The damages are estimated to be just under $1,500.00. 
A group within the community is offering and administering a $1,000 reward for the person who provides information which leads to the arrest and conviction of the individual(s) responsible. 
The Sheriff's Office is asking anyone who may have knowledge about the damage to contact deputies at (541) 440-4471 referencing Case #24-2418.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildlife Safari celebrates cheetah transfer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d1d2feba-2e73-11ef-bac7-8f4d310be219</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/wildlife-safari-celebrates-cheetah-transfer/article_d1d2feba-2e73-11ef-bac7-8f4d310be219.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Wildlife Safari is celebrating the transfer of a recently born cheetah cub to the Cincinnati Zoo and Botanical Garden for fostering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARIAH JOHNSTON For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Van crashes into house]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d0f8e40c-2e76-11ef-ac77-633351ecca65</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/van-crashes-into-house/article_d0f8e40c-2e76-11ef-ac77-633351ecca65.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T20:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Two people were sleeping around 1 a.m. Wednesday in a home in the 1700 block of Southeast Jackson Street when a van came through the wall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pickup crashes into Costco fuel station]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bbd49d38-2e75-11ef-9e9d-cb4c87414f6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/pickup-crashes-into-costco-fuel-station/article_bbd49d38-2e75-11ef-9e9d-cb4c87414f6c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T19:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A pickup truck crashed into a vehicle and then the Costco fuel station around 2:20 p.m. Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120140</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-9/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-9"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T18:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping Wednesday morning. An RPD report said at 2:00 a.m. the 49-year-old was contacted in a tent, between the bike path and the creek in Charles Gardner Park in the 2600 block of Northwest Edenbower Boulevard. He was in violation of the “place”...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRAIN MAN JAILED FOR DUII, RECKLESS DRIVING, DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120138</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/drain-man-jailed-for-duii-reckless-driving-disorderly-conduct/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=drain-man-jailed-for-duii-reckless-driving-disorderly-conduct"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T17:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 10:50 a.m.  A Drain man was jailed on charges of driving under the influence of intoxicants, reckless driving and second-degree disorderly conduct Tuesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said 32-year-old Nicholas Snyder was called in numerous times as callers said he was driving recklessly around Yoncalla and Drain. Snyder was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CURTIN MAN JAILED AFTER ALLEGED BURGLARY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120136</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/curtin-man-jailed-after-alleged-burglary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=curtin-man-jailed-after-alleged-burglary"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T17:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 10:35 a.m.  A Curtin man was jailed after an alleged burglary on Tuesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 11:15 p.m. a caller said two people were burglarizing a vacant residence in the 3000 block of Territorial Highway. Units arrived on the scene and found a pickup stashed in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE MAN JAILED AFTER SOUTH COUNTY PURSUIT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120134</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/riddle-man-jailed-after-south-county-pursuit/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riddle-man-jailed-after-south-county-pursuit"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T17:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 10:25 a.m.  A Riddle man was jailed after pursuit in south county on Tuesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 9:20 p.m. a deputy attempted to stop a vehicle on Canyonville Riddle Road for violations. A pursuit ensued out Shoestring Road towards Glenbrook Loop Road. The vehicle appeared to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR KICKING GLASS DOORS AT THE COURTHOUSE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120132</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-kicking-glass-doors-at-the-courthouse/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-kicking-glass-doors-at-the-courthouse"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T17:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man after an incident at the Douglas County Courthouse on Southeast Douglas Avenue on Tuesday night. An RPD report said at 6:10 p.m. officers contacted the 39-year-old after he was called in on a separate situation. As officers were speaking with him, the suspect reportedly began...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUVENILE TAKEN TO HOSPITAL AFTER SIDE-BY-SIDE WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120130</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/juvenile-taken-to-hospital-after-side-by-side-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=juvenile-taken-to-hospital-after-side-by-side-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:58:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 9:50 a.m.  A juvenile was taken to the hospital after a side-by-side wreck early Wednesday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at approximately 1:20 a.m. an adult witness said the 14-year-old was riding the side-by-side with him when they crashed on Canyon Creek Road in the Canyonville area. Deputies were ultimately...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRIVER TAKEN TO HOSPITAL AFTER VEHICLE COLLISION AT GAS STATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120128</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/driver-taken-to-hospital-after-vehicle-collision-at-gas-station/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=driver-taken-to-hospital-after-vehicle-collision-at-gas-station"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 9:40 a.m.  A driver was taken to the hospital after a vehicle collision at a gas station Tuesday afternoon. A Roseburg Police report said at 2:20 p.m. a 93-year-old from Winchester was traveling from his residence when he stated he began to feel tired. The man said he pulled into the Costco...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER VEHICLE GOES INTO A HOUSE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120126</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/roseburg-police-jail-man-after-vehicle-goes-into-a-house/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-after-vehicle-goes-into-a-house"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 9:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man after he drove his vehicle into a house early Wednesday. A Roseburg Police report said at 1:00 a.m. officers responded to a home in the 1700 block of Southeast Jackson Street after a caller said that a van had crashed into the residence. Two people...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 6.19.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120122</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/morning-conversation-6-19-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-6-19-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Karen Fager from the Altrusa Club of Roseburg talks about their Stuff  the Bus event at Sherm’s Thunderbird Market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club held next week for youth 5-12]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3e6d6f18-2dbd-11ef-818c-b38fae9ec4c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/club-held-next-week-for-youth-5-12/article_3e6d6f18-2dbd-11ef-818c-b38fae9ec4c3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Youth ages 5 to 12 are invited to the 5-Day Club at Creekside Family Church for games, songs, Bible stories and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cow Creek Umpqua Indian Foundation hosts 82 charities and award grants]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/05ce2c2c-2dc4-11ef-8c9b-7b6c0077d09f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/local_biz/cow-creek-umpqua-indian-foundation-hosts-82-charities-and-award-grants/article_05ce2c2c-2dc4-11ef-8c9b-7b6c0077d09f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE — Elkton Community Education Center was one of 82 nonprofits that received a grant from the Cow Creek Umpqua Indian Foundation during Tuesday's bi-annual awards ceremony at Seven Feathers Casino Resort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spiderking Studios, local film production company, to open studio downtown]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fd64180a-2d9e-11ef-95ce-d7d5de29163c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/spiderking-studios-local-film-production-company-to-open-studio-downtown/article_fd64180a-2d9e-11ef-95ce-d7d5de29163c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of operating as a video production company in Douglas County, Spiderking Studios will now have a studio space in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WILL GESCHKE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Meeting Notice: Dog Control Advisory Board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news173057</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news173057"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG, Ore. - The Douglas County Dog Control Advisory Board will hold a meeting on Wednesday, June 26, 2024, at 6:00 p.m. at the Douglas County Courthouse, Room 216, located at 1036 SE Douglas Avenue, Roseburg, Oregon 97470.
The agenda meeting agenda can be located at: www.dcso.com/dogboard 
To view the live stream or post-meeting recording, please visit: https://video.ibm.com/channel/douglascountyoregon.
In compliance with ORS 192.610 to 192.690, we will accommodate any member of the public who wishes to submit public comment related to specific agenda items. Members of the public who wish to comment can do so: (1) In person, (2) by submitting via email at kaylee.tucker@douglascountyor.gov or (3) by virtual format via www.zoom.com Meeting 850 9182 7983 (Passcode – 6hV4Wa).
As part of public policy, Douglas County will attempt to provide public accessibility to services, programs, and activities. If accommodation is needed to participate at this meeting, please contact Kaylee Tucker (541) 440-4449 kaylee.tucker@douglascountyor.gov at least 48 hours prior to the scheduled meeting time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leader of international drug trafficking organization heads to prison]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fd8178de-2e4b-11ef-affd-2b053d2828d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/leader-of-international-drug-trafficking-organization-heads-to-prison/article_fd8178de-2e4b-11ef-affd-2b053d2828d0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leader of an international drug trafficking organization operating in Lane County, responsible for trafficking large quantities of methamphetamine, heroin and cocaine into the state between 2018 and 2020, was sentenced to federal prison on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restructuring eliminates 18 positions at CHI Mercy Health, Centennial Medical Group]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a3b6326c-2a69-11ef-b4e3-cbda885f3235</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/health/restructuring-eliminates-18-positions-at-chi-mercy-health-centennial-medical-group/article_a3b6326c-2a69-11ef-b4e3-cbda885f3235.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the next six weeks, CHI Mercy Health and Centennial Medical Group will eliminate 18 positions, according to CHI Mercy Health CEO and President Russell Woolley.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County announces new program called The Grand Lunch in Yoncalla]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/598d77ce-2dd7-11ef-abbc-3b9f65f1557b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/douglas-county-announces-new-program-called-the-grand-lunch-in-yoncalla/article_598d77ce-2dd7-11ef-abbc-3b9f65f1557b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YONCALLA — The Grand Lunch, an intergenerational lunch series hosted by Douglas County’s Bistro Sixty Senior Dining Site in Yoncalla, begins Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DREW WINKELMAIER The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEADER OF INTERNATIONAL DRUG TRAFFICKING ORGANIZATION HEADED TO PRISON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120116</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/leader-of-international-drug-trafficking-organization-headed-to-prison/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=leader-of-international-drug-trafficking-organization-headed-to-prison"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T11:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 4:15 a.m.   The leader of an international drug trafficking organization operating in Lane County and credited with impacting Douglas County, responsible for trafficking large quantities of methamphetamine, heroin and cocaine into the state between 2018 and 2020, was sentenced to federal prison on Tuesday. A release from the U.S. Attorney’s Office –...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES ARREST MAN FOR ESCAPE/RESISTING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120114</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/deputies-arrest-man-for-escape-resisting-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-arrest-man-for-escape-resisting-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 3:40 a.m. Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office arrested a man following an escape and resisting incident on Monday. A DCSO report said at 2:10 p.m. a deputy saw 36-year-old Vincent Rios of Riddle walking in the 2500 block of Canyonville-Riddle Road and knew Rios had an active felony warrant for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COW CREEK UMPQUA INDIAN FOUNDATION AWARDS NEARLY $858,000]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120112</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/cow-creek-umpqua-indian-foundation-awards-nearly-858000/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cow-creek-umpqua-indian-foundation-awards-nearly-858000"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June, 19, 2024 3:30 a.m.   On Tuesday the Cow Creek Umpqua Indian Foundation awarded eighty-two charities a total of $857,975 in its spring round of giving. The awards presentation took place at the Seven Feathers Convention Center in Canyonville. The non-profits receiving awards are located in Coos, Deschutes, Douglas, Jackson, Josephine, Klamath and Lane counties....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON-DILLARD FIRE DISTRICT GETS NEW WATER TENDER FROM OSFM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120105</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/winston-dillard-fire-district-gets-new-water-tender-from-osfm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-dillard-fire-district-gets-new-water-tender-from-osfm"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:26:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Winston-Dillard Fire District is one of the first fire agencies to get a new water tender as part of a program from the Oregon State Fire Marshals Office. An OSFM release said the initial deliveries mark a significant milestone in the state’s ongoing efforts to enhance firefighting capabilities and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY REPUBLICANS IN SUPPORT OF MOGA RALLY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120103</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/douglas-county-republicans-in-support-of-moga-rally/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-republicans-in-support-of-moga-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 3:05 a.m. The Douglas County Republican Central Committee has partnered with the Jackson County GOP in support of a Make Oregon Great Again Rally this Saturday. The event will run from 9:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m. in the Jackson County Expo Center. Speakers include: *Mike Lindell – speaking on election integrity *Joe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 GRAFFITI WEEKEND COMING JULY 10TH-14TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120100</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/2024-graffiti-weekend-coming-july-10th-14th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=2024-graffiti-weekend-coming-july-10th-14th"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 19, 2024 2:50 a.m. Graffiti Weekend 2024 is coming soon – July 10th to July 14th. The annual series of events began in Roseburg in 1983. The celebration of classic cars includes car shows, a dance-off, ice cream social, retirement and rest home tour, and much more. It also features a burnout competition, cruizin’...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Music on the Half Shell kicks off with Jon Cleary and The Absolute Monster Gentleman]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4fb9a5fa-2df1-11ef-9c58-cfae99cf60d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/music-on-the-half-shell-kicks-off-with-jon-cleary-and-the-absolute-monster-gentleman/article_4fb9a5fa-2df1-11ef-9c58-cfae99cf60d4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kicking off the Music on the Half Shell music season with a bang, Jon Cleary & The Absolute Monster Gentlemen made their Roseburg debut Tuesday at Stewart Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARIAH JOHNSTON The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half Shell kicks off with Jon Cleary and The Absolute Monster Gentleman]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4fb9a5fa-2df1-11ef-9c58-cfae99cf60d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/half-shell-kicks-off-with-jon-cleary-and-the-absolute-monster-gentleman/article_4fb9a5fa-2df1-11ef-9c58-cfae99cf60d4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kicking off the Half Shell music season with a bang, Jon Cleary & The Absolute Monster Gentlemen made their Roseburg debut on Tuesday at Stewart Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARIAH JOHNSTON For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 6.18.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120097</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/19/true-wealth-6-18-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-6-18-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T01:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littlejohn Financial> Matt Dickson and Justin Bruggeman have our weekly local financial program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RHS Class of 1954 hosts 70th reunion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f0d548a2-2dc1-11ef-a049-070cc335ea95</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/rhs-class-of-1954-hosts-70th-reunion/article_f0d548a2-2dc1-11ef-a049-070cc335ea95.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Roseburg High School class of 1954 will celebrated its 70th reunion from 5-8 p.m. Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 6.18.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120093</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/inside-douglas-county-6-18-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-6-18-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas Timber Operators Executive Director Matt Hill talks about an Oregon Department of Fish and Wildlife budget proposal that could lead to the permanent closure of the Rock Creek Hatchery, instead of rebuilding it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Notice - Medcom Ambulance Authority Board Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news173126</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#news173126"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T19:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NOTICE OF MEETING OF THE MEDCOM BOARD OF DIRECTORS
NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN that the MedCom Ambulance Authority Board of Directors will hold a regular meeting on Thursday June 20, 2024, at 12:00 pm at 1290 NE Cedar St. Roseburg, OR.
To comply with House Bill 2560, those that wish to participate can attend through videoconference or by telephone. If you plan on attending the meeting, please contact the MedCom Administrator at (541) 673-5503 during normal business hours prior to 11:00 am on Thursday, March 21, 2024, for instructions.
Regular meeting agenda items include: Monthly Financials, Service Provider Reports, and 2024 Addendum to Medcom Authority IGA and Provider Distribution – 2nd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Fire Dist. No.2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riddle man arrested after chase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/f0beacb4-2da3-11ef-b6df-8b954fec3db6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/riddle-man-arrested-after-chase/article_f0beacb4-2da3-11ef-b6df-8b954fec3db6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T18:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE — Vincent Allen Rios was arrested following a foot pursuit Monday afternoon in Riddle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UACT WRAPS UP DR. JEKYLL AND MR HYDE THIS WEEKEND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120089</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/uact-wraps-up-dr-jekyll-and-mr-hyde-this-weekend/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uact-wraps-up-dr-jekyll-and-mr-hyde-this-weekend"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T18:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 18, 2024 11:00 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Actors Community Theatre wraps up its production of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde this weekend. It is directed by Ashley Chitwood and focuses on Dr Jekyll, a well-respected London physician who struggles to control his horrific and fiendish evil side named Mr. Edward Hyde....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODF SOUTHWEST DISTRICT MOVING TO MODERATE FIRE DANGER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120085</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/odf-southwest-district-moving-to-moderate-fire-danger/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=odf-southwest-district-moving-to-moderate-fire-danger"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 18, 2024 10:40 a.m.  The fire danger level on Oregon Department of Forestry Southwest District-protected lands in Josephine and Jackson counties will increase to “moderate” on Thursday, Public Information Officer Natalie Weber said this will impact 1.8 million acres of state, private, county, city and Bureau of Land Management lands. A number of public...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adaptive Management Program Committee meets June 24]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173120</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news173120"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Adaptive Management Program Committee will meet at noon on Monday, June 24 in the Clatsop Room, Building C, at the Oregon Department of Forestry headquarters, located at 2600 State St. in Salem. To join virtually, please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes:

Finalize Eastern Oregon Steep Slopes question package (Substantial decision item)
Affirm roads research questions honed by the IRST (Substantial decision item)
Introduce process for determining new priorities (Substantial decision item)

The meeting is open to the public to attend in person and online via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted near the start of the meeting. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours before the meeting by emailing adaptivemanagementprogram@odf.oregon.gov.
The 13-member committee The Adaptive Management Program Committee helps determine if forest practices are meeting their goals to protect natural resources through a science-based and transparent process. The committee sets the research agenda that the Independent Research and Science Team (IRST) implements. View more information on the AMPC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEPTIC TANK FALLS OUT OF MOTORHOME AS ITS BEING TOWED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120083</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/septic-tank-falls-out-of-motorhome-as-its-being-towed/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=septic-tank-falls-out-of-motorhome-as-its-being-towed"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 18, 2024 10:20 a.m. Roseburg Police dealt with a unique situation on Monday afternoon. Around 4:00 p.m. a towing company was taking an abandoned motorhome to the landfill, due to city ordinance, and was in the 400 block of Northeast Jackson Street when the motorhome’s septic tank fell out the bottom of the vehicle....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO PEOPLE CITED BY ROSEBURG POLICE FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120080</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/two-people-cited-by-roseburg-police-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-people-cited-by-roseburg-police-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 18, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Two people were cited by Roseburg Police for prohibited camping on Monday. An RPD report said at 2:10 p.m. the 34-year-old woman and 42-yer-old man were contacted at their camp, which was set up under the cover where the carved eagle statue sits near the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120078</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-prohibited-camping-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-prohibited-camping-4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T16:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 18, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a woman for prohibited camping on Monday. An RPD report said at 11:30 a.m. the 54-year-old was found camping in a large tent -along the South Umpqua River just west of Stewart Park. The woman was camping in a prohibited area and had a large amount trash...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL FUGITIVE MONDAY MORNING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120076</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-monday-morning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-fugitive-monday-morning"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 18, 2024 9:40 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a fugitive after contacting him Monday morning. An RPD report said at 10:30 a.m. the 43-year-old was found in his tent behind Legion Field near Northwest Stewart Park Drive. The suspect reportedly lied about his name multiple times and was found to have a warrant for his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING TRAFFIC STOP MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120073</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-traffic-stop-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-traffic-stop-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T16:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[June 18, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man following a traffic stop on Monday. An RPD report said just after 7:15 p.m. officers contacted the 35-year-old in the 1400 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. He was found to have a warrant for his arrest. Dispatch confirmed the warrant, and he was taken...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 6.18.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=120067</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/06/18/morning-conversation-6-18-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-6-18-24"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T16:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kelly Leonard joins us live from Stewart Park to set the scene for preparations that are underway for tonight’s Music on the Half Shell concert.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extension offers workshop on selling ag products]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ff5e3242-29a4-11ef-8672-c3ac231ea687</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/agriculture/extension-offers-workshop-on-selling-ag-products/article_ff5e3242-29a4-11ef-8672-c3ac231ea687.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON — Oregon State University Extension Service welcomes agricultural producers to attend the "Don’t Get in a Jam, Learn How to Sell Farm Direct" workshop July 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Woofstock: Dogs, people gather at Sutherlin's Central Park]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c3bb2052-2bb5-11ef-870a-4f1e7c2a54ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/woofstock-dogs-people-gather-at-sutherlins-central-park/article_c3bb2052-2bb5-11ef-870a-4f1e7c2a54ee.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — The annual Umpqua Woofstock Festival battled the weather Saturday as dogs and their people gathered in Sutherlin’s Central Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>