<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.roseburgscanner.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2025-10-12T13:17:23.223Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.roseburgscanner.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.roseburgscanner.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-Speed Internet for Every Community: Oregon Invests Federal BEAD Funding Statewide]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9079</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/high-speed-internet-for-every-community-oregon-invests-federal-bead-funding-statewide/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-12T10:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon will achieve 100% broadband-access coverage with 19 awardees, 317 projects and 212 district grant areas  Oregon is investing the $689 million federal Broadband Equity, Access, and Deployment (BEAD) award to expand affordable, high-speed, and reliable internet service to thousands of unserved and underserved residents. The application window closed on Wednesday, August 6, 2025, with…
The post High-Speed Internet for Every Community: Oregon Invests Federal BEAD Funding Statewide  appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fiscal year 2025 among best for SOU philanthropy]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9076</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/fiscal-year-2025-among-best-for-sou-philanthropy/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-12T10:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Ashland, Ore.) — Southern Oregon University continued its historic fundraising run in fiscal year 2025, raising $14.17 million. The philanthropic total for FY25 is the second-highest annual total ever raised for the university; in fiscal year 2023, the university raised more than $19 million, including $10 million from Lithia Motors and Green Cars. “We’re generating…
The post Fiscal year 2025 among best for SOU philanthropy appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new members appointed to SOU board]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9073</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/three-new-members-appointed-to-sou-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-12T10:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Ashland, Ore.) — A local credit union president and CEO with extensive public service experience, a Southern Oregon University alumna and administrator, and a student in the SOU Master’s in Business Administration program have been appointed by Oregon Gov. Tina Kotek and confirmed today by the Oregon Senate to serve on the Southern Oregon University Board…
The post Three new members appointed to SOU board appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOU board chair receives highest Chamber honor]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9069</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/sou-board-chair-receives-highest-chamber-honor/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-12T10:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOU Board of Trustees Chair Sheila Clough was honored for her volunteerism and community service in a surprise presentation of the Honorary Life Member Award at last week’s 115th annual dinner of the Ashland Chamber of Commerce. The award is the highest honor that the Ashland Chamber bestows on individuals. “Through her vision, her dedication and…
The post SOU board chair receives highest Chamber honor appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamics of Team Development]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9064</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/dynamics-of-team-development/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-12T10:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the toughest issues business owners deal with are with transitioning from a sole proprietor form to a fully functional organization with employees working in defined areas of responsibility, all working together to deliver services and products to willing customers. The volume of information available to entrepreneurs is incredibly large, and although considerable effort…
The post Dynamics of Team Development appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Need to Effectively Manage Employee Benefits Across International Borders]]></title>
        <id>https://southernoregonbusiness.com/?p=9061</id>
        <link href="https://southernoregonbusiness.com/the-need-to-effectively-manage-employee-benefits-across-international-borders/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-12T10:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jon Neidermeyer International expansion is a business strategy that U.S. organizations – including Oregon’s – may be holding back on these days given an uncertain economy that’s aggravated by trade wars. Yet even through the pain of tariffs and deepening trends like reshoring, businesses still need to protect and bolster the investments they have made and…
The post The Need to Effectively Manage Employee Benefits Across International Borders appeared first on Southern Oregon Business Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Teece</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCCUPANTS WITH MINOR INJURIES FOLLOWING ROLLOVER CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138823</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/11/occupants-with-minor-injuries-following-rollover-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=occupants-with-minor-injuries-following-rollover-crash"/>
        <updated>2025-10-11T21:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 11, 2025 3:00 p.m.   Two occupants received minor injuries following a single vehicle rollover crash early Thursday. An Oregon State Police report sat at 3:15 a.m. a trooper responded to the wreck on Highway 38, about nine miles west of Elkton. A westbound SUV had left the roadway, after the driver said he was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg High Walkout Draws National Attention]]></title>
        <id>68eaa834cbfd6b0001fa537a</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/roseburg-high-walkout-draws-national-attention/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-11T19:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A student walkout at Roseburg High over transgender locker room access has gained national attention, with major outlets and social media accounts sharing the story. Supporters praised the protest while critics called it discriminatory, highlighting ongoing debates about privacy and gender identity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County fire season ends today: tips for safe debris burning]]></title>
        <id>http://www.kezi.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1821ce58-aad0-4354-9368-5781c3207c03</id>
        <link href="https://www.kezi.com/news/local/douglas-county-fire-season-ends-today-tips-for-safe-debris-burning/article_1821ce58-aad0-4354-9368-5781c3207c03.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T23:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas Forest Protective Association (DFPA) officially ended the 2025 fire season on today, according to DFPA officials, noting that recent rains and cooler temperatures have reduced fire risks in the area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BB Gun Discovery Triggers Brief Security Measure at Roseburg High School]]></title>
        <id>68e97bc4cbfd6b0001fa5364</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/bb-gun-discovery-triggers-brief-security-measure-at-roseburg-high-school/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T21:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg High School briefly entered a “Secure” status after a BB gun was found near campus Friday afternoon. Police confirmed there was no credible threat, but students were kept inside as a precaution amid ongoing protests. The situation was resolved and classes dismissed as scheduled.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.10.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138818</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/inside-douglas-county-10-10-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-10-25"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T20:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Officers Sarah Pytalski and Mandy Elder from The Ford Family Foundation talk about this year’s publication of Oregon By The Numbers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA ENDS FIRE SEASON ON FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138814</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/dfpa-ends-fire-season-on-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-ends-fire-season-on-friday"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T17:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 11:00 a.m.  The Douglas Forest Protective Association officially ended fire season on Friday at 9:00 a.m. Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said this applies for lands under their protection and management. Pope said the end of fire season is a result of recent wetting rains and an overall cooling trend that has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT ON THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138812</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-alleged-theft-incident-on-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-alleged-theft-incident-on-thursday"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T17:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 10:40 a.m.    Roseburg Police cited a woman for an alleged theft incident on Thursday. An RPD report said at 3:15 p.m. officers responded the WinCo Foods in the 2700 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway, after loss prevention employees called and said the 46-year-old from Winston had stolen items from the business...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR DRUG LAW VIOLATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138810</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-drug-law-violation-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-drug-law-violation-2"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T17:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a woman for a drug law violation on Thursday. An RPD report said just before 2:00 p.m. officers contacted the 29-year-old in the 1600 block of Northeast Douglas Avenue during a trespassing call. Officers allegedly located several pieces of drug paraphernalia. The woman was reportedly found to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR FAILURE TO APPEAR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138808</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-failure-to-appear-warrant-8/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-failure-to-appear-warrant-8"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T17:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 10:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for a failure to appear warrant Friday morning. An RPD report said at 2:30 a.m. officers contacted the 36-year-old near the intersection of Southeast Pine Street and Southeast Oak Avenue, knowing he had an unworked warrant for his arrest. The warrant was confirmed, and the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT EARLY FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138806</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-early-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-early-friday"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T17:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 10:10 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant early Friday. An RPD report said at 1:45 a.m. officers contacted the 45-year-old in the 400 block of Southeast Spruce Street, regarding a warrant for his arrest. The man allegedly tried to walk away from officers and was taken to the ground....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fire Season Officially Ends in Douglas County - 2025]]></title>
        <id>68e93643cbfd6b0001fa534f</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/fire-season-officially-ends-in-douglas-county-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T17:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA officially ended the 2025 fire season on Oct. 10 at 9:01 a.m. after recent rain and cooler weather. Restrictions are lifted, but caution is urged when burning debris. Logging slash still requires a permit, and some private or public lands may maintain fire restrictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR VIOLATION OF NO CONTACT ORDER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138804</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-violation-of-no-contact-order-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-violation-of-no-contact-order-2"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T16:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for violation of a no contact order on Thursday evening. An RPD report said the 34-year-old allegedly violated the order by entering the victim’s residence on multiple occasions since being served. All parties involved claimed the man could be at the residence in the 900...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138802</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-40/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-40"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T16:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 9:50 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged trespass incident on Thursday. An RPD report said just before 2:30 p.m. officers contacted the 65-year-old after he returned to property in the 100 block of Northeast Garden Valley Boulevard. He had previously been trespassed by the property manager and by officers....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOTORCYCLIST SUCCESSFULLY ELUDES DEPUTY THURSDAY MORNING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138800</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/motorcyclist-successfully-eludes-deputy-thursday-morning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=motorcyclist-successfully-eludes-deputy-thursday-morning"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T16:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 9:30 a.m.   A motorcyclist successfully eluded a deputy with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office on Thursday. A DCSO report said at 11:15 a.m.  a deputy tried to stop a street bike for several traffic infractions on Interstate Five southbound just north of Rice Valley near milepost 147. The motorcyclist took off southbound...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Growing and caring for Hebes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/28418f65-abe1-4f39-90cc-022428354cb7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/life/ask-a-master-gardener-growing-and-caring-for-hebes/article_28418f65-abe1-4f39-90cc-022428354cb7.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: Can you suggest a small shrub I can add to my landscape now for fall and winter color?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Rusch Master Gardner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hot book season at the library]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/537369bb-22d4-4efa-8f9a-9e83a08add47</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/hot-book-season-at-the-library/article_537369bb-22d4-4efa-8f9a-9e83a08add47.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fall is the biggest season of the year for new books, and Roseburg Public Library will have the hottest titles available for checkout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kris Wiley For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 10.10.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138795</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/local-real-estate-today-10-10-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-10-10-25"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T16:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group of Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our weekly local look at real estate. She joins us live from Scottsdale, Arizona.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.10.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138791</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/morning-conversation-10-10-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-10-25"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T16:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bob Hoehne of Umpqua Watersheds talks about the 41st annual Umpqua Rivers Cleanup, happening on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Man Faces Multiple Charges After Two-Day Crime Spree and Jail Outburst]]></title>
        <id>68e93072cbfd6b0001fa5340</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/roseburg-man-faces-multiple-charges-after-two-day-crime-spree-and-jail-outburst/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T16:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Brett Vroman, 48, faces multiple felony charges after allegedly committing two crimes in one day, including a daycare burglary and breaking a home’s window. He appeared via video from jail after refusing to attend his arraignment and has declined a court-appointed attorney.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He was a gem']]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2ac6ff5a-ebcc-43b2-8b0f-5043825e132f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/he-was-a-gem/article_2ac6ff5a-ebcc-43b2-8b0f-5043825e132f.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lauren Donald Young, a prominent businessman and longtime community volunteer who was instrumental in the establishment and growth of the YMCA of Douglas County, Umpqua Valley Tennis Center, Douglas County Library, Wildlife Safari and other beloved local institutions, died Sept.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New fashion, clothing alteration storefront The Herb & Thread Academy to hold grand opening in Roseburg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0f7b048f-2420-41f2-9a0a-b9edda9f9525</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/new-fashion-clothing-alteration-storefront-the-herb-thread-academy-to-hold-grand-opening-in-roseburg/article_0f7b048f-2420-41f2-9a0a-b9edda9f9525.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For sewist Amanda Nash Shields, her new business Public Spectacle is more than a chance to present her knack for fashion design; It’s a chance to prop up and support other artists and fashion enthusiasts in her community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOPE Drug Court participants announce fundraisers, drive to give back to community]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/240a641d-eb7a-45b1-b399-ed8503d3880b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/hope-drug-court-participants-announce-fundraisers-drive-to-give-back-to-community/article_240a641d-eb7a-45b1-b399-ed8503d3880b.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 1996, the H.O.P.E. Drug Court program has provided struggling addicts a chance to find stability, break their habits and turn their life around. This fall, H.O.P.E. participants are taking on projects to demonstrate their growth with fundraisers and a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025]]></title>
        <id>68e90b3dcbfd6b0001fa51c5</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/october-10-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T13:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County recreation report for October 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/64fa54e6-556d-44e9-aa01-2b9861471c70</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/douglas-county-recreation-report-for-october-2025/article_64fa54e6-556d-44e9-aa01-2b9861471c70.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The News-Review]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reedsport business, mayor receive Oregon Main Street awards]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/82b93e0a-bda6-4a59-b537-e0ef8330b030</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/reedsport-business-mayor-receive-oregon-main-street-awards/article_82b93e0a-bda6-4a59-b537-e0ef8330b030.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REEDSPORT — Reedsport was named a winner of the 2025 Excellence on Main awards through Oregon Main Street on Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RAIN, AFTERNOON HIGHS TEN DEGREES BELOW NORMAL THROUGH MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138789</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/rain-afternoon-highs-ten-degrees-below-normal-through-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rain-afternoon-highs-ten-degrees-below-normal-through-monday"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T12:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 5:20 a.m.  Rain and afternoon high temperatures ten degrees below normal are in the forecast for the Umpqua Valley through Monday. Information from the National Weather Service in Medford said that highs will hover around 60 degrees or slightly above. The seasonal normal high temperature for this part of October is 70...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE LANE SECTION OF OLD HIGHWAY 99S CLOSES DUE TO GLUE LIKE SPILL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138784</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/one-lane-section-of-old-highway-99s-closes-due-to-glue-like-spill/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=one-lane-section-of-old-highway-99s-closes-due-to-glue-like-spill"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T11:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 4:10 a.m.  A one lane section of Old Highway 99S in the Dillard area closed for over three hours on Thursday, due to a glue-like substance in the road. Roseburg Forest Products Communications Manager Kenny Larson said at about 11:00 a.m. a truck delivering an interior-grade adhesive used in the production of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COOLER CONDITIONS, FORECAST RAIN, ALLOW FOR FIRE DANGER DECREASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138781</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/cooler-conditions-forecast-rain-allow-for-fire-danger-decrease/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cooler-conditions-forecast-rain-allow-for-fire-danger-decrease"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T10:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 3:50 a.m.  Recent fall-like weather and multiple days of widespread rain in the forecast have made it possible to ease off on some public fire prevention regulations on lands protected by the Oregon Department of Forestry Southwest Oregon District Public Information Officer Natalie Weber said effective Saturday, the public fire danger level...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COMMISSIONERS ISSUE PROCLAMATION FOR BREAST CANCER AWARENESS MONTH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138777</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/commissioners-issue-proclamation-for-breast-cancer-awareness-month/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=commissioners-issue-proclamation-for-breast-cancer-awareness-month"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T10:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 3:40 a.m.  On Wednesday at their weekly business meeting, the Douglas County Board of Commissioners, Tim Freeman, Tom Kress and Chris Boice issued a proclamation calling upon all citizens of the county to observe the month of October 2025 as National Breast Cancer Awareness Month. Board Chair Commissioner Tim Freeman said, “It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG CITY COMMISSIONS STILL HAVE A NUMBER OF OPENINGS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138773</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/roseburg-city-commissions-still-have-a-number-of-openings/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-city-commissions-still-have-a-number-of-openings"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T10:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 3:30 a.m.   The City of Roseburg still has a number of openings on city commissions. A city release said applications are being taken from people interested in serving on these commissions: Homeless, Parks and Recreation, Planning and Public Works. The planning and public works commissions have two vacancies each. The other commissions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AGENT ORANGE TOWN HALL MEETING IS SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138771</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/agent-orange-town-hall-meeting-is-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=agent-orange-town-hall-meeting-is-saturday"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T10:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 3:20 a.m.  An Agent Orange Town Hall meeting is taking place on Saturday. Sponsored by the Associates of Vietnam Veterans of America Umpqua Valley Chapter 805, the event will be held at Garden Valley Church, at 3047 Garden Valley Road, west of Roseburg, from 10:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. Information on toxic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TAKE BACK THE NIGHT NEON WALK OCTOBER 23RD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138768</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/take-back-the-night-neon-walk-october-23rd/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=take-back-the-night-neon-walk-october-23rd"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T10:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 3:05 a.m.  Peace at Home Advocacy Center will have their first Take Back the Night event on Thursday, October 23rd. It is being held to raise awareness about how Douglas County can support survivors of sexual violence. Participants will walk through downtown Roseburg to speak out about not tolerating sexual violence, to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THRIVE UMPQUA WITH COMMUNITY 5K AT FORD’S POND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138765</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/10/thrive-umpqua-with-community-5k-at-fords-pond/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=thrive-umpqua-with-community-5k-at-fords-pond"/>
        <updated>2025-10-10T10:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 10, 2025 2:50 a.m. Thrive Umpqua will host a Community 5K Walk/Run on Saturday, October 18th. It will be held at Ford’s Pond in Sutherlin beginning at 10:00 a.m. The first 300 participants will receive a T-shirt and a snack voucher. Registration is free. Friends of Ford’s Pond and the City of Sutherlin are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.9.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138762</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/inside-douglas-county-10-9-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-9-25"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T20:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kareem El-Badry, a scientist from Roseburg, has been given a 2025 McArthur Fellowship and an unrestricted $800,000 grant from the foundation. He talks about his love of science, his work as an astrophysicist, and his role as an Assistant Professor of Astronomy at the California Institute of Technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG VA HAS FLU SHOT CLINICS CONTINUING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138760</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/roseburg-va-has-flu-shot-clinics-continuing/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-va-has-flu-shot-clinics-continuing"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T18:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 11:05 a.m. As this winter’s flu season approaches, the Roseburg VA Health Care System has drive-through and walk-in clinics where veterans can receive free flu shots. In Roseburg, a drive-through clinic continues Tuesdays through Thursdays from 4:30 p.m. to 6:00 p.m. through October 16th. A Saturday clinic will be held on October...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INCOME TAX EXTENSION FILING DEADLINE JUST A FEW DAYS AWAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138758</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/income-tax-extension-filing-deadline-just-a-few-days-away/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=income-tax-extension-filing-deadline-just-a-few-days-away"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T17:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 10:50 a.m.   More than 2.1 million Oregonians have filed their tax year 2024 state personal income tax returns this year. A release from the Oregon Department of Revenue said with just a few days left before the tax filing extension deadline on October 15th, as many as 100,000 Oregonians are expected to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138756</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-39/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-camping-39"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T17:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 7:45 a.m. the 32-year-old was contacted in Fir Grove Park, in the 1300 block of West Harvard Avenue. The park is in a restricted area, where camping is already prohibited. The man was released after...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138754</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-driving-while-suspended-21/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-driving-while-suspended-21"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T17:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 10:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police cited a man for driving while suspended on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 2:15 p.m. an officer conducted a traffic stop on a large SUV for several traffic violations near the intersection of Southeast Pine Street and Southeast Woodward Avenue. During the stop, the officer discovered that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR FELONY PROBATION VIOLATON/CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138752</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-felony-probation-violaton-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-felony-probation-violaton-camping"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T17:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a felony probation violation and for prohibited camping on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 9:00 a.m. the 52-year-old was contacted along the river in Stewart Park in the 2000 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive, where camping is prohibited at all times. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WINSTON MAN FOR VIOLATION OF RESTRAINING ORDER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138750</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/roseburg-police-jail-winston-man-for-violation-of-restraining-order/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-winston-man-for-violation-of-restraining-order"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T16:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 9:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a Winston man on Wednesday for violation of a restraining order. An RPD report said just after 3:30 p.m. officers contacted a victim who said the 37-year-old was calling and sending her messages, which violated the restraining order that she had against him. Officers called the suspect,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138748</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-38/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-38"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T16:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 9:30 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant early Thursday. An RPD report said at approximately 12:45 a.m. while patrolling in the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard, an officer recognized the 42-year-old near the front of a store after business hours. The man was checked for warrants. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CHARGE MAN WITH FIRST-DEGREE CRIMINAL MISCHIEF]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138744</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/roseburg-police-charge-man-with-first-degree-criminal-mischief/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-charge-man-with-first-degree-criminal-mischief"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T16:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 9:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police charged a man already in custody with an additional crime on Wednesday. An RPD report said at 11:00 a.m. officers recognized 49-year-old Jeremy Vroman as the suspect in a previous criminal mischief case where a male was seen throwing a brick through a large residential window in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.9.25]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138740</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/morning-conversation-10-9-25/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-9-25"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T16:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community Cancer Center Program Manager Angelia Freeman and Oregon Health Sciences University Cancer Control Specialist Sarah Swanson talk about Breast Cancer Awareness Month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Students Walk Out at Roseburg High Over Locker Room Access Debate]]></title>
        <id>68e7cebfcbfd6b0001fa5186</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/students-walk-out-at-roseburg-high-over-locker-room-access-debate/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T15:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students at Roseburg High walked out Wednesday during eighth period to protest transgender students using locker rooms matching their gender identity. Counter-protesters also attended, calling the demonstration transphobic. Oregon law allows students to use facilities by gender identity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grant for Oakland water plant upgrade, breast cancer awareness proclamation discussed by Douglas County Commissioners]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/78565320-bb7a-4ae0-b056-663c3d3159ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/grant-for-oakland-water-plant-upgrade-breast-cancer-awareness-proclamation-discussed-by-douglas-county-commissioners/article_78565320-bb7a-4ae0-b056-663c3d3159ef.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, the Douglas County Board of Commissioners met to discuss two major developments: A proclamation to recognize those fighting chronic disease and an agreement to provide funding to those fighting crippled infrastructure. Here’s what to know:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heat Lamp Blamed for Dixonville House Fire; Kitten Rescued]]></title>
        <id>68e7c3eacbfd6b0001fa5175</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/heat-lamp-blamed-for-dixonville-house-fire-kitten-rescued/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T14:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefighters responded to a house fire Tuesday morning on Buckhorn Road in Dixonville. Flames were coming from several windows, and one kitten was rescued. The blaze started from a heat lamp used to warm baby chickens, officials said. No injuries were reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spooky fun, food, contests, games and more available for pets at Howl-O-ween]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/70fd414b-95e8-4b02-bdca-1f779d9020ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/spooky-fun-food-contests-games-and-more-available-for-pets-at-howl-o-ween/article_70fd414b-95e8-4b02-bdca-1f779d9020ff.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Howl-O-Ween is scheduled to bring music, games, contests, food, vendors and “all things dog” Saturday in Sutherlin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[National News] Florida Man Arrested for Arson in Deadly Palisades Fire That Killed 12]]></title>
        <id>68e7c153cbfd6b0001fa5161</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/national-news-florida-man-arrested-for-arson-in-deadly-palisades-fire-that-killed-12/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T14:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Florida man has been arrested for allegedly starting the blaze that became January’s deadly Palisades Fire in Los Angeles, which killed 12 and destroyed thousands of homes. Officials say 29-year-old Jonathan Rinderknecht first set a smaller fire that later reignited amid strong winds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RHS students and parents hold walkout over transgender rights]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/78bbabcf-ff2e-4107-92c2-349de78900a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/rhs-students-and-parents-hold-walkout-over-transgender-rights/article_78bbabcf-ff2e-4107-92c2-349de78900a4.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“No boys in girls’ locker rooms.” “Trans rights are women’s rights.” “Girls deserve privacy too.” “Protect trans kids.” “My privacy is important too.” “Honk if you support trans rights.” “This all ends when enough of us say no.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANDREW GRIFFIN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025]]></title>
        <id>68e7b736cbfd6b0001fa4fd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/morning-scoop/october-9-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T13:42:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roseburg Receiver Morning Scoop]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking forward: Roseburg High School hosts college fair for Douglas County students]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ee1c582a-f744-4cb7-aac9-94402b59a851</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/looking-forward-roseburg-high-school-hosts-college-fair-for-douglas-county-students/article_ee1c582a-f744-4cb7-aac9-94402b59a851.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brooke Alexander and Lexie Rabern of South Umpqua High School walked around the Roseburg High School gymnasium Wednesday morning, holding many pieces of paraphernalia for various colleges and universities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CREWS RESPOND TO STRUCTURE FIRE IN DIXONVILLE ON TUESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138738</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/crews-respond-to-structure-fire-in-dixonville-on-tuesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=crews-respond-to-structure-fire-in-dixonville-on-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T11:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 4:10 a.m.  Crews with Central Douglas Fire & Rescue responded to a structure fire in DIxonville on Tuesday. A CDF&R release issued Wednesday night, said the fire in the 1000 block of Buckhorn Road was called in at approximately 10:40 a.m. Upon arrival, firefighters found a single-story home with fire coming out...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DFPA CONTINUES WITH PRESCRIBED BURN THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138736</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/dfpa-continues-with-prescribed-burn-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dfpa-continues-with-prescribed-burn-thursday"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T10:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 4:00 a.m.    The Douglas Forest Protective Association is continuing with prescribed burns around the Douglas District. DFPA Public Information Officer Rachel Pope said a burn in the 10500 block of Old Highway 99 South in Dillard will resume. Smoke may be visible from Dillard, Winston, Green, Roseburg, Round Prairie, Interstate 5,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOYLE ISSUES STATEMENT ON ISRAEL AND HAMAS CEASEFIRE AGREEMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138734</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/hoyle-issues-statement-on-israel-and-hamas-ceasefire-agreement/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=hoyle-issues-statement-on-israel-and-hamas-ceasefire-agreement"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T10:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 3:50 a.m.  Wednesday evening, 4th District Congresswoman Val Hoyle released a statement after it was announced that a ceasefire agreement had been reached between Israel and Hamas. Hoyle said, “I welcome the news of a ceasefire. I want to thank the White House and everyone involved in the process”. Hoyle said, “The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCIENTIST FROM ROSEBURG RECEIVES 2025 MACARTHUR FELLOWSHIP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138730</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/scientist-from-roseburg-receives-2025-macarthur-fellowship/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=scientist-from-roseburg-receives-2025-macarthur-fellowship"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T10:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 3:40 a.m.    Kareem El-Badry, a scientist from Roseburg has received a 2025 MacArthur Fellowship – an unrestricted $800,000 grant from the foundation recognizing extraordinary creativity and impact. A foundation release said El-Badry is an astrophysicist improving people’s understanding of the stellar population of the Milky Way Galaxy, particularly the formation and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BURN PERMITS BEING ISSUED THROUGH OCTOBER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138728</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/burn-permits-being-issued-through-october/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=burn-permits-being-issued-through-october"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T10:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 3:30 a.m. The City of Roseburg Fire Department is issuing residential burn permits through the end of the month. A city release said these permits are issued for seven days at a cost of $75. Residential yard waste is the only material that may be burned. Prohibited items include standing berry wines,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[H.O.P.E. DRUG COURT PARTICIPANT HOLDS PACKS WITH PURPOSE FUNDRAISER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138725</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/h-o-p-e-drug-court-participant-holds-packs-with-purpose-fundraiser/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=h-o-p-e-drug-court-participant-holds-packs-with-purpose-fundraiser"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T10:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 3:20 a.m. A H.O.P.E Drug Court participant is holding a Packs with Purpose fundraiser to support those completing the Residential Substance Abuse Treatment program in the Douglas County Jail. A Douglas County Circuit Court release said the RSAT program helps repeat property and drug offenders who are eligible for downward-departed prison sentences....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANNUAL UMPQUA RIVERS CLEANUP HAPPENING ON SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138723</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/annual-umpqua-rivers-cleanup-happening-on-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=annual-umpqua-rivers-cleanup-happening-on-sunday"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T10:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 3:05 a.m.  Community members from around the Umpqua Valley are invited to take part in the 41st annual Umpqua Rivers Cleanup on Sunday. Sponsored by Umpqua Watersheds, Native Fish Society and Thrive Umpqua, the cleanup continues a legacy of care for the rivers that sustain fish, wildlife and communities. Volunteers will gather...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIVERBEND LIVE! ONE OF 31 ORGANIZATIONS TO RECEIVE ARTS LEARNING GRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=138721</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2025/10/09/riverbend-live-one-of-31-organizations-to-receive-arts-learning-grants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riverbend-live-one-of-31-organizations-to-receive-arts-learning-grants"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T10:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 9, 2025 2:50 a.m.   In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Riverbend Live! in Winston is one of 31 organizations statewide to receive a $10,000 grant from the Oregon Arts Commission’s Arts Learning grant program. An OAC release said every funded project is a collaboration with local schools and communities across Oregon designed to strengthen K-12...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spearheaders Leather Goods Opens New Storefront in Downtown Roseburg]]></title>
        <id>68e7367dcbfd6b0001fa4fb7</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/spearheaders-leather-goods-opens-new-storefront-in-downtown-roseburg/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T04:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spearheaders Leather Goods is opening its new storefront in Roseburg on Oct. 11. Owned by local craftsman Dan Spencer, the shop features handmade belts, wallets, and bags. The grand opening runs 2–6 p.m. at 1614 NE Vine St, Suite 102, with vendors, displays, and in-store specials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prescribed burn continues]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/438aa5c8-6ed2-48c7-894d-6991123c196b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/prescribed-burn-continues/article_438aa5c8-6ed2-48c7-894d-6991123c196b.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T04:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DILLARD — A prescribed burn is scheduled for 10 a.m. Thursday at Roseburg Forest Products in Dillard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dixonville house burns Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/888f4315-2107-4498-88b2-1fe2056a7965</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/dixonville-house-burns-tuesday/article_888f4315-2107-4498-88b2-1fe2056a7965.html"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DIXONVILLE — Central Douglas Fire & Rescue responded to a reported structure fire in the 1000 block of Buckhorn Road in Dixonville around 10:30 a.m. Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Drug Arrest in Roseburg Nets Fentanyl and Methamphetamine]]></title>
        <id>68e7292acbfd6b0001fa4fa8</id>
        <link href="https://www.roseburgscanner.com/major-drug-arrest-in-roseburg-nets-fentanyl-and-methamphetamine/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-09T03:18:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Roseburg man was arrested after deputies found 48.3 grams of fentanyl and 11 grams of meth. Detectives say 47-year-old Clinton Reed admitted to planning a fentanyl sale. He faces multiple charges for unlawful delivery and possession of controlled substances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Ziegler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>