<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-03-02T02:13:53.749Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCAN TO OPEN WARMING CENTER FOR SATURDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116262</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/ucan-to-open-warming-center-for-saturday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucan-to-open-warming-center-for-saturday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 11:10 a.m.  The United Community Action Network is set to open a warming center in response to the inclement weather. Douglas County Housing and Homeless Services Program Manager Jacob Schlueter said the center will open Saturday night to bring people out of the cold and the expected elements. UCAN Executive Director Shaun...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DUII-ALCOHOL, WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116260</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-alcohol-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-alcohol-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man following an alleged DUII incident early Friday. An RPD report said just after 12:20 a.m. a 55-year-old man was scene leaving a business in the 200 block Northeast Jackson Street and travelling north on Southeast Stephens Street. The driver failed to signal his lane change...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED HIT AND RUN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116258</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-hit-and-run/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-hit-and-run"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 10:40 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man after an alleged hit and run incident on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 6:15 p.m. officers contacted the 32-year-old after his pickup allegedly crashed into the side of another vehicle and drove away from the intersection of Northwest Stewart Parkway and West Harvard...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man arrested after hitting cars in Taco Bell parking lot]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3c4d1192-d7fb-11ee-bea8-a7bcb27a6eb8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/man-arrested-after-hitting-cars-in-taco-bell-parking-lot/article_3c4d1192-d7fb-11ee-bea8-a7bcb27a6eb8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A 29-year-old Washington man hit two vehicles in the Taco Bell parking lot Thursday afternoon, then fled the scene before returning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WASHINGTON STATE MAN FOR ALLEGED DUII WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116256</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-police-jail-washington-state-man-for-alleged-duii-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-washington-state-man-for-alleged-duii-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 10:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a Washington State man following an alleged DUII wreck on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report said the 29-year-old allegedly struck two vehicles in the parking lot of a business in the 100 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard with his company truck, towing a twenty-foot trailer, in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN, CITE WOMAN, IN DRUG LAW VIOLATION CASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116254</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-cite-woman-in-drug-law-violation-case/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-cite-woman-in-drug-law-violation-case"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man and cited a woman in a drug law violation case on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report at 1:45 p.m. officers responded after a caller said there was a suspicious vehicle in the 2000 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard. Officers contacted a 49-year-old man and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODF sends Strike Team to Assist in Texas Wildfires (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170377</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170377"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. – Today the Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) deployed a strike team to Amarillo, Texas to assist in their wildfire suppression efforts. The strike team is equipped with five engines and a strike team leader, with a total of 16 firefighters traveling down to the state.  
The firefighters are going to Texas under mutual assistance agreements, making it easier to share resources. When wildfire activity is low in Oregon, firefighters can be spared to help in other places experiencing high levels of wildfire response. 
“We’re ready and willing to help whenever we receive the call from one of our partner states,” said Chris Cline, ODF’s Interim Fire Protection Division Chief.  “It’s the right thing to respond when someone is in a time of need, and we are honored to have the opportunity to serve.”
So how does Oregon send resources to help other states? This is all done through mutual assistance agreements creating a cache of reciprocal resources and a larger more comprehensive fire management system. In this system, Oregon does not only send out resources, but also receives and has received helpful resources when local capacity becomes overwhelmed.
 “The relationships built through our assistance in other states not only benefits them, but also Oregonians as we reach out for help when our fire season hits its peak.” Cline explained. In the 2023 fire season, Oregon received 173 out-of-state firefighters. 
Sending our firefighters on these out-of-state deployments helps them build relationships outside of our organization, learn new suppression tactics and gives them the opportunity to fight fire in a different landscape. These off-season deployments keep their skills sharp so they can come back to Oregon with new knowledge that can be applied to our future fire seasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED FOLLOWING DUII FREEWAY CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116252</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-man-jailed-following-duii-freeway-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-following-duii-freeway-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T17:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 9:50 a.m.  A Roseburg man was jailed by the Oregon State Police following a DUII crash on Thursday night. An OSP report said at 11:50 p.m. a sports car was traveling northbound on Interstate 5, a mile north of the Winston exit, when the vehicle hydroplaned. The driver lost control and the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEARCH FOR WOMAN/VEHICLE SUSPENDED DUE TO CONDITIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116250</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/search-for-woman-vehicle-suspended-due-to-conditions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=search-for-woman-vehicle-suspended-due-to-conditions"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T17:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 9:30 a.m.  The search for a woman and a vehicle both believed to have gone into the North Umpqua River on Thursday morning has been suspended due to current river and weather conditions. A report from Captain Kyle Kennedy of the Oregon State Police said just before 8:40 a.m. troopers were advised...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glide teacher missing following car accident]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3df04cb0-d7e9-11ee-aa46-87da366597a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/glide-teacher-missing-following-car-accident/article_3df04cb0-d7e9-11ee-aa46-87da366597a3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T16:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — Rachel Merchant-Ly, a kindergarten teacher at Glide Elementary School, is missing after her vehicle left Highway 138 on Thursday morning and landed in the North Umpqua River.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rural Electrical Pre-Apprenticeship program expanding with mobile units]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cd34d0dc-d76a-11ee-a928-af9b6a94856a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/rural-electrical-pre-apprenticeship-program-expanding-with-mobile-units/article_cd34d0dc-d76a-11ee-a928-af9b6a94856a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — Students gathered Thursday in the gym at Glide High School to hear about how they might be involved in a career that would pay them approximately $40 right out of high school.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RECORD RAINFALL FOR FEBRUARY 29TH IN ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116247</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/record-rainfall-for-february-29th-in-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=record-rainfall-for-february-29th-in-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 6:50 a.m. The Umpqua Valley saw a record amount of rain for the date on Thursday, but the fact that it was February 29th impacts the data. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that 1.71 inches of rain was recorded at the Roseburg Regional...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The yeast of my worries]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6097001e-cf4d-11ee-b261-0bf1ffb67a96</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/the-yeast-of-my-worries/article_6097001e-cf4d-11ee-b261-0bf1ffb67a96.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, an unlikely group teamed up to do something remarkable. They were archaeologist Serena Love, microbiologist Richard Bowman and Seamus Blackley — best known as the creator of the original X-box. The remarkable thing that they did was also…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AIMEE LOVE For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Divide and conquer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/145d037c-d4cc-11ee-a9c9-87c567271ea5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/ask-a-master-gardener-divide-and-conquer/article_145d037c-d4cc-11ee-a9c9-87c567271ea5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I’ve noticed that my daylilies are not producing as many flowers as in the past and seem overcrowded. Is spring a good time to divide them, and how do I go about that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BONNIE COURTER For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workshop to cover sourdough starter and discard recipes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c2dd7618-d678-11ee-9f87-27998aa26187</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/workshop-to-cover-sourdough-starter-and-discard-recipes/article_c2dd7618-d678-11ee-9f87-27998aa26187.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Oregon State University Extension Service and Douglas County Master Food Preservers are offering a workshop dedicated to sourdough from 6-8 p.m. March 21 at the Lookingglass Grange, 7426 Lookingglass Road in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Storm Warning in effect through Saturday morning]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/922ebe38-d744-11ee-a273-c708eec89381</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/winter-storm-warning-in-effect-through-saturday-morning/article_922ebe38-d744-11ee-a273-c708eec89381.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Winter Storm Warning is in effect through 10 a.m. Saturday for Douglas County areas above 2,000 feet. A Winter Weather Advisory is in place for areas above 800 feet during that same time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Storm Warning in affect through Saturday morning]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/922ebe38-d744-11ee-a273-c708eec89381</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/winter-storm-warning-in-affect-through-saturday-morning/article_922ebe38-d744-11ee-a273-c708eec89381.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect through 10 a.m. Saturday for Douglas County areas above 2,500 feet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116242</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/winter-storm-warning-for-central-douglas-county-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-for-central-douglas-county-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 4:15 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect for central Douglas County above 2,000 feet through Saturday Morning at 10:00 a.m. A Winter Weather Advisory remains in place above 800 feet through Saturday morning at 10:00 a.m. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said for the Warning area, heavy snow, with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116239</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/winter-storm-warning-for-mountain-areas-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-for-mountain-areas-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 4:00 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect for mountain areas in southern Oregon through 10:00 a.m. Saturday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow and blowing snow is expected with total snow accumulations of 2 to 3 feet, but around 10 to 14 inches at the Siskiyou Summit....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO ONE HURT IN SEMI VERSUS SCHOOL BUS CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116237</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/no-one-hurt-in-semi-versus-school-bus-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=no-one-hurt-in-semi-versus-school-bus-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 3:50 a.m. No one was hurt in a semi-truck versus school bus crash in Glendale on Thursday afternoon. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said just after 3:30 p.m. deputies were dispatched to the intersection of Brown Street and Sether Avenue. O’Dell said upon investigation it was determined that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERKLEY TOWN HALL HAPPENING SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116235</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/merkley-town-hall-happening-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=merkley-town-hall-happening-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 3:40 a.m. U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley will have an in-person town hall in Douglas County on Saturday. The event kicks off Merkley’s 2024 town hall tour of Oregon, where he will hold community conversations for each of the state’s 36 counties. Merkley said he holds a town hall for every Oregon county...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADAPT OPIOID TREATMENT PROGRAMS RECEIVE 3-YEAR ACCREDITATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116233</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/adapt-opioid-treatment-programs-receive-3-year-accreditation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=adapt-opioid-treatment-programs-receive-3-year-accreditation"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 3;20 a.m. Adapt Integrated Health Care has announced that it has earned a 3-year accreditation for both the Roseburg and North Bend clinics from CARF International. An Adapt release said this accreditation is the highest level that can be given to an organization and shows their substantial commitment to upholding the standards...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FRIENDS OF LIBRARY BOOK SALE HAPPENING THROUGH SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116231</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/friends-of-library-book-sale-happening-through-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=friends-of-library-book-sale-happening-through-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 3:05 a.m. Friends of the Roseburg Public Library are continuing their Spring Book Sale through Saturday. It includes fiction and nonfiction books that have been donated or withdrawn from the library and may be slightly worn or have library markings. There is a table of antique books and atlases and movie DVDs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG LION’S CLUB SELLING SEE’S CANDY TO BENEFIT COMMUNITY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116229</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-lions-club-selling-sees-candy-to-benefit-community/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-lions-club-selling-sees-candy-to-benefit-community"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Roseburg Lions Club will be selling See’s Candy to help support the club’s various projects in the community between March 15th and March 30th. This fundraising event also supports the Oregon Lions Sight and Hearing Foundation’s KTP Days. KTP stands for “Keeping the Promise”. See’s Candy sales will take...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man found guilty except for insanity in arson, attempted murder]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a7b3ec40-d6a1-11ee-9d71-33a7449b6b4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/man-found-guilty-except-for-insanity-in-arson-attempted-murder/article_a7b3ec40-d6a1-11ee-9d71-33a7449b6b4a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T03:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Paul Kliestik was found guilty except for insanity Monday on two counts of first-degree arson and four counts of attempt to commit any degree of murder or aggravated murder after trying to set his parents’ house on fire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dream Center moves forward with plans for urban campground]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e5b35b8e-d5ca-11ee-a066-bf377e9f343b</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/dream-center-moves-forward-with-plans-for-urban-campground/article_e5b35b8e-d5ca-11ee-a066-bf377e9f343b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T03:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plans for an urban campground located east of downtown Roseburg are taking shape, despite opposition from nearby business owners and residents, and an estimated price tag upwards of $1 million for the first year alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merkley to hold town hall Saturday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/84bd4678-d6c4-11ee-a67b-73b2c9a59936</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/merkley-to-hold-town-hall-saturday/article_84bd4678-d6c4-11ee-a67b-73b2c9a59936.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T02:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley will visit Douglas County on Saturday for his first town hall of 2024. He will host the Douglas County town hall from 5:30-6:30 p.m. Saturday at the Southern Wine Institute at Umpqua Community College,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glendale accident]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2b947dea-d760-11ee-a387-3fff0adadb83</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/glendale-accident/article_2b947dea-d760-11ee-a387-3fff0adadb83.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T00:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLENDALE — An accident between a school bus and a semitruck occurred in the area of Brown Street and Sether Avenue in Glendale at about 3:30 p.m. Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGON HOUSE VOTES TO RECRIMINALIZE HARD DRUG, CRACK DOWN ON DEALERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116225</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/oregon-house-votes-to-recriminalize-hard-drug-crack-down-on-dealers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregon-house-votes-to-recriminalize-hard-drug-crack-down-on-dealers"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T22:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 3:00 p.m.  In what is being called a historic vote on the House Floor, on Thursday representatives passed HB 4002 by a vote of 51-7. Douglas County State Representative Christine Goodwin says the move sends a strong message to the rest of the country that the movement to legalize drugs nationwide ends...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Senate passes bill to relief financial burden of wildfire victims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/00c33fea-d745-11ee-9718-dbb6cba94215</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/oregon-senate-passes-bill-to-relief-financial-burden-of-wildfire-victims/article_00c33fea-d745-11ee-9718-dbb6cba94215.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oregon Senate unanimously passed a bill Wednesday that would allow wildfire victims to be exempt from paying state taxes on settlements related to wildfire losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FAIR RESERVED CONCERT TICKETS GO ON SALE FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116220</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/fair-reserved-concert-tickets-go-on-sale-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fair-reserved-concert-tickets-go-on-sale-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T19:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 11:05 a.m. Reserved concert tickets for headline entertainment at the Douglas County Fair go on sale Friday morning at 8:00 a.m. Reserved seats are $30 per person and do not include the cost of fair admission. This year’s concerts are: *Country band Parmalee on August 9th *Country artist Cold Ford on August...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FUGITIVE JAILED DUE TO WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116217</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/fugitive-jailed-due-to-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fugitive-jailed-due-to-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a fugitive on Wednesday night. An RPD report said at 6:10 p.m. the 23-year-old was contacted for trespassing in the 1400 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard. He was found to have a warrant out of Linn County. The man was detained without bail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT OF BOOTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116215</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-of-boots/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-theft-of-boots"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 10:25 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged theft incident early Thursday. An RPD report said at just before 5:20 a.m. officers detained the 32-year-old on the charge of second-degree theft and for a parole violation after he allegedly stole a pair of boots off the front step of an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED TRESPASS INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116213</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-19/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-trespass-incident-19"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 10:15 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged trespass incident early Thursday. An RPD report said at approximately 1.00 a.m. the 44-year-was trespassed from a business in the 1400 block of Northwest Mulholland Drive. Just before 3:30 a.m. the suspect reportedly returned to the location. Officers responded and found him...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Forest Glen tenants have few options if Canyonville evictions occur]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7008dec8-d664-11ee-a62e-33a1233d0fec</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/most-forest-glen-tenants-have-few-options-if-canyonville-evictions-occur/article_7008dec8-d664-11ee-a62e-33a1233d0fec.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE — Sitting in the well-worn seat of his electric scooter on Thursday evening in the lobby of the Forest Glen Senior Residence, 63-year-old Michael Liston said he’s not rattled by much.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BUFFY POLLOCK Rogue Valley Times</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED HIT AND RUN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116211</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-hit-and-run/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-hit-and-run"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T18:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a reported hit and run incident on Wednesday night. An RPD report said at 6:45 p.m. the 39-year-old was contacted after his large SUV crashed into a cement retaining wall and he left the scene after the business owner confronted him. This took place...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER BAY TRANSIENT JAILED FOR ALLEGED ASSAULT/BURGLARY INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116208</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/winchester-bay-transient-jailed-for-alleged-assault-burglary-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winchester-bay-transient-jailed-for-alleged-assault-burglary-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a Winchester Bay transient following an alleged assault and burglary incident on Monday night. A DCSO report released late Wednesday said a deputy was dispatched twice for disturbances to a victim’s trailer in the 75000 block of Highway 101 near Reedsport. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG WOMAN JAILED FOLLOWING TUESDAY AFTERNOON CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116206</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/roseburg-woman-jailed-following-tuesday-afternoon-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-woman-jailed-following-tuesday-afternoon-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T17:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 9:20 a.m.  A Roseburg woman was jailed by the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office following a crash on Tuesday afternoon. A DCSO report said earlier in the day, the 30-year-old had been called in while near a business in the 200 block of Grant Smith Road in Green for seemingly being intoxicated before...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leap day birthday: Joe Latham gets to celebrate on Feb. 29]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7e2ef19e-d692-11ee-bf11-5754a37b121d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/life/leap-day-birthday-joe-latham-gets-to-celebrate-on-feb-29/article_7e2ef19e-d692-11ee-bf11-5754a37b121d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like most, Joe Latham deems his birthday a special event. This year, though, it's a bit more special than most, as he will celebrate on the actual day of his birth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oakland Bridge now open to traffic]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9f3b562c-d677-11ee-ba93-1b136e870b1a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/oakland-bridge-now-open-to-traffic/article_9f3b562c-d677-11ee-ba93-1b136e870b1a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — The historic community of Oakland is entering a new era with the opening of its bridge Wednesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A novel idea: Children learn the magic of reading at Celebration of Literacy play]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4e461fac-d58e-11ee-b59c-3bdc8061d16e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/a-novel-idea-children-learn-the-magic-of-reading-at-celebration-of-literacy-play/article_4e461fac-d58e-11ee-b59c-3bdc8061d16e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wizard held literacy captive from a princess, a pirate, a knight, an explorer and a fairy godmother Wednesday at Roseburg High School.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING ABOVE 2,500 FEET FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116201</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/winter-storm-warning-above-2500-feet-for-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-above-2500-feet-for-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T12:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 4:00 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect through 10:00 a.m. Saturday above 2,500 feet for central Douglas County and its eastern foothills, eastern Curry County and Josephine County. A Winter Weather Advisory remains in place through 10:00 a.m. Saturday above 1,500 feet. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING THROUGH 10:00 A.M. SATURDAY FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116198</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/winter-storm-warning-through-1000-a-m-saturday-for-mountain-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-through-1000-a-m-saturday-for-mountain-areas"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 3:50 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect through 10:00 a.m. Saturday for mountain areas in southern Oregon. Forescasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow and blowing snow is expected. Total snow accumulations of 2 to 4 feet with 12 inches at the Siskiyou Summit. Winds will gust as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FINANCIAL RELIEF FOR WILDFIRE VICTIMS PASSES OREGON SENATE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116194</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/financial-relief-for-wildfire-victims-passes-oregon-senate/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=financial-relief-for-wildfire-victims-passes-oregon-senate"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 3:20 a.m. On Wednesday, the Oregon Senate unanimously voted to pass SB 1520. A release from the Oregon Senate Republican Caucus said the legislation allows Oregon wildfire victims to recover and rebuild their lives without the additional strain of taxation or settlements related to their wildfire losses. The measure proposes to exempt...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FEEDING UMPQUA CHEESE AND THANK YOU FUNDRAISER IN MARCH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116191</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/feeding-umpqua-cheese-and-thank-you-fundraiser-in-march/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=feeding-umpqua-cheese-and-thank-you-fundraiser-in-march"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 3:05 a.m. Feeding Umpqua will have its Cheese and Thank You fundraiser for the month of March. Fourteen restaurants in Roseburg, Sutherlin, Glide and Myrtle Creek will be offering their unique take on an old favorite – grilled cheese. Each sale of a grilled cheese item from the participating businesses will result...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC CONCERT BAND PRESENTS MYTHICAL AND MAGICAL WONDERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116188</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/29/ucc-concert-band-presents-mythical-and-magical-wonders/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-concert-band-presents-mythical-and-magical-wonders"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 29, 2024 2:50 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: The Umpqua Community College Concert Band will perform “Mythical and Magical Wonders” on Tuesday, March 12th at 7:00 p.m. in Jacoby Auditorium on the UCC campus. The concert is an evening of music that is based on magical and mystical stories and will feature a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE MAN JAIILED FOR FELONY COUNT OF DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116186</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/glide-man-jaiiled-for-felony-count-of-driving-while-suspended/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=glide-man-jaiiled-for-felony-count-of-driving-while-suspended"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T23:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 2:50 a.m.  A Glide man was jailed by Roseburg Police for a felony count of driving while suspended early Wednesday. An RPD report said at 6:10 a.m. officers stopped an SUV for speeding on Highway 138E near Buckhorn Road. The 46-year-old was also detained for a probation violation. He was held without...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING TRAFFIC STOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116184</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-traffic-stop-5/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-traffic-stop-5"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T23:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February Roseburg Police jailed a man following a traffic stop early Wednesday morning. An RPD report said at 3:40 a.m. officers stopped a minivan for a traffic violation in the 200 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. The 42-year-old returned for a misdemeanor count of driving while suspended and for a warrant associated with another...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO CITED FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING IN OVERNIGHT CONTACTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116182</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/two-cited-for-prohibited-camping-in-overnight-contacts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-cited-for-prohibited-camping-in-overnight-contacts"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T23:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 3:30 p.m.    Two Roseburg men were cited by Roseburg Police for prohibited camping after being contacted separately early Wednesday. An RPD report said at 1:25 a.m. a 43-year-old was spotted camping in the 100 block of Southeast Templin Avenue. That is a restricted area per the Time Place and Manner ordinance....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW OAKLAND BRIDGE NOW OPEN TO TRAFFIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116178</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/new-oakland-bridge-now-open-to-traffic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=new-oakland-bridge-now-open-to-traffic"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T23:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 3:00 p.m.  A new era has arrived for this historic community of Oakland. For two years, work has been underway to replace the aging single-lane Oakland Bridge at the north end of town. Wednesday morning, just before sunrise, traffic was diverted onto the new bridge. Dan Latham of the Oregon Department of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NORTHEAST STEPHENS STREET WATER MAIN PROJECT STARTS MARCH 11TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116173</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/northeast-stephens-street-water-main-project-starts-march-11th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=northeast-stephens-street-water-main-project-starts-march-11th"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T18:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 11:00 a.m.   The City of Roseburg Public Works Department has a water main project on Northeast Stephens Street which will start on March 11th. A city release said the southbound lane of Northeast Stephens Street between Northeast Isabell Avenue and Northeast Newton Creek Road will be closed overnight for about seven months...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG SCHOOL DISTRICT ACCEPTING PRE-K APPLICATIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116171</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-school-district-accepting-pre-k-applications/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-school-district-accepting-pre-k-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T18:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28 2024 10:20 a.m. Roseburg School District will begin accepting Pre-K applications for the 2024-25 school year on Friday, March 1st. Early Learning Facilitator Tatum Stedman said all families living within district boundaries are encouraged to apply now for their child to be considered for placement in the program. Stedman said to be eligible,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116169</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 9:50 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for a warrant after contacting her early Wednesday. An RPD report said at 1:50 a.m. officers spotted the 34-year-old at her camp in the 1400 block of Southeast Micelli Street. She was detained for the warrant and cited for prohibited camping. Bail was set at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED FOR REPORTED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116167</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-man-jailed-for-reported-theft-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-for-reported-theft-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 9:30 a.m. A Roseburg man was jailed by Roseburg Police for a reported theft incident. An RPD report said at 12:30 p.m. officers responded after a caller said there was a shoplifter in the 3000 block of Northwest Aviation Drive. The 52-year-old admitted to stealing over $500 worth of merchandise and was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED FRAUD INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116165</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-fraud-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-fraud-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 9:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for an alleged fraud incident on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 10:00 a.m. officers responded to a business in the 400 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard after a caller said a man had used a stolen credit card for a multiple night stay...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reustle-Prayer Rock Vineyards awarded at American Fine Wine Competition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/06e6cb38-d594-11ee-a3b7-5f30b09437ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/reustle-prayer-rock-vineyards-awarded-at-american-fine-wine-competition/article_06e6cb38-d594-11ee-a3b7-5f30b09437ef.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Reustle-Prayer Rock Vineyards received nine gold medals, including three double gold awards, at the 17th annual American Fine Wine Competition in Florida.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spend your cheddar: UCAN hosts Cheese and Thank You fundraiser]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b56f74e6-d58c-11ee-b3a9-1f945c7b6289</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/spend-your-cheddar-ucan-hosts-cheese-and-thank-you-fundraiser/article_b56f74e6-d58c-11ee-b3a9-1f945c7b6289.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The grilled cheese — gooey cheese sandwiched between toasty slices of bread — will get 11 makeovers this March in Roseburg, Sutherlin, Glide and Myrtle Creek in an effort to fundraise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dancing and singing to raise money at Peace at Home fundraiser]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ad088a0e-d5d2-11ee-88df-3763d2407c37</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/dancing-and-singing-to-raise-money-at-peace-at-home-fundraiser/article_ad088a0e-d5d2-11ee-88df-3763d2407c37.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch performers dance and sing the night away with the goal of raising money for survivors of family violence, sexual assault, stalking and human trafficking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yoncalla's Riley Templeton to represent rural schools at conference]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/50f347f8-d5a6-11ee-9239-d73abfbe4331</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/yoncallas-riley-templeton-to-represent-rural-schools-at-conference/article_50f347f8-d5a6-11ee-9239-d73abfbe4331.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riley Templeton has big plans to place Yoncalla High School on the map.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cerebellum, mind and mood]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/a9fb57f4-d101-11ee-9052-b3f5a8112c40</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/cerebellum-mind-and-mood/article_a9fb57f4-d101-11ee-9052-b3f5a8112c40.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cerebellum is an evolutionarily old part of the brain. It is a multilayered structure that lies beneath and behind the larger, paired areas of the brain called the cerebral hemispheres.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SCOTT MENDELSON For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teen candidates prepare for Miss Douglas County Outstanding Teen competition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d90c92e4-d596-11ee-a550-bbbb2c020fed</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/teen-candidates-prepare-for-miss-douglas-county-outstanding-teen-competition/article_d90c92e4-d596-11ee-a550-bbbb2c020fed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Miss Douglas County and Miss Douglas County Outstanding Teen Competition will take place at 2 p.m. Sunday at the Jacoby Auditorium at Umpqua Community College, 1140 Umpqua College Rd in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deck out your halls: home and garden show this weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8e6f592e-d50a-11ee-a7dd-f37615e47943</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/deck-out-your-halls-home-and-garden-show-this-weekend/article_8e6f592e-d50a-11ee-a7dd-f37615e47943.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take advantage of the weekend to learn from experts about maintaining koi ponds, keeping garage doors safe and affording mortgages with the Umpqua Valley Home Builder’s Association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heart Health Fair a success, encouraging cardiovascular disease prevention]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4fbf6d9e-d033-11ee-ab3a-57d952207724</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/heart-health-fair-a-success-encouraging-cardiovascular-disease-prevention/article_4fbf6d9e-d033-11ee-ab3a-57d952207724.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHI Mercy Health had community members, health workers, children, adults and affectionate therapy dogs packed in the conference rooms during its annual Heart Health Fair this past Friday, Feb. 23. The event had about 300 in attendance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heart Health Fair a success, encouraging cardiovascular prevention]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4fbf6d9e-d033-11ee-ab3a-57d952207724</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/heart-health-fair-a-success-encouraging-cardiovascular-prevention/article_4fbf6d9e-d033-11ee-ab3a-57d952207724.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHI Mercy Health had community members, health workers, children, adults and affectionate therapy dogs packed in the conference rooms during its annual Heart Health Fair this past Friday, Feb. 23. The event had about 300 in attendance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING/WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR REGION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116161</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/winter-storm-warning-winter-weather-advisory-for-region-4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-winter-weather-advisory-for-region-4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T12:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 4:00 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning is in effect from 4:00 p.m. Wednesday through 4:00 a.m. Friday above 2,500 feet in central Douglas County and its eastern foothills, and in Josephine County. A Winter Weather Advisory is in place from 4:00 a.m. to 1:00 p.m. Thursday above 1,500 feet. For the Warning...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON THROUGH EARLY FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116155</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/winter-storn-warning-wednesday-afternoon-through-early-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storn-warning-wednesday-afternoon-through-early-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T11:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 3:50 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect from 4:00 p.m. Wednesday through 4:00 a.m. Friday for mountain areas of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said that heavy snow and blowing snow is expected. Total accumulations of 6 to 12 inches with 1 to 2 feet expected above...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL GLIDE MAN FOLLOWING ALLEGED ELUDING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116153</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-police-jail-glide-man-following-alleged-eluding-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-glide-man-following-alleged-eluding-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T11:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 3:40 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a Glide man following an alleged eluding incident on Monday night. An RPD report said shortly after 10:00 p.m. officers responded to a suspicious sedan in the parking lot of a business in the 2100 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard. Immediately after officers parked behind the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED FRAUD INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116151</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-fraud-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-fraud-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T11:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 3:30 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged theft incident on Tuesday morning. An RPD report said at 7:45 a.m. officers responded after a shoplifter was detained at a business in the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. Upon arrival, the 53-year-old reportedly admitted to stealing $10 worth of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR UNAUTHORIZED USE OF A VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116149</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-unauthorized-use-of-a-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-unauthorized-use-of-a-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T11:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 3:20 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for unauthorized use of a vehicle on Monday afternoon. An RPD report said at 3:30 p.m. officers responded after a caller said a man was traying to gain access into numerous vehicles in the parking lot of Department of Human Services in the 700 block...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116146</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-theft-incident-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-theft-incident-2"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T11:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 3:00 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a woman for an alleged theft incident on Tuesday morning. An RPD report said at 7:45 a.m. officers responded after a shoplifter was detained at a business in the 700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. Upon arrival, the 53-year-old reportedly admitted to stealing $10 worth of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CITED FOR WARRANT, TAKEN TO HOSPITAL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116144</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/28/roseburg-man-cited-for-warrant-taken-to-hospital/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-cited-for-warrant-taken-to-hospital"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T11:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 28, 2024 2:50 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for a warrant after contacted him on Monday afternoon. An RPD report said just before 4:50 p.m. officers spotted the man in the 900 block of Southeast Rowe Avenue and knew he had an unworked warrant for his arrest. The warrant was confirmed, and the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Forests Advisory Committee meets March. 8 in Salem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170306</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170306"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T19:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore.—The State Forests Advisory Committee (SFAC) will meet in Salem on March 8 at 8:30 a.m. This is a hybrid meeting and those interested can attend in person or via Zoom. The meeting agenda with Zoom link is posted on the SFAC webpage.
The State Forests Advisory Committee will meet from 8:30 a.m. to 3 p.m. at the Oregon Department of Forestry (Tillamook Room), 2600 State St., Salem, 97310. Opportunity for public comment is on the agenda and is scheduled for 8:45 a.m.
Agenda topics include:

Draft habitat conservation plan and forest management plan for Western Oregon state forests project update
Overview of Fiscal Year 2025 annual operations plan
Implementation plan revision considerations for Fiscal Years 2026-27
Planning for SFAC meeting and field tour in May

SFAC’s role
The State Forests Advisory Committee includes citizens and representatives of timber, environmental and recreation groups. SFAC provides a forum to discuss issues, opportunities and concerns, and offer guidance to ODF on the implementation of the Northwest Oregon State Forests Management Plan. The plan provides guidance for managing 616,000 acres within the Tillamook, Clatsop and Santiam State Forests, and several scattered state-owned forest tracts in Benton, Polk, Lincoln and Lane counties through a balanced approach to generate revenue while preserving environmental and social benefits.
The meeting location is accessible to people with disabilities. Requests for an interpreter for the hearing impaired or other accommodations for persons with disabilities should be made at least 48 hours prior to the meeting. Questions about accessibility or special accommodations for the meeting can be directed to the Oregon Department of Forestry at(503) 945-7200.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REPRESENTATIVE BOICE SAYS REPEAL OF MEASURE 110 REMAINS CRITICAL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116142</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/27/representative-boice-says-repeal-of-measure-110-remains-critical/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=representative-boice-says-repeal-of-measure-110-remains-critical"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T19:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 27, 2024 11:10 a.m.  State Representative Court Boice says the repeal of Measure 1110 remains critical. Boice issued a release regarding recent news from the U.S. Center for Disease Control showing that Oregon has seen the highest increase of overdose deaths, 41.5 percent, of all states in the last 12-month period. Boice said he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG LIBRARY HOSTING RESUME WORKSHOP]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116140</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/27/roseburg-library-hosting-resume-workshop/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-library-hosting-resume-workshop"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T18:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 27, 2024 10:50 a.m. Roseburg Public Library is hosting a free resume-building workshop at 4:00 p.m. Thursday for people who have limited experience with creating a professional resume. Led by Christian Sala, the library’s Resource Assistance for Rural Environments AmeriCorps member, the event will share tools and knowledge to help participants generate resumes that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LENTEN MEDITATIONS IN MUSIC CONTINUES FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116138</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/27/lenten-meditations-in-music-continues-friday-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=lenten-meditations-in-music-continues-friday-2"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T18:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 27, 2024 10:20 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Lenten Meditations in Music 2024 continues this Friday at First Presbyterian Church in downtown Roseburg. Held weekly during Lent, the event is designed as a time for gathering and contemplation. It takes place from 12:15 p.m. to 12:45 p.m. in the church sanctuary. This week...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRESENTATION ON FUELS AND FIRE MANAGEMENT THURSDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116136</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/27/presentation-on-fuels-and-fire-management-thursday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=presentation-on-fuels-and-fire-management-thursday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T18:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 27, 2024 10:00 a.m.  On Thursday, Dr. John Bailey of Oregon State University will make a presentation on Fuel and Fire Management in Western Oregon Forests. It will begin at 7:00 p.m. in the Jacoby Auditorium on the campus of Umpqua Community College. Dr. Bailey’s presentation will focus on trends, causes and impacts of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SENATOR BROCK SMITH/REPRESENTATIVE GOODWIN INTRODUCE HB 4002 AMENDMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116134</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/27/senator-brock-smith-representative-goodwin-introduce-hb-4002-amendment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=senator-brock-smith-representative-goodwin-introduce-hb-4002-amendment"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T17:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 27, 2024 9:40 a.m. On Monday, State Senator David Brock Smith and State Representative Christine Goodwin introduced what they called a “common sense amendment” to HB4002 that would flag the U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement when a fentanyl dealer and manufacturer is in violation of federal immigration law. A release from the lawmakers said...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fly-In Pig scheduled for May 18-19]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bb99cf1a-d596-11ee-ab33-134e4dfb3247</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/fly-in-pig-scheduled-for-may-18-19/article_bb99cf1a-d596-11ee-ab33-134e4dfb3247.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T17:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — The Fly-in Pig barbecue competition is set for May 18 and 19 at the Myrtle Creek Municipal Airport.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battle of the Badges to get blood donations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6afd0b9e-d596-11ee-8232-ffafb1346e84</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/battle-of-the-badges-to-get-blood-donations/article_6afd0b9e-d596-11ee-8232-ffafb1346e84.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — The Battle of the Badges will be held March 21 at the Sutherlin Community Center on South Willamette Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FISH FOOD PANTRY HOLDING OPEN HOUSE ON WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116132</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/02/27/fish-food-pantry-holding-open-house-on-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fish-food-pantry-holding-open-house-on-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T17:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[February 27, 2024 9:20 a.m.  The FISH Food Pantry is holding an open house on Wednesday from 4:00 p.m.to 6:00 p.m. Executive Director Jenn Reida said the non-profit is seeking to attract more volunteers, but all are welcome to learn about FISH and its work in the community. Reida said volunteers will be on hand...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miss Douglas County candidates take the stage Sunday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/57dab2ac-d4f4-11ee-8373-ffe05b5f94a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/miss-douglas-county-candidates-take-the-stage-sunday/article_57dab2ac-d4f4-11ee-8373-ffe05b5f94a2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty-three young women will participate in the 2024 Miss Douglas County and Miss Douglas County’s Teen Competition at 2 p.m. Sunday at the Jacoby Auditorium at Umpqua Community College.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coastal caucus urges BOEM to address concerns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0104c6f6-d4dc-11ee-8e38-2bce0b56c6e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/coastal-caucus-urges-boem-to-address-concerns/article_0104c6f6-d4dc-11ee-8e38-2bce0b56c6e5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oregon Legislative Coastal Caucus issued a call Friday for the federal Bureau of Ocean Energy Management to address significant concerns before advancing offshore wind projects off the coast of Oregon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>