<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-11-01T23:11:23.108Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 11.1.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125566</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/inside-douglas-county-11-1-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-11-1-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T20:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congresswoman Val Hoyle talks about her campaign and issues she plans to focus on if she is relected to the U.S. House in District 4.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE TWO FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125563</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/roseburg-police-cite-two-for-prohibited-camping-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-two-for-prohibited-camping-2"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T18:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 11:15 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited two people for prohibited camping on Thursday. An RPD report said at 11:40 a.m. officers contacted a 57-year-old man and a 50-year -old man at Deer Creek Park, in the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street. Their makeshift tents were erected in a prohibited zone. Both have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR PROHBITED CAMPING THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125561</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-prohbited-camping-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-prohbited-camping-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T18:06:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 11:05 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for prohibited camping on Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 7:45 a.m. the 47-year-old was contacted at his camp below the frisbee golf course in the 2000 block of Northwest Stewart Park Drive. The camp had been previously posted for cleanup to be done...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED DUII INCIDENT EARLY FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125559</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-duii-incident-early-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-duii-incident-early-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 10:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for a reported DUII incident early Friday. An RPD report said at 5:30 a.m. the 21-year-old’s vehicle was parked in the northbound lane of the 1600 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway. Officers noticed signs of impairment and the driver consented to standard field sobriety tests....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING REPORTED THEFT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125557</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-theft-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-following-reported-theft-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 10:40 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man following a reported theft incident on Thursday. An RPD report said just before 7:50 p.m. officers contacted the 32-year-old after he allegedly stole food from a business in the 1700 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard. He was charged with third-degree theft and a probation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VEHICLE ROLLS IN WEDNESDAY NIGHT WRECK IN THE DRAIN AREA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125555</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/vehicle-rolls-in-wednesday-night-wreck-in-the-drain-area/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=vehicle-rolls-in-wednesday-night-wreck-in-the-drain-area"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Troopers with the Oregon State Police responded to a single-vehicle rollover crash in the eastbound lane of Highway 38, two miles west of Drain on Wednesday night. An Oregon State Police report said it took place just before 8:00 p.m. The driver allegedly showed signs of impairment and refused to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO-VEHICLE WRECK AT GARDEN VALLEY/MELROSE ROAD INTERSECTION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125553</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/two-vehicle-wreck-at-garden-valley-melrose-road-intersection/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-vehicle-wreck-at-garden-valley-melrose-road-intersection"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 10:20 a.m.  No one was injured in a two-vehicle wreck at the intersection of Garden Valley Road and Melrose Road, just west of Roseburg, on Thursday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 3:30 p.m. a 61-year-old Roseburg man was attempting to drive from the stop sign at Darley Drive, across...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSIENTS JAILED AFTER ALLEGED STORE BURGLARY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125551</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/transients-jailed-after-alleged-store-burglary/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=transients-jailed-after-alleged-store-burglary"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Two transients were jailed after an alleged store burglary on Thursday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 11:00 p.m. a business owner said he could see a man attempting to break into his store, in the 5500 block of Northeast Stephen Street in Winchester, via his security...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN FOLLOWING ELUDE INCIDENT FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125549</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/sutherlin-police-jail-man-following-elude-incident-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-following-elude-incident-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 9:20 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a man following an alleged elude incident early Friday. An SPD report said at 12:10 a.m. an officer observed a pickup being driven at 46 miles per hour in a 30 mile per hour zone near the intersection of West Central Avenue and Ponderosa Drive. The driver,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LOCAL REAL ESTATE TODAY 11.1.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125546</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/local-real-estate-today-11-1-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=local-real-estate-today-11-1-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Gilbert of the Mary Gilbert Group of Keller Williams Southern Oregon has our weekly in-depth look at local real estate:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 11.1.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125541</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/morning-conversation-11-1-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-11-1-24"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Farmers Market Board President Erin Maidlow talks about the market’s move to downtown Roseburg starting Saturday:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING REMAINS IN EFFECT THROUGH 5:00 P.M. FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125532</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/winter-storm-warning-remains-in-effect-through-500-p-m-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-remains-in-effect-through-500-p-m-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T11:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 4:10 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect for mountain areas of southern Oregon above 5,000 feet through 5:00 p.m. Friday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected with additional accumulations between 6 and 12 inches. Winds will gust as high as 45 miles per hour. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEARLY 44 PERCENT OF COUNTY VOTERS HAVE CAST A BALLOT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125530</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/nearly-44-percent-of-county-voters-have-cast-a-ballot/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nearly-44-percent-of-county-voters-have-cast-a-ballot"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T10:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 4:00 a.m. Nearly 44 percent of county voters have cast a ballot in the 2024 Douglas County November Presidential General Election, as of Thursday evening. County Clerk Daniel Loomis said 43.61 percent, or 39,176 ballots have been received. Loomis said that lags 18.22 percent behind the participation rate for the same point...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN WOMAN RESCUED FROM WILDERNESS NEAR REEDSPORT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125525</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/sutherlin-woman-rescued-from-wilderness-near-reedsport/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-woman-rescued-from-wilderness-near-reedsport"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T10:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 3:50 a.m.   A Sutherlin woman was rescued from the wilderness area outside of Reedsport on Wednesday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said 43-year-old Mandy Greer had been picking mushrooms in the vicinity of Camp Creek Road east of Loon Lake on Tuesday afternoon. She and her significant other had only planned...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COMMISSIONERS ISSUE PROCLAMATION IN HONOR OF VETERANS/MILITARY FAMILIES]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125520</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/commissioners-issue-proclamation-in-honor-of-veterans-military-families/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=commissioners-issue-proclamation-in-honor-of-veterans-military-families"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T10:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 3;30 a.m. On Wednesday, the Douglas County Board of Commissioners issued a proclamation at the weekly business meeting, calling upon all residents to celebrate and honor veterans on Veterans Day and attend the 69th annual Douglas County Veterans Day Parade. Commissioner Tim Freeman presented proclamation certificates to a long list of U.S....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FARMERS MARKET NEW LOCATION STARTING SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125516</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/farmers-market-new-location-starting-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=farmers-market-new-location-starting-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T10:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Umpqua Valley Farmers Market has announced its official relocation to downtown Roseburg starting this Saturday. Board President Erin Maidlow said after years of growth and support from the community, this move represents a new chapter for the market. Maidlow said it will offer expanded opportunities for local farmers, artisans,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WILDLIFE SAFARI WELCOMES TWO CHEETAH CUBS BORN TO ZURI]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125509</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/wildlife-safari-welcomes-two-cheetah-cubs-born-to-zuri/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wildlife-safari-welcomes-two-cheetah-cubs-born-to-zuri"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T10:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 3:05 a.m. Wildlife Safari has announced the arrival of two male cheetah cubs. A safari release said they were born on September 24th to Zuri, the most genetically valuable female cheetah in the Species Survival Plan population in North America. The SSP is a cooperative breeding program among accredited zoos and wildlife...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMPQUA VALLEY ARTS ANNUAL MEMBERS’ EXHIBIT OPENS FRIDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125506</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/11/01/umpqua-valley-arts-annual-members-exhibit-opens-friday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=umpqua-valley-arts-annual-members-exhibit-opens-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T10:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 1, 2024 2:50 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: Umpqua Valley Arts will celebrate the support and dedication of its members in the 2024 Members’ Exhibit opening Friday. The show celebrates the artistic practices of its artist members. Works range from traditional media like painting and drawing to mixed media work. Subject matter ranges...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Woman Rescued from Wilderness Near Reedsport (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news176463</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news176463"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T03:42:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY, Ore. – A 43-year-old Sutherlin woman has been rescued from the wilderness area outside of Reedsport.
Mandy Greer was picking mushrooms in the vicinity of Camp Creek Road east of Loon Lake on Tuesday afternoon. She and her significant other had only planned to be out for a few hours.
Just before 5 pm Tuesday, October 29th, 9-1-1 dispatchers received a call from her companion advising they had split up while picking mushrooms, and Greer hadn’t returned to their shared vehicle as planned.
Deputies and Search and Rescue responded and spent several hours searching for Greer in response to this report. Search efforts included ground, fixed wing aircraft and drone work. A drone operator identified potential heat signatures, but searchers did not locate Greer. Efforts were paused in the early morning hours but resumed Wednesday morning.
On Wednesday, Douglas County Search and Rescue received resources from the Jackson County Sheriff's Office Search and Rescue unit to assist in search efforts which resumed at 7:00 am.
At approximately 9:15 am, a deputy was able to make voice contact with Greer who responded to the deputy's siren sound sweep. Searchers learned Greer was injured and would need assistance in extracting from the forest. When rescuers located Greer, it was determined she had suffered a non-life-threatening injury, was cold and wet.
Rescuers provided first aid, food and hot tea before assisting Greer to the roadway where she was transferred to the care of EMS providers.
The Douglas County Sheriff's Office was assisted by Douglas County Search and Rescue, Jackson County Sheriff's Office Search and Rescue, Oregon State Police Aircraft Unit, Sutherlin Police, and Umpqua Valley Ambulance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.31.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125501</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/inside-douglas-county-10-31-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-31-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T20:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican candidate for Oregon Attorney General talks about why is running for the office and his plans to make changes if elected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPOUSAL AND SURVIVOR BENEFITS EDUCATIONAL SEMINAR HAPPENING SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125498</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/spousal-and-survivor-benefits-educational-seminar-happening-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=spousal-and-survivor-benefits-educational-seminar-happening-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T17:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 10:50 a.m.  Associates of Vietnam Veterans of America will have a spousal and survivor benefits educational seminar on Saturday. It will be held from 10:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. at Garden Valley Church, at 3047 Garden Valley Road, west of Roseburg. Several speakers will share information regarding benefits for children, educational benefits,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN JAILED FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125496</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/myrtle-creek-man-jailed-for-warrant-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-jailed-for-warrant-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T17:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 10:50 a.m.   A Myrtle Creek man was jailed for a warrant on Wednesday evening. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 6:15 p.m. a deputy contacted the 41-year-old at his residence in the 800 block of North Old Pacific Highway, knowing he was wanted. Once the warrant was confirmed, he was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DUII/UNLAWFUL POSSESSION OF COCAINE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125494</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-unlawful-possession-of-cocaine/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-unlawful-possession-of-cocaine"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T17:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for DUII and unlawful possession of cocaine, early Thursday. An RPD report said at 2:00 a.m. the 26-year-old was stopped in his vehicle at the intersection of Northeast Stephens Street and Northeast Imbler Avenue because the vehicle had no taillights whatsoever. He performed poorly on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR TRESPASS OUTSIDE OF A BUSINESS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125492</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-trespass-outside-of-a-business/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-trespass-outside-of-a-business"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T17:19:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 10:20 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for trespassing outside of a business early Thursday morning. An RPD report said at 3:45 a.m. officers contacted the 41-year-old who was lying on the sidewalk by a store in the 700 block of Southeast Jackson Street. The man was within the city exclusion zone...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125488</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-27/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-disorderly-conduct-27"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T17:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 10:00 a.m.    Roseburg Police jailed a man on the charge of second-degree disorderly conduct following an incident on Wednesday. An RPD report said just after 10:15 a.m. the 35-year-old was taken into custody for allegedly causing a disturbance while armed with a box cutter outside the entrance of Adapt in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON AREA WOMAN JAILED IN STOLEN VEHICLE INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125486</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/winston-area-woman-jailed-in-stolen-vehicle-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-area-woman-jailed-in-stolen-vehicle-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T16:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 9:40 a.m.    A Winston area woman was jailed for a stolen vehicle incident on Wednesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 7:00 p.m. a victim called dispatch and said a woman had stolen her vehicle from a driveway in the 300 block of Weaver Road in the Myrtle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WOMAN HOSPITALIZED FOLLOWING DUII CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125484</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/woman-hospitalized-following-duii-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=woman-hospitalized-following-duii-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T16:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 9:20 a.m. A Roseburg woman was hospitalized after a DUII crash on Wednesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 9:00 p.m. the 69-year-old was eastbound in the 4300 block of Old Melrose Road when her vehicle almost struck a passing vehicle, whose driver had his son in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.31.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125480</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/morning-conversation-10-31-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-31-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T16:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.31.24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Domestic assault in Oakland leads to felony charges against Roseburg woman]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4e885a72-97a1-11ef-b88f-bf5c46c0b2ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/domestic-assault-in-oakland-leads-to-felony-charges-against-roseburg-woman/article_4e885a72-97a1-11ef-b88f-bf5c46c0b2ba.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heather Jo Shafer, 28, was in custody Thursday morning on felony charges resulting from an incident in Oakland Tuesday night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PATRICK MOORE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Farmers Market moves downtown]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2c1688ec-9738-11ef-a8a1-471e08640ab9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/umpqua-valley-farmers-market-moves-downtown/article_2c1688ec-9738-11ef-a8a1-471e08640ab9.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andi Phiras began working at the The Knotty Lady yarn shop when it was downtown Roseburg, but when it closed she didn't want to leave the wooly business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING ABOVE 5,000 FEET THROUGH FRIDAY AT 5:00 P.M.]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125475</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/winter-storm-warning-above-5000-feet-through-friday-at-500-p-m/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-above-5000-feet-through-friday-at-500-p-m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T11:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 4:10 a.m.    A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect for mountain areas in southern Oregon above 5,000 feet through 5:00 p.m. Friday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected with accumulations of between 1 and 2 feet. Winds will gust as high as 50 miles per hour....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEARLY 40 PERCENT OF COUNTY BALLOTS HAVE BEEN TURNED IN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125473</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/nearly-40-percent-of-county-ballots-have-been-turned-in/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nearly-40-percent-of-county-ballots-have-been-turned-in"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T10:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 4:00 a.m. Nearly 40 percent of registered voters have turned their ballot in, in the 2024 Douglas County November Presidential General Election, as of Wednesday evening. County Clerk Danial Loomis said 39.85 percent, or 35,795 county ballots have been received. Loomis said that lags 17.91 percent behind the participation rate for the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COW VERSUS SEDAN ACCIDENT EARLY WEDNESDAY MORNING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125471</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/cow-versus-sedan-accident-early-wednesday-morning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=cow-versus-sedan-accident-early-wednesday-morning"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T10:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 3:50 a.m. Troopers with the Oregon State Police dealt with a cow versus sedan accident early Wednesday morning. An OSP report said just after 4:30 a.m. a 46-year Camas Valley man was eastbound on Highway 42 near Hoover Hill Road when the cow entered the lane of travel and collided with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVIVA TO HOLD THIRD ANNUAL VETS AND THEIR PETS CELEBRATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125468</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/aviva-to-hold-third-annual-vets-and-their-pets-celebration/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=aviva-to-hold-third-annual-vets-and-their-pets-celebration"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T10:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 3:40 a.m. Aviva Health is holding its third annual Vets and Their Pets Veteran’s Day celebration on Thursday November 7th from 11:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. An Aviva release aid the event honors U.S. Armed Forces veterans with a complimentary lunch prepared by Aviva Health staff. The Myrtle Creek Elks Lodge will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHILDREN’S LITERACY NONPROFIT SEEKS COMMUNITY VOLUNTEERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125466</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/childrens-literacy-nonprofit-seeks-community-volunteers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=childrens-literacy-nonprofit-seeks-community-volunteers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T10:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 3:30 a.m. The SMART Reading program is entering its 33rd year and plans to reach 1,400 students and give away more than 20,000 books in the Southwest area, which includes Coos, Curry and Douglas counties, during the 2024-25 school year. A SMART release said data collected from teachers annually shows that 90...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGON AND FOUR TRIBES EARN OVER $12 MILLION IN FEDERAL FUNDS-GRID RESILIENCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125464</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/oregon-and-four-tribes-earn-over-12-million-in-federal-funds-grid-resilience/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregon-and-four-tribes-earn-over-12-million-in-federal-funds-grid-resilience"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T10:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 3:20 a.m. On Wednesday, Senators Ron Wyden and Jeff Merkley as well as Representatives Earl Blumenauer and Val Hoyle announced that Oregon’s Energy Department has secured $10.9 million and four Tribes with members in Oregon have earned a combined $1.16 million in federal investment. A joint release said this is to modernize...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOVEMENT ARTS NONPROFIT BRINGS “DYSTOPIA” TO ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125460</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/movement-arts-nonprofit-brings-dystopia-to-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=movement-arts-nonprofit-brings-dystopia-to-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T10:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 3:05 a.m. In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight: A new way to enjoy the spooky holiday season will be available to live entertainment audiences with “Dystopia”, a variety show featuring The Diva Dancers and local special guest performers. The show is a production from the Umpqua Movement Arts Collaboration, a new nonprofit organization...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RHS MARCHING BAND WITH FINAL PERFORMANCE OF THE SEASON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125453</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/31/rhs-marching-band-with-final-performance-of-the-season/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rhs-marching-band-with-final-performance-of-the-season"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T10:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 31, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Roseburg High School Marching Band will present their final performance of the season next Tuesday November 5th at 7:00 p.m. This “Platinum Arrow” performance will take place at Finlay Field on the RHS campus. This is the only chance to see the entire Roseburg Marching Ensemble half time show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cow Creek Tribe secures federal funding]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0849e15a-9749-11ef-930b-7715a257733e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/cow-creek-tribe-secures-federal-funding/article_0849e15a-9749-11ef-930b-7715a257733e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T05:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CANYONVILLE — Cow Creek Band of Umpqua Tribe of Indians secured $268,172 in federal funds as an investment to modernize the electric grid and reduce the impacts of extreme weather while ensuring power sector reliability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Almost 40% of ballots turned in]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7b7f4964-9747-11ef-8e3c-7b827eef422c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/almost-40-of-ballots-turned-in/article_7b7f4964-9747-11ef-8e3c-7b827eef422c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T05:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — The current 2024 Douglas County November Presidential General Election shows 39.85% of Douglas County ballots have been received, which lags 17.91% behind the participation rate for the same point in the 2020 election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIKE WINTERS LAWN AND GARDEN SHOW 10.30.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125450</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-10-30-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-10-30-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T00:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County’s Commissioner of Dirt, Mike Winters, has our weekly local lawn and garden show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 10.30.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125445</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/inside-douglas-county-10-30-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-10-30-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T20:21:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican candidate for Congress Monique DeSpain provides another update on her campaign and talks about why she would like to be elected in the 4th district.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRINKING IN PUBLIC]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125443</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-19/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-drinking-in-public-19"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T18:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 11:10 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for drinking in public on Tuesday afternoon. An RPD report said at 4:40 p.m. officers contacted the 63-year-old behind a business in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street. He had an open beer in his possession. An officer confirmed the beer was still half...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR DRIVING WHILE SUSPENDED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125441</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-driving-while-suspended-9/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-driving-while-suspended-9"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T17:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 10:40 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for driving while suspended on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 11:20 a.m. officers stopped a large SUV for traffic violations near the intersection of West Harvard Avenue and West Corey Court. The driver was a 55-year-old Oakland man. His driving status returned suspended at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK MAN JAILED FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125439</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/myrtle-creek-man-jailed-for-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-man-jailed-for-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T17:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 10:30 a.m.  A Myrtle Creek man was jailed for a warrant on Tuesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 9:40 p.m. the 72-year-old was stopped for traffic violations at a business in the 200 block of Grant Smith Road. Dispatch informed the deputy that the driver had a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125437</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-10/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrant-10"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T17:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 10:10 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for a warrant on Tuesday evening. An RPD report said at 6:20 p.m. the 62-year-old was contacted along the bicycle path near the 200 block of Southeast Pine Street, due to a failure to appear warrant. He was detained on $12,500 bail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR SECOND-DEGREE CRIMINAL TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125435</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-second-degree-criminal-trespass-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-second-degree-criminal-trespass-2"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T17:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 10:00 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a woman for second-degree criminal trespass on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 11:45 a.m. officers contacted the 35-year-old at a Walmart in the 2100 block of Northwest Stewart Parkway after learning that loss prevention employees had formally trespassed her for stealing about a month ago. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR REPORTED DISORDERLY CONDUCT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125433</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-5/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-5"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T17:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 9:50 a.m. Roseburg Police jailed a man for reported disorderly conduct on Tuesday. An RPD report said at 5:00 p.m. four separate witnesses said the 33-year-old was running in traffic, causing drivers to slam on their brakes near the intersection of Northwest Renann Avenue and Northwest Stewart Parkway. He was charged with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR ALLEGED ASSAULT INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125430</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/sutherlin-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-assault-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-woman-for-alleged-assault-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T16:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed a woman for an alleged assault incident Tuesday night. An SPD report said just after 11:00 p.m. the 28-year-old suspect and a victim were involved in a disturbance in the 100 block of Southeast First Avenue in Oakland. The woman was allegedly highly intoxicated and was also...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 10.30.31]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125425</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/morning-conversation-10-30-31/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-10-30-31"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T16:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizer Stacey Crowe talks about  the Neewollah Parade in Roseburg, which began in 1933.  The tradition continues Thursday night at 5:00 p.m. in downtown Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Committee for Emergency Fire Cost meets for a special meeting Nov. 6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176398</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176398"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T15:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. — The Emergency Fire Cost Committee will meet virtually on Wednesday, Nov. 6 at 10 a.m. for a special meeting. Please use the Zoom video conference information found on the agenda.
The committee’s agenda includes:

Oregon Forest Land Protection Fund proposed rules
Eligibility of firefighting costs policy
Guidelines for eligibility of firefighting costs for the Oregon Forest Land Protection Fund Directive

The meeting is open to the public to attend virtually via Zoom. Public comments will be accepted near the end of the meeting. Accommodations for people with disabilities, and special materials, services, or assistance can be arranged by calling at least 48 hours in advance of the meeting at 503-945-7200 or by email at forestryinformation@odf.oregon.gov.
The Emergency Fire Cost Committee (EFCC) oversees the Oregon Forest Land Protection Fund (OFLPF), established by the Oregon Legislature as a fund with the purpose of equalizing emergency fire suppression costs among the various Oregon Department of Forestry protection districts and forest protective associations. All districts/associations contribute to the fund so that money will be available to any individual district/association to pay fire suppression costs on eligible emergency fires. View more information on the EFCC webpage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Community College introduces social work degree opportunities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e5d09ab0-9653-11ef-9d58-b7dd63e073a6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/umpqua-community-college-introduces-social-work-degree-opportunities/article_e5d09ab0-9653-11ef-9d58-b7dd63e073a6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — Receiving a Bachelor of Arts in social work without leaving Douglas County will be possible through a new partnership between Umpqua Community College and Idaho State University.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New urban campground comes to south Roseburg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e06e68c6-9640-11ef-862d-3fc5ee29bf88</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/new-urban-campground-comes-to-south-roseburg/article_e06e68c6-9640-11ef-862d-3fc5ee29bf88.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bernie Woodard’s company, Elk Island Trading Group LLC, worked on its third urban camp Tuesday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PATRICK MOORE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free marching band perfomance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c97e800c-9630-11ef-97ef-6fb1448d9003</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/free-marching-band-perfomance/article_c97e800c-9630-11ef-97ef-6fb1448d9003.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Roseburg High School Marching Ensemble will perform the entire production of "The Outlaw of Nottingham" at 7 p.m. Tuesday, Nov. 5, at Roseburg High School's Finlay Field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>STEPHANIE HALE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg delegates visit Kuki, Japan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ddc4572a-92f8-11ef-927c-d3d3fd93d549</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/roseburg-delegates-visit-kuki-japan/article_ddc4572a-92f8-11ef-927c-d3d3fd93d549.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Al and Trudy Walker took their first trip to Asia, visiting Kuki, Japan, in early October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING ABOVE 5,000 FEET IN MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125419</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/winter-storm-warning-above-5000-feet-in-mountain-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-above-5000-feet-in-mountain-areas"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 4:00 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect from 2:00 p.m. Wednesday through 5:00 p.m. Friday for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected above 5,000 feet with 1 to 2 feet possible. Winds will gust as high as 50...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEARLY 34 PERCENT OF REGISTERED VOTERS HAVE CAST LOCAL BALLOTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125414</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/nearly-34-percent-of-registered-voters-have-cast-local-ballots/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nearly-34-percent-of-registered-voters-have-cast-local-ballots"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 3:45 a.m. Nearly 34 percent of registered voters have cast a ballot in the 2024 Douglas County November Presidential Election, as of Tuesday evening. County Clerk Daniel Loomis said 33.91 percent, or 30,461 ballots have been received. Loomis said that lags 18.36 percent behind the participation rate for the same point in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODOT and city of Roseburg seek public opinion on freeway interchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/765287f6-9613-11ef-9877-0f1fede8f58d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/odot-and-city-of-roseburg-seek-public-opinion-on-freeway-interchange/article_765287f6-9613-11ef-9877-0f1fede8f58d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Oregon Department of Transportation and the city of Roseburg are hosting an online event to share information and receive public opinion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>STEPHANIE HALE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POWER OF PINK STUDENT ESSAY COMPETITION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125412</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/power-of-pink-student-essay-competition/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=power-of-pink-student-essay-competition"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Community Cancer Center has been presenting the Power of Pink awareness campaign during the month of October, including a new addition to their outreach approach. The Power of Pink campaign is described as a community-wide effort to raise awareness around cancer risks and empower individuals to take control of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRATER LAKE NATIONAL PARK PRESCRIBED FIRE PROJECTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125410</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/crater-lake-national-park-prescribed-fire-projects/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=crater-lake-national-park-prescribed-fire-projects"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 3:05 a.m. Due to the recent snowfall, Crater Lake National Park Fire Management staff are implementing three prescribed fire projects this fall. Fire managers at the park have begun burning operations and will continue throughout the fall as conditions allow. These prescribed burns include – The Munson Valley Defensible Space project, which...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALL ODF DISTRICTS END FIRE RESTRICTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125407</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/30/all-odf-districts-end-fire-restrictions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=all-odf-districts-end-fire-restrictions"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:15:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 30, 2024 2:50 a.m. All Oregon Department of Forestry districts have terminated fire restrictions, marking the end of the record-breaking 2024 Oregon fire season declaration. With over 1.9 million acres burned across the state, officials said firefighters and resources experienced extreme strain. Kyle Williams, ODF Deputy Director of Fire Protection said, “This season proved...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH RADIO 10.29.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125402</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/true-wealth-radio-10-29-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-radio-10-29-24"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T00:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littejohn Financial Services,  David Littlejohn and Justin Bruggeman has our weekly local financial program]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Recreation Report November 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/66778336-964f-11ef-a25f-03e131a43ea0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/douglas-county-recreation-report-november-2024/article_66778336-964f-11ef-a25f-03e131a43ea0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T23:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FISHING REPORT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CITY MANAGER RECEIVES SUPPORT AT CITY COUNCIL MEETING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125400</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/city-manager-receives-support-at-city-council-meeting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=city-manager-receives-support-at-city-council-meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T23:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 29, 2024 4:10 a.m.  The News-Review reports that the Roseburg City Council heard from numerous community members in support of City Manager Nikki Messenger during a City Council meeting Monday. Umpqua Community College President Rachel Pokrandt, Roseburg Urban Sanitary Authority General Manager Jim Baird, former employees and former members of council voiced their support...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With recent warning from CBB, learn how to spot phishing scams]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/788ae3ee-9643-11ef-bfc6-0fb0e133f92a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/with-recent-warning-from-cbb-learn-how-to-spot-phishing-scams/article_788ae3ee-9643-11ef-bfc6-0fb0e133f92a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Construction Contractor’s Board is warning people of emails that appear to be sent from the Oregon branch but are a phishing scam, according to a press release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>STEPHANIE HALE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RPD arrests woman on forgery and theft charges]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125398</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/rpd-arrests-woman-on-forgery-and-theft-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rpd-arrests-woman-on-forgery-and-theft-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct. 29, 2024 1:50 p.m.  A Roseburg woman was arrested for allegedly attempting to pass counterfeit bills at a restaurant on Harvard Avenue Monday morning. Roseburg Police responded to the business just before 9 a.m. The 40-year-old woman allegedly tried to use a counterfeit bill to pay for more than $20 worth of food. Officers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Keeran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC partners with Idaho State to provide social work degree]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125395</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/ucc-partners-with-idaho-state-to-provide-social-work-degree/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucc-partners-with-idaho-state-to-provide-social-work-degree"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct. 29, 2024 1:50 p.m.  Umpqua Community College is partnering with Idaho State University to help meet the growing need for trained social workers in rural areas. UCC students will now have the opportunity to transition seamlessly from an associates degree to a bachelor’s degree in social work through Idaho State’s online program. Upon completing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Keeran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police arrest man on DUII and concealed weapons charges]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125393</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/police-arrest-man-on-duii-and-concealed-weapons-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=police-arrest-man-on-duii-and-concealed-weapons-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct. 29, 2024 1:45 p.m.  Roseburg Police arrested a 23-year-old Roseburg man on charges of DUII and carrying a concealed weapon after a traffic stop early Tuesday. RPD reports it stopped the man on Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard at 1:35 a.m. after observing him commit several traffic violations. The officer noticed signs of impairment and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Keeran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RPD arrest man after alleged strangulation]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125391</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/rpd-arrest-man-after-alleged-strangulation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rpd-arrest-man-after-alleged-strangulation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct. 29, 2024 1:35 p.m.  A Roseburg man was arrested on strangulation and harassment charges after a disturbance Monday night. The Roseburg Police Department said it responded to a residence on Northeast Pomona for a disturbance. Officers were told a 25-year-old man had reportedly grabbed a woman by her throat and held her down on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Keeran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Myrtle Creek woman in custody on DUII and assault charges]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125389</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/myrtle-creek-woman-in-custody-on-duii-and-assault-charges/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=myrtle-creek-woman-in-custody-on-duii-and-assault-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct. 29, 2014 1:35 p.m.  A 57-year-old Myrtle Creek woman was arrested for felony DUII and other charges by Douglas County Sheriff’s deputies Monday on Highway 42 near Coates Road. Deputies said they stopped a vehicle that was reportedly involved in a domestic disturbance around noon. Renita Kleeber was determined to be the driver and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Keeran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCSO arrests man camping on BLM lands]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=125387</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/10/29/dcso-arrests-man-camping-on-blm-lands/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dcso-arrests-man-camping-on-blm-lands"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct. 29, 2024 1:30 p.m. Douglas County Sheriff’s deputies arrested a man on a dozen charges Monday morning in the Azalea area. DCSO says 50-year-old Jeremy Yow was served a trespassing notice on Oct. 22 for illegally camping on BLM land off Quines Creek Road in Azalea. He was given 72 hours to leave the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Keeran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODF firefighters return home from hurricane recovery assignment (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176371</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176371"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore. – The Oregon Department of Forestry is excited to welcome home 13 firefighters after a two-week deployment in North Carolina to assist in Hurricane Helene recovery efforts. The crew supported the North Carolina Forest Service in state forest clean up, wildfire initial attack and other assignments. To date, they accomplished over 55 miles of clearing roads and trails, averaging about three to five miles a day.  
“It was an honor and a privilege to work with such an outstanding group of individuals,” said Dave Larson, ODF’s Agency Representative for the assignment and Southern Oregon Area Director.  
The crew was mobilized on October 9 to North Carolina with a simple instruction: to help wherever needed. Upon landing, they almost immediately saw the level of devastation and were …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Department of Forestry launches Prescribed Fire Liability Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176370</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news176370"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salem, Ore.— The Oregon Department of Forestry is happy to announce the launch of the Prescribed Fire Liability Program. This pilot program is intended to increase use of prescribed fire and cultural burning and support fire practitioners by providing liability coverage for enrolled burns.
Introducing periodic fire to fire-adapted landscapes and reducing forest fuels has been shown to lessen the potential for high-intensity wildfires and the large volume of smoke they produce. 
While the rates of escape and loss are very low due to the careful planning and preparation required for prescribed fire and cultural burning, there is always some residual risk when working with fire. This risk, and the resulting liability for damages due to escape if uninsured, can deter some practitioners from using beneficial fire.
Governor Kotek signed House Bill 4016 in 2024 establishing the pilot Prescribed Fire Liability Program. It authorizes claims covering certain losses arising from escaped prescribed fires and cultural burns. Participation in the program is voluntary.
For your burn to have liability coverage under the program, all the following conditions must be met: 

The burn is enrolled in the program prior to burning.
The burn is conducted or supervised by an appropriate party for the burn.
Ensure the burn follows all applicable laws related to the burn (obtain and follow any required permits/burn plan, make required notifications for Certified Burn Manager-led burns, additional paperwork/ submissions for Power Driven Machinery, etc.).
If the burn escapes, the fire must not be a result of willful, malicious, or negligent actions in the origin or subsequent spread.

Learn more about the program and apply at ODF’s Prescribed Fire Liability Program web page. 
For more information on prescribed fire and correlating programs, visit ODF’s Prescribed Fire web page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final defendant in crime spree pleads for leniency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/006ed810-959a-11ef-aab6-a3dcfafa344c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/final-defendant-in-crime-spree-pleads-for-leniency/article_006ed810-959a-11ef-aab6-a3dcfafa344c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dillon Eugene Oden, 34, formerly of Klamath Falls, appeared in Douglas County Circuit Court on Monday morning as the third and final defendant from a spree of armed robberies of convenience stores that occurred last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PATRICK MOORE The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>