<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-03-04T16:13:10.203Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHANGES FOR MONDAY DUE TO WEATHER CONDITIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116316</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/changes-for-monday-due-to-weather-conditions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=changes-for-monday-due-to-weather-conditions"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 4:00 a.m. Wintry weather conditions in some areas are leading to a few changes for Monday. *Camas Valley Charter School is on a two-hour delay. Pre-school is canceled. *Winston-Dillard School District has morning buses on snow routes. Routes 15 and 18 will be on snow routes while Route 20 Bryson Creek students...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING ABOVE 1800 FEET IN CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116314</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/winter-storm-warning-above-1800-feet-in-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-above-1800-feet-in-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:55 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning is in effect through 4:00 p.m. Tuesday above 1,800 feet for central Douglas County and its eastern foothills. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected with accumulations of 2 to 6 inches with up to 12 inches above 3,000 feet in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNINGS FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS OF SOUTHERN OREGON]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116311</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/winter-storm-warnings-for-mountain-areas-of-southern-oregon/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warnings-for-mountain-areas-of-southern-oregon"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:45 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning is in effect through 4:00 p.m. Tuesday for mountain areas in parts of southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow is expected with accumulations of 20 to 30 inches. The Warning area is for the south-central Oregon Cascades including Crater Lake, Diamond...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR REPORTED DISORDERLY CONDUCT/MISUSE OF 911]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116309</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/winston-police-jail-woman-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-misuse-of-911/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-police-jail-woman-for-reported-disorderly-conduct-misuse-of-911"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:40 a.m. Winston Police jailed a woman for a reportedly disorderly conduct incident early Sunday. Sergeant Mike Miller said at about 3:20 a.m. 45-year-old Angela Osburn allegedly called 911. Miller said Osburn reportedly rambled and yelled at dispatchers with no emergency. When officers responded to her residence, she allegedly acted in a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K9 EROS TRACKS DOWN STOLEN VEHICLE SUSPECT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116306</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/k9-eros-tracks-down-stolen-vehicle-suspect/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=k9-eros-tracks-down-stolen-vehicle-suspect"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:30 a.m. Douglas County Sheriff’s Office K9 Eros tracked down a stolen vehicle suspect on Friday. Information from DCSO and the Sutherlin Police Department said officers located a stolen vehicle being driven in the 1000 block of West Central Avenue near Ponderosa Drive shortly after 2:30 p.m. The suspect failed to stop...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINSTON CITY COUNCIL WILL NOT MEET MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116304</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/winston-city-council-will-not-meet-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winston-city-council-will-not-meet-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:20 a.m. Due to a lack of agenda items, Winston City Council will not meet Monday evening. City Recorder Cindy Sarti said the next scheduled meeting is March 18th at 7:00 p.m. For more information about the City of Winston, go to: www.winstoncity.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS HALL HETS NEW ROOF/HVAC SYSTEM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116301</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/douglas-hall-hets-new-roof-hvac-system/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-hall-hets-new-roof-hvac-system"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 3:05 a.m.  Douglas County Commissioners Chris Boice, Tim Freeman and Tom Kress have announced that work has officially been completed on the roof replacement and new HVAC system project on Douglas Hall at the Douglas County Fairgrounds. A County release said the project began in 2023 and took about nine months to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OREGON SENATE RECRIMINALIZES HARD DRUGS IN HISTORIC VOTE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116299</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/04/oregon-senate-recriminalizes-hard-drugs-in-historic-vote/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oregon-senate-recriminalizes-hard-drugs-in-historic-vote"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 4, 2024 2:50 a.m. On Friday, the Oregon Senate voted to turn the page on Oregon’s drug decriminalization experiment by passing HB 4002. A release from the Senate Republican Caucus said the bipartisan proposal will give law enforcement, district attorneys, and local government leaders many of the tools they need to get people off...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANTA ROSA MAN RESCUED BY SAR AFTER FOLLOWING GPS DIRECTIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116294</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/03/santa-rosa-man-rescued-by-sar-after-following-gps-directions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=santa-rosa-man-rescued-by-sar-after-following-gps-directions"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T22:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 3, 2024 2:00 p.m.   A Santa Rosa, California man was rescued by Douglas County Search and Rescue after he followed Global Positioning System directions when he encountered a weather- related delay on Interstate 5. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said on Saturday just after 12:00 a.m. 911 dispatchers received a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man rescued after getting stuck in snow, while following GPS]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c1cb7e64-d993-11ee-904e-7b3704e2dc8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/man-rescued-after-getting-stuck-in-snow-while-following-gps/article_c1cb7e64-d993-11ee-904e-7b3704e2dc8f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AZALEA — A 34-year-old man was rescued by Douglas County Search and Rescue after he got stuck in the snow following his GPS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santa Rosa Man Rescued by SAR After Following GPS to Avoid Travel Delays (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170408</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170408"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T18:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AZALEA, Ore. - On March 2, 2024, shortly after midnight, Douglas County 9-1-1 received a text-to-911 from an individual stating he had gotten stuck in snow after following his GPS and was in need of assistance.
Deputies learned 34-year-old Juan Carlos Torres-Esquivel of Santa Rosa, California had purchased a 1996 Ford F150 in Corvallis and was enroute to his residence in Santa Rosa when he encountered weather related delays on I-5. Google maps recommended a detour which he selected that instructed him to take exit 88, drive east on Upper Cow Creek for approximately 13 miles, and turn south onto Snow Creek Rd.
Torres-Esquivel made it approximately 5 miles up Snow Creek Road before sliding the passenger side of the vehicle into a deep ditch and getting the vehicle stuck in approximately 24" of snow. He was unprepared for the conditions and was unsuccessful in attempting to dig the vehicle out without a shovel.
Douglas County Search and Rescue was activated and responded to assist. SAR responded and was unable to make it to his location with the Snowcat due to a U-Haul truck being abandoned approximately 2 or 3 miles up Snow Creek Rd in the middle of the roadway. Members of the 4x4 team were able to maneuver around the U-Haul after airing down their tires and retrieved Torres-Esquivel.
Deputies provided Torres-Esquivel a courtesy ride to Seven Feathers.
The Sheriff's Office would like to remind drivers of the dangers of blindly following GPS devices.
"GPS devices are often set to direct drivers through the fastest route to their destination. Oftentimes, this means direction through non-maintained road systems, including forest roads," Lt. Brad O'Dell said. "Blindly following GPS navigation can potentially lead to dangerous situations and have serious consequences. Although travel delays can be disruptive, it is best to remain on routes that are maintained."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY/WINTER STORM WARNING FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116292</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/03/winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T14:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March, 2024 6:40 a.m. A Winter Weather Advisory remains in effect until Sunday evening at 10:00 p.m. above 1,500 feet with a Winter Storm Warning from 10:00 a.m. Monday through 4:00 p.m. Tuesday for central Douglas County and its eastern foothills above 1,800 feet. For the Advisory, an additional 3 to 7 inches of snow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY/WINTER STORM WARNING FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116289</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/03/winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-mountain-areas-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-winter-storm-warning-for-mountain-areas-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T14:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 3, 2024 6:20 a.m.  A Winter Weather Advisory remains in effect through Sunday evening at 10:00 p.m. with a Winter Storm Warning from 10:00 a.m. Monday through 4:00 p.m. Tuesday for mountain areas of southern Oregon. For the Advisory, an additional 4 to 9 inches of snow is expected. Winds will gust as high...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homes and gardens need upgrades, too]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/099a65b6-d8ef-11ee-b402-771fd10f312e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/homes-and-gardens-need-upgrades-too/article_099a65b6-d8ef-11ee-b402-771fd10f312e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For homeowners wondering about how to modernize their carpets or which massage chair is the best to buy, the Home & Garden Show was the perfect weekend activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merkley fields questions about the Winchester Dam, mental health in town hall]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/70fff4f4-d913-11ee-bd90-1788db7cc549</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/merkley-fields-questions-about-the-winchester-dam-mental-health-in-town-hall/article_70fff4f4-d913-11ee-bd90-1788db7cc549.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley braved the weather to appear in Douglas County for his first town hall of the year Saturday night at the Southern Oregon Wine Institute at Umpqua Community College.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K-9 Eros tracks down suspect]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8f463bf0-d8da-11ee-a352-7f809482119d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/k-9-eros-tracks-down-suspect/article_8f463bf0-d8da-11ee-a352-7f809482119d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — A Roseburg man was arrested Friday with the assistance of Douglas County Sheriff’s Office K-9 Officer Eros.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K-9 Eros tracks down suspect]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/8f463bf0-d8da-11ee-a352-7f809482119d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/k-9-eros-tracks-down-suspect/article_8f463bf0-d8da-11ee-a352-7f809482119d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND — A Roseburg man was arrested Friday with the assistance of Douglas County Sheriff's Office K-9 Officer Eros.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marriages: Feb. 19-23]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2ad2436a-d4e5-11ee-b870-573fe5d90e62</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/marriages-feb-19-23/article_2ad2436a-d4e5-11ee-b870-573fe5d90e62.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T20:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Douglas County Clerk’s Office issued these licenses Feb. 19-23]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K9 Eros Tracks Down Stolen Vehicle Elude Suspect (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170404</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170404"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T20:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND, Ore. - On Friday, March 1, 2024, shortly after 2:30 p.m., Sutherlin Police Department attempted to stop a stolen 2017 Nissan Rogue on W. Central Avenue near Ponderosa Drive in Sutherlin. The suspect failed to stop and attempted to elude officers in the stolen vehicle.
The suspect crashed and fled on foot in the 600-block of Fawn Ridge Drive in Oakland. A perimeter was established and a Sheriff’s Office K9 was requested to respond to the scene.
K9 Eros responded and began to track the suspect from his last known location. During the track, Eros located clothing that had been worn by the suspect. K9 Eros eventually lead officers to a red pump house indicating the suspect was inside. Deputies began giving announcements that the suspect had been located by the K9 and should surrender. The suspect, 50-year-old Kevin Wade Davison of Roseburg, opened the door to the pump house and gave up without further incident.
Davison was taken into custody and lodged at the Douglas County Jail by Sutherlin Police Officers on their case.
K9 Eros, a 4.5-year-old German Shepherd, has been with the Douglas County Sheriff's Office since November 2021. He was purchased by an anonymous donor in the community and gifted to the agency. The Sheriff's Office K9 program, consisting of three Patrol K9 teams and 1 narcotics K9 team, is supported financially by private donations and the Friends of Umpqua Valley Police K9 Programs, a non-profit organization whose mission is to support local police K9 teams. Bailey's Veterinary Clinic provides medical care and some food for the Sheriff's Office K9 program while Coastal Farm and Home Supply provides all other food. The agency’s current K9 program has been highly active since 2013.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bailey discusses prescribed fire burns in fire management presentation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/708af21a-d794-11ee-9785-d34724342ff3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/bailey-discusses-prescribed-fire-burns-in-fire-management-presentation/article_708af21a-d794-11ee-9785-d34724342ff3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WINCHESTER — Fire and what fuels them was the hot topic Thursday night when John Bailey gave a presentation on fire management to about 50-70 people sitting in Umpqua Community College's Jacoby Auditorium.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116287</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/winter-weather-advisory-for-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-for-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T18:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 10:20 a.m.  A Winter Weather Advisory is in effect until 10:00 a.m. Sunday above 2,000 feet for central Douglas County. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said additional accumulations of 3 to 6 inches are expected. The Advisory area includes Canyon Creek Pass on Interstate 5. Up to 1 inch of snow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116284</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/winter-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas-16/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas-16"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T18:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 10:00 a.m.  A Winter Weather Advisory is in effect through 10:00 p.m. Sunday for mountain areas in southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said additional accumulations of 6 to 10 inches of snow are expected. Winds will gust up to 30 miles per hour over exposed terrain. The Advisory area...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRAFFIC CRASH CLAIMS LIFE OF RIDDLE TEEN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116282</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/traffic-crash-claims-life-of-riddle-teen/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=traffic-crash-claims-life-of-riddle-teen"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T17:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 9:30 a.m.  A Riddle teenager died Friday evening in a single vehicle crash. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said at approximately 10:30 p.m. dispatchers received a report of the wreck in the 15000 block of North Myrtle Road in the Myrtle Creek area. O’Dell said deputies arrived on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riddle teen dies in crash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6d8185b2-d8ba-11ee-866d-afb34d038014</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/riddle-teen-dies-in-crash/article_6d8185b2-d8ba-11ee-866d-afb34d038014.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T17:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK — A Riddle teenager died Friday in a single vehicle accident.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ERICA REYNOLDS The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fatal Traffic Crash Claims Life of Riddle Teen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170401</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news170401"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T17:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYRTLE CREEK, Ore. - A Riddle teenager died Friday evening in a single vehicle crash.
On March 1, 2024, at approximately 10:30 pm, 9-1-1 dispatchers received a report of a single vehicle crash with injuries in the 15000-block of North Myrtle Road in Myrtle Creek.
Deputies arrived on scene to find a 2006 Mazda sedan which had been traveling westbound at a high rate of speed in poor weather conditions. The driver, 17-year-old Brooke Leeann Dubuc of Myrtle Creek, lost control of the vehicle which rolled several times before striking a tree. A passenger, 17-year-old Jonathan Wylie Rosenstiel of Riddle, was ejected from the vehicle and trapped under the car when it came to rest. Rosenstiel was pronounced deceased at the scene by EMS. A second passenger, 19-year-old Canyonville resident Avorie Dunsmore, was able to self-extricate from the vehicle. Both Dubuc and Dunsmore were transported to Mercy Medical Center by Ambulance.
The investigation is ongoing at this time. Anyone with information related to the actions of the individuals involved prior to the crash is asked to contact the Douglas County Sheriff's Office at (541) 440-4471 referencing case #24-1140.
The Sheriff's Office was assisted by the Myrtle Creek Police Department, Douglas County District Attorney's Office, Umpqua Valley Ambulance, Myrtle Creek Fire Department and Joe's Towing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCSO SEEKING SEDAN FOLLOWING REPORTED ELUDE INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116280</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/dcso-seeking-sedan-following-reported-elude-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=dcso-seeking-sedan-following-reported-elude-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T17:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 9:00 a.m.  The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office is seeking a sedan following a reported eluding incident early Thursday. A DCSO report said just after 1:20 a.m. a deputy saw the vehicle commit multiple traffic violations in an attempt to get away while traveling southbound on Interstate 5 near Canyonville. The deputy caught...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES JAIL MAN FROM GREEN FOLLOWING ALLEGED DUII INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116278</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/deputies-jail-man-from-green-following-alleged-duii-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-jail-man-from-green-following-alleged-duii-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 8:50 a.m.   Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office jailed a man from Green, following an alleged DUII incident Friday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said shortly before 8:50 a.m. the 47-year-old went to a residence in the 2200 block of Castle Street to yell at the homeowner. A deputy arrived...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Searchers find pickup, driver not located]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/4386b854-d8b5-11ee-8408-3b6dddb4b18f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/searchers-find-pickup-driver-not-located/article_4386b854-d8b5-11ee-8408-3b6dddb4b18f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — Friday afternoon, searchers located a pickup that crashed into the North Umpqua River east of Glide on Thursday, but the body of the driver was not located.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Valley Christian students celebrate reading]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cb15a024-d80a-11ee-bca0-9759c3aff968</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/umpqua-valley-christian-students-celebrate-reading/article_cb15a024-d80a-11ee-bca0-9759c3aff968.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eggs were flipped, fish were counted and Whos were heard Friday when Umpqua Valley Christian School celebrated National Read Across America Day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New year, new books at Roseburg library]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b04a98ce-d7f8-11ee-8021-3716bfbf8184</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/new-year-new-books-at-roseburg-library/article_b04a98ce-d7f8-11ee-8021-3716bfbf8184.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library regularly adds new books to the collection, including these recently published titles that we recommend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AURORA ROPP AND KRIS WILEY For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Blackberry Festival adds scholarship]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bddd0da6-d6cb-11ee-a2f0-df8679f1e858</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/sutherlin-blackberry-festival-adds-scholarship/article_bddd0da6-d6cb-11ee-a2f0-df8679f1e858.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sutherlin Blackberry Festival expanded its scholarship program for 2024 and are is introducing a new-this-year Returning/Second Year Student Trades Scholarship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Registration open for 2024 North Douglas dodgeball tournament]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7c831d5a-d680-11ee-b133-27f2a851f101</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/registration-open-for-2024-north-douglas-dodgeball-tournament/article_7c831d5a-d680-11ee-b133-27f2a851f101.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team registration is open until March 11 for the second annual North Douglas Travel Club’s Dodgeball Tournament.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEARCHERS FIND PICKUP BUT DRIVER NOT LOCATED]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116275</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/searchers-find-pickup-but-driver-not-located/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=searchers-find-pickup-but-driver-not-located"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T15:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 7:00 a.m. Friday afternoon searchers located a pickup that crashed into the North Umpqua River east of Glide on Thursday, but the body of the driver was not located. Captain Kyle Kennedy of the Oregon State Police said a 1995 GMC pickup, believed to have been operated by 27-year-old Rachel Merchant-Ly was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to parent in a digital world presentation Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c07765c4-d67c-11ee-aeeb-b76e79ac3114</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/how-to-parent-in-a-digital-world-presentation-thursday/article_c07765c4-d67c-11ee-aeeb-b76e79ac3114.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pastor and certified Family Life Coach Jana Lee will present on how to parent in a digital world Thursday at the Roseburg Christian Academy, 1653 NW Troost St., Roseburg. The free seminar will begin with a light dinner at 6…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg library starts year strong]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e241776c-d75d-11ee-8859-d32051169e30</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/roseburg-library-starts-year-strong/article_e241776c-d75d-11ee-8859-d32051169e30.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Library is rocking in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KRIS WILEY Library News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCC nursing instructors stay local with tuition-free master’s degree]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e2d86de0-d594-11ee-9447-532af8e76ad7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/ucc-nursing-instructors-stay-local-with-tuition-free-master-s-degree/article_e2d86de0-d594-11ee-9447-532af8e76ad7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Community College nursing faculty members Rivka Spain Butler and Mary Barron are taking advantage of a new grant program enabling them to earn a master’s degree without leaving the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SUZI PRITCHARD For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Lions Club sells candy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6a90b002-d744-11ee-9f10-0f01cdd3f7e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/roseburg-lions-club-sells-candy/article_6a90b002-d744-11ee-9f10-0f01cdd3f7e4.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Roseburg Lions Club will be selling See's Candy from March 15-30 from a yellow trailer in the northwest corner of the Sherm's Thunderbird Marketplace parking lot, 2553 NW Stewart Parkway, Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County recreation report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7129bd8c-d802-11ee-93f3-c3685f5f730c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/douglas-county-recreation-report/article_7129bd8c-d802-11ee-93f3-c3685f5f730c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FISHING REPORT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING/WEATHER ADVISORY FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116270</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/winter-storm-warning-weather-advisory-for-central-douglas-county/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-weather-advisory-for-central-douglas-county"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T14:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 6:00 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect until 10:00 a.m. Saturday above 2,000 feet with a Winter Weather Advisory in place until 4:00 p.m. Sunday above 800 feet for central Douglas County. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said for the Warning, heavy snow is expected with additional accumulations of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING/WEATHER ADVISORY FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116267</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/02/winter-storm-warning-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-weather-advisory-for-mountain-areas"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T13:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 2, 2024 5:30 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect until 10:00 a.m. Saturday with a Winter Weather Advisory in place from 10:00 a.m. Saturday through 4:00 p.m. Sunday for mountain areas in southern Oregon. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said for the Warning, heavy snow is expected with additional accumulations of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCAN TO OPEN WARMING CENTER FOR SATURDAY NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116262</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/ucan-to-open-warming-center-for-saturday-night/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ucan-to-open-warming-center-for-saturday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 11:10 a.m.  The United Community Action Network is set to open a warming center in response to the inclement weather. Douglas County Housing and Homeless Services Program Manager Jacob Schlueter said the center will open Saturday night to bring people out of the cold and the expected elements. UCAN Executive Director Shaun...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR DUII-ALCOHOL, WARRANT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116260</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-alcohol-warrant/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-duii-alcohol-warrant"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T19:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man following an alleged DUII incident early Friday. An RPD report said just after 12:20 a.m. a 55-year-old man was scene leaving a business in the 200 block Northeast Jackson Street and travelling north on Southeast Stephens Street. The driver failed to signal his lane change...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR ALLEGED HIT AND RUN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116258</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-hit-and-run/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-alleged-hit-and-run"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 10:40 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a man after an alleged hit and run incident on Thursday night. An RPD report said at 6:15 p.m. officers contacted the 32-year-old after his pickup allegedly crashed into the side of another vehicle and drove away from the intersection of Northwest Stewart Parkway and West Harvard...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man arrested after hitting cars in Taco Bell parking lot]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3c4d1192-d7fb-11ee-bea8-a7bcb27a6eb8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/man-arrested-after-hitting-cars-in-taco-bell-parking-lot/article_3c4d1192-d7fb-11ee-bea8-a7bcb27a6eb8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — A 29-year-old Washington man hit two vehicles in the Taco Bell parking lot Thursday afternoon, then fled the scene before returning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WASHINGTON STATE MAN FOR ALLEGED DUII WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116256</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-police-jail-washington-state-man-for-alleged-duii-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-washington-state-man-for-alleged-duii-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 10:20 a.m.   Roseburg Police jailed a Washington State man following an alleged DUII wreck on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report said the 29-year-old allegedly struck two vehicles in the parking lot of a business in the 100 block of Northwest Garden Valley Boulevard with his company truck, towing a twenty-foot trailer, in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN, CITE WOMAN, IN DRUG LAW VIOLATION CASE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116254</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-police-jail-man-cite-woman-in-drug-law-violation-case/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-cite-woman-in-drug-law-violation-case"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 10:10 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man and cited a woman in a drug law violation case on Thursday afternoon. An RPD report at 1:45 p.m. officers responded after a caller said there was a suspicious vehicle in the 2000 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard. Officers contacted a 49-year-old man and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ODF sends Strike Team to Assist in Texas Wildfires (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170377</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=1072#news170377"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SALEM, Ore. – Today the Oregon Department of Forestry (ODF) deployed a strike team to Amarillo, Texas to assist in their wildfire suppression efforts. The strike team is equipped with five engines and a strike team leader, with a total of 16 firefighters traveling down to the state.  
The firefighters are going to Texas under mutual assistance agreements, making it easier to share resources. When wildfire activity is low in Oregon, firefighters can be spared to help in other places experiencing high levels of wildfire response. 
“We’re ready and willing to help whenever we receive the call from one of our partner states,” said Chris Cline, ODF’s Interim Fire Protection Division Chief.  “It’s the right thing to respond when someone is in a time of need, and we are honored to have the opportunity to serve.”
So how does Oregon send resources to help other states? This is all done through mutual assistance agreements creating a cache of reciprocal resources and a larger more comprehensive fire management system. In this system, Oregon does not only send out resources, but also receives and has received helpful resources when local capacity becomes overwhelmed.
 “The relationships built through our assistance in other states not only benefits them, but also Oregonians as we reach out for help when our fire season hits its peak.” Cline explained. In the 2023 fire season, Oregon received 173 out-of-state firefighters. 
Sending our firefighters on these out-of-state deployments helps them build relationships outside of our organization, learn new suppression tactics and gives them the opportunity to fight fire in a different landscape. These off-season deployments keep their skills sharp so they can come back to Oregon with new knowledge that can be applied to our future fire seasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oregon Dept. of Forestry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN JAILED FOLLOWING DUII FREEWAY CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116252</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-man-jailed-following-duii-freeway-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-jailed-following-duii-freeway-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T17:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 9:50 a.m.  A Roseburg man was jailed by the Oregon State Police following a DUII crash on Thursday night. An OSP report said at 11:50 p.m. a sports car was traveling northbound on Interstate 5, a mile north of the Winston exit, when the vehicle hydroplaned. The driver lost control and the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEARCH FOR WOMAN/VEHICLE SUSPENDED DUE TO CONDITIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116250</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/search-for-woman-vehicle-suspended-due-to-conditions/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=search-for-woman-vehicle-suspended-due-to-conditions"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T17:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 9:30 a.m.  The search for a woman and a vehicle both believed to have gone into the North Umpqua River on Thursday morning has been suspended due to current river and weather conditions. A report from Captain Kyle Kennedy of the Oregon State Police said just before 8:40 a.m. troopers were advised...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glide teacher missing following car accident]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/3df04cb0-d7e9-11ee-aa46-87da366597a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/glide-teacher-missing-following-car-accident/article_3df04cb0-d7e9-11ee-aa46-87da366597a3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T16:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — Rachel Merchant-Ly, a kindergarten teacher at Glide Elementary School, is missing after her vehicle left Highway 138 on Thursday morning and landed in the North Umpqua River.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rural Electrical Pre-Apprenticeship program expanding with mobile units]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/cd34d0dc-d76a-11ee-a928-af9b6a94856a</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/rural-electrical-pre-apprenticeship-program-expanding-with-mobile-units/article_cd34d0dc-d76a-11ee-a928-af9b6a94856a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — Students gathered Thursday in the gym at Glide High School to hear about how they might be involved in a career that would pay them approximately $40 right out of high school.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RECORD RAINFALL FOR FEBRUARY 29TH IN ROSEBURG]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116247</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/record-rainfall-for-february-29th-in-roseburg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=record-rainfall-for-february-29th-in-roseburg"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 6:50 a.m. The Umpqua Valley saw a record amount of rain for the date on Thursday, but the fact that it was February 29th impacts the data. Forecasters at the National Weather Service told News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN that 1.71 inches of rain was recorded at the Roseburg Regional...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The yeast of my worries]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/6097001e-cf4d-11ee-b261-0bf1ffb67a96</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/the-yeast-of-my-worries/article_6097001e-cf4d-11ee-b261-0bf1ffb67a96.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, an unlikely group teamed up to do something remarkable. They were archaeologist Serena Love, microbiologist Richard Bowman and Seamus Blackley — best known as the creator of the original X-box. The remarkable thing that they did was also…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AIMEE LOVE For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask a Master Gardener: Divide and conquer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/145d037c-d4cc-11ee-a9c9-87c567271ea5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/ask-a-master-gardener-divide-and-conquer/article_145d037c-d4cc-11ee-a9c9-87c567271ea5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question: I’ve noticed that my daylilies are not producing as many flowers as in the past and seem overcrowded. Is spring a good time to divide them, and how do I go about that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BONNIE COURTER For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workshop to cover sourdough starter and discard recipes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c2dd7618-d678-11ee-9f87-27998aa26187</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/workshop-to-cover-sourdough-starter-and-discard-recipes/article_c2dd7618-d678-11ee-9f87-27998aa26187.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Oregon State University Extension Service and Douglas County Master Food Preservers are offering a workshop dedicated to sourdough from 6-8 p.m. March 21 at the Lookingglass Grange, 7426 Lookingglass Road in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Storm Warning in effect through Saturday morning]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/922ebe38-d744-11ee-a273-c708eec89381</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/winter-storm-warning-in-effect-through-saturday-morning/article_922ebe38-d744-11ee-a273-c708eec89381.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Winter Storm Warning is in effect through 10 a.m. Saturday for Douglas County areas above 2,000 feet. A Winter Weather Advisory is in place for areas above 800 feet during that same time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Storm Warning in affect through Saturday morning]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/922ebe38-d744-11ee-a273-c708eec89381</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/winter-storm-warning-in-affect-through-saturday-morning/article_922ebe38-d744-11ee-a273-c708eec89381.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY — A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect through 10 a.m. Saturday for Douglas County areas above 2,500 feet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING FOR CENTRAL DOUGLAS COUNTY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116242</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/winter-storm-warning-for-central-douglas-county-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-for-central-douglas-county-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 4:15 a.m. A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect for central Douglas County above 2,000 feet through Saturday Morning at 10:00 a.m. A Winter Weather Advisory remains in place above 800 feet through Saturday morning at 10:00 a.m. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said for the Warning area, heavy snow, with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WINTER STORM WARNING FOR MOUNTAIN AREAS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116239</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/winter-storm-warning-for-mountain-areas-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=winter-storm-warning-for-mountain-areas-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T12:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 4:00 a.m.  A Winter Storm Warning remains in effect for mountain areas in southern Oregon through 10:00 a.m. Saturday. Forecasters at the National Weather Service said heavy snow and blowing snow is expected with total snow accumulations of 2 to 3 feet, but around 10 to 14 inches at the Siskiyou Summit....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO ONE HURT IN SEMI VERSUS SCHOOL BUS CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116237</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/no-one-hurt-in-semi-versus-school-bus-crash/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=no-one-hurt-in-semi-versus-school-bus-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 3:50 a.m. No one was hurt in a semi-truck versus school bus crash in Glendale on Thursday afternoon. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell of the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office said just after 3:30 p.m. deputies were dispatched to the intersection of Brown Street and Sether Avenue. O’Dell said upon investigation it was determined that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERKLEY TOWN HALL HAPPENING SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116235</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/merkley-town-hall-happening-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=merkley-town-hall-happening-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 3:40 a.m. U.S. Senator Jeff Merkley will have an in-person town hall in Douglas County on Saturday. The event kicks off Merkley’s 2024 town hall tour of Oregon, where he will hold community conversations for each of the state’s 36 counties. Merkley said he holds a town hall for every Oregon county...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADAPT OPIOID TREATMENT PROGRAMS RECEIVE 3-YEAR ACCREDITATION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116233</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/adapt-opioid-treatment-programs-receive-3-year-accreditation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=adapt-opioid-treatment-programs-receive-3-year-accreditation"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 3;20 a.m. Adapt Integrated Health Care has announced that it has earned a 3-year accreditation for both the Roseburg and North Bend clinics from CARF International. An Adapt release said this accreditation is the highest level that can be given to an organization and shows their substantial commitment to upholding the standards...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FRIENDS OF LIBRARY BOOK SALE HAPPENING THROUGH SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116231</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/friends-of-library-book-sale-happening-through-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=friends-of-library-book-sale-happening-through-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 3:05 a.m. Friends of the Roseburg Public Library are continuing their Spring Book Sale through Saturday. It includes fiction and nonfiction books that have been donated or withdrawn from the library and may be slightly worn or have library markings. There is a table of antique books and atlases and movie DVDs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG LION’S CLUB SELLING SEE’S CANDY TO BENEFIT COMMUNITY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=116229</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/03/01/roseburg-lions-club-selling-sees-candy-to-benefit-community/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-lions-club-selling-sees-candy-to-benefit-community"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 1, 2024 2:50 a.m. The Roseburg Lions Club will be selling See’s Candy to help support the club’s various projects in the community between March 15th and March 30th. This fundraising event also supports the Oregon Lions Sight and Hearing Foundation’s KTP Days. KTP stands for “Keeping the Promise”. See’s Candy sales will take...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>