<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html</id>
    <title>The Roseburg Receiver News</title>
    <updated>2024-01-26T02:18:34.368Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://news.theroseburgreceiver.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARREST MADE FOLLOWING LENGTHY MANHUNT AFTER ASTORIA MAN ELUDED LAW ENFORCEMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115255</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/arrest-made-following-lengthy-manhunt-after-astoria-man-eluded-law-enforcement/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=arrest-made-following-lengthy-manhunt-after-astoria-man-eluded-law-enforcement"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T21:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 1:40 p.m. Thursday morning the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office arrested a man following a lengthy manhunt after he allegedly eluded police following a traffic stop on Wednesday night. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell said at 9:00 a.m. deputies received information that a man matching the description of 47-year old Billy Best of Astoria had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 1.25.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115250</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/inside-douglas-county-1-25-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-1-25-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T21:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas Education Service District Superintendent Analicia Nicholson with a mid-year update on programs being offered by the ESD.  Click here to download for later listening:  IDC 1 25 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PLANT AND GARDEN EXPO ORGANIZERS ACCEPTING APPLICATIONS FOR VENDORS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115247</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/plant-and-garden-expo-organizers-accepting-applications-for-vendors/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=plant-and-garden-expo-organizers-accepting-applications-for-vendors"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 11:10 a.m.  Booth applications are available for vendors interested in being part of the annual Plant and Garden Expo organized by Douglas County Master Gardeners. The expo will be held on Saturday, May 4th at the Douglas County Fairgrounds. The event draws several thousand people that day between the hours of 9:00...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE MAN FOR LITTERING NEAR WATERS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115245</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-littering-near-waters-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-littering-near-waters-2"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T19:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for a littering near waters incident. An RPD report said at 6:40 a.m. the 40-year old was contacted at his camp at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. His camp consisted of two tents and a substantial amount of trash covering...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR REPORTED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115243</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-reported-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-reported-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 10:30 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a woman Wednesday for a reported prior theft incident. An RPD report said on Tuesday the 27-year old allegedly stole multiple items from a business in the 1300 block of Northeast Stephens Street. She was contacted at 4:00 p.m. and admitted to the theft. The woman was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRIVER CITED AFTER ACCIDENT DURING MORNING COMMUTE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115239</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/driver-cited-after-accident-during-morning-commute/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=driver-cited-after-accident-during-morning-commute"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:23:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 204 10:25 a.m.  A driver was cited after a two-vehicle accident during the morning commute on Wednesday. A Roseburg Police report said at about 7:55 a.m. officers responded to the 2600 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard. An investigation showed the driver of a box truck made a dangerous left turn from the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL AFTER AFTER INCIDENT ON BUSY STREET]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115237</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/roseburg-police-jail-after-after-incident-on-busy-street/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-after-after-incident-on-busy-street"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 10:15 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man after an alleged incident on a busy street on Wednesday. An RPD report said at approximately 9:10 a.m. officers responded to the 300 block of West Harvard Avenue after callers said a man was walking into traffic and throwing rocks at vehicles. The 25-year old...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE MAN JAILED AFTER ALLEGED ESCAPE INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115235</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/riddle-man-jailed-after-alleged-escape-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riddle-man-jailed-after-alleged-escape-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 10:00 a.m.   A Riddle man was jailed after an alleged escape incident on Tuesday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 9:10 p.m. a deputy saw the 38-year old standing in the driveway of a home in the 4000 block of Canyonville Riddle Road in the Riddle area, and knew...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manhunt for Wanted Man Who Eluded Law Enforcement (Photo)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news169571</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=5204#news169571"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T17:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN, Ore. - A wanted man eluded law enforcement Wednesday evening following a vehicle pursuit. 
On Wednesday, January 24, 2024, shortly after 5:00 pm, a deputy attempted to stop a silver 2008 Ford Focus near the 800-block of John Long Road in Oakland. The driver failed to stop for the deputy and attempted to elude at a high rate of speed driving southbound on Interstate 5. 
Near the Oakland exit, a Sutherlin Police Officer was able to successfully deploy spike strips on the eluding vehicle. The driver of the Focus later crashed into a ditch and fled on foot near Interstate 5, Exit 136 in Sutherlin. The driver of the vehicle, later identified as Billy James Best of Seaside, Oregon, was believed to be armed with a handgun. Law enforcement issued a “reverse 9-1-1” call to the area using an alerting system to notify area residents.
DCSO, Sutherlin Police Department and Oregon State Police searched the area for hours with assistance of canines without success. Best has multiple warrants for his arrest including new crimes committed during the elude. 
There remains a heavy law enforcement presence in the area searching for Best, although it is believed he has likely left the area. “We ask the community to remain vigilant and report any suspicious activity to 9-1-1," Lt. Brad O'Dell said.
A female passenger, Christina Marie Dominguez of Cave Junction was taken into custody for Unlawful Possession of Methamphetamine.
Best is described as a white male adult, approximately 6'00" tall weighing approximately 200 lbs, with several tattoos. He was last seen wearing dark clothing at the time he ran from police. Booking photos of Best from 2022 are being released to assist in his apprehension.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Sheriff's Office</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OAKLAND MAN JAILED AFTER REPORTED TRESPASS INCIDENT EARLY THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115226</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/oakland-man-jailed-after-reported-trespass-incident-early-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=oakland-man-jailed-after-reported-trespass-incident-early-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T17:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 9:30 a.m. An Oakland man was jailed after a reported trespass incident early Thursday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 2:00 a.m. a deputy responded to the 100 block of Williams Road in Yoncalla after a caller said the 35-year old could not be at the location due to a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEPUTIES SEEK ALLEGEDLY ARMED MAN AFTER HE ELUDED LAW ENFORCEMENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115224</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/deputies-seek-allegedly-armed-man-after-he-eluded-law-enforcement/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=deputies-seek-allegedly-armed-man-after-he-eluded-law-enforcement"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T17:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2025 9:20 a.m.  Deputies with the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office are seeking an allegedly armed Seaside man who eluded authorities following an attempted traffic stop on Wednesday. Lieutenant Brad O’Dell said shortly after 5:00 p.m. a deputy attempted to stop a sedan in the 800 block of John Long Road at Rice Hill....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 1.25.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115221</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/morning-conversation-1-25-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-1-25-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T17:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Representative Court Boice talks about his opposition to the Oregon Department of Forestry Habitat Conservation Plan. Click here to download for later listening:  830 1 25 24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Point in Time survey counts the homeless]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/c9952ce8-ba1d-11ee-be13-5b10451de370</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/point-in-time-survey-counts-the-homeless/article_c9952ce8-ba1d-11ee-be13-5b10451de370.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Faith Foundry Church in Roseburg temporarily turned into a one-stop social service center Wednesday, as it served as headquarters for the annual Point-in-Time count of homeless individuals in Douglas County.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Carroll The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zonta Club discusses Amelia Earhart in terms of modern aviation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b211aeda-bb0c-11ee-92ef-b72fa2975074</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/zonta-club-discusses-amelia-earhart-in-terms-of-modern-aviation/article_b211aeda-bb0c-11ee-92ef-b72fa2975074.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Zonta Club of Roseburg held one of their free Wednesday meetings at noon in Abby’s Pizza’s Annex on Stephens Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Out of this world: Roseburg man's cremains launched into deep space]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/304ec808-ba10-11ee-af48-c32447dd3371</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/out-of-this-world-roseburg-mans-cremains-launched-into-deep-space/article_304ec808-ba10-11ee-af48-c32447dd3371.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Arwood Jr. is headed deep into space, but he won’t be able to tell the tales of his adventure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County welcomes Dr. Phillip and Dr. Kate Braunlich]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e56289ae-b57a-11ee-b95a-a3f58f5bae3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/douglas-county-welcomes-dr-phillip-and-dr-kate-braunlich/article_e56289ae-b57a-11ee-b95a-a3f58f5bae3f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although it has been a wet one, Dr. Phillip Braunlich and his wife, Dr. Kate Braunlich, have said it has been the warmest of welcomes as the both of them settle into their new medical roles and life in Roseburg.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUSPICIOUS ACTIVITY LEADS TO DCSO ALERT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115216</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/suspicious-activity-leads-to-dcso-alert/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=suspicious-activity-leads-to-dcso-alert"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T12:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 4:15 a.m.  Suspicious activity just west of Sutherlin Wednesday night led to the Douglas County Sheriff’s Office alerting some residents and asking that they lock their doors and stay in their homes. A reverse 911 was sent out around 7:00 p.m. to people living in the area of the Oak Hills Golf...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FLOOD POTENTIAL OUTLOOK FOR FRIDAY/SATURDAY AS STORM HITS REGION]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115213</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/flood-potential-outlook-for-friday-saturday-as-storm-hits-region/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=flood-potential-outlook-for-friday-saturday-as-storm-hits-region"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T11:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 4:00 a.m. The National Weather Service has issued a Flood Potential Outlook for parts of the region for Friday and Saturday. This means there could be quick rises and potential flooding of low-lying areas and poorly drained urban areas in western Douglas, western Josephine and Coos and Curry counties. Forecasters said a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG CHEER HOLDING COMPETITION SATURDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115209</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/roseburg-cheer-holding-competition-saturday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-cheer-holding-competition-saturday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T11:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 3:50 a.m.  Roseburg Cheer is holding a cheer competition on Saturday at Roseburg High School. The giant event will include seven teams from Douglas County and nearly twenty-five teams from all over western and central Oregon. Around 80 performances are expected to take place throughout the day. There will be several recreational...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AUDUBON SOCIETY/LIBRARY TO STREAM CONSERVATION PROGRAM]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115206</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/audubon-society-library-to-stream-conservation-program/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=audubon-society-library-to-stream-conservation-program"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T11:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 3:40 a.m. Umpqua Audubon Society and Roseburg Public Library will have a Facebook Live streaming event with conservationist Paul Engelmeyer on Wednesday, February 7th at 6:30 p.m. A City release said Engelmeyer will present “Land-Sea Conservation Issues and Strategies” covering topics such as marine reserves, salmon conservation efforts and the Endangered Species...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG EDUCATION ASSOCIATION AWARDING SCHOLARSHIPS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115204</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/roseburg-education-association-awarding-scholarships/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-education-association-awarding-scholarships"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T11:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 3:30 a.m. The Roseburg Education Association is awarding two $1,500 scholarships this year for two graduating seniors. A REA release said applicants must be a child of a member of the association. This scholarship is not restricted to Roseburg High School graduates. The scholarship may be used to attend any accredited school...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUCK CARRYING BOULDERS CRASHES JUST EAST OF REEDSPORT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115202</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/truck-carrying-boulders-crashes-just-east-of-reedsport/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=truck-carrying-boulders-crashes-just-east-of-reedsport"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T11:16:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 3:10 a.m. Covering coastal Douglas County: Troopers from Oregon State Police responded to Highway 38 about two miles east of Reedsport on Monday, after tractor truck pulling a flat-bed trailer carrying large boulders crashed into an earthen embankment. An OSP report released Wednesday said the accident happened shortly before 9:50 a.m. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SENATORS JOIN CALL FOR LOW-INCOME WATER ASSISTANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115200</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/25/senators-join-call-for-low-income-water-assistance/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=senators-join-call-for-low-income-water-assistance"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T10:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 25, 2024 2:50 a.m. On Wednesday, Oregon’s U.S. Senators Ron Wyden and Jeff Merkley said they have joined Senate colleagues in calling on the Senate Appropriations Committee to restore funding for the Low-Income Household Water Assistance Program for Fiscal Year 2024. A release said the crucial funding that expired at the end of FY23...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riddle celebrates 131st birthday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fe5d8a1a-ba6d-11ee-82d8-f3f2a15993ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/riddle-celebrates-131st-birthday/article_fe5d8a1a-ba6d-11ee-82d8-f3f2a15993ac.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T04:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE — Riddle’s 131st birthday is Jan. 31.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manhunt for Billy Best who eludes law enforcement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/af6557e2-bb32-11ee-a05c-3b93e1c98e83</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/manhunt-for-billy-best-who-eludes-law-enforcement/article_af6557e2-bb32-11ee-a05c-3b93e1c98e83.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T03:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Some Sutherlin residents were asked to lock their doors and stay in their homes Wednesday evening as law enforcement searched for an armed suspect in the area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Armed suspect runs from police]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/af6557e2-bb32-11ee-a05c-3b93e1c98e83</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/armed-suspect-runs-from-police/article_af6557e2-bb32-11ee-a05c-3b93e1c98e83.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T03:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Some Sutherlin residents were asked to lock their doors and stay in their homes Wednesday evening as law enforcement searched for an armed suspect in the area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement in pursuit of armed suspect near Sutherlin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/af6557e2-bb32-11ee-a05c-3b93e1c98e83</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/crime/law-enforcement-in-pursuit-of-armed-suspect-near-sutherlin/article_af6557e2-bb32-11ee-a05c-3b93e1c98e83.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T03:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN — Some Sutherlin residents were asked to lock their doors and stay in their homes as law enforcement searched for an armed suspect in the area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIKE WINTERS LAWN AND GARDEN SHOW 1.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115197</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-1-24-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mike-winters-lawn-and-garden-show-1-24-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County’s Commissioner of Dirt Mike Winters has our weekly local law and garden program.  This is an encore program from January 25, 2023.  Click here to download for later listening:  MWLGS 1 25 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State emergency management looking to partner with local businesses]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/2dfb3104-b970-11ee-a565-9b700ea98c47</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/environment/state-emergency-management-looking-to-partner-with-local-businesses/article_2dfb3104-b970-11ee-a565-9b700ea98c47.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T21:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past few weeks have brought winter weather back to Oregon, and with it some incidents, and the state is hoping for communities to be prepared to offer assistance in case of disaster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 1.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115193</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/inside-douglas-county-1-24-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-1-24-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T21:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg Public Schools Superintendent Jared Cordon has a mid-school year update on things happening in the district.   Click here to download for later listening: IDC 1 24 24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audubon, library to stream conservation program]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/bf522788-baf7-11ee-912d-6777e88b50a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/audubon-library-to-stream-conservation-program/article_bf522788-baf7-11ee-912d-6777e88b50a2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T20:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Umpqua Valley Audubon Society and Roseburg Public Library are co-hosting a Facebook live streaming event with conservationist Paul Engelmeyer at 6:30 p.m. Feb. 7.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TICKETS STILL ON SALE FOR EMPOWER EVENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115191</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/tickets-still-on-sale-for-empower-event/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tickets-still-on-sale-for-empower-event"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T18:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 10:50 a.m.  In the KQEN Cultural Spotlight; Tickets are still on sale for the Peace at Home Advocacy Center EMPOWER Event. It will take place Saturday March 2nd starting at 5:00 p.m. at Seven Feathers Casino Resort in Canyonville. The evening includes a buffet dinner, dance and vocal performances, a paddle raising...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County employers add 170 jobs in December]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/63485470-bae9-11ee-b550-5f810b5d3592</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/business/douglas-county-employers-add-170-jobs-in-december/article_63485470-bae9-11ee-b550-5f810b5d3592.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County payroll employment increased a seasonally adjusted 170 jobs in December after a gain of 50 in November and a decrease of 250 in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melrose Road has reopened]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/34a16ad0-bae9-11ee-8a71-87b3d7664b34</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/melrose-road-has-reopened/article_34a16ad0-bae9-11ee-8a71-87b3d7664b34.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T18:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Oregon Department of Transportation reopened Melrose Road in the area of the Conn Ford Bridge construction project on Tuesday evening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COUNTY COMMISSIONER SPEAKING AT DTO MEETING THURSDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115189</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/county-commissioner-speaking-at-dto-meeting-thursday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=county-commissioner-speaking-at-dto-meeting-thursday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T18:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 10:30 a.m.   Douglas County Commissioner Chris Boice will speak at the Thursday meeting of the Douglas Timber Operators. Boice will have a presentation titled, “Douglas County Recap of 2023 and Forecast of What is to Come in 2024”. The new host breakfast will begin at 8:00 a.m. in the loft at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG FIRE ANNOUNCES HIRING OF DEPUTY FIRE MARSHAL]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115186</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/roseburg-fire-announces-hiring-of-deputy-fire-marshal/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-fire-announces-hiring-of-deputy-fire-marshal"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T18:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 10:10 a.m.  The City of Roseburg Fire Department has announced the hiring of new Deputy Fire Marshal Ben Simons. Under the direction of Fire Marshal Flick, Simons will work in the Fire Prevention Division. Simons was welcomed to the department on January 16th. Simons has received numerous certifications, from both Oregon and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL MAN FOR WARRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115184</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-man-for-warrants"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T18:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man for multiple warrants on Tuesday evening. An RPD report said at 7:30 p.m. officers contacted the 51-year old in the 400 block of Northeast Hewitt Avenue. He was charged with three warrants. Bail was set at $5,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITE WOMAN FOR WARRANTS/TRAFFIC VIOLATIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115182</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-warrants-traffic-violations/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-woman-for-warrants-traffic-violations"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T17:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 9:50 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a woman for a warrant and for traffic violations on Tuesday night. An RPD report said shortly after 10:00 p.m. the 58-year old was stopped for a traffic violation in the 2200 block of Northeast Diamond Lake Boulevard. During the stop, the officer learned that the driver...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN POLICE JAIL MAN AFTER REPORTED THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115180</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/sutherlin-police-jail-man-after-reported-theft/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sutherlin-police-jail-man-after-reported-theft"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T17:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 9:30 a.m.  Sutherlin Police jailed two men after a reported theft incident on Tuesday. An SPD report said at approximately 11:15 a.m. the 46 and 48-year old men were allegedly caught on video stealing from a business in the 500 block of West Central Avenue. They were located down the road and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WASHINGTON MAN JAILED AFTER ALLEGED RESISTING AND ESCAPE INCIDENT MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115178</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/washington-man-jailed-after-alleged-resisting-and-escape-incident-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=washington-man-jailed-after-alleged-resisting-and-escape-incident-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T17:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 9:20 a.m. A Washington State man was jailed following an alleged resisting and escape incident on Monday. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said at 11:30 a.m. a deputy attempted to stop a man for disorderly conduct and offensive littering in the 500 block of John Long Road at Rice Hill. 32-year...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 1.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115175</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/morning-conversation-1-24-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-1-24-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T17:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live from Salem, State Representative Christine Goodwin talks about changes to Measure 110 being proposed by both Republicans and Democrats and how the ideas differ. Click here to download for later listening:  830 1 24 24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebration of Literacy takes place in February]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/1d6a3f26-b941-11ee-8bd1-fb332d8afb0c</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/celebration-of-literacy-takes-place-in-february/article_1d6a3f26-b941-11ee-8bd1-fb332d8afb0c.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celebration of Literacy is a series of events happening throughout February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHI Mercy Health Behavioral Health Unit celebrates soft opening]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/be0ef56e-ba15-11ee-b7be-035c480b5421</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/chi-mercy-health-behavioral-health-unit-celebrates-soft-opening/article_be0ef56e-ba15-11ee-b7be-035c480b5421.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peaceful blue walls and light streaming in from the many windows served as the backdrop to a large group of community members, from medical professionals to government officials to the general public, all admiring CHI Mercy Health’s new Behavioral Health…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glide Wildflower Show accepting volunteers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/9c146876-ba48-11ee-a93e-c3d480708d1e</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/glide-wildflower-show-accepting-volunteers/article_9c146876-ba48-11ee-a93e-c3d480708d1e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GLIDE — The Glide Wildflower Show is accepting volunteers for its April 27 and 28 showcase. Several opportunities require no knowledge of botany or flowers, though those positions need help, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas County Animal Control Deputy retires after 33 years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ce9d290c-b707-11ee-8d71-cb80d773d497</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/douglas-county-animal-control-deputy-retires-after-33-years/article_ce9d290c-b707-11ee-8d71-cb80d773d497.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Bartholomew said he feels plenty comfortable with humans, but is way more comfortable with animals, so comfortable he spent 33 years as a Douglas County Animal Control Deputy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HANNAH SEIBOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brittany learns pickleball]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/5f96f678-ba13-11ee-ae3c-9b2b9ea9b7ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/brittany-learns-pickleball/article_5f96f678-ba13-11ee-ae3c-9b2b9ea9b7ec.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve noticed the growing camaraderie on the YMCA courts. I’ve noticed my parents, grandparents and friends begin to play. But it wasn’t until I saw a young woman wearing a sweatshirt reading, “In my pickleball era,” and entered Target recently…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lifestyle medicine takes root in rural Oregon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/5da10fc0-ba1d-11ee-b848-7f4c4c9994d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/guest_submission/lifestyle-medicine-takes-root-in-rural-oregon/article_5da10fc0-ba1d-11ee-b848-7f4c4c9994d0.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nestled among rolling hills and between flowing rivers, In a culture of deeply ingrained sense of community, unpretentiousness, hard-work and neighborly connections, a quiet revolution is taking place — one that focuses not just on treating illness but on preventing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JULIETE PALENSHUS For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of the Days Creek School District]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/d0d7eb24-b9bb-11ee-a5a6-b781fd909271</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/state-of-the-days-creek-school-district/article_d0d7eb24-b9bb-11ee-a5a6-b781fd909271.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAYS CREEK — Days Creek Charter School’s interim superintendent Joe La Fountaine held a State of the District open night Monday in the gym at the school. Parents, students and school staff showed up to hear what the school has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get in the game: the rise of pickleball]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/7f6522ea-b95a-11ee-a817-837dc2a93464</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/get-in-the-game-the-rise-of-pickleball/article_7f6522ea-b95a-11ee-a817-837dc2a93464.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walking past the YMCA pickleball courts, it would be hard not to notice the large crowds gathering along with the sounds of laughter, lively conversation and squeaking tennis shoes spilling off the courts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BRITTANY ARNOLD The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MELROSE ROAD HAS REOPENED IN CONSTRUCTION AREA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115169</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/melrose-road-has-reopened-in-construction-area/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=melrose-road-has-reopened-in-construction-area"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T11:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 3:50 a.m.  The Oregon Department of Transportation says that Melrose Road reopened in the area of Conn Ford Bridge construction project on Tuesday evening. The road had been closed for one week at the South Umpqua River about one mile west of Roseburg, as contractors placed beams on the new bridge. A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE SEEKING MISSING MAN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115165</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/roseburg-police-seeking-missing-man/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-seeking-missing-man"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T11:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 3:40 a.m. Roseburg Police are seeking information into the whereabouts of Tykerrious (Ty) Ray. An RPD release said the 28-year old has not been seen or heard from since December 28th.  Ray was last known to be driving his white Dodge Durango pickup which was abandoned in the 3000 block of Old...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY EMPLOYERS ADD 170 JOBS IN DECEMBER]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115163</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/douglas-county-employers-add-170-jobs-in-december/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=douglas-county-employers-add-170-jobs-in-december"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T11:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 3:30 a.m. Douglas County payroll employment increased a seasonally adjusted 170 jobs in December after a gain of 50 in November and a decrease of 250 in October. A State of Oregon Employment Department release said Douglas County has gained back 92 percent of the jobs lost in March and April 2020...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FARM BUREAU AWARDING UP TO FIVE $1,000 SCHOLARSHIPS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115161</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/farm-bureau-awarding-up-to-five-1000-scholarships/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=farm-bureau-awarding-up-to-five-1000-scholarships"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T11:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 3:20 a.m. The Douglas County Farm Bureau is pleased to announce that it will be awarding up to five $1,000 scholarships for the 2024-2025 school year. A release said this is for students who are either pursuing a course of study in agriculture or forestry or are children or grandchildren of a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REPUBLICANS CRITICIZE DEMOCRATS PLAN TO ADDRESS MEASURE 110]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115159</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/republicans-criticize-democrats-plan-to-address-measure-110/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=republicans-criticize-democrats-plan-to-address-measure-110"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T11:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 3:10 a.m. Three Republican leaders are criticizing a Democratic plan released on Tuesday, to address Measure 110. A GOP release said Republicans have also introduced several key pieces of legislation which can be found at: https://olis.oregonlegislature.gov/liz/2023I1 Senate Republican Leader Tim Knopp of Bend, said, “Above all, I am saddened by the Democrats...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WYDEN URGES FEDERAL AGENCIES TO BOOST FOOD/AG RESEARCH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115157</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/wyden-urges-federal-agencies-to-boost-food-ag-research/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wyden-urges-federal-agencies-to-boost-food-ag-research"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T11:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 2:50 a.m. U.S. Senator Ron Wyden said he has joined Senate colleagues to urge top federal officials to increase the Department of Agriculture’s research budget by at least five percent, plus inflation, for Fiscal Year 2025. In a letter to Agriculture Secretary Thomas Vilsack and Office of Management and Budget Director Shalanda...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reedsport seeks city attorney]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fada1f6c-ba6c-11ee-89de-0361f62be045</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/government/reedsport-seeks-city-attorney/article_fada1f6c-ba6c-11ee-89de-0361f62be045.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T03:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REEDSPORT — The City of Reedsport is seeking a city attorney.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pets receive microchips in Myrtle Creek pop-up clinic]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/0c4c250c-b8c3-11ee-bc5a-77ecde68ea6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/health/pets-receive-microchips-in-myrtle-creek-pop-up-clinic/article_0c4c250c-b8c3-11ee-bc5a-77ecde68ea6d.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T01:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Myrtle Creek — Saving Grace Pet Adoption Center took over the back room at Tractor Supply Co. in Myrtle Creek on Saturday for a microchip clinic, with a line of dogs, cats and humans stretching through the aisles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GLORIA COLEMAN The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRUE WEALTH 1.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115154</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/24/true-wealth-1-23-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=true-wealth-1-23-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T01:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presented by Littlejohn Financial, David Littlejohn and Matt Dickson are joined by Scott Littlejohn for our weekly local financial program.  Click here to download for later listening:  TRUE WEALTH 1 23 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 1.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115150</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/inside-douglas-county-1-23-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-1-23-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T21:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the State of the City with Roseburg Mayor Larry Rich and City Manager Nikki Messenger. Click here to download for later listening:  IDC 1 23 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CITED A MAN FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115147</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/roseburg-police-cited-a-man-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cited-a-man-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T19:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 11:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited camping on Monday. An RPD report said at 8:50 a.m. the 40-year old was found camping under the pavilion at Gaddis Park in the 800 block of Northwest Highland Street. There were large amounts of trash everywhere. The man has been warned numerous...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAN CITED FOR FALSE SWEARING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115144</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/man-cited-for-false-swearing/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=man-cited-for-false-swearing"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T18:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 10:50 a.m.  A Roseburg man was cited by Roseburg Police for false swearing on Monday evening. An RPD report said officers were notified of a denied firearm application that occurred on November 14th. The 30-year old suspect had allegedly applied to purchase a handgun from a business in the 2800 block of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tue. 23rd, 10:54 AM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#emerg72102</id>
        <link href="https://www.flashalert.net/news.html?id=6158#emerg72102"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T18:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOUGLAS COUNTY FIRE DISTRICT No. 2NEWS AND INFORMATION                                 1400 Buckhorn Road, Roseburg, OR 97470                              Phone (541) 673-5503 / Fax (541) 673-5505www.dcfd.org_____________________________________________________________________________________Type of Incident:     Water Rescue                                                              Date:               01-22-2024                                                                                                           Release Date:          01-23-2024                                                                                                                           Contact:          Battalion Chief's Office                                   Phone:          541-440-7623 (desk)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Co. Fire Dist. No.2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO JAILED FOR OFFENSIVE LITTERING/WARRANTS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115142</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/two-jailed-for-offensive-littering-warrants/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-jailed-for-offensive-littering-warrants"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T18:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 10:45 a.m. Two people were jailed for offensive littering and for warrants by the Roseburg Police Department early Tuesday. An RPD report said just after 12:00 a.m. officers located a transient camp above Brookdale Senior Living in the 3200 block of Northwest Edenbower Boulevard. The camp had a large amount of trash...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FEMALE JUVENILE HOSPITALIZED AFTER BEING STRUCK BY A VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115140</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/female-juvenile-hospitalized-after-being-struck-by-a-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=female-juvenile-hospitalized-after-being-struck-by-a-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T18:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 10:35 a. m. A female juvenile was hospitalized after being struck by a vehicle on Monday afternoon. A Roseburg Police report said just before 3:10 p.m. officers responded to the accident in the 2300 block of Northeast Stephens Street. The female was hit by a full-sized pickup which was driven by an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garden Valley off-ramp to close next week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e58b22ea-ba1d-11ee-94d3-ff3176bdb2a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/garden-valley-off-ramp-to-close-next-week/article_e58b22ea-ba1d-11ee-94d3-ff3176bdb2a3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T18:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Interstate 5 northbound off-ramp at exit 125, Garden Valley Boulevard, will be closed Sunday, Monday and Tuesday nights for construction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO MEN RESCUED IN SOUTH UMPQUA RIVER MONDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115138</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/two-men-rescued-in-south-umpqua-river-monday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-men-rescued-in-south-umpqua-river-monday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T18:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 10:20 a.m. Two men were rescued in the South Umpqua River in the area of Elk Island in Roseburg on Monday afternoon. A release from Douglas County Fire District No. 2 said crews with the Roseburg Fire Department were dispatched just after 2:40 p.m. They requested a Technical Rescue Team from DCFD2....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roseburg man reported missing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/518e5298-ba1c-11ee-be8f-cb8fe56760ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/briefs/roseburg-man-reported-missing/article_518e5298-ba1c-11ee-be8f-cb8fe56760ed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Tykerrious "Ty" Ray has been reported missing to the Roseburg Police Department.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I-5 NORTHBOUND OFF-RAMP AT EXIT 125 TO CLOSE STARTING SUNDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115133</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/i-5-northbound-off-ramp-at-exit-125-to-close-starting-sunday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=i-5-northbound-off-ramp-at-exit-125-to-close-starting-sunday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T17:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 9:30 a.m.  The Interstate 5 northbound off-ramp at Exit 125, Garden Valley Boulevard, is scheduled to be closed next Sunday, Monday and Tuesday nights, January 28th-30th for construction. Dan Latham of the Oregon Department of Transportation said a three-mile detour will be provided those nights from 8:00 p.m. to 6:00 a.m. Latham...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANNUAL POINT IN TIME COUNT HAPPENING WEDNESDAY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115130</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/annual-point-in-time-count-happening-wednesday/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=annual-point-in-time-count-happening-wednesday"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T17:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 9:10 a.m.  The United Community Action Network is holding the annual Point in Time Count on Wednesday. The annual attempt to find out how many residents in the community are homeless or living without housing will take place at Faith Foundry Church, at 2545 West Harvard Avenue from 10:00 a.m. to 3:00...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 1.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115126</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/morning-conversation-1-23-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-1-23-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T16:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Representative Virgle Osborn covers a number of current legislative topics, with the short session of the legislature beginning soon. Click here to download for later listening:  830 1 23-2-24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Food Preserver workshop coming in February]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b000d728-b93c-11ee-b44f-cb8845bcb398</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/master-food-preserver-workshop-coming-in-february/article_b000d728-b93c-11ee-b44f-cb8845bcb398.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T15:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — The Oregon State University Extension Service has a Master Food Preserver Workshop happening from 12:30-4:30 p.m. Feb. 17 at Pine Grove Community Church on Buckhorn Road.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Library to host cultural event]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/60230478-b938-11ee-be43-c7731343fd77</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/education/library-to-host-cultural-event/article_60230478-b938-11ee-be43-c7731343fd77.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Roseburg Public Library will be hosting a Charreria program from 6:30 p.m.-8:30 p.m. Feb. 1. A Charreria is a the 500-year-old practice of horsemanship and roping, and became Mexico's national sport in 1933.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcement: Ryan Rios promoted to Chief Master Sergeant]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/fd8bbba0-b655-11ee-9509-a30918c7c14f</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/family/announcement-ryan-rios-promoted-to-chief-master-sergeant/article_fd8bbba0-b655-11ee-9509-a30918c7c14f.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Air Force Senior Master Sgt. Ryan Rios from Roseburg is currently stationed in Osan Air Base, South Korea. He was recently selected for promotion to the grade of Chief Master Sergeant or “Chief.” This is the highest level of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>www.nrtoday.com - RSS Results in news/local of type article</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RESCUERS RESPOND AFTER BOAT CAPSIZES NEAR ELK ISLAND]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115113</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/rescuers-respond-after-boat-capsizes-near-elk-island/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=rescuers-respond-after-boat-capsizes-near-elk-island"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T11:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024  3:50 a.m.  Rescuers from several agencies responded after a boat capsized near Elk Island in the South Umpqua River in Roseburg on Monday afternoon. An initial call for help came in around 2:40 p.m.  Scanner reports indicated that three men were in boat when it turned over. The News Review reported that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTH UMPQUA SCHOOL BOARD NAMES FINALISTS FOR NEXT SUPERINTENDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115111</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/south-umpqua-school-board-names-finalists-for-next-superintendent/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=south-umpqua-school-board-names-finalists-for-next-superintendent"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T11:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 3:40 a.m.  After completing a rigorous multi-state search, the South Umpqua School Board and screening advisory committee, consisting of school staff, parents, and community members, narrowed the diverse applicant pool to three finalists on January 19th. The finalists to be the next superintendent are: *Erika Bare:  Bare is currently the assistant superintendent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REEDSPORT SEEKING CITY ATTORNEY]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115109</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/reedsport-seeking-city-attorney/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=reedsport-seeking-city-attorney"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T11:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 24, 2024 3:30 a.m. Covering coastal Douglas County: The City of Reedsport is seeking a city attorney. A City release said they are inviting proposals for contracted attorney service. For a list of duties and services required, go to the city’s website: www.cityofreedsport.org. Proposals are due to the city recorder’s office by 4:00 p.m....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIDDLE’S 131ST BIRTHDAY IS TUESDAY JANUARY 30TH]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115105</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/riddles-131st-birthday-is-tuesday-january-30th/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=riddles-131st-birthday-is-tuesday-january-30th"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T11:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 3:20 a.m. Riddle’s 131st birthday is next Tuesday, January 30th. A number of events will be taking place around the community: *Memorabilia will be on display at Riddle City Hall from 9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. *Exhibits from elementary students will be featured on business windows on Main Street *Early day photographs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERCY OPEN HOUSE FOR NEW BEHAVIORAL HEALTH UNIT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115103</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/mercy-open-house-for-new-behavioral-health-unit/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mercy-open-house-for-new-behavioral-health-unit"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T11:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 3:10 a.m. CHI Mercy Health has a community open house for its new Behavioral Health Unit Tuesday afternoon from 4:00 p.m. to 6:00 p.m. It is located on Mercy’s Campus at 2601 Northwest Mercy Drive. Community members are invited to see the patient care rooms, patient activity room, and meet the Behavioral...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UVC FIRST PITCH DINNER HAPPENING FEBRUARY 3RD]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115101</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/23/uvc-first-pitch-dinner-happening-february-3rd/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uvc-first-pitch-dinner-happening-february-3rd"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T10:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 23, 2024 2:50 a.m.  Umpqua Valley Christian School is holding a First Pitch Dinner on Saturday February 3rd at 6:00 p.m. Dale Cranford has more: “Dale” Q: News Radio 93-9 FM and 1240 KQEN High school seniors on their baseball team have been playing together since they were 3 and 4 years old, navigating...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boat capsized on South Umpqua River, people rescued]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/20aee658-b97f-11ee-9a62-776c709d8eb2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/boat-capsized-on-south-umpqua-river-people-rescued/article_20aee658-b97f-11ee-9a62-776c709d8eb2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T23:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two people were rescued near Elk Island in Roseburg after their boat capsized Monday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SANNE GODFREY The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE DOUGLAS COUNTY 1.22.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115098</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/inside-douglas-county-1-22-24/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=inside-douglas-county-1-22-24"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T21:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2nd District Congressman Cliff Bentz joins us live from the Ontario area, to cover a number of current issues in Congress. Click here to download for later listening: IDC 1 22 24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN CITED FOR PROHIBITED CAMPING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115094</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/roseburg-man-cited-for-prohibited-camping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-cited-for-prohibited-camping"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T18:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 10:50 a.m.  A Roseburg man was cited by Roseburg Police for prohibited camping on Sunday. An RPD report said at 10:00 a.m. the 42-year was found with a camp allegedly blocking the doors of the soccer association building in the 500 block of Stewart Park Drive. In addition, the camp was set...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG  POLICE CITE MAN FOR PROHIBITED OUTDOOR BURNING]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115092</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-outdoor-burning-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-cite-man-for-prohibited-outdoor-burning-2"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T18:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 10:45 a.m. Roseburg Police cited a man for prohibited outdoor burning on Sunday. An RPD report said 3:40 p.m. officers contacted the 48-year old at a camp located under the Stewart Park Bridge at the intersection of West Harvard Avenue and Northwest Stewart Parkway after multiple callers said there was a large...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL AFTER MIRROR ALLEGEDLY HITS PEDESTRIAN]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115090</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/roseburg-police-jail-after-mirror-allegedly-hits-pedestrian/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-after-mirror-allegedly-hits-pedestrian"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T18:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 10:35 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a man after part of his vehicle allegedly hit a pedestrian on Sunday. An RPD report said at 11:30 a.m. a victim was walking his dog in the 2800 block of Southeast Douglas Avenue when the incident took place. 63-year old David Triplett told officers his minivan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG WOMAN JAILED FOR REPORTED CRIMINAL TRESPASS]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115088</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/roseburg-woman-jailed-for-reported-criminal-trespass/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-woman-jailed-for-reported-criminal-trespass"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T18:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 10:25 a.m.  A Roseburg woman was jailed by Roseburg Police for the charge of second-degree trespass on Saturday. An RPD report said just after 7:00 p.m. officers contacted the 70-year old after she returned to an address in the 2000 block of Northeast Stephens Street after she had been advised of trespass....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE CHARGE A WOMAN WITH THIRD-DEGREE THEFT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115086</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/roseburg-police-charge-a-woman-with-third-degree-theft-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-charge-a-woman-with-third-degree-theft-2"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T18:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 10:15 a.m.   Roseburg Police charged a woman with third-degree theft following an incident on Friday night. An RPD report said at 7:00 p.m. officers responded after a caller said a woman had stolen some gift cards from a business in the 900 block of West Harvard Avenue. The 34-year old was located...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG POLICE JAIL WOMAN FOR UNLAWFUL USE OF A VEHICLE]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115084</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-unlawful-use-of-a-vehicle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-police-jail-woman-for-unlawful-use-of-a-vehicle"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T18:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 10:00 a.m.  Roseburg Police jailed a woman for unlawful use of a vehicle and other charges early Friday. An RPD report said at 6:40 a.m. officers contacted 35-year old Jessica Thompson as the driver of a stolen vehicle near the intersection of Southeast Stephens Street and Southeast Pine Street. Thompson was detained...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Georgia Stiles, volunteer and community leader, dies at 91]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/b0f0ae3a-b93f-11ee-8e46-f3399119a279</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/georgia-stiles-volunteer-and-community-leader-dies-at-91/article_b0f0ae3a-b93f-11ee-8e46-f3399119a279.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Georgia Lee Hoover Stiles, who was an active volunteer and business woman, died Jan. 18 at age 91.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG MAN ARRESTED FOR ALLEGED MENACING INCIDENT]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115082</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/roseburg-man-arrested-for-alleged-menacing-incident/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=roseburg-man-arrested-for-alleged-menacing-incident"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 9:50 a.m.  A Roseburg man was arrested for an alleged menacing incident on Friday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just after 10:30 p.m. a 25-year old man and the victim got their vehicle stuck on Akin Road near Julian Lane in the Winchester area. The report said this caused...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHERIFF’S OFFICE INVESTIGATING A BURGLARY IN THE AZALEA AREA]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115080</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/sheriffs-office-investigating-a-burglary-in-the-azalea-area/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sheriffs-office-investigating-a-burglary-in-the-azalea-area"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 9:30 a.m.  The Douglas County Sheriff’s Office is investigating a burglary in the Azalea area. Sunday morning at 11:30 a.m. a victim reported that within the last week someone entered his property in the 400 block of Upper Cow Creek Road, got into some of the cabins and stole two batteries, a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE TAKEN TO HOSPITAL AFTER SINGLE VEHICLE WRECK]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115078</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/one-taken-to-hospital-after-single-vehicle-wreck/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=one-taken-to-hospital-after-single-vehicle-wreck"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 22, 2024 9:20 a.m.   Covering coastal Douglas County: One person was taken to the hospital after a single vehicle wreck on Sunday night. A Douglas County Sheriff’s Office report said just before 8:45 p.m. the 18-year old woman was driving south on North Fork Smith River Road in the Reedsport area, when her vehicle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORNING CONVERSATION 1.22.24]]></title>
        <id>https://kqennewsradio.com/?p=115068</id>
        <link href="https://kqennewsradio.com/2024/01/22/morning-conversation-1-22-24-2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=morning-conversation-1-22-24-2"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coach Dave York and players Daniel Withers and Tygue Barron from the Umpqua Valley Christian School baseball team talk about their First Pitch Dinner fundraiser happening February 3rd at the Danny Lang Event Center at Umpqua Community College.  Tickets are now on sale.  Click here to download for later listening: 830 1 22 24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feeding Umpqua received semitruck of food]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/e0947a12-b940-11ee-b883-93a2de483ee7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/news/local/feeding-umpqua-received-semitruck-of-food/article_e0947a12-b940-11ee-b883-93a2de483ee7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T16:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSEBURG — Feeding Umpqua received a semi-truck load of food Friday from Wanda and Steve Olsrud, owners of Sherm’s Thunderbird Market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UACT presents 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea]]></title>
        <id>http://www.nrtoday.com/tncms/asset/editorial/ef76b8e6-b93c-11ee-be1f-33aeba111fe6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nrtoday.com/a_and_e/uact-presents-20-000-leagues-under-the-sea/article_ef76b8e6-b93c-11ee-be1f-33aeba111fe6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T15:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Umpqua Actors Community Theatre will present 20,000 Leagues Under the Seas from Feb. 1-Feb. 8.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Bailey For The News-Review</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>